You are face to face with an inorganic
non-living robot.
Can you kill it?
And then we travel to British Columbia to examine one of the most odd Sasquatch stories you've ever heard.
Is it possible that
not only can they talk, but they also can cast magical spells today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
*Music*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Couldn't even get through that intro without laughing. At the absurdity of the Bigfoot story
We're about to talk about but first we got another story and before that we have another patreon
I want to thank you so much for your support. Herbert, Herbert, thank you so much for supporting this show.
It really really helps out a lot. If you can't support the patreon, that's fine. Just hope you get the word about the show.
That also really really helps a lot. We're gonna give Herbert the keys to the Jason Jalotti.
He's going to drive us up to British Columbia. So basically
He donated to the patreon just so he can be our Lyft driver. We're sitting in the back. We roll up the little divider window
He's like aww, he's all lonely. We're like having a huge party back there. We're headed...
Wait, no we're headed to British Columbia. Knock on the window. No, no, no. Don't go there yet. Herbert, no, no, no
We're not going to British Columbia. First we're going to a laboratory. So we're gonna all walk in a laboratory, put on our little lab coats
We're actually the people being experimented on. So take yours off. No, I'm still in a lab coat. You're not.
You just get to sit in this room and there's a little robot in front of you, right? This little tiny guy.
He's not a cool robot. He's not a transformer or nothing like that. He's just a little dude sitting there.
So, and this is a way it works. You're sitting in this room and I come over the loudspeaker and I click it
Hey guys, it's me, Jason Garbender, host of the TVRevVar Radio. How you doing? And you're like fine?
You're the one who led me and here we know who you are. Don't interrupt me.
So what you're gonna do is see that little robot sitting on the table in front of you? Yeah, that guy.
You are going to play a game with it. You're gonna play like Go or some other nonsense game and
if the robot does well
then you can like say things. But if the robot sucks, then you can like berate the robot. Now you want the...
Obviously you want to win the game. At this point you're like, Jason, just let a real scientist give the rules. No, don't interrupt me.
Don't interrupt me. So here's the thing. The robot is going to build a personality throughout this test by interacting with you.
When you shut it off, the personality will be erased, but it's just a robot. So you know what you're gonna do?
Okay, test starts now and then you hear like a timer. So you're sitting there and there's this little robot in front of you.
He's just like a little lump. He's not... Okay, he's like a little little amiibo looking robot.
He's not like super advanced and not transforming nothing like that. He's probably about, I don't know, three apples high.
And he's sitting there and you're like, "Uh, I'm playing Go."
And which move should I make? The robot's like, "You should do this." And then you should do this.
"Oh, good job. Wait, no, don't do that." And he's helping you out.
And you're like, "Yeah, dude, this is pretty cool." And you win the game.
And you're like, "Yes, robot, you really, really helped me." And then I come back on the intercom and I go,
"Okay, go ahead and shut the robot off and prepare to leave the room."
And you go to shut the robot off and before your hand can reach the switch, it goes, "Don't kill me."
What? Robot goes, "Don't kill me. Don't kill me. I'm afraid of the dark. I don't know if I'll turn back on."
"Please don't shut me off. Don't shut me off."
So this was an actual steady that they did.
Some of them, they asked the robot's questions. The robot had to answer.
Obviously, AI's not that advanced. There was a scientist in the other room controlling the robot and making it talk.
Stuff like that. I think anyone with an IQ of over, say, 100 would walk in there and be like,
"Once the robot starts talking to me, like, 'Oh my God, are you guys kidding me? This robot's this advanced?'"
The average person was getting suckered into this thing.
If I walked in a room and a robot was like, "Nice shoes." I'd be like, "Whoa."
"Thank you for the compliment." But also, "Whoa, that's way too advanced for a robot to be able to do stuff like that."
Maybe not nice shoes, but you know what I mean? Like,
they're not super advanced. They can't pass the Turing test. So anyways, though, but you, the test was this.
Some of them played the game. Some of them asked them questions. It was meaningless.
The whole test was, "Could you shut off a robot as it begged for its life?"
And so they did one study and they had 43 people who, some people just were just with a regular old robot,
didn't say, they just shut it off. They didn't say anything. Out of the 43 people that the robot actually pleaded to be left on,
30 people took twice as long to shut it off as the other group that was just like flicking.
How do you take twice as long to flick a switch? I guess maybe if you're like, "Hmm,
should I flick that switch for like a minute?" The other people just did it. But 13 people outright refused to shut it off.
They let, they go, "I'm not shutting it off." And it's interesting because they would tell the people that the person like, as you, when you shut it off,
it's completely erased. So it's not like you would think that it would come back on and would just be at a safe state.
It would not be the same if someone else came and turned it on. So that also factored into these people's decisions.
And this, these war quotes that the robot was actually saying, again, it was an operator in the other room, but no, don't shut me off.
I'm afraid of the dark. That would be my first clue.
My first clue is that the robot is fully functional, able to carry on a conversation.
But my second clue would be stuff like fear and dark that fear of the dark is something only humans have.
Animals aren't afraid of the dark. And, and you know, I think I've gone over this before too, not to go on a side track,
but you ever been out in the middle of like a dark field or just a backyard of your house and hear a noise?
A lot of times your dog will go running off into the dark. Well, not a well trained dog,
but a just an idiot dog will run off into the darkness. If it's well trained,
it'll stay near you because you just waiting to see what you do. You'll stay on there and you look at the perimeter.
You'll be in the light and you'll see your idiot dog walk off into the darkness run off into.
The reason why they do that, I remember I was talking to someone and someone goes, well, it's because they can see at night.
I go, they're not the predator. Dogs don't have perfect night vision.
The reason why a dog or animals will bolt off into the darkness,
unlike humans, because they have no imagination.
We imagine the man with a knife or the boogeyman or boogeyman with a knife just outside of your
vision and that darkness, but a dog doesn't think like that. Animals don't think like that. They have no imagination.
They will run into a pitch black cave. If they can't smell danger, they'll run right in. So anyways,
where was it going? Oh, yeah, so robots. The idea of being afraid is too human. That would have been another clue.
But also it says, I don't know if I'll wake up again. So very, very scary thing.
So yes, even though you know it's an inorganic thing, it's not a human baby sitting on the table.
If it pleads for his life, people are going to have a harder time shutting it off.
What the reason why they're doing this study, they were trying to look at the implications of, you know,
having robots and stuff in human society and everything like, here, here, listen, man, let's be honest.
The only, there's two reasons why robots will ever exist side by side in society.
Military or sex, that's it. The internet was invented so the government could communicate
after a nuclear war and then it became the perfect pornography machine. Everything else
that the internet does is a spin off of those two things. Every technology, military and sex,
and almost always in that order. I've never, I don't know of any sexual devices that eventually
got co-opted by the military, but it's always like that. So it, but oh, so robots. Yeah, yeah,
so eventually you're going to have robot soldiers. We have them now, but I'm talking about like
humanoids, robot soldiers walking down the street, hopefully not, not our streets, hopefully someone
else's streets and they're USA soldiers. Yes, GI Joe bots. And then, you know, like you're banging
a robot, like you have a robot made and you're banging it and then you're done and it just keeps
cleaning up your apartment. That would be, that's the perfect, we don't have to fight wars and we
get bangbots everywhere. They're actually work, I was going to say this for another story, but I
think it's short enough to talk about now. These scientists are creating these things called the
Xeno bots. They take cells, cells of hearts from horned African frogs, right? Because you're like,
Jason, you're not up enough on science to talk about this. Heart cells automatically contract.
So that's what they're built for, right? So they're scraping off the heart cells of a horned
African frog and they get some other like useless skin cells and then they run this program, they
make a block of cells in a computer and they go walk and the computer will go, if we want to walk,
these are the way the cells should be molded and then they'll take that and they'll go take that
new modified version and put that in the computer and say walk and then the computer runs a program
and goes, oh, it could use a little bit of adjustment here, a little bit of adjustment there.
They'll do that like a thousand times until they get the, basically it's evolution in a computer.
They get a computer model of the best thing that involves, you know, a couple thousand skin cells
and heart cells. If we wanted to make it walk, there's going to be an article in the show notes
if this is too, you're like, Jason, I'll just read this stupid article. Anyways, they're building,
they're basically building robots out of nothing but skin cells and heart cells. The heart cells are
to make it move because they're constantly just contracting. They're bio bots and what they're
saying is they build them, they've been successfully built. They're like a centimeter big, but they've
built them and they can make them last only a week. They're given, when they're created,
they only have enough energy to last a week and then they die and they dissolve. And they said
they can, because they can say computer, take this clump of cells, make it able to carry stuff. So it
started to evolve little legs and then the, the program keeps running and then it evolved a little
dent and it's back. So it's really, really fascinating stuff. What's interesting though is
it says in the article, eventually you want to like give it eyeballs and all this stuff and we
want to build it to scale because what are you going to do with a bunch of centimeter tall mucus
bots? Like, will they just throw them in an enemy's face? I'm mildly inconvenienced. No, if you can do
the same thing and have it be the size of a horse that can walk around for maybe not the size of a
horse, that's quite extreme. The size of a dog and it only lasts a week and like you can ride it in a
battle very, very slowly, right? In a battle or just have it like carry stuff, everything like that.
So they want to basically, they said a lot of people want to make robots out of inorganic stuff,
but these things can actually heal. They have a set time limit. So you don't have to worry about it.
You can kill them. They have no thought process and some people are concerned about that. But as
I'm reading this article and then once they said they want to make them to scale, the first thing
I thought of was eventually someone's going to bang one of these giant mucus bots. There's just
going to be a lump of flesh. It's going to have heart cells for legs and the rest of it's just a
bunch of undulating skin cells and some guys like, "Ooh baby, yeah, yeah, carry your load over here."
It's a military dude in the middle of nowhere just banging this thing, right?
It's not going to be in the middle of nowhere. It'll be in downtown Chicago. Some guy will order
one online, build it himself and get arrested for banging this this lump of skin cells. So yes,
there we go. The future of technology. I think I would want to go if I had to choose a race to
live alongside of us. I would choose the organic Xenobots because I think they'd be easier to
control. But if I wanted to have sex with one, I would pick like a robot robot because that seems
infinitely less disgusting than banging what is really dead skin cells of a frog from Africa.
Like I'd much rather bang this robot that looks like Britney Spears than even if,
that's interesting. If the frog cells look like Britney Spears. Anyways, let's go ahead and move
on to our next topic here. We're giving the key. We're leaving behind the laboratory. We're leaving
behind the laboratory. You're like, "Hey Jason, where's Herbert? We left him in the research facility.
We watch him. He's like tied down there like scraping skin cells off his arm. He's like, "No,
no, not this fate. Not this fate." Door slight shift. We leave. We're by Herbert. Thanks for giving
me your money. We're hopping in the Jason Jalapie. We're driving up to British Columbia.
A lot of this story, and I want to give credit where credit's due, a lot of the story was,
I got from a single article. It's called The Strange Tale of the Sasquatch Curse. It's written
by an author known as Red Pill Junkie. This is a really bizarre story. This is a really,
really bizarre story. Let's go ahead and get started. We're driving up to British Columbia.
We're going to go to the Squaw Reservation. It's near Chillywack, British Columbia. So
stop the Jason Jalapie. We all hop out. Herbert's with us. He's missing a couple skin cells on his
arm, but he's able to join us for the rest of the episode. There's this old man. This is like the
1950s, '60s. There's this old man sitting on a chair outside of a shop. He's just sitting there.
He has a little puppy, a little old puppy sitting next to him, dogs on the verge of death. This man's
on the verge of death. We just stopped to buy some snacks. We're getting some beef jerky for the trip.
Let's go find this Bigfoot, and he goes, "Bigfoot? Why, do you want to know about Bigfoot? Sit down
on this dusty, dirty street. Just sit down. Can't bring any chairs with you. Just sit down. I will
tell you all about Bigfoot. I met the Bigfoot." I'm like, "Really? Okay, that'll save us a trip."
We don't have to drive through the woods. You're like, "No, Jason, I enjoy the splendor of nature,
but I enjoy sitting in front of strangers." So we all sit down, and he goes, "I'll tell you this
story, and my voice will change, so I don't do an irritating voice for the next 20 minutes."
My name is Charlie Victor, and this is my dog. I don't have a name written down for the dog. This
is my dog. And Charlie Victor explains he's a member of the Douglas Indian tribe, which is the
Indian tribe in this area. He goes, "I'm going to have to go back in time." Not literally,
because that would be cool, but I'm going to go back in time with my words, and we're going to go
back to the year 1914. Back in 1914, I was known as the fastest rifle hunter in British Columbia,
not just the area, but all over, because British Columbia is a province, right? And in 1914,
so now we are traveling back in time to be with Charlie on this journey, it's 1914. We're in the
mountains near a place called Hatzik, which again is in British Columbia. It's all in there.
Charlie's walking around in the woods. He has his gun, he has his trusty, nameless dog walking
alongside of him, and he's just looking for stuff to blow away. He just wants to shoot stuff in the
brain, but he's all disappointing. He's like, "Oh, I haven't taken any life today." But then his dog
starts going crazy. Charlie's like, "What is it? Did you find something for me to murder?"
dog's like "Row how how" and the dog is like looking at this tree and Charlie's like "What is it
boy? what is it?" and then apparently now he's from the Dukes of Hazard his accent has completely
changed them Duke boys he sees there's a cave but blocking it is all like this trees and this
shrub, so apparently Charlie Victor is Paul Benning because he moves the tree, maybe he just moved
the branches but still, he moves enough of the tree around for the rest of the story to take place.
This hole was previously completely covered by foliage and now he's like "Rrrr!" throws it to one
side. The dog runs into the cave and at that point he hears what's known as a suffocated whale.
Not like "Wooooooow!" but like that was his words "whale" as in W-A-I-L like I don't even know what
that sound would be like maybe it's a maybe something hunter maybe it's a hunter thing I
wouldn't understand but that's what he hears in this cave and he's like "Yes my dog must have found
a baby bear and he's gonna flush it out better get my rifle ready better get ready to pull this
trigger no matter what I see come out of this cave because the only thing I can think of is a baby
bear" and he gets his rifle ready fastest rifle in British Columbia and this lump this thing starts
staggering out of the cave and he sees it and without thinking like any good hunter just pulls
the trigger without seeing what he's shooting at gunshot echoes through the valley and what he sees
is this kid this 12 year old boy "mwhack" fall to the ground bleeding from a gunshot wound
bleeding very very badly so so Charlie is like "Oh this isn't good it's this white kid he estimated
the age like 12 to 14 years old the kid's just screaming his head off which is what you generally
do when you're shot by a total stranger in the middle of the woods he's naked by the way too not
Charlie this kid so you have a 12 year old naked dude bleeding out in front of you in the forest
and Charlie goes "I immediately felt bad and I was like I wish I had died I wish that I hadn't
shot this kid but you know you don't own a time machine dude so you got to live with it now this
kid's screaming now you're like Jason this is funny hold on hold on hold on that is how it
starts off that's the series beginning so what happens according to Charlie the kid is screaming
so the kid's screaming on the ground and then he hears off in the distance of the woods
another scream he's like did I shoot a kid over there too to the bullet get ricocheted
what is going on I got this naked kid screaming I got this weird noise behind me I need to figure
out to do something quickly 30 minutes past though he does nothing at all he just stands there for
30 minutes 30 minutes later he's still like hmm what should I do I got this kid shot that noise
behind me and then that is when Sasquatch shows up and this giant this is this is interesting for
a couple different reasons it's a woman which is rare we don't see a lot of Sasquatch we don't see
any Sasquatch to be clear but in the lore we don't see many women Sasquatch it's a Sasquatch woman
and she's only six feet tall you're like Jason that's not I know women that tall that's not big
foot you don't let me finish it's just some tall WNBA player walking through the woods hiking hey
guys she is covered in hair which isn't particularly a trait known in the WNBA this woman is covered
head to toe in hair and oddly enough also has long hair going down past her waist as well which I
don't know if that's possible can a gorilla have long hair can gorilla have like ferra faucet hair
is that possible isn't the fur kind of all grow to the same size all over the body or could you have
like a beautiful like set of like hair could you give like a gorilla aria on the ground a
extensions little ponytail but anyway so this one comes out and sees this shot kid and starts
totally flipping out now we haven't shooting this little kid right bleeding out we have not doing
anything for half hour now we have a big foot that's quote unquote big foot you're like dang it Jason
that's a pain switch it's still a big foot even though it's only six feet tall come out of the
woods you have all this all of these elements are kind of ridiculous but I think this next statement
really shows whether or not we should take this dude seriously okay your mileage may vary but for
me I was like okay here's this quote from him I'd seen this is on pond seeing this sqaq woman for
the first time I've seen a lot of wild things in my life when I was out in the forest but nothing
like this creature which really frightened me when I was young and not to brag I had to
strangle a bear with my bare hands it was it or me but I'm sure that if this hairy bean had laid
one hand on me not a single one of my bones would have remained in one place so we're sitting now
we're back and we're sitting in front of this dusty storefront this dude Charlie's talking to us and
he's like I don't mean to brag guys but one day I strangled a bear but this thing scared me now at
that point we all kind of look at each other and we're like first off nobody ever says if you say
I don't mean to brag and the next statement is I killed a bear with my bare hands you meant to brag
secondly that really puts everything for me at least puts everything else very suspiciously
he shouldn't have had that in there that if I'm making up a story if I'm making up a story where
I'm like yeah dude I was I got abducted by aliens you're like really it's like yeah dude and I got
like brought up on the ship they tried strapped me down I started fighting them and then I was like
beating them up and then like then like my pants fell off and they saw that I had like a big wiener
and then they let me go like you would be like Jason I believe this story up until the obvious
brag when you're telling me you can just say I I've seen a lot of crazy things but nothing this
spooky the fact that he go maybe I'm submitted to a shy mom since it's gonna get edited out but
the fact that he's saying he can strangle a bear with his bare hands has strangled a bear with his
bare hands that's a lie I don't believe that I don't think that's I mean maybe a bear embryo maybe
a bear being born the mama bear is asleep I'm reneating the baby bear's coming out maybe
he could do that but I don't think so so anyways now we're going back in time now we're highly
suspicious of what this guy says this ass quatch woman is standing there she looks at Charlie
she looks at the boy the boy looks very weak now it's been 30 hours dude you could have at least
given him a bandaid and the bear woman looks again at Charlie and goes you have shot my friend
and if it's that's an interesting quote for a couple reasons and red pill junkie pointed this
out the fact that she said and there's different variations of it she was saying this in the
dialect of the douglas indians according to Charlie if she said you have shot my friend that would
make her have a working knowledge of firearms which would put her much closer to human level
intelligent other variations of the quote are you have hurt my friend or you've killed my friend but
anyways and it's just to be clear the boy on the ground on the sasquatch that little boy is not a
boy sasquatch that is a human boy and then we have this sasquatch showing up so we'll get into that
as well and the guy starts to apologize but it doesn't matter he shot a kid who what can you say
at that point she then starts to do this dance trying not to be racist as i'm making a dance noise
and she's holding out of nowhere she pulls us out of nowhere she's holding what charlie describes as
either a six foot long snake which is possible right maybe not in america but you know she she
is sasquatch he might be well traveled he's standing just feet away from this creature
apparently she's chanting to stovakor at this point and as she's doing this he can hear chanting
in the forest as well at this point i'm thinking those are just echoes dude but anyways she's swinging
around this six foot long snake or charlie goes it could have been a snake or it could have been six
feet of intestines so again charlie listen dude you i'm not a hunter i'm not a nature guy you
trying to convince me that you've seen a lot of wild things in the woods i can tell the difference
between a snake and a and a guts i can at least do that if i am at a zoo and i'm like oh let's go
to the snake exhibit and that's today they forgot to like you know bring the snakes so they just
started throwing lamb intestine in there i'd be like hey wait i'm i'm that savvy nobody's
anyways anyway so again that's me making me question this but whatever it is you're like
jason that's your takeaway you have a talking bigfoot doing this dance swinging this around
well i want to be specific she starts splashing it she starts hitting it against the ground
making these noises saying this chant and she's just doing this thing now then and then with one
hand so she's swinging around the snake slash intestine and then the other hand she picks up
the kid like he says like a wax doll which what the what the what the hell's a wax doll
anyway maybe that's some old-timey thing but anyway what would be the point of having a doll
that you're like can i play with it outside they're like no honey it's made of wax it's all melting
faces all the little anyways picks them up like a wax doll and she's holding the kid with one arm
i'm assuming the kid's deceased at this point he's no longer saying anything and then she turns to
charlie and she's swinging this thing around in the air that's either spewing out venom or blood
we don't know it's either snake or intestines and she looks at charlie and says and now charlie
pauses the story because this is his first person account in this that is being reported in this
article charlie pauses the story to say this now every time i tell this story nobody wants to believe
what happened next i'm having a hard time believing what's happened before because this this you know
meant however you say this ending of the story is actually the least spectacular part of it
the monster woman turns to charlie and says si wash you will never kill another bear in your life
and then he drops his rifle which he had the whole time he's i guess i just said earlier he said he
couldn't even pull the trigger like when he saw it he was so terrified he couldn't pull the trigger
the whole time though he sold this rifle he drops the rifle and he's standing up there and at that
point he realizes he's paralyzed the creature's just dancing in front of him looking at him
he cannot move and now we're sitting back on the porch and he's sitting there and he's like and that
my children is the story of how i became paralyzed and that's why i am sitting in this chair in the
1950s we're looking at each other we're like what he's like yes i'm paralyzed because i was cast a
sasquatch woman which cast a spell on me paralyzed me so kind of started getting dusting ourselves
off giving him some money he's like i need your charity have a 401k jerk i'm just enjoying the
sun with my wax doll there's just puddles there's puddles everywhere the obvious question is this
if this story is true at all which most likely isn't but if the story is true at all he's paralyzed
he remember this story ends with him being paralyzed on a mountain and the monsters in front of him
now i don't know if the monster walked away the bigfoot walked away teleported away swung
its magical snake guts around and like jumped into a portal but he didn't disappear or go into a
portal he was paralyzed on the mountaintop but then apparently then he just gets back to town
and then gets reparalleled the end end of the story makes no sense now it's interesting because
this story is very very controversial and it's obviously controversial for a couple different
reasons i'm gonna go over these quick because i don't want to run long but when bigfoot people
not the actual bigfoot people but bigfoot researchers there is a divide most of them
believe it's a biological group that actually lives in the woods and they leave feces and
footprints and bo it's whatever that's a nonsense theory but a lot of people believe in that one
a smaller group of people and i think the most logical one even though this is absolutely bizarre
it's bigfoot some sort of interdimensional connected to UFOs high strangeness other dimensions
something like that that makes more sense because it clears up why there's no evidence of them or
why when we find evidence it's inconclusive they're basically in between a UFO and a ghost they're
more biological than a ghost but they're not extra trust you're like UFO that's the more likely
scenario if any of these stories are true this story though is foolish on the outset you have a
bigfoot that's talking you have it casting magical spells you have it kidnapping a little boy and
it's funny because a lot of bigfoot people though say that does fit with the bigfoot lore
of young children being kidnapped and it goes into it can also play into the whole missing
four on one people go missing in the woods and stuff like that this story though is so controversial
that red pill junkie got doxxed because of it when a site was disputing this they were printing
his real name which was absolutely bizarre because it's obviously and so he got the story from a
there's a book written in Italy called this is how obscure this story is there was a book written
in Italy back in the back 1979 called Sasquatch enigma anthropological it was written in Italy
then the red pill junkie found a copy of it when he was a kid at a at a mexican flea market so his
copy was a spanish translation of an italian book and here he is he got the book like in the 80s
when he was a kid now we're in the i think this article came out in 2015 somewhere around that
he's translating the book into english this story is being going from italian to spanish to english
and there's been no translation of this story published and like in a book form in english so
very very rare and there was a i when i found this story there was another article that was debunking
it and they were just said the author's role i'm not a fan of anonymity to begin with i think that
it's much better to just use your real name and to be in front of it but if you choose to use a name
like red pill junkie or you choose to use a pseudonym i think that it only under extreme
circumstances should you dox those people and writing a story about trying writing a funny
story saying look at the story i found about bigfoot is not a reason why you should print
someone's full name again i think people should not be anonymous online anyways but super bizarre
like i was shocked the controversy behind the story was more shocking than not but people
really don't like the story really hasn't been out there i think it's a funny story i think it's
an interesting story i don't necessarily think it's true but i don't think it's true because of
stuff like him standing around a bleeding kid for a half hour him teleporting off the mountain
when he's like he's paralyzed on the mountain then he appears in town the next day there's a lot of
details missing from it not because i don't believe that bigfoot's have the ability to
okay because if bigfoot's real i go with the interdimensional thing it's i would say well
if they're coming from another dimension maybe they do have snake guts maybe they do have
the ability to cast spells and stuff like that we do know that bigfoot's have been tied to kidnapping
children was the kid a prisoner was the kid really the friend the kid was definitely human
there's a lot of like interesting questions to it not dox worthy definitely but let's end
it like this let's end it like this i think there's an interesting component to this if you
were walking through the woods and you saw bigfoot and you came home you probably wouldn't tell anyone
for a long time but let's say you come home and you tell your buddies do to solve bigfoot last night
people are going to be like yeah yeah whatever and they might believe you they might humor you they
might make fun of you behind your back but you'd probably get over it no no no i really saw him
yeah yeah whatever but then let's say you were walking through the woods and you saw bigfoot
and you interacted with it in some ways thrown rocks at you or you guys were playing go and he's
like don't shut me up don't let me out shut me off i'm afraid of the dark you go back you tell
your buddies they're like what that's that story is ridiculous and you're like no no no but it really
happened and you would understand that it was ridiculous you'd understand why people didn't
believe you but imagine if you went into the woods and you had a negative interaction with a bigfoot
to the point that it actually crippled you for life and as the helicopter shows up to lifelight
you out of there and they're like what happened you fall down a ravine where you like shut off a
particularly mean robot he's like no none of those things none of those things bigfoot uh
bigfoot punched my my spine uh i can't move helicopters flying away that's one of those
things where you would i would actively be mad if people didn't believe me in that story i would
actively be upset if i suffered some sort of horrible physical tragedy and it was caused by
bigfoot and then people are like big bigfoot yeah right you're like dude look at the scars i can't
look at these giant footprints on my stomach what those are fake i think that would make me mad and
it's funny because i never thought about this before i think that's like some people can say
i think that's the difference between people who believe in aliens and people who've been abducted
by aliens people who have said oh yeah i saw UFO or i believe in like the galactic brotherhood or
all that nonsense stuff like that or i believe reptilians are taken over the planet they don't
necessarily take it personal if you don't believe them i mean they might feel like they're more
enlightened than you but i don't think i've ever gotten in a fight with someone because i don't
believe reptiles are taken over the planet secretly i would just use my my secret reptilian strength
to take them down but if i was abducted by aliens like if i was physically or like mentally harmed
but me directly not myles iris and it was some stupid theory i had but me directly if i was
abducted by aliens and tormented physically or mentally or sexually and people didn't believe
me that would make me really mad that would make me probably more prone to not tell these stories
to anyone else and this is kind of creepy now that i'm thinking about this too and that would
actually make it worse because one of the ways in real life that you stop abuse is you have to let
other people know so other people can intervene but if you're being abducted by aliens and now
this is an alien ending but if you're getting abducted by aliens and you're being abused and
you're put back in your bed at night and you wake up and you don't tell anyone they're just going
to keep doing it they're going to keep doing it until you get help but who do you reach out for help
if no one's going to believe you who are you going to reach out for help if you're afraid that
20 years after telling your story to someone some jackass podcaster is going to be making an episode
about a poor paralyzed man in british columbia i don't know maybe i turned around maybe bigfoot
did mess this dude up but i guess i'll never know unless i end up having a close encounter
of the ferd kind wait cuz furry the bigfoot ferd dead rabbit radio at gmail.com it's going to be
your email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead
rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
you don't have to listen to it every day and i'm glad you listened to it today have a great one guys
(upbeat music)