roads, streets, lanes, alleys. You may know these as places to walk, but in the world
of the paranormal, they mean so much more than that. First off, we're gonna take a
look at the story of a woman who's walking through Russia. Now that's not
abnormal, people do it all the time, but this woman is weird. She shouldn't be
doing that. And then we take a look at a man who's chasing a sister's
witch stories of people walking. Hold on, let me get through the intro. And then we
take a look at the story of an old farm out in the middle of nowhere. They're
having a good old time in the Hootenanny until a stranger walks up to the house.
And then we take a look at a bizarre musical mystery. When a folk singer goes
missing, people think suicide, people think the mob, but to this day his fans
proclaim he was taken by the aliens today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host
Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
This episode is actually being recorded in just minutes. After yesterday's episode,
because I'm getting ready to wrestle a hog and I want to be in fighting shape,
and I want to have all my episodes recorded. In case I get horribly injured, I
just have to edit them. The recording process is the most problematic part of
it, because it's where things can go wrong. The performance can be bad, the
mic can be bad. I can run out of things to say all sorts of stuff. So this is the
technically the hardest part. Once this part's done, I can kind of just hit
buttons and edit and then interact with you guys. And speaking of interacting
with you guys, let me give a shout out, starting off right now, to our legacy
Patreon supporter coming into Dead Rabbit Command flying Frisbees.
Frisbees everywhere, that's what he's into, I guess. Paul Martinez, he's hovering on a Frisbee as
he's throwing Frisbees around at us. He's playing a little bit of that Frosh Paul.
You're gonna be our captain, our pilot's episode. If you guys hate Frisbee
Cough or you guys can't spread the Patreon, that's fine too. Just helps
spread the word about the show. Really, really helps out a lot. You'll also see
that it is. Fan Art Friday, and today's selection for Fan Art Friday, is from
Super Awesome Robot. So give everyone a robot clap for the Super Awesome Robot.
Thank you so much for Fan Art Friday. So Paul is now wearing a full-on Tron
Legacy outfit. He's now throwing data discs around. It's super cool. I now have
on my Tron Legacy outfit, I'm Renzler. But after him Cosplaying is one of the
most underrated sci-fi films. Let's go ahead Paul. I'm gonna toss you the keys
to the Dead Rabbit Durgible. We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're
headed out to Siberia. We were actually just in Russia yesterday. So Paul is
flying us out in the Dead Rabbit Durgible. We're headed out to Siberia. The year is
2017. And we're headed out to a place called the Road of Bones. No, it's not
your big brother's D&D supplemental manual from 1983. This is an actual place.
It was called that because it was built by prison labor during Soviet Russia and
they basically were like, "You prisoners, we don't care what happens to you." In the
construction of this road in Siberia, they estimate between 250,000 to 1
million people died building this road, or as it's known in Soviet Russia,
Tuesday. When you were building this road and you died, you basically fell down on
the ground, which tends to happen when you die, right? But the soil was too frozen
to bury you. Plus, they don't have time. You're building this road, you got
deadlines to meet. Get it? Deadlines? Because everyone's dying?
Maybe I should have taken more of a break between episodes. It's called the
Road of Bones because for a while there were bones littering the highway. The
government has now apologized for that whole program, but that was the case.
That's why they called it the Road of Bones. Now it's known as officially the
Kolyema Federal Highway. In 2017, a woman is sighted walking down the road.
Again, not unusual. People are allowed to walk down the roads all over the place,
but truck drivers are driving by. See a girl walking on the side of the road.
Cars driving by. Girls walking by. Truck drivers are like doing their routes
coming back the other way. She's still walking. "Breaker, breaker, do you see that
young lady walking on the side of the road? Spooky bear? Do you see that?" "Oh yes,
pile of bones, pile of bones. I see that. I'm coming up here." This woman is sighted
on this road making a 1200 mile walk. She's sighted between Yaksduk and
Magadan. Apparently she has made this 1200 mile walk multiple times because
she's been seen all along the length of it multiple times. So you're like, "Jason,
is this a phantom? Did she get in the backseat of Smokey Bear's big rig?"
And then he takes her to the prom and then they get there and the backseat's
empty. Nothing but a wet raincoat? No. There's a photo of this woman. Not a blurry
photo late at night. That's the jump scare photo. There's a photo of this woman
walking on the street. It is a real woman that has been documented. The police
have actually talked to this woman. "What are you doing walking?" It's a free country,
isn't it? And their eyes shift from side to side. They're like, "Yeah, kind of. Nowadays."
50 years ago it wasn't. She's like, "Yeah, bug her off." Truck drivers have stopped.
"Hey, you need a ride?" She doesn't engage with anybody. She'll answer questions for
the police because you kind of have to, but she just keeps walking. The police go,
"She's not breaking any laws. You are allowed to walk down the street." People who
have like, "Hey, miss. You need a ride? You need a ride?" Eventually they think
she's mentally ill. They'll grab her. She freaks out. She starts screaming
incoherently. "You got to run. You get in your car. Now she's in your backseat with
a wet coat. She's strangling you with it." She's not equipped for winter travel.
See, if you saw someone in a big park with a sled and a bunch of snow dogs, you'd be,
"Oh, that's fine. It's a little weird. It's a little weird. It's like holding up traffic."
But whatever. But she's walking. She's wearing, they said she's wearing a white
jacket and blue jeans. And then she has like, on like a coat. Not like a big old
GI Joe winter soldier coat. Just a coat. She's never seen in a populated area. And
oddly enough, no one has ever seen her eat. Which I'm sure she's like going off
into the bushes eating berries and stuff like that. Squirrels. She's grabbing the
rogue squirrel and taking a bite out of it. Trucks and cars are seeing her walk all
this time. They've never seen her get to a destination. They've never seen her
kick her feet up at a McDonald's. They have no idea why she's doing this walk.
She's just seen walking. She was first reported in 2017. The last report I
could find was in April of 2018. So it had at least a year, if not more. She may
still be doing it now. It's just old news over there. They're like, "Woman walks."
It's super great news the first time. And now people are like, "Yeah." I got that from
the 40 and map too. That's a really cool resource. That's gonna be in the show
notes. You guys can look around. See if you find anything odd. But it's real. This
isn't a phantom. This isn't the ghost of a girl trying to get home
after a drunk driving accident. This is a real woman walking 1200 miles multiple
times through Siberia photographed and nobody knows why. Obviously it's
probably some sort of mental illness, but it's just a weird story and it's one
of those things that no one will ever know the answer for. We did that one story
a long time ago about the guy in France who was just walking through the bushes
dressed in a gas mask and everyone is trying to follow him around and then
the newspaper published a story on him and he took all of his gear off and left
it on a rock and said, "Now I'm dead." So we do have and we covered the flout, the
floutest, the guy who was playing the recorder in Brazil. We do have these
weird people kind of hanging out. I met Joe Trombone in San Leandro. He's one of
the greats. The rapping crazy man who'd get on a bus and rap for you. I think
these people are always interesting when we run into these anomalies of humankind,
people who are outside the edges, but not in like an edgy way. Not like an annoying
way. Not like the person who's playing my chemical romance at top volume while
you're trying to talk to the girl at the party. Just like in a cool weird way.
But this woman might also be into my chemical romance, so stay away. Stay away.
If she gets in your vaccine, she reaches for your radio. Be prepared for Black
Parade for 1200 miles. Listen to that album for 1200 miles. Paul, let's go
ahead and hop in the Jason Jalopy. Let's give her a ride. She wants to ride with
us because she's super cool. She has on all the mascara. Yes, we will listen to
Black Parade for the rest of the journey. The rest of the journey. Hope you guys
are into that. Paul, take us out of Siberia. We are headed back to the United
States. We are specifically going to Canada. I don't know what's wrong, but
that's near the United States. It's the United States little brother. We're headed
up to Canada. Jason Jalopy's driving on the road. We get to Camperville. That's in
Manitoba, Canada. The year is 1930.
The winter storm pauses to take a deep breath. It's winter. It's late at night.
The snow is falling. It's super cold outside. It's below 30 degrees and this
family is fast asleep. They're wearing their PJs. They got their thermal socks
on. Winter storm is wrapping around the building. Outside their dogs are going
nuts. The dad wakes up, "Huh? What? What's going on?" And he goes and he looks out
the window and the dogs are like, "Ahhhhh!" They're now no longer barking. They look
like they're rabbits. It's just like foam coming out of their mouths.
"Ahhhhh!" Apparently they also sound like a man. The dog sounded like a 44 year old
man trying to record a podcast without waking up his neighbors. It was crazy. The
dad's standing there. The rest of the family is looking through the window and
they see a man standing in their front yard. Now the winter storm is pelting the
building with snow. It's also hitting the stranger. He's not immune to the
weather, but he's dressed like he is. He's wearing a tuxedo. He's just standing out
in the snow.
The dogs are still just out of it. So the dad and the older brother, they open
the door. "Ahhhhh!" Super, super spooky door opens up. "I need to fix that," the dad
says. He walks out with his son and the man is just standing there in the
tuxedo. "What do you want? What's going on here? Why are you bugging my dogs? Why are
you making them sound like a 44 year old man trying to record a podcast late at
night?" The man just stands there in the snow. He's like, "What does that even mean?"
He's just standing there. So the father and his son begin to approach the man and
the man takes a step backwards and they get closer to him and he takes another
step backwards. And they're like, "Okay, well now it's on. This guy's obviously just
kind of being a jerk. No one walks backward on my property." They keep walking
towards him. He keeps walking backwards. Now he's walking backwards one step at a
time. The men speed up. They start jogging towards him. He continues to take one step
back. And that's when the men realize, and even the people witnessing this from
the house, no matter how fast the men move towards this figure, they can never
close the distance. And the man is constantly just taking one step backwards.
They're running towards him. He takes one step backwards. They're still 20 feet away.
They follow him up to a hill and then they just stop. And he's still just
walking backwards. He walks backwards down the road and is soon swallowed by the
winter storm.
That's Dead Rev Radio creepypasta hour. Now I actually got that from thinkaboutadox.com
They got it from paranormal.com back in June 2003. I give a lot of credit to
thinkaboutadox.com when they report stuff. I haven't been led wrong yet.
So this story does sound a lot like creepypasta. I've never heard it before.
I think it's really interesting. I think it's a creepy visual. Anything that
plays with time and space like that. And it's so funny because when I was reading
the story, I imagine him as like a tall, lanky guy. Doesn't actually say that in
the notes. Never says that he's tall and lanky. But I think that's just kind of how
you get it. It's interesting because the only visual description they don't say
and he had a creepy grin and real life blood was pouring out of his eyeballs.
It was just that it was a guy in a tuxedo which makes it creepier. You fill in
your own details. I filled it in as like a lanky guy in a tuxedo. But as a man in a
tuxedo and no matter how fast they move towards him, he was always able to stay
away from him. He's just walking one step at a time. It's very very simple
story. Very very simple story. Wasn't an alien intruder, some sort of phantom, a
demonic entity, interdimensional traveler. You pretty much choose whatever you want
with it. Very very simple story, frightening visual, and the fact that it
doesn't have an ending where it's like I'll be back to take your firstborn. It
doesn't have an implication of why the creature was there. It makes it that
creepier. So we cover stories about some crazy kid in Brazil like we did earlier
in the week who's beaten up chickens. You just go, "I don't have chickens. I'm not
living in Brazil. I'm not worried about this Dennis the Menace-esque character
messing up my life." This guy came out of nowhere, had no goal, and left. And that
could happen to any of us. You could be walking to your car later tonight and you
just see a figure standing there next to your car. I mean there's nothing they did
to start this and there was nothing they did to finish it, so you don't know why
it was there. Those type of stories are fine. Very unsettling. Also park underneath
the street lights. Park underneath the street lights. But sometimes that doesn't
even help, right? You're walking towards the car and your street lights like
and every time it flickers black you see a figure standing there, but then the
lights back and it's gone. Paul's like, "Tingya Jason! I have to go to bed after listening to this part of guys."
It's okay. It's okay Paul. Let's go ahead and leave behind the Jason Jalopy. We're
gonna hop in the carboner copter. We are headed out to one more story that
involves walking. You like this theme episode? You like this walking theme
episode? We are leaving behind Canada. Paul, I want you to take us out to Los
Angeles. We're in the 1960s, so we're dressed up. We got really cool clothes on
and stuff like that. As opposed to the lame clothes we're wearing today. We got
really cool clothes on. We're walking around LA. We're sitting at these cool
nightclubs. We're hanging out with a bunch of old stars, but they weren't old
back then. They were young. There's a man on stage and he's tuning his guitar and
this band's getting ready and Debbie Reynolds is sitting next to me and she
goes, "Hey dude, you won't believe this dude is dope. This guy's super
awesome." I was like, "Who is it?" Debbie Reynolds goes, "This is the only old star I can think of
off the top of my head because I just watched singing from the rain a couple
weeks ago. I never saw it before." Debbie Reynolds goes, "Yeah, dude, this guy's killer.
His name is Jim Sullivan." He's sitting there and he gets his little
pedestal ready. He starts playing a jaunty little tune and all of these rich,
powerful people at LA are mesmerized by this simple folk singer singing simple
folk songs. He was one of those guys. Jim Sullivan was one of those guys who
wanted to make it. We all want to make it, right? Whatever your career could be.
You want to make it as a stockbroker or you want to make it as an artist. You
want to make it as a mechanic. Everyone has dreams and aspirations, which is
great. You got to have those. You got to keep moving forward. Jim Sullivan was
just like us. His aspiration was music and he actually kind of lucked out
because his wife worked for Capital Records. Now, she wasn't a producer. She
was like a staff member there. She did her best to try to get his music in
front of the people at Capital Records, but it just wasn't successful. She
couldn't get them to really pick up the album. So you go, "Okay, you know, he's
trying his best." He had this weird way of mesmerizing people where his first
gigs were at very, very prestigious nightclubs. He's playing these songs.
Now, this is the 1960s, so folk music is huge right now. And the audiences are
full of musicians. They're full of actors. They're full of these powerful
people. And they're like, "Oh my god, this is really, really good music. This guy
needs an album deal." He's like, "Yeah, I'm working on it. You know, my wife's
trying to pull strings, but Capital Records won't listen to it." He had a bunch
of celebrity friends pool their money together. They pool their money together
to get him studio time. And not only studio time, he's just a simple man with a
guitar who's writing these songs. They have to get backing musicians for him.
They get him studio time with the Wrecking Crew. The Wrecking Crew were studio
musicians for some of the biggest acts at the time. This cost serious money. His
friends really, really believed in Jim Sullivan. They got him the studio. They
got him the Wrecking Crew. They got him the best of the best. And his first album
was entitled UFO. Didn't take off, though. It was pure folk music, but it just
didn't take off. 1972, he does get signed to a record label. He gets signed to
Playboy Records, the Playboy company, decides to actually get into the music
business. And one of the very first acts, because this guy had such a great
reputation, to launch their record company, they picked Jim Sullivan. But that
album also flops. You can have the best music out there, the best art out there,
and it just doesn't line up. And that's what happened to Jim Sullivan. His
marriage started a fall apart. He had a child. That's the one. The marriage started
a fall apart. He's like, Barney, the reason why we're raking up is you know,
they had a kid, but the marriage was starting to fall apart. He started a
drink, which is never going to make things good. He starts to drink very, very
heavily. And he says, you know what, okay, maybe Los Angeles isn't the place for me
to be. I'm gonna try my luck in Nashville. So, honey, Barney, he gives
sign to Barney. He almost broke me and me and your mom up. He goes, I'm gonna go to
Nashville. I'm gonna try to make it there, and then I'll bring you guys out with me.
Or get a divorce, you know. One or the other, this marriage isn't going so great.
But he did still talk to his wife into this adventure we're going on. So he
goes, I'm gonna go to Nashville. It's March 4th, 1975. At this point, he is loading
up his Volkswagen Beetle, and he's gonna make the trip from Los Angeles to
Nashville. On the way out there, he stops at a motel in Santa Rosa, New Mexico.
Goes in, gets a room, buys some vodka. Not a great thing to do, especially when
you're on a road trip, but that's what he does. He's in for the night. He gets a
hotel room, he buys some vodka. He calls his wife from the hotel room, and he goes,
I'm alright. You know, I'm down here in New Mexico. I'm not in Nashville just yet.
The journey just began. What do you expect? What do you expect? No, he goes, I'm still
headed there, but... And the wife's like, what's going on? Like, she could tell
something was off. She could tell something was off. She thought it was
weird because when he called, he told her, I'm alright. Everything's okay. And she
thought, well, yeah, you just left your New Mexico. You just left a couple hours
ago. What could go wrong between LA and New Mexico? She thought that was weird. She
could tell something was wrong, so she starts pressing them for stuff. He goes,
quote, you want to believe if I told you, unquote. She asked him then, Jim, what's
the matter? Is anything wrong? And he replied, quote, forget it. Just forget I
said anything. I'll call you from Nashville, unquote. Next day, 26 miles away from
the hotel, he's seen walking near a remote ranch. He's walking away from a
parked car. He was never seen again. When he didn't get to Nashville and he didn't
call his wife, they started a missing persons case on this. And what they
figure out is that he got the hotel, but he never slept there. He got the
motel room. He left his key in the motel room, never slept in the bed. He must have
driven out that night. The last time he was seen was walking around that ranch,
26 miles away. In his car, they found money. They found clothes. They found like
luggage. They found a box of unsold records. And they found his guitar. And
that's when his wife goes, okay, something's wrong because I'll tell you
right now, he would leave all of that stuff, but he would never leave that
guitar. If he ever needed to make money, you'd probably take the cash too, but she
goes, he needs that guitar to make money. That's his life. With that guitar, he can
make it anywhere. So the fact that he left the guitar really, really made her
afraid that something bad happened. Now, the police were looking at the obvious.
One suicide. He got out of his car, just walked into the wilderness, and died on
purpose. The other one was that the car maybe had some trouble, and he walked to
go get help and died of exposure. There was no reports of the car having trouble,
though, so that puzzled them. Then there's things like foul play, that he was
forced to go out there, that somebody kidnapped him, that somebody murdered him,
and his bleached bones are somewhere in the wilderness that would show evidence
of him being murdered. But of course, because his first album was titled UFO,
the story that really took hold was the Space Brothers took him home. That he
went out into the middle of nowhere, New Mexico, which is home of Roswell, and he
got abducted by aliens. One of his best friends, Al Dobbs, this old famous actor
who actually was one of the guys who helped raise money for him, he says,
"Listen, I think it's really poetic to think that he's out there wandering
somewhere, but I think something bad happened to the guy. I don't think that
he got picked up by aliens, or he's wandering the wilderness or anything
like that." That was his take on it. But the fans of his, they're like, "How
did Dobbs you big old party pooper?" Let's say that he went and hung out with
aliens, because we don't know. And his album wasn't a success, his follow-up
album wasn't a success, and it became a collector's item for decades. In the
underground folk music scene, people would talk about Jim Sullivan, and this
mystery would be part of it. They're like, "Yeah, he recorded this album about UFOs.
He recorded the song he goes on talking about just walking." The songs are
really interesting song. The song UFO is basically about, like, the alien
brotherhood. And if you saw UFO, would you believe it was Jesus, or would you
believe Jesus was a UFO? It's a really interesting song. The album, I'll tell you
this right now, the album is great. You guys who know that I listen to music,
everyone listens to music, but I listen to West Coast 90s gangster rap, and I
listen to pop music. And that's why I don't do a dead rabbit, recommends music,
because you guys don't want to hear me recommend Spice Ones 1996. It's a great
album, it's a great album. But you guys are gonna listen to 1996 or Holo Tip,
Taking No Shorts, or any of that stuff. You guys should. It's great. You guys aren't
gonna listen to Taylor Swift's 1989, unless you guys listen to it already.
There isn't why I don't do dead rabbit recommends for music, because music is
such a personal thing. But my music tastes are pretty specific. I like
Bubblegum Pop and 90s West Coast gangster rap, in equal amounts. My mp3
player is almost a 50/50 split of those two. So when I was researching this story,
I put in Jim Sullivan's UFO album. I don't know how many times I listen to it.
It's like a half hour album, and it is so mellow and cool. You feel cool listening
to it. And I've, it's a really cool album to research to, because it's so mellow
and just kind of underneath everything. And you guys know that's not my type of
music. So I really recommend that in the show notes both albums are in there. You
can listen to them on YouTube. And sure, you can buy them as well. Because what
happened was, it was this Colt collector's item. There was only so many copies of
these albums pressed. It was a vanity press the first time. The second time it
was a flop album from Playboy Records. And in 2010, this guy who had heard this,
he's like, dude, this album is great. This guy is an amazing musician, and his
story is just bonkers. He just walked into the desert. Whether or not he got
abducted by aliens, he did just disappear without a trace. So this guy was able to
buy the rights of both albums and reissued them in 2010, and they became a big
hit. And you know why they became a big hit? Because the story of Jim Sullivan
was covered on Coast to Coast AM. It's an interesting story. It's actually kind of
heartwarming. And it does suck that he's passed on or walked away or lost or
anything like that. But his music lived long past him. Like his legacy lived on.
And it lived on through Coast to Coast AM, because he had this album called UFO.
And he very well might have been abducted by aliens. We don't know. If he had
walked off willingly, he would have taken his guitar. And if it was some sort of
mob hit, you figured they would have taken the cash. So what was going on? What
did he see? And he told his wife, "Ah, forget it. Forget it. Forget I said
anything." Did he see something in the sky? Was that simple song that he wrote
about UFOs and contactees and spiritual enlightenment involving extraterrestrial
space brothers? Did that trigger something? Maybe Jim Sullivan couldn't find an
audience on Earth, but he found an audience that was out of this world. And
then, because his story involved aliens, 50 years later, it was reported on an
alien radio show and gained the earthly audience that he deserved all along. The
story of Jim Sullivan transcends just a man walking into the desert and walking
into mystery. It's a story of an artist who struggled but never gave up. Never
gave up. He was just a man who would hit a barrier, readjust, and try again. So
whether or not Jim Sullivan was abducted by aliens, and hopefully he was.
Hopefully he wasn't murdered or he just didn't walk into the desert. Maybe he
walked into a portal. Hopefully it's something like that.
It wasn't happy or endings, because unfortunately he is missing. I can't just
make him reappear. But hopefully he did pass on into some great grand cosmic
adventure. But regardless of that, I think Jim Sullivan is a perfect example for
us and our current 90 days to a better you challenge. Right now we're all
spending the next 90 days to be better than we are today. And Jim Sullivan is
one of those people. It wasn't perfect. He had a drinking problem, his marriage was
falling apart. None of our lives are perfect, but he kept having a goal and
when he was stymied he would simply readjust and keep shooting for that goal.
He wanted to be a musical legend so much that even his disappearance from the
mortal world couldn't stop his drive. And here we are today in the year 2021
talking about a man who dreamed of being a music legend.
DeadRavverRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up
at facebook.com/DeadRavverRadio. Twitter is @DeadRavverRadio. DeadRavverRadio is
the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen
to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great weekend guys. I
have an appointment with a hog.
Are you struggling to lose weight and keep it off? Tired of wasting time and
money on starvation diets that lead to more frustration and stress? If there was
a weight loss solution that could actually work for you, would you try it? Then head to
golo.com. If you're ready to take back control of your life, head to golo.com now and see
how Golo can work for you. That's G-O-L-O.com.
My sleep is way better. My inflammation has gone way down. Golo saved my life. I was way
overweight. That's what sent me down the path. I wanted to make sure and live for my kid.
I have literally tried everything. I was on the verge of getting gastric bypass surgery
and I saw the Golo commercial and it was the last thing I tried because it worked.
Join over 2 million people who have found a better way to lose weight with Golo. Your
healthier and happier life begins at golo.com. That's G-O-L-O.com. Again, G-O-L-O.com.