Learning to swim is a magical time in a child's life.
The excitement of the water.
Playing with friends.
Making memories on vacations that will last a lifetime.
British Swim School has locations throughout the U.S.
where we specialize in teaching anyone to swim.
From babies to adults, beginners to those who need a refresher.
British Swim School's instructors make learning to swim fun
with gentle teaching methods.
Sign up your kids for swim lessons at BritishSwimSchool.com.
What happens when you're recording a paranormal podcast
and the world of the paranormal wants a sneak peek at your latest episode?
Then we travel to a lonely road in Georgia
where an overnight attendant is besieged by a smelly vagrant.
It's paranormal. It's not just somewhere.
It's not just some smelly oboe walking around.
It's paranormal and then we uncover a brand new conspiracy theory
that's currently making the rounds.
Well, one guy's talking about it, so we're going to talk about it on the show.
Is it possible that elderly people are actually grey aliens in disguise
today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey, everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Garvenor. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing.
Also, I hope you're not over the age of 65 because you might be a grey alien
and then you might want to kill me for the second story.
But before we get to that, before we get to your elderly enraged vengeance streak
against me, let's go ahead and introduce our Patreon supporter.
I don't know how old this guy is. This guy might be 88.
Coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now, everyone give a round of applause to
LacanianLifter.
Woo! Come on in Lacanian.
Yeah, give you a big round of applause. Checking your ID, seeing how old you are.
Lacanian actually used to be a Patreon and then something happened and they stopped.
They're like, "Your show started to suck, bro."
Now, something happened and they stopped, but they're joined back on.
So thank you so much, Lacanian.
You're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
Because you can't to wear the Patreon, I totally get it.
Trust me, I do. Just help spread the word about the show that really, really helps out a lot.
Lacanian, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the...
Jason Jett.
We're actually, no, we're not going anywhere right now.
Give me those keys back, bro.
I want to tell you guys this.
If you guys listened to yesterday's episode, it might have ended a little bit abrupt.
I haven't finished the final edit of yesterday's episode, but actually our first story takes place
here in Dead Rabbit Command, here in the recording studio.
What happened yesterday was I was finishing up the story about the ghost car.
It was really cool. I really liked the story of the guy walking around taking the trail through Georgia.
Got some good Georgia stories this week.
And let me play you the audio.
I edited this out because I thought it was too distracting.
It's definitely too distracting, right?
So here, let me set this up for you.
So when I'm recording, I do record in a closet.
I call it the haunted closet because I have sensed the ghost in this closet before,
but it's really been a long time since I've seen anything in my house or really anything even in the closet.
Now, as a studio, studio, it does what it does.
It has pretty good audio, but it also gets really, really hot.
These are my first episodes coming back from a long break.
I was super nervous.
I was just sweating the whole time.
So what I did was at a certain point, I cracked open the door.
I know that's not good for studio recording.
They normally don't snoop, dog normally doesn't go, "Hey, I'm about to bust the track."
Open the windows.
Let's get all that outside noise.
But I opened the door.
Okay.
The doors open maybe, I don't know, a little less than a foot.
I'm getting some sunlight in here.
I'm getting some fresh air.
And if you've never, I do a live show every Sunday morning for the Patreon supporters.
So they'll often see this.
Sometimes I add video to it.
They definitely hear it.
None of this show is really scripted.
It's all just notes.
And then I just kind of go off the top of my head.
That's why I'm always laughing at the jokes because it's the first time I've heard those jokes too, right?
But a lot of times I come to the end of an episode and I'll just kind of go riff for like 10 minutes
trying to find the right combination of words to wrap up an episode.
And that's what was happening yesterday.
And I'm sitting there in my closet.
I'm trying to figure out a good way to wrap up the story about a guy who saw a ghost car.
And I just can't find it.
And you know, it's like 8 o'clock at night.
I'm super tired and I'm super sweaty.
And I look out the little, look out my door, right?
I'm just kind of gazing around trying to think of a way to finish this episode.
And when I look out the door, I see an apparition.
I straight up see a ghost.
Well, okay, so what I see, it's so weird.
I turn and I look and I see standing right outside my door like this thing was watching me record the podcast.
It was as if you took a ribbon.
Now it was a black ribbon that was bold black on the edges and in the middle was like translucent, almost see-through, almost smoky material.
I turned and I look and I saw hovering there for a good few seconds, hovering there, a ribbon.
And it looked like if you had an invisible woman, invisible man standing outside your closet, like you're like, "Oh, I know exactly what that looks like, Jason."
If you had an invisible person and you placed a ribbon on them, you could see, I could see the outline of the top of their head.
And then it came down and then it was the outline of their left shoulder.
The ribbon was probably about maybe two feet long.
And I'm turning, I'm gonna play the clip for you without any audio processing or anything.
I'll play that for you in a second so you can kind of hear what was going on while I was experiencing this.
But I turn and I look because I'm just trying to think of a way to end this episode.
I've been recording for like two hours at this point.
I did two episodes back to back yesterday.
So I look and I see this ribony, this smoky ribony thing outside of my closet in full bedroom light, you know, full lamp.
Jason's not saying to the term.
You know, full light bulb light.
And I see it and it hangs there for a second and then it disappears.
And it doesn't go, "Bip!"
It doesn't disappear like a flash.
It just slowly fades from view.
And you can hear the audio of me experiencing this.
I just stopped talking and I'll play that for you right now.
I think the answer to that is pretty clear.
We have a lot of stories of people mysteriously vanishing in the woods
or down dark alleys
or inside houses.
We have a lot of stories of people mysteriously vanishing in the woods
and very, very few of them ever return.
Would you be one of them?
Would you be one of those that make it back to the world of our reality?
Dude, no joke.
There was something standing outside my closet watching me record that.
That was insane.
Yeah, I turned.
I don't know why I turned to look.
You guys might have even heard me turn while I was talking.
This is not scripted and nothing like that.
I don't mess around with this type of stuff.
Like I don't joke about this stuff.
No, he profools or nothing.
I turned and I looked.
And it was like a black ribbon.
Would have been.
Hold on.
Yeah, this is not joking around.
It would have been about maybe six feet tall, but it was a black ribbon.
But it looked like a phenomenon in my house.
I do have to live.
It's probably it would be like if you put a ribbon on somebody's head
and like laid across the top of their head, but there's no ribbon.
I don't know how often you guys watch videos of my house.
I don't.
I'm not a big ribbon a fishy and not.
That was weird.
I got that was creepy.
There was straight up something watching me do that.
Now I it was so weird, right?
I kind of then I got up and I walked.
I don't know how much of the clip I'm actually going to play for you.
But what if I don't play at all?
What I do is then I get up and I walk around my bedroom.
I'm kind of processing what I saw and I'm still talking into the microphone.
I'm saying how tall.
So here's the thing.
This is the weird thing about ghosts.
There's a lot of weird things about ghosts.
First off, they're dead people or demons or whatever they are.
But one thing that I've had in my experience because I've seen a lot of ghosts in my life is ghosts.
Don't and if it's a real ghost in a place that I'm at, I'm not scared of it.
I'm a little bit be a little bit at ease like uneasy.
If it's real, I'm not scared.
If it's fake, I'm scared.
So I saw this black ribbon materialize outside my closet.
Like it was peeking in.
Not scared.
When about my business actually went to the living room and while I was kind of editing episodes and stuff like that,
I see something out of the corner of my eye in the living room.
And then my black mouse, you know, my computer mouse is black and it's shiny.
I actually see something move over the mouse like the reflection changed.
So we also had that stuff going on as well.
So wasn't scared.
Right.
Came in, shut my light off to go to bed, pulled down my phone, goofing off,
going to stupid websites, stuff like that went to bed.
Even though I saw a ghost that don't know what it is, don't know what its intent is.
I see it in here.
Yesterday morning, I was walking to work.
I just watched the movie, the bye bye man.
I'd watched the movie, the bye bye man and I was walking to work and I was thinking of the bye bye man
and a squirrel jumped out of a bush and I almost beat my pants.
It's so weird.
Like something that's fake will scare me.
The bye bye man.
I'm like, oh, but when there's a ghost in my actual apartment, it doesn't scare me.
However, I know I'm a paranormal researcher.
I know I'm a ghost hunter.
You don't want it in your house.
Really.
I mean, now it's attacking me.
Ah, no, I'm not saying you got to leave, but it's more troublesome.
Like I don't really think this, whatever this is, has any ill will towards me.
So that's interesting.
But like if the goblins are supposed to be at your house and then I go to your house
and investigate goblin activity.
I don't think even a hunter, like if you were a hunter, I don't think you want a bunch of rabbits
jumping around in your house.
Right.
I mean, you're like, I love shooting rabbits in the brain with the shotgun, but I like to go.
I like to do it on my off time, not at home.
So we'll see what happens.
Like this could have been a one off thing.
I didn't feel any ill will towards if it does decide to stick around, you know, I'll deal with it.
I'm not going to sage the place or anything like that if it has good intent, right?
But that was really weird.
It was really weird to see something like that.
It's been years since I've seen a ghost on that level.
But there's one here now, apparently.
Maybe it's just passing through.
Maybe it's waiting for the ghost bus.
Maybe it's on the way to your house.
And if so, then I think it's pretty chill.
Actually, I wouldn't worry about it.
But yeah, it's just weird, just weird to be record.
And you know, it's so funny.
I think it was in that episode or the episode before it.
I was like, oh, that ghost can come to my house.
I kept talking about someone who's trying to get a ghost to come to their house.
I think it was the Monday episode and maybe a ghost, maybe a ghost.
And then understand I was speaking in the third person.
Who knows?
But a weird story nonetheless.
You know, that took a lot longer.
And I know with all the processing and everything like that,
that segment's probably going to be like 20 minutes.
Let's go ahead and set aside the hobo vagrant story.
We're going to save that for tomorrow.
Let's move into a snowier region than my house.
So let's go ahead and toss the canning and lifter the keys to the carpenter copter.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're flying all the way out to a snowy mountain town.
This story is short.
We might have time for the Georgia story, but I want to make sure I can give the story.
It's full, full due.
And I've got to give a shout out to Amphis Allen.
Amphis Allen, longtime supporter of the show, sent us a lot of really good stuff for Dead Rabbit.
I really, really appreciate it.
This story is just as good as the other ones.
Like sending me nothing but gold.
Amphis Allen apparently posted this video the other day of a 70 year old woman.
He, let me get this straight actually.
So he videotaped, no, no, no.
He posted a video.
He's skiing and his mother-in-law is filming him.
His 70 year old mother-in-law is filming him.
And he's like, "Chair in a month, go Amphis Allen, go!"
And it was like, "Hey, look at this."
It was from a subreddit called Praise the Cameraman.
Because the cameraman's doing, or camera woman, don't be sexist subreddit.
So anyways, this actually was a woman.
They're going down the hill.
So he posted this video.
It's like, "Hey, look at my mother-in-law is filming me as I'm flying down the slopes."
This dude actually is like a world renowned athlete, Amphis Allen.
So he posted this video and because the internet is a super, super weird place,
he gets a comment from a guy known as Ahoyle.
And Ahoyle tells this story.
Ahoyle says, "You know what?
I used to live in a mountain town."
And that's where we're walking around right now.
We're walking around this unnamed mountain town.
We got big mittens on in like the parkas and we're walking around.
Ahoyle's story is this.
He used to live in a mountain town up in a snowy region.
And he worked at the local pizza shop, the local pizzeria where you'd go in and you'd
get some delicious food, maybe throw back a brusque or two and watch the snow fall outside.
And he says, you know what?
He's referring to Amphis Allen's 70-year-old mother-in-law videotaping this.
He goes, "You know what?
I'm going to be surprised how many old people can ski in snowboard and do it fairly well."
And he goes, "I have a theory and to be honest, I'm kind of joking, but I'm kind of not.
I believe that aliens hide out in mountain towns all over the world."
So think about it.
Old people look like gray aliens, right?
Hold your questions until the end.
Old people kind of do look like gray aliens, right?
They're balding.
Gray aliens are bald.
They got skinny little limbs.
Gray aliens have skinny little limbs.
That's kind of weird that they're not gray.
Most old people aren't gray.
However, they do start to get a little ashy looking, right?
Why do they do that?
Why do you old people...
YouTube's going to shut this down for ageism, but when you get old, you know, you do...
You kind of lose a little bit of color in your skin.
So why?
Is it because they're old and they are having less nutrients or they're out in the sun less?
Is it because they're not human anymore?
Gray aliens?
But he says it's weird because old people do kind of look like gray aliens, but that's
not the only thing.
That's not the only part of this conspiracy theory.
He goes, "Sometimes when I'm working at a pizzeria, I'd get these elderly people showing
up to the pizza shop and they would be paying me in cash.
And the cash was always old money, like the bills, the bills, the dates when the bills
were printed were like the 1960s, but they looked brand new.
So I was getting this money that was brand new that had old dates on it from like the
60s, and I thought, hmm, maybe they're gray aliens, right?
These people up in mountain regions pay me in weird money.
Now I would assume there's some sort of counterfeit ring going on.
That would be my first assumption.
Did I ever talk to you?
Did I ever mention that before?
My grandpa knew a guy who counterfeited money.
My grandpa's dead.
You can't come after him, FBI, but my grandpa knew a dude who would counterfeit money and
he lived on a boat in Sacramento and he would just have a water cooler of $5 bills, fake
$5 bills, and he would just hand them out to people.
I don't know who the guy was before the feds come and asked me.
I don't know who the guy was.
It's been 20 years since I heard that story, but so you do have old people who counterfeit
and they just counterfeit very, very low bills.
But anyways, anyways, now that it's a counterfeit ring, he thinks they might be gray aliens,
but here's the interesting part, right?
Ampestal and Sendis told me we both had a good chuckle, but there was something that
could be fact checked with this conspiracy theory, and those are always the best conspiracy
theories, the ones that we can actually take a really close look at.
He said snow, this is what Ohio said, snow is actually kind of a rare phenomenon as far
as the galaxy goes.
Now I can't fact check that old people love to use new bills other than the fact that
my grandpa knew a counterfeiter, an elderly counterfeiter.
And yeah, sure, old people do kind of look like gray aliens if you forget the fact they
have giant eyeballs and they're three feet tall and they have these massive heads, sure,
they share some of the qualities of a gray alien, i.e. they have arms and legs and they're
bold.
But snow is a rare phenomenon galactically.
So me and Ampestal were kind of joking about this and then I looked it up.
Snow is extremely rare.
H2, I know a bunch of scientists, I know a bunch of people who are into science who listen
to this podcast are typing comments and emails right now, hold on.
Snow as we know it, H2O snow that sticks and packs and forms snow shelves and snowy mountains
and stuff like that, we're the only place in the solar system that we know that this
happens.
There's other planets, there's moons that we think it snows, but it's like volcanic
ash coming down from the sky.
It's carbon snow.
It's like Mars, it snows like there's ice, but snow they said it doesn't stick, like
it snows in the poles, but by the time it hits the ground it's gone.
We think, we think it might snow on Pluto, as much as we know that Pluto is like super
frozen.
We don't know for sure.
Even then it's Pluto.
Even then it's a dirt ball of a planet that's super far away.
This is super interesting because snow is so rare in our solar system that you would
have to extrapolate that out.
It's probably very rare galactically.
Something that for the most part we take for granted.
I always thought it was interesting that the number one, as far as we know, the number
one rarest thing in the universe, liquid water, we pour all over our bodies, we splash it
in our face.
I mean we do drink it, right?
But we build holes in the ground and fill it full of the most precious resource in the
universe.
As far as we know, liquid water is one of the rarest things ever.
It rains diamonds on like Jupiter or Saturn or something like that, or one of the moons.
But there's no liquid water anywhere else that we know of.
And we put it in balloons and throw it at people, right?
We spray our dogs with a hose and they go "ugh" and they get it all wiggly all over you and
it's fun.
And then Charles Crone yells at you "Bate-O-Van!"
That's weird.
That is the detail that makes me go "Maybe there is something to this."
Now again, YouTube and anyone else who thinks I'm being "agist" I'm not saying that all
old people are grey aliens.
So what I am saying is that if you could travel the galaxy and you'd seen stars explode and
you'd watch your buddies get sucked into a black hole and you're like "Oh that prank went
bad!"
As you watch their entire starship get stuck on the event horizon, you've seen all of these
great things but snow.
Standing outside watching frozen water softly come down sticking out your little tongue,
getting some on it.
It's to be so rare you could experience so many other amazing things throughout the galaxy
but if you wanted to see snow you'd have to come here.
You wanted to ski, snowball fight, igloos, whatever.
You'd have to do it here.
That's so interesting and think about this when you have like old people here or rich
people whatever and they want to vacation, sure they could go to a tropical location
anywhere on the planet.
They could go to some deserted island.
They're rich and powerful.
They can go anywhere, right?
They can afford anything.
But they still go to the same resort towns that everyone else goes to because the infrastructure
is there to support them.
If Bill Gates wanted to go to a tropical island but there's no landing pad there and let's
say that he goes "Build the landing pad then he gets there."
There's no hotels, there's no houses.
It's just a deserted island.
He's like "Ah, this totally sucks and you'd have to build the infrastructure."
All that infrastructure is here.
So sure even if there was another planet where it did snow, H2O, there's no resorts, there's
no pizzerias, there's no infrastructure for that.
So this, it's interesting because we always talk about Earth being a prison planet.
We talk about Earth being a zoo.
The aliens a long time ago put us here and they crossbred themselves with the monkey
people and then that's where the Homo sapiens came from and we went to dig up gold for the
Anunnaki and da da da da.
It's always so dismal and dark and evil, right?
It's always we were slaves or we are prisoners or the Archons or drinking our loosh when
we die and we get stuck in a reincarnation.
Why is it always so dismal with conspiracy theories?
Why is it always so negative?
Pretty Earth is the happiest place in the galaxy.
I mean, okay, outside of all the wars, outside of all the wars and the pestilence and stuff
like that and all the horrible crimes.
Galactically speaking, we don't have volcanoes that rip the atmosphere in two.
We are not sitting on the edge of a star system that's about to go supernova.
Pretty chill, right?
The environment is stable.
It snows, it rains, there's beautiful sunsets.
You can sit on a beach and a day later be scaling a mountain, looking down at the valley
below.
It's really a beautiful place.
So maybe we aren't a prison planet.
Maybe we aren't some sort of zoo where the monkeys have taken over.
Maybe we're club med as far as the galaxy goes and that's why so many aliens are coming
here.
We're always hearing about these reptilians and Pleiadians and the grays and all these
other guys, right?
Because you imagine, I don't think the Pleiadians have a bunch of reptilians walking around.
And I imagine on the gray alien homeworld, if that even exists, a lot of people think
it's their biorobots created by the reptilians.
But we're going to into the weeds here.
We're the only planet that all these other different species can come to, right?
Maybe we are a resort planet.
Maybe we are the cancun of the galaxy.
And so it would make sense that you would have gray aliens coming down or any aliens,
right?
I think a lot of alien with an alien lore, especially with reptilians, their shapeshifters,
it would make sense for them to come down to a place that's peaceful, that doesn't have
all of their wars.
It has our wars, but it doesn't have these galaxy spanning conflicts.
We may actually be the Casablanca of the galaxy, a neutral planet that people can come and
relax.
Very, very fascinating conspiracy theory, I think.
And we need more positive conspiracy theories.
I really do.
If you want to talk about the Archons drinking our lush, the way you could generate the
mo- We did a whole episode on that.
That's really what in the world's lush.
I'm not sure what that episode is.
The idea is that there's this matrix built around the planet.
And when you die, when it says go into the light, that's actually a trick to get your
soul to reincarnate on Earth.
And these demons, Archons, whatever you want to call them, these alien overlords are drinking
all of your negative energy.
And what produces more negative energy than telling somebody that they're trapped in a
matrix full of negative energy?
We need more positive conspiracy theories.
And I think the fact that if you start looking at elderly people thinking they're actually
gray aliens on vacation, that's pretty dope.
Again, not all of them.
Don't go to a retirement home and have a conga line and be like, "Come on, grays, get on
up."
Actually, that sounds pretty good.
You should volunteer at your local retirement home.
It really helps out.
But do not retire just because you think they're gray aliens.
You're like, "Now I'll do the probing."
Don't do that.
There's actually a lot of crimes that happen in retirement homes.
My point is, this is a good conspiracy theory.
I like this.
We need more of this stuff.
We need more stories that don't inspire negativity in us, but inspire hope.
So ohoyle, I hope you are correct.
I hope there is a portion of the elderly community that are gray aliens.
Because then it would mean that this world isn't a dismal place on the brink of annihilation
every single day.
It's actually stable enough for aliens of all races to come here and hang out for a
bit.
That's a great conspiracy theory.
I really do like that.
Or I have to be very careful because I'm sure there's one guy right now probably grabbing
his crowbar being like, "I got to take care of those gray aliens."
They're walking to the retirement home.
I am not saying that all elderly people are gray aliens just so we are clear.
But I love this conspiracy theory.
Are some of them, are some elderly people gray aliens visiting in disguise?
Are really any aliens, right?
Although if I was a reptilian, I think I would take the form of like Shaquille O'Neal
and not a 80 pound old man.
But I like this.
I like this.
I like positive conspiracy theories.
And what a way to think of the world as a beautiful place that other people want to
come to visit.
Not a dismal place of hate and vengeance and blood and ash, but a place that is so okay
to be fair.
It is those things.
But maybe it is better than those things combined.
I think maybe the love and the joy and the passion that humanity truly has for each other
reaches out and attracts aliens of all stripes to this world.
Because we're that dope.
We're that awesome.
We're the only place in the known galaxy where it snows.
They may have the starships.
They may have the technology.
They may have the cure for all the diseases that plague us.
But from the highest peak to the lowest valley, earth is the place to be.
They're jealous of us.
They have all that technology, but they're jealous of us.
This is the only place in the known galaxy where you can walk outside and watch it snow
from the heavens.
Powdery white bliss raining down on the beautiful planet known as our home.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also head us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great one guys.
(upbeat music)
[ Music ]