Could we soon be facing a crime wave of cuddly criminals?
And then we travel to Connecticut to meet five teenagers with attitude
out practicing their martial arts late one night.
They thought they were just gonna have some fun throwing kicks in the air.
Instead they go toe to toe with the demonic force today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover here so we're gonna get started. We got some
breaking news coming but first off I want to give a shout out to our latest
Patreon Tommy Davidson. Tommy thank you so much for supporting the show really
really helps out a lot. You're gonna be driving us around you're gonna be our
captain this episode. You can't support the Patreon. Totally get it. Totally
understand. Just help get the word out about the show. That also really really
helps out a lot. Let people know online. Let people know in person. That all helps.
Tommy let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgable. We're
gonna take a little flight. This is a breaking story. I didn't plan on doing
this but it just popped up today. Let's go ahead and fly on over to Rochester,
Indiana. That's the Durgable flying over. We're not gonna be here long so
you know take your tourist pictures now. If there's anything to see in Rochester,
Indiana I'm not for sure but we're here because these two num schools,
John L. Schultz the fourth. That means there was three preceding this guy. The
three stooge isn't in this guy and then Donald V. Robin Jr. Allegedly, allegedly
these two guys decided to shoot up two schools. These two idiots thought it
would be a great idea to go shoot up two schools just as the school year
starting and things like that. Somebody, they were telling friends because they're
so cool and they're like bragging about it and stuff and then one of their
friends who was a who wasn't an idiot alerted authorities and both these
people got arrested. Yes it is all alleged so they're allegedly num schools. I do
think it's funny though that they went and bought trench coats because they
wanted to be like the Columbine dudes. They even have tattoos of Columbine
quotes on their arms. Allegedly I mean I guess that's provable right? I'm like hey
dude show me your arm and he's like I will allegedly lift up my sleeve. I'm
like whatever just show me your arm. Anyways these two guys are in jail. They
had trench coats. They had that's not all. They actually had more stuff. It's just like
there's a bunch of guys who don't like the rain and the cops are like oh boy oh
wait and they're resting them. Guys were bragging they had access to guns and all
that stuff so the cops made a move and they have arrested them so far and then
the county prosecutor goes listen it could be a case of free speech. It was
an interesting thing. The prosecutor's like it's really the prosecutor goes
basically when you're talking about like Columbine and worshiping. Let me read you
the actual quote because it's such a bizarre quote. This is from Fulton
County prosecutor Michael Mars. He said so I mean anytime anyone's obsessed with
Columbine yes it's a fine line between free speech and when you cross the line
but I think in this case clearly what they had done was going to interfere with
the occupancy of a school. So even the prosecutors like yeah I get it they
could just be larping. They actually probably see a lot of that in law
enforcement. People have been like oh I'm gonna make them pay. I'm gonna make them all pay and
then the cops investigated and it's just like an edgy blog on Tumblr right. And
the prosecutor again yeah they must come across this a lot. That's a very weird
quote from a county prosecutor. He's like yeah you know when it comes to
Columbine sometimes people just really like Columbine but this was more than
that. So the way that this is going to anyways that is the numbskull of the week
that's my new segment. That's my new segment. It starts and ends today. If you
want to know more about these guys and their trench coat purchasing history
it'll be in the show notes. Okay let's go ahead and move to the actual first
story. Tommy or flying that dead rabbit dirgeable away from Indiana we are headed
out to Sri Lanka. This is a story that popped up the other day. The ramification
the story itself is kind of cute. The ramifications of it can be terrifying.
Dirgeable going all the way to Sri Lanka. We're gonna go to Aruna Sri Lanka
specifically in Aruna. There is the Wellicotta prison. It's high security
prison. It's where they put all their big bad guys in Sri Lanka. It's July 2020.
This just happened last month. Normal day at a prison at a high security prison.
As normal as a day you can have in a high security prison. A cat breaks into the
perimeter. Not a big deal right? Cats and rats and stuff like that are always
hanging out at prisons. A lot of people adopt them as friends or a little extra
snack on the side. You know a tasty black rat to supplement your top ramen and
cheese and crackers. But this cat was no ordinary cat. This cat was a heroin
smuggler. Now when I first read that I thought that's dope right? And then when
I kept reading the article I go that's even doper than I originally thought.
Because not only was this cat this cat just wasn't just didn't have it some
heroin on him and happened into the prison. He knew exactly what cell block to
go to. There is a cartel that has been smuggling contraband into the prison.
Specifically this cat had two grams of heroin, some sim cards, and a microchip.
Apparently so a Dr. Mindbender could finish building some sort of device to
help Cobra Commander escape. When's the last time you've even heard the term
microchip? But anyways this cat is smuggling in a microchip, a couple sim
cards, and two grams of heroin. You know like the guy who got the heroin was
like oh this is so awesome. And then the other guy who gets the sim cards he's
like ah this is okay but I have some heroin. And then the guy who gets the
microchip is like the total nerd of the prison. Everyone's like boo throwing stuff
at him. He drops his microchip he's like oh no I'll never find it now. Anyways this
cat gets arrested for smuggling this stuff in. The question is how many times
did this cat actually successfully smuggle stuff in? And the authorities are
like okay here's the plan. We're not actually gonna press charges against the
cat because that's foolish but we can follow the cat back to its hideout and
then we'll arrest the people who trained the cat. Good plan right? But before they
could do that guards at a high security prison mind you this is the level of
the level of the employees at this high security prison guards going to feed the
cat opened the door and the cat ran out. So I don't know how many prisoners
escaped from this prison on any day right? The guards are like lunchtime
people are just scattering in every direction they're like oh no anyways and
the authorities they go ah the cat's gone we can't really track it but this is
what makes this story even more bizarre. They know the cartel that trained the
cat because they know where it was going and dropping the stuff off and no joke.
In this article I'm reading this article this same cartel previously before
using the cat had trained an eagle to fly over the prison and drop stuff into
the yard. Now in America we've been having an issue with drones flying over
prisons and dropping off contraband that's cool because it's kind of like
futuristic but I'd much rather have an eagle dropping me stuff off.
Your clout in prison would be so high if you're just like standing out there
playing a little basketball in here and everyone looks up and they're like oh
yeah Johnny's getting a delivery today and then a little baggy you just hold
your hand out. A baggy falls in your hand. You might not want to be that obvious about it
because then the guards are like they hear the eagle screeching they're like
oh get ready to arrest Johnny he's gonna have a handful of microchips. It's so
funny because I read that and I was like dude that's super dope. They did end up
catching the eagle. They caught the eagle. They went to like they had found the
eagle before they'd seen the eagle flying around and they did a raid on the
cartel and there was just like an eagle in a cage and they're like hey we
recognize you. Eagles like gulp. Then I go I wonder if there are other like
criminal animals and stuff so I went to this article about it's like nine
wacky animal criminals. That's exactly what it sounds like when you read the
article in your head and it was like this alligator. I was like oh this is dope dude.
What does alligator do? It's all this alligator is a home invader. It broke into
a dood house. I'm like that's not a crime. That's not a crime. I mean it is. I can't do that.
That's just an alligator. It doesn't know what a house is. It's just breaking in.
They had a, here's a better one. They had a bird who would sit outside of this
gas station like this Aldi's in England or something like that.
Do you like my notes? Do you like my notes for this segment? There's this bird who
would sit on the sidewalk and the doors would open and close automatically and
he would just sit there and then once he like had a moment he'd fly into the
store grab a bag of chips and then fly out and eat them. There okay that's kind
of more what I'm talking about but I started to think remember back in the
day you don't because we're not a hundred years old but remember like hearing
about like the monkey grinders was that there were monkey grinders. They were the
organ grinders that had monkeys. The monkey grinders is something totally
different. Pay me a dime and I'll grind this monkey right in front of you lad.
You know what I'm talking about like not that but you give the old man a dime and
And he plays the box thing goes do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do He's like cranking it and then the little monkey dances for you
You're like, no Jason. I was not born in the year 1890. I don't remember that
I've seen it on movies and read about it in books. Those little monkey men we're trained to like pick pockets
They're like taking money out of your pocket according to a rinsed to a rintent in comic I saw so
There my here's my thing with this whole thing. Yes, I am going somewhere with this
We have animals that just do animal things like a bear is not a criminal if it breaks into your car and steals all your food
It's just being a bear and then you can actually train an animal to be a criminal
Where is the limit to that? You know the US military has trained
I always thought this was one of the funniest stories the military the US military had bred these super smart dolphins and
they would help detect mines like underwater mines and
To be funny or like that's just you know like a dog can do that a swimming dog
but these these
Dolphins would were also trained so when Russian frogmen Soviet Union frogmen were like trying to spy at US military bases and stuff like that Navy
Bases they would let these dolphins kind of just float around in the water and they would see a
Frogman they would see like an underwater spy and they would crush their ribs
They would poke them super hard in the ribs and you can't swim with broken ribs and you die now that might not be very funny
You're like Jason that's terrible. That's how my uncle died. He was a frog man. I apologize
But I always thought that was hilarious, but that's not even the funniest part of that story
That's not even the funniest part of that story Tommy. Let's take this dead rabbit dirgeable out to New Orleans
We're going to New Orleans during Hurricane Katrina. That is where they actually had a training facility for these super smart
Dolphins who was in New Orleans and it was connected to the sea
But there was these giant walls because you know the military is like listen these things are hyper smart
We've trained these things to kill people
Whatever you do don't let them go and everyone's like yeah, of course, of course, we're not gonna let these genetically
I don't know if they're genetically modified. Okay wink wink nudge nudge. I'm pretty sure they were but they were quote-unquote trained
Trained at the genetic level maybe but anyways super smart dolphins
They were in this enclosure and everyone's like, okay, this has worked for like 20 years
We've been able to keep these contained and then Hurricane Katrina showed up and everyone's like, ah, they're running away
I remember reading about this at the time. It was a sparkle of joy during that time a horrible misery
That was a horrible natural disaster
But I remember laughing out loud when I came across this article as like the researchers and the people who worked the laboratory like oh
No, what are we gonna do this this huge hurricanes coming and then it started flooding and then the floodwaters
Started to get as tall as the wall of the dolphin holding pin
And then it got taller and all the dolphins escaped all of these super smart dolphins
escaped into the sea and I remember reading an article at the time and
The basically I'll see if I can try to find the article off definitely find an article on it
But at the time I remember the military is like there's no way we're not gonna be able to catch these things
They're super intelligent dolphins that were trained to like look for explosives and kill people
You don't want those out there, right? And they just swam away
Selectively bred and trained wink wink trained at a molecular level so they're out there
So you I my thing is this is like you can train certain animals to commit crimes
The cat doesn't know he's smuggling heroin right the eagle knows something's up
He's a little fishy, but because he eats little fishies. Uh-uh you like that joke you don't but
Anyways, I want to keep it in you haven't you can teach an animal to commit a crime
They probably don't know what a crime is those dolphins know that they're murdering
Russians like they they totally are aware of that could you get to the point where week you could train a rhino to smash open a bank vault
You can actually train a rhino
I think would be your first question
But like you could have hippos and stuff because they're like bulletproof for the most part
I mean cops aren't walking around with elephant guns
You just like unleash hippos into a city and they're just like smashing cop cars and stuff like that
And then you go in and you're just like robin banks and stuff like that
Like could we get to a point where if the military is I've always said this I always say this is the first thing
I say when I meet somebody
Generally technology works like this first it works as a military application and then it works as a criminal application
bulletproof vests
Invented for the military and now
You know 50 cent can wear one in a music video, but I mean you know like originally it's a military component
And then it becomes a quote-unquote civilian thing
Which can be used to protect civilians or to aid in a crime Tommy guns weren't invented for the army
And then yeah people were writing their names on walls. I heart dick tracy just a couple years later
If they're training these dolphins and now we see criminals also training the house pets basically
To do these things will we reach a level where criminals are just like
genetically modifying animals
To commit crimes not just unleashing a cat with heroin on it, but like
unleashing a cat
It successfully delivers the heroin and as it's sneaking out of the prison it's all
And the cat had a bunch of geckos sitting on the cat. So it was completely
Camouflaged you can never see it although I guess at that point you probably just genetically modify a giant gecko
But yeah, you could have a suit made of geckos and you're just walking around and no one can see you
Everyone doesn't wonder what you have a thousand eyeballs
Thousand little eyeballs on you, but you know it's modern art and you're just walking around it from perfectly blended in
No one would know no one would know if it wasn't for that handful of microchips that you're holding
Let's go ahead Tommy Davidson. We're gonna stop giving the criminal underworld ideas
Let's hop in that carbonar copter. We are headed off to Manchester, Connecticut
We're leaving behind a bunch of octopi they've taken over the city one of them is standing in the mayor's office
The mayor's lay in motionless covered in ink
A brave new world my friends a brave new world
We're flying away. We're going to Manchester, Connecticut. It's november 6 1999
It's 2 a.m. There's a man. He's sleeping at home. He's the reverend david w bowser senior
He's sleeping at home with his wife and then
reverend
reverend reverend open up
what
He gets up and he walks through his house. He looks at the people and he sees two young men standing outside of his door
It's 2 a.m. He thinks he recognizes one of them, but both of them are dressed in all black
And he can see in the road is a car
That contains three more men
also dressed in all black and it seems that they have some sort of
Is that a sword?
Reverend open up. We need your help. Let's skip to a couple hours earlier
It's the devil's hop yard state park in east hadam
There's five young men there in the park. It's late at night one of them swinging a baseball bat
Through the air the other one has a sword
The guy with the baseball bat's like oh man. I can't wait till I get my allowance. I can buy a sword
Guy with the swords practicing his sword moves
One of the guys is hiding behind a tree. Can you see me yet? Yeah, I can kind of see you move move a little bit more behind the tree
Can you see me now? No, I can't see you. Perfect. Perfect
These five men are martial arts enthusiasts
They just got done with a rigorous martial arts workout back in town
But they said you know what if we really want to perfect our ninja moves
We have to go to devil's hop yard state park
This is something they did this wasn't like a spur of the moment thing
They're like, what should we do dinnies or pretend we're ninjas tonight and they're like, hmm
Well, we've never done the ninja thing. They've done this before
I don't know if they've done it this specific location, but these five guys
They were all 18 or older by the way
Like to pretend they were ninjas they were training themselves in the martial arts to be fair
But they also just like to pretend to be ninjas. So they would
They're swinging the baseball bats. They would do that to build muscle
Swing a baseball bat over and over and over again. You get big
They saw their heroes mark maguire and josecan seiko get totally strong
Just by swinging a baseball bat sammy sosa totally natural
We actually believed that in 1999. I don't think they'd been exposed at that time, but
Swinging them baseball bats now one of the guys there his name is paul punnitowski
He's practicing his ninja moves having a good time with his friends
Even if they're not going to be able to take on a roko sake anytime soon
It's still just a fun night with your friends. But while he's practicing his ninja moves he hears
paul
Here's his voice clearly call out from the darkness paul
Leave now or you'll join us forever
paul kind of pauses for a second looks around into the darkness
But he's not the only one who hears it. Paul paul
Leave now or you'll join us forever
He stops him in his tracks and he asked whoa, did you say that what other friend goes no
I I heard it too dude. I heard it too at that point
Playtime's over right it you may not be the master of your ninja game
But you can practice you can practice that at a ymca. It's time to leave a place called devil's hop yard
They decide to leave todd silber. He's the oldest one of the group. He's 23 years old
So get in his stuff together and he hears
Oh
Joseph Robinson 18 years old he looks over it where there's a fence line
And there's something sitting on it watching them
He described it as beast like it definitely wasn't human
More monster than man, but the one word he really used to describe it was
a demon sitting on the fence
Watching them everyone seems to be having their own
little encounter with this
element that's out there because when joseph goes hey guys guys guys guys guys guys
I know you guys really want to pack. I really want to pack too, but what is that when paul looks over and sees
What joseph is pointing at he says he sees a shadow with a jagged edge
At this point they're on their way out right they're not gonna have arguments over whether or not
It's a jagged shadow or a demon sitting on the fence. They're leaving at this point todd silber as he's getting up
He actually gets attacked by this thing. He is picked up and throwing
Through the air and crashes into a tree
Whoa
Okay guys, we really should have left. I know we really should have left when I heard that laughing
I don't know why we stood around for that to happen todd silber looks down and there's
Four claw marks on his pants. No. Oh man. My mom's totally gonna kill me
She's bought me these the other day these ninja pants now
They all get in the car and they're leaving behind devils hop yard. They all understand something supernatural happened there
Sean sear. He was one of the kids in the car. He's 18 years old
He's sitting there and he goes we need to go to my pastor's house. We need to go to my pastor's house
And they're like what and he's like we need to go to my pastor's house
We can't go home. You just can't go home something what we experienced. We need to be
Blessed now. Everyone's like, why are you talking about what did you see Sean?
Sean said
nothing
Sean said he would not he not that he couldn't that he would not describe what he saw
Had devil's hop yard. He wouldn't he flat out refused. He goes but we are not going home
You're not driving around at five driven houses and dropping us off and you can go home and play nintendo 64
But you are taking us to my minister's house reverend bowser because
This isn't over
2 a.m. They show up at the house the two men outside the house is todd silver
And Sean sear the other three guys are sitting in the car reverend bowser opens up the door and these two guys start blabbering about demons
Again picked up. Oh my god. Look at my pants. Oh, dude. You won't believe what happened
Sean sears like you got it. You I think it's still with us. I think this demon's still with us
You got to take care of us and reverend bowser basically does the only thing someone can do when he's confronted by two ninjas and three more in the car
He goes. Yeah. Yeah. Um wait right here. I'm gonna go
Get my blessing tools. I'm gonna go give you my blessing stuff. He shuts the door
calls the cops and says
Hey, man, it's too. I got these kids outside
They're not wearing masks, but everything else about them is ninja related
And one of them has some ripped pants, which is kind of bizarre, but they're talking about demons and stuff like that
Cops roll up
And the dudes in the car did have swords. This was their inventory. They had a 38 inch samurai sword three knives a club
four bats
dark colored clothing and masks
The cops are talking to the guys in the car
Sean and totter out the door the minister comes back and he's like listen
You guys just need to calm down. This is super weird. So I did call the cops
But everything's fine and at that point the cop comes up to talk to todd and shon at the door with the minister
Cop goes. Hey, I need to see your guys ID. That's standard procedure, right? I've been pulled over a hundred times
I've had my ID popped a hundred times. It's just a standard procedure
Sean
starts to shake
and then starts to resist
the officers commands
Now I don't know if they both took a position and then it was ninja versus cop training
It was something dope like that. It was probably just two people kind of pushing each other, but
There was definitely a scuffle todd's trying to break shon and the police officer up guys guys
What are you doing? What are you doing? No, he's doing a flying jump kick. Why is it super dramatic?
We'll just pretend it was right
But it doesn't matter whether or not it was on the level of enter the dragon or it was just a guy getting pushed and then
push another person because
Sean ends up collapsing
Everyone gets arrested right even Sean is just like laying there. Sean is having a
Diabetic fit like low blood sugar or something like that. That's why he began shaking in the beginning
And maybe maybe diabetics like fighting with police. I don't know
But he had it had it was complications due to diabetes is what it was called
He's treated for that
cops arrest everyone
Todd and Sean are charged with interfering with the police and all the friends were charged with breach of peace and carrying dangerous
Weapon now like I said this happened back in 1999. It was in the newspaper. It was in the current
Which is a newspaper out in Connecticut. It's all in the show notes
So I don't know. I don't think these guys actually did any hard time for it
I don't know if these guys are still in jail right now just waiting for their cat delivered heroine
Probably not of these charges most likely probably got dropped on some level or another
I don't know if Sean's been cured of his diabetes or if it's still something has to deal with but
There's an interesting footnote to this whole story
Sean starts scuffling with the cop. Let's go back to that part
Sean shaking he starts scuffling with the cop. He collapses
and that's all kind of chalked up to him having an issue with
Um low blood sugar and shaking and all that stuff fighting with the cop again
Maybe that's a normal diabetes symptom
But afterwards his friends were like Sean why in the world?
Did you think it would be a good idea to take on that cop?
Why in the world after everything that had happened everything? We're just going to check our IDs
Why'd you start fighting with the cops?
And Sean looks over at him and goes
That's what I saw
They're like what he's like
When we were at devil's hop yard remember I didn't tell anyone what I saw
I saw this
saw this thing
And when the officer approached us at the doorstep he became that thing
That wasn't a cop
That came to that doorstep
That was a demon
It's possible that Sean was starting to have some sort of complications due to low blood sugar
And hallucinating I don't know if that's a symptom of diabetes
But a skeptic could say he was a low blood sugar high
Adrenaline event
All this stuff he's seen stuff
Goes up on this cop
But here's another more chilling way and we'll end it like this
Sean was insistent that it wasn't over yet that they had to get blessed
By the minister
Couldn't just drop him off at home. This thing was loose
They had to get blessed by the minister. So when they go to the minister's house, what doesn't happen?
They don't get blessed
What if Sean
Was right and this thing did follow them out of the park
Leave now or you'll join us forever is what the voice said at the park
What would be the point of taking over an 18 year old pretend ninja?
The minister himself would have protections from such possessions
But if a patrol unit a cop car coming about to do his duty now that
Is someone that a demon could have a lot of fun possessing
By the time the police officer walks up to Sean and Todd
It's already almost in full possession
This demon is now free and in the body of a law enforcement officer
And the only one who knows
is Sean
and his four friends
They were training to be ninjas, but instead they found themselves on the front line of a supernatural invasion
So the next time you're driving through town
You see those red and blue lights behind you. You know, you haven't broken any traffic laws
But you pull over it's weird because the cop car behind you looks older. It doesn't even look like one from this
decade
But the lights keep flashing and the officer walks up to the driver's side of the car flashlight blinding you
You can't really see who it is. You can't see that the uniform is older. You can't see that the badge
Is from a different state, but as that officer
Asked you for your driver's license
You have to wonder
Is he pulling you over because he thought you were speeding or is he pulling you over because he's looking for a fresh body
For one of his demonic friends
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio
Twitter is @deadrabberadio. Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today 500 episodes
Season 11 have a great one guys
Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)
[music ends]