(children cheering)
- Learning to swim is fun.
British Swim School is welcoming all new students
to start their journey in the world of water.
The team of highly trained experts at British Swim School
will show your little fish all the ins and outs
of life in the water,
while also sharing valuable knowledge on water safety.
So is it time for your kids to get their feet wet?
Sign them up now at britishswimschool.com.
That's britishswimschool.com.
British Swim School, make us flash.
Previously on Dead Rabbit Radio.
(growls)
Knocking stuff over.
This is "Dead Rabbit Show."
Whatever it's called,
"Dead Rabbit Radio" is the actual name,
but this show is revealing the secret truths we have.
Every episode he does is true.
But some of his episodes counter-dict
the other episodes that he does.
It doesn't matter.
Those episodes are actually even more true.
We have to stop him.
We have to stop him before he exposes
all of our evil plans.
(upbeat music)
Oh man, so fun playing Apex Legends
while my break's going on,
but it's time to shut it off.
And now I'm going to sit back, relax,
and assume nothing bad is going to happen.
(upbeat music)
Oh, what was that?
Game's off.
I ran outside.
What?
Open my squeaky door.
Oh my God.
Bodies everywhere.
The destruction.
If you could only see it is,
it's shocking.
But I don't know any of them, so that's cool.
But, oh my God.
My hanger.
And my garage that's attached to my hanger.
No, I wasn't clapping.
I was running into the hanger.
Oh my God.
No.
Carpenter copter.
It's on fire.
Oh my God.
And it's destroyed.
It's completely destroyed.
The Jason Jalopy.
Oh no.
The Jason Jalopy burned to a crisp.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Oh my God.
The Dead Rapid Durageable is still here
and it's in one piece.
No.
There's only one thing I can do now.
I have to assemble a team.
(upbeat music)
(yells)
After I finish playing some more Apex Legends,
but now I will assemble my team.
So, I urge you the man to come to,
if I need some muscle.
Mungo has lots of muscle,
given to me by God and supplements.
Thank you Mungo, will you be on my team?
(yells)
As long as we can push nerds.
Hey, do that anyways.
Come on Mungo.
Hey.
(mimics gunshots)
A bunch of pictures being taken.
I don't know how to make that sound.
I had phones, either using the phones,
there's no noises.
All these photos are being taken.
Hey, hey.
Jason, my best friend ever.
Yes, yes, Miley Cyrus.
It is I, your best friend.
I'm putting together a team.
Say no more.
Now, we just have one more person to put on our team.
Hello?
소?!
Is anyone here?
Here?
Yeah.
Bongono liked this house.
Looks like Gollum's house from nerd novel.
Yeah, what we're about to face is far worse than Gollum.
Did you know?
Franz, Franz dude, quit creeping us out with your- how are your arms that long?
Why do you come here?
Franz listen dude, truce, I need your help to fight the bad guys who blow up all my stuff.
You need my help?
As I sound very Gollum like?
Yes, Franz, we need your help.
I'm declaring a truce.
You did not know about the truce?
What do you have to offer me?
How about a 12 pack of diet cranberry sprites?
Maybe, listen Franz, you don't have anything better going on.
You're scurrying around your dark apartment, just come with us.
Okay.
And now, season 5 of Dead Rabbit Radio.
That's a preview when we go to the jungle and we get attacked by a giant cat and I throw
Franz in front of it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.