They truly are like family to us.
We are so lucky to have these people that just care.
At Ann and Robert H. Lurie Children's Hospital of Chicago,
we know that caring for your child takes more than medicine.
They're not just treating the disease.
They're caring for Olivia.
They know my baby's name.
They make me happy.
And they make me feel better.
With cutting-edge treatments and kid-friendly care,
there's a reason Lurie Children's has ranked the number one
Children's Hospital in Illinois.
I would always recommend Lurie Children's, always.
The world ends in the coolest way possible.
And then we take a look at the Gifted and Talented Education Program.
Some people say it's a program that helps young kids
who are gifted and talented achieve their dreams.
Others say it's a twisted mind-scape used to control the future.
Today on Dead Ravver Radio.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, everyone.
Welcome back to another episode of Dead Ravver Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day, too.
It's the start of season 10.
It's crazy when this season's done.
We'll be at episode 500.
Isn't that crazy?
We're just going to keep checking along, like a choo-choo train,
the conspiracy train.
How come I don't have a train?
If I ever come up with a train, the Carpenter Caboose?
We'll think about that.
But while we're thinking about that,
we've got to say thank you to one of our newest Patreon.
We got Caleb.
Caleb in the house.
Thank you so much for supporting the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
Let's get him on board that Carpenter Caboose.
That just sounds wrong, because the Caboose is the end, right?
Whatever.
We're a backwards train.
Let's hop on board the Carpenter Caboose, Caleb.
You are going to be piling in it.
You're like, "Dude, I can't see from back here."
Yeah, yeah, you'll figure it out.
So anyways, as Caleb is shoveling coal
into our brand new vehicle, the Carpenter Caboose,
we are headed out to Rostov-on-Don.
That's in Russia.
It's October 7th, 1989.
It's midnight.
There's like a full moon in the sky.
Don't look that up.
If you find out there's not a full moon on October 7th, 1989,
like in some sort of like National Geographic
Farm Resolomon Act nonsense, don't even mouth me.
Just for visual, right?
Just for, you're like, "Jason, that's factually incorrect."
Yeah, but it's a beautiful factually incorrect image.
Full moon.
I don't know why it's making wind noises,
but it's doing it.
That was in the Farm Resolomon Act.
Look that up.
Moon.
And there's a young woman named Valentina Boldina
walking on the street.
She's walking on the street
and she sees two glowing orbs.
Right now that's weird, right?
You don't expect to see orbs
when you're leaving your place of work.
Unless you work at orbs arrest
and you're like, "Bye orbs.
Seize these orbs.
I don't know why you would be saying goodbye
to the merchandise you sell.
No one's walking out of toys arrest me.
I'm like, "See you later, toys.
See you tomorrow.
I can't wait to sell more of you."
And apparently you're Mickey Mouse as well
in that scenario.
The little orbs are flying down.
Now one of the orbs turns into the shape of a human.
She's just like, "What in the world is going on?
I should not be walking around at night.
It's a midnight.
She's walking around the outskirts of the city.
She sees these two orbs.
One of them shapeshifts into a human.
And then the other orb just goes
(imitates engine)
and starts like shining lights on the human.
Weird.
She's bringing her own disco ball with you.
(imitates engine)
And the humanoid is just standing there.
And then the other one's just (imitates engine)
And that's the end of that.
That's not the end of the whole story,
but that's the end of that part of the story.
She just goes home.
Couple days later, she's at home.
She's laying in bed.
It's nighttime.
Now she's not ready to go to sleep,
but she's having a hard time with life in general.
Because ever since she saw that little impromptu disco show,
terrible splitting migraines has a hard time staying awake.
And then she's laying in bed and her lights go off.
Bedroom light, (imitates engine)
all the lights in her house go off.
Now, she's probably like, "Oh, this is great.
"I'm already super sick.
"I can't stay awake.
"I'm like all lethargic, my head's splitting.
"And now I gotta go and I gotta screw in a bunch of light bulbs,
"check the fuse box and stuff like that.
"My life stinks."
But before she can really start to think about that,
there's a huge crash of lightning outside her house.
But no sound.
No sound.
There's just a big bright light going,
(imitates explosion)
right outside her house.
Illuminates her room for a minute.
Totally scares her.
And then, guess who floats into her room?
Don't you, don't guess.
There's actually an answer.
I don't wanna hear a bunch of people being like,
"Ronald McDonald."
Oh, it's not Ron McDonald.
It's the original ghost, not a ghost.
It's the original alien that appeared
doing the disco show a couple days ago.
And this glowing figure just,
(imitates explosion)
just kind of floats into her room.
And this time, it's no longer a humanoid shape
that she's kind of seeing off in the distance.
We get an actual description of what this thing looks like.
Here's the description.
It's this hot chick.
I'll jump to the, I'll just jump to the end.
It's a hot chick.
She's this tall, really curvy brunette.
I mean, that's fine, I guess.
But she's this tall, really curvy brunette
with big dark eyes.
Not like creepy alien dark eyes,
but like Kim Kardashian dark eyes.
And she had shiny black hair.
She was pale skin and stuff like that.
And she had on a skin tight coveralls.
So she had like on a skin tight spacesuit.
Pretty sexy alien, right?
If anyone's going to walk into your bedroom
after giving you migraines
and turning you into a zombie who can't stay awake,
it better be a hot chick.
Hot chick floats into her room.
Valentina's lying there in bed, just totally.
(groans)
She'll totally super sick.
She's like, "Oh no, I didn't have time to put on my makeup.
Oh, it looks so ugly."
And the alien's like, "I'm not worried about that."
I came from another star system.
You are quite ugly by our standards,
even if you didn't wear makeup, but don't worry about that.
The alien goes on to tell this story to Valentina.
She says, "They're from a place known as the blue star."
Sounds like a strip club, but it's not.
This refers to an alien thing.
It's because an alien's saying it, right?
If an alien came down to you and been like,
"I'm from Chevron," you're not gonna be like,
"What, the guest station down the street?
You know Billy?"
I mean, obviously it means something.
Blue star, though, sounds again like a strip club.
But you would assume because an alien's saying it,
they're referring to an actual blue star.
Valentina, her first question out of her mouth is,
"Why are you here?"
And this alien woman says this.
We have some quotes.
Quote, "To take you with me, do you want to come?
You will not regret it."
This alien says, "Hey, do you want to come with us?"
Which, it's a pretty good selling point at this point.
This woman's dying, right?
For the past couple of days,
she had horrible migraines and can't stay awake
and an alien's like, "Come on, come on, you go."
Anywhere's better than where she's at right now,
which will actually end up being,
that's a very true statement.
But she's, the woman's like, "No, I don't want to go."
And she's totally petrified,
despite the fact that she's super, super sick.
She feels the aliens are giving this to her.
So she's like, "No, I don't want to go with you.
So you can give me worse migraines on our planet.
Migraines are considered orgasms."
No, this is awful.
Just want to stay here.
And the alien goes, "Watch this."
And then a giant view screen appears
in Valentina's bedroom.
That's kind of cool, right?
She refused to go on the ship,
but they brought the ship technology to her.
That's pretty polite.
A view screen appears in,
and I know you're going chasing this woman,
obviously, is having some sort of fever dream.
She's in bed, she's been sick for three days,
and alien shows up and now the alien's magical.
She's obviously having some sort of delirium.
Let me just finish this story, skeptic Joe.
The giant magical screen appears in the Valentina's bedroom,
and it shows images of an alien planet.
Supposedly the alien planet the alien's from, right?
That wouldn't make sense.
The alien could be tricking her
and showing her like a really cool planet
that's near their planet, near the blue star,
but not the one they're taking to her, not migraineopolis.
But she starts, we'll assume it's the alien's homeworld
that the alien's not some con man.
You see this, on this view screen,
Valentina sees this beautiful alien landscape
with just beautiful lakes.
She said that the lakes looked like,
the color was mother of pearl.
She actually doesn't look that appetizing.
That looks kinda good.
They would look unclean to a human.
If you saw like a cloudy white lake, I'm like,
"Ugh, no thanks, ugh."
That's gross, I'm not swimming in that.
You get out, you're all covered in white goo, uh-uh.
Then she sees these large, like, virgin fields of grass.
There's no buildings is what that means.
It doesn't mean that the grass doesn't procreate.
It means that it's just like, "It's just grass,
grass as far as the eye can see."
Which to you and me would be super boring, right?
Eventually you'd wanna run into something,
like at least some patch of dirt.
You'd be like, "Oh, that's exciting.
There's the pictures mound out here."
But anyways, grass as the eye can see,
virgin grass as far as the eye can see,
creamy white soup, lakes, that's gross.
And then that doesn't sell Valentina.
She, Valentina does say it's one of the most beautiful
images she's ever seen in her life.
Like, she's absolutely mind-boggling.
She sees these sea, this sea of the white film,
ugh, and all this virgin grass and stuff like that.
And then, but that doesn't make the sale.
That doesn't make the sale, right?
This is the alien's ace in the hole.
This is alien, so basically the alien woman showed up,
gave her crippling migraines.
That might've been accidental.
Then breaks into her house, says, "Come home with me.
You won't regret it."
And then the Valentina's like, "No."
And then the alien goes, "Well, look how beautiful
my planet is."
I shift from side to side when she says,
"My planet, it's the planet next door."
And still doesn't sell Valentina.
And then this is where we get to what's important to us
as humans, as homo sapiens.
This is the most important part of this story.
So then the alien goes, "Okay, ping."
And then the view screen dims and it comes back
to a human city.
So now she's seeing a vision of Earth.
So it's like this human city.
And Valentina wasn't able to identify if it was Seattle
or San Francisco or Kiev or anything like that.
What is Aries?
But what she sees is this human city and a giant monster.
(growling)
Knocking over buildings, (growling)
stepping on stuff.
And then another giant monster sweeps down into the city.
(growling)
grabs a skyscraper, rips it into, (growling)
people are running down the street,
creatures of immense magnitude.
(panting)
Chasing them down, grabbing humans underneath their claws,
ripping them. (growling)
One looks right at the camera, charges the camera.
She sees the end of the world will not be through fire
or storm, it will be through massive monsters
that are going to destroy our man-made cities
with their bare hands.
And the alien goes, this is the future of Earth.
This is the future of Earth.
This is her, should we have a quote
from these horrible images,
and admittedly pretty badass images, right?
Here's these quotes.
Here is what awaits the Earth.
We are shielding you from this,
but we are not omnipotent.
Remember that.
I give you three days, and then I will come for you.
So now, Valentina, it's not just,
hey, you got a horrible migraine,
why don't you come visit my place for a while?
Now, it's listen, monsters are going to destroy your cities.
Giant, all those monster movies you ever saw,
talk about predictive programming,
mothrides, real, all of these creatures
are actually going to destroy human civilization.
And we can hold them off, but we can't stop them forever.
I'm gonna give you three days to think about them.
Alien fades from view.
I'm assuming the view screen faded from view as well,
because I don't think she spent the next three days
not going into her bedroom,
because it's just snuff films of monsters eating people.
She's like, where's the remote?
Where's the remote?
She's sleeping in the living room.
She can hear the, ah!
It's the 18th day of the monsters
attacking all of civilization.
And we're still, no, ah!
She hears all of the,
she would not have a hard time staying awake at that point,
knowing that in the other room,
people are being murdered in the future.
Three days pass, Valentina.
I'm assuming her migraines have gone away this point too.
Now she's probably just puking up blood from anxiety,
but we don't have any more notice
of her having the migraines.
But three days pass, and all of a sudden,
she feels a tingling, or what she calls quote,
signals in her brain.
Ah, ah, ah.
And you're like, Jason, that is,
the biggest piece of evidence that this woman
is having some sort of neurological disorder, okay?
You're saying this woman,
the story is probably true in the sense that this woman
has some sort of neurological problem,
'cause she was exposed to some Russian technology
that was bright lighting it causing
an instant tumor in her brain.
She's hallucinating, obviously, Jason,
and now she's having signals in her brain.
That's, that's but a reasonable answer, right?
There's something physically wrong with her brain,
but we're not looking at the reasonable answer.
We're gonna do the cool one, the sci-fi one.
So she has these signals in it,
she feels these signals in her brain,
ah, and Valentina all of a sudden feels her body
like almost force herself to lay down.
And then she, whoo, now she starts floating around her house.
She's like knocking over vases and stuff like that.
She's floating around her house.
She's, they're not doing it on purpose.
She's not like, oh, it's my one o'clock float time.
She's floating around the house,
and then all of a sudden her house morphs
into this long, dark corridor.
So she's floating down this hallway,
and she hears the voice of the alien woman in her head.
And we have another quote.
These are always interesting
when we have these exact quotes from these things.
We have this quote here, quote,
"We want to help you.
"Here we already have many people like you.
"When no one remains on earth,
"everything will start from the beginning,
"here in this place.
"We will do that, and for that purpose,
"we need you."
Then bam, Valentina sitting on her couch,
in her house, totally alone.
It's an interesting story.
I mean, obviously the first thing is,
it could be completely made up.
It was, I got it from ThinkAbout@Docs.com.
They got it from a place called Cosmo Letts.
It's a newspaper in Russia at the time
that dealt with UFO stuff.
It was also documented in a 20th century
Chronicle of Unexplained Phenomenon,
a book published in Moscow in 1998.
So she could be totally making it up.
Someone else could have made it up.
Those are all obvious things that can happen.
Could be some sort of biological,
like I said, some sort of tumor,
some sort of mental breakdown, things like that.
But, and that's all fair to discuss,
but this story's gone on a long time,
so we're actually gonna wrap it up
with the ending that we like,
which is the science fiction ending.
You go, it's weird that the alien's trying
to get her to come, and then when they finally do get her,
she basically doesn't have a choice.
She starts floating down the hallway,
and then they give that little speech to her,
that they need her, that the world is going
to be emptied of humans, and this place she's in
will be the birth of a new cycle, a new race,
the new set of human.
Then she appears back on her couch.
I think there's two ways to look at that.
One is that they decided they didn't need her.
Like she went on that journey,
she was floating down that thing.
She either, they said, you know what?
We don't need her to deposit her back on earth.
She refused again to go.
She was so afraid of the unknown.
She refused again to go, and she doesn't remember
that part in the aliens.
They're like, just cut her loose, we'll find someone else.
She ends up back on the couch.
It's possible the whole thing may be a near-death experience.
I think the scary, other than the fact
that monsters are eventually going to destroy the world,
which is really cool.
Like if we're going, if the world is going to end,
I want it to end with monsters crushing cities,
'cause that would be a sight to behold.
I want a meteorite attack.
That'd be okay, 'cause it'd be kind of cool, I guess,
to watch, but monsters attacking the planet,
you'd be able to stretch it out as long as possible.
You'd be fighting them in the streets,
and you have military, and eventually giant robots,
and stuff, power rangers, and all that.
That's cool.
It would suck, though, to be showing a vision
of how the world was going to be destroyed,
and then taking aboard an alien ship,
and the next thing you know, you're back on your couch.
So you would think, wait a second,
you just showed me that the world's going to be destroyed,
and I was special, but now I'm back on this couch.
What gives?
Now here's my theory.
This is creepy.
Valentina Valdina is an alien clone.
The real her is in this realm,
swimming in these mother of pearl lakes.
The clone left behind in her place is such a perfect clone.
She doesn't know she's a clone.
She believes that all of the life leading up to being placed
back on that couch was her life.
This woman who was built on an alien spacecraft,
so no one would notice that Valentina was missing.
All of a sudden, sitting on a couch,
back filled with all these memories
leading up to this event.
True memories, but not a real person,
and that clone doesn't know that it's not human,
and is so distraught with these experiences
that have been programmed into its alien brain,
it calls up a UFO researcher.
So something's happened to me.
Never suspecting for a minute
that the real Valentina is safe and sound
near the blue star preparing for the destruction of Earth
while her clone was sent here to be sacrificed
with the other seven billion humans.
But again, if you're gonna get killed by anything,
you might as well be giant monsters.
Caleb, let's get out of the Carpenter Caboose.
I'm Natasha the Keys of the Carpenter Copter.
We are flying out to middle of USA, Kansas.
(mimics car engine)
We're flying over a bunch of farmland,
bunch of like wheat and stuff like that,
corns everywhere, and we're flying over it,
and we're just landing in a ordinary school,
landing right in their playground.
Tetherballs are getting cut by the rotor blades,
they're flying everywhere,
we're purposely landing on the four square courts.
Just mess it up, let's hop out of this Carpenter Copter.
Now, this is a conspiracy theory
that's been going on for a long time,
and it's actually a request from a listener named George.
So thank you so much, George,
for recommending this.
This is a story that's been around a long time.
Now, let's go ahead and hook up one of those tetherballs.
I feel bad that I wrecked them all,
'cause I really like tetherball.
We're gonna play tetherball a bit
while I'm giving you the introduction for this story.
So let's see how good your skills are.
(whooshing)
So, and before we get started,
let me give you some quick background here,
some quick background.
The GATE program is called Gifted and Talented Education.
It is a program to take kids that have higher IQ
or are more skilled in certain areas.
They are then put into a,
for one hour a week,
they're put in their own classroom
to work with other gifted kids.
It's also called Tag, Talented and Gifted.
It's called different things in different states,
and there's programs like this all over the world.
So that is what the GATE program is.
That's a quick overview of it.
Let's talk about what the actual conspiracy theory is
as well, and I am not adding this in
after I've already added the episode
and realized that I left out some key details.
So the fact that this sounds different,
it's just magic, it's just magic, okay?
This is not an edit fix.
The conspiracy theory that we're gonna be talking about
is this, there are a series of traits
that people who are in these programs seem to share.
And the conspiracy theory started off with the idea
that people who were chosen to be in these
gifted and talented programs had some sort of other odd
biological or social markers that also identified them
to be in these programs.
The conspiracy theory quickly shifted from that
to the fact that the people who were in these
GATE programs were being identified to be gifted
and talented young kids, but they were too talented.
They were too gifted.
And the group, the shadowy group that actually ran
the GATE program wiped their memories clean
because a lot of things, a lot of the kids
who went to these GATE programs don't remember being in GATE.
They remember being in GATE, but they don't remember
what was actually in the classroom.
So the conspiracy theory starts off with,
isn't it weird, I did a survey online
of all these traits of people who had been in the GATE program
and it quickly morphed into a Illuminati Control narrative.
Where the reason why we were chosen to be in GATE programs
in the first place was because we posed a threat
to the New World Order and so they took us
and they wiped our brains.
That is the conspiracy theory in a nutshell.
And then you're gonna hear me, I go into more detail
as far as that goes, but I realize I neglected
to actually tell you what I was building up to.
So the conspiracy theory we're gonna talk about
involves gifted and talented education programs
and the fact that people are being pulled out
of their classes, being mind wiped
so they don't pose a threat to the coming New World Order.
That is the conspiracy theory, which I managed
to talk about for 20 minutes.
It's never actually explained it, so there you go.
Let's go ahead, we're traveling back in time
to when I recorded this episode, here we go.
So this is a conspiracy theory that's fairly new.
It really goes back to about 2009, 2010.
It really started a game traction on a forum
called Godlike Productions.
It's also where the nobody came from.
We discussed the nobody last week, I believe it was,
the last week of season nine.
On Godlike Productions, there was a user back in 2010
who went by the name Jane Gray,
who originally started this thing saying,
here's a list of all of these traits
that seem to be universal among people
who go to the gate program.
So get out your pencils or pins or tablets
for you young whippersnappers,
however you wanna keep tally of the stuff.
You go, well, Jason, I didn't go to gate, why should I?
It's actually probably more interesting
if you didn't go to the gate program,
if you meet these things, right?
So you'll be our control group.
Now I changed schools every two years.
Let me say this up front too.
I know I've kind of been winding.
I changed schools every two years.
I never joined a gate program.
I was never in gate.
However, I did do an episode way back in the day.
It was episode 201 of Dead Rabbit Radio.
It's called The Dragon.
And it, although I was never actually in the gate,
and I recommend listening to that episode
after listening to this one.
I think you might appreciate it more after this one.
But even though I was never in a gate program,
I was in a similar type program.
That's really the only way I can identify it.
I remember when I was a kid, they talked about gate,
but we moved every two or three years.
So they, I was getting identified to be in gate programs,
but I never was 'cause I was moving around too much.
It's the parent's choice of whether or not
to put the kids in the gate program.
However, when I was at a elementary school,
at the Strawberry Point Elementary School in Mill Valley,
an interesting thing happened, a gate-esque thing happened,
where I was taken out of my class once a week
to go to this cubicle, and that's all I remember.
It's all I remember.
So I recommend listening to episode 201.
It doesn't, you don't have to,
but I think it's an interesting companion piece
to this story.
So I was not in the gate program.
I was identified to go into the gate program,
but I never went.
But anyways, here's the thing.
Get ready, guys.
Gate program or not,
let's take a look at some of these things.
Do you have blue eyes or hazel eyes?
That's a pretty huge swath of the human population, right?
But that seems to be a sign most people in the gate program
have blue or hazel eyes.
Oxypital buns, that's where you got a little bump
on the back of your skull.
You got that?
I mean, I have a skull.
I don't think I have that bun.
The Oxypital bun is apparently the math bump,
which I obviously don't have 'cause I despise math.
Birth complications.
Either born premature, born extremely late,
or born not breathing.
So, and I guess I should say this.
I have hazel eyes.
I don't have an Oxypital bun.
I was born, I had a heart attack as a baby.
My mom says that's not true,
but my doctor was like, no, no, no.
When you were born, you flatlined.
We had to bring you back to life.
So you're listening to a podcast from a zombie, bro.
Near-death experiences, particularly drowning,
I had that.
Lack of memory of the gate program.
Definitely had that.
And again, what I was in was not gate,
but it was something, technically it was speech therapy
is what they actually was billed as.
It was me and this girl,
and we were taken into a cubicle,
and then I don't remember anything.
I have no memory of it.
Listen to episode 201, 'cause the story's just not me going,
"I don't remember."
Like, there's an interesting conclusion to it,
but I don't wanna give it away.
And it's not important to this episode anyways,
but lack of memory of gate.
That's something that always stood out to me
whenever I went to speech therapy.
I don't remember anything.
I can obviously talk much better now.
Windows were covered in the gate classroom.
That was the same for me.
Now we get to tendency to being followed,
tracked, abducted by aliens or other humans.
What?
Where do these people live?
No, I haven't had that.
A law enforcement being extremely lenient
and easy during chance encounters.
Absolutely.
I mean, I've had my tangles with law enforcement,
but for the most part, it's been,
like, have a good day, officer.
You too, sir.
So that one is true.
But see, this is where we start to get to stuff
that's kind of biased, right?
Because then you get to stuff like early,
lots of drug use in teenage years.
Drug experimentation.
So not just drug use, but you're like,
"I wanna test the limits of my psychedelic mind,"
stuff like that.
An interest in paranormal phenomenon is one of them.
Forehead scars.
Early speech therapy is actually one of them listed
like I was born into.
Migraines, maybe Valentina was one of these things.
The thing with the lenient law enforcement,
early psychedelic use or drug experimentation,
that if you weren't, if it wasn't lenient police,
you weren't on godlike productions, right?
If you were into drugs and the police nabbed you
and they threw the book at you,
and then you do five years for trafficking marijuana
in federal prison, then you come out,
you're not on godlike productions.
That's important to look at,
'cause you're listing things that if they're wrong,
guesses, they're not gonna pop up in the stats.
It's one of those things of saying
100 people who jump off the Grand Canyon die.
That's true, right?
But then there could be a guy
who jumps off the Grand Canyon, flies away.
Okay, that's a bad analogy, but you know what I mean.
The guy who flies away, let's say the 100th person,
99 people jump off the Grand Canyon and die.
Don't do this, don't do this.
But then the 100th person jumps off the Grand Canyon
and flies away and goes to the blue star.
The stats would still always show
that 100% of the people who jumped off the,
jumped off the Death Canyon, what is it?
Not the Death Canyon, 100 people jump,
it's the new name of it, we said petition change.org.
100 people who jump off the Grand Canyon die.
It never accounts for the fact
of the person who flies away and goes to the blue star.
There's a stupid analogy, but my point is, is that,
yes, police have been lenient on me
because if they weren't lenient on me
and they caught me with weapons in my car
or caught me for going so far over the speed limit
or caught me for driving uninsured with no registration
and causing a car accident,
and all of those things happened
and they were just like, yeah, whatever.
If they didn't happen, I wouldn't be on Godlike Productions.
I would be in jail or prison.
You see how that works.
And the other thing is interested in paranormal phenomenon.
It's on a paranormal board.
So everyone who is, was in the gate program
and is on the paranormal board are like,
(gasps)
that's me, that's right, it's a bias thing.
If this was on Barstool Sports website,
then you get a bigger cross-section of people.
And that was another thing they said,
none of these gate people ever reported
being involved in sports at all.
We're playing tetherball, so we're athletes.
So we're not part of that either, but no sports at all.
And then we get into probably the weirdest thing,
Israeli art student girlfriends.
Apparently that's super common
among people who went to the gate program
that they all somehow met a girl
who was an Israeli art student.
Now, millions of people have been through
the gate program over the years.
So technically, if this part of it was true,
you'd have more people who have an Israeli art girlfriend
than there are citizens of Israel.
So again, I mean, maybe that seems to be
like an outlier thing.
Like 10% of the people have Israeli art student girlfriends.
And that's weirder than the average.
I don't, so, this is where I'm starting to think
this was a joke, right?
But this, I remember reading this,
this took off really, really quickly.
And a lot of people were running with this
and going, (gasps)
I also have migraines.
And I used to have a crush on an Israeli art student girl.
So maybe that's the same thing.
And the cops have been really lenient on me
when I was stalking that girl.
But this one really took off.
So people started looking into this.
And really what it is, it's a list of traits
that if you meet half of them,
you qualify to be an interesting and unique person.
This is one of those conspiracy theories
that is based on ego,
which are the most cunning of all conspiracy theories, right?
This conspiracy theory is telling you,
you gifted it and talented education student,
that there's something different about you.
Even as an adult.
So people started looking into what this could be.
Some people say that it's the government
looking for the next wave of leaders.
That's probably the most realistic one.
That a, and I talked about this a couple times
on the show before, if a government,
a government's goal is to do two things,
to maintain the future of said government
and to create the next generation of taxpayers.
That's it.
This is 100% it.
That's all any world government wants to do.
They wanna keep being around
and they wanna have the next generation of taxpayers.
And when you look at world politics through that lens,
you'll see so many things make sense.
So many things make sense that we attribute
hostile or bad action to.
They wanna be around in a hundred years
and they wanna have taxpayers next year.
That's 100% how governments operate.
So you would wanna identify gifted children
in your population.
So you can have the next generation of scientists,
of chemists, of architects, of engineers,
stuff like that.
You wanna go, because it wasn't they were putting
in their own schools.
It wasn't Professor Xavier showing up
pulling them out of schools.
They were just giving a little bit extra
high level training.
They were just, and let's go back to the thing too
about people not remembering things.
It's funny because there's two different sides of this.
Some people go, I don't remember anything.
And then other people go, oh, I remember all of these
programs we did and it was like these weird
social experiments.
So what is it?
Is it that people don't remember it?
Or that people remember weird experiments going on?
Again, it kinda breaks down there.
But a government does wanna identify gifted people
in their population.
No doubt.
Now, generally it's a federal program
and then the states are in charge of it
and the states go to the school districts.
And some school districts don't have money
to have these programs.
They still have to identify them for the state to go,
yeah, we have this amount of gifted kids in our program,
but this one kid is really gifted at tetherball.
I'm looking out the window right now, dude.
This dude's super buff and he's just hitting that ball.
You have that.
Then you have a group of people who believe
that it's private nonprofit organizations
that are trying to control the world.
Here's where we get to the whole Illuminati thing.
They wanna control the world.
So what they're doing is they're identifying
these gifted kids and they're doing MK Ultra type
experiments to them in these classrooms.
So the brains don't work.
These kids are going to be the future leaders of the world.
They're gonna be the John Connors.
And you have these evil organizations
in the shadows being like, oh no,
we know that someday this new generation will rise up
and they'll destroy us.
What can we do?
Well, we could kill them.
That'd be the best option, but no, no, no, no,
we're going to engage in a decade long program,
decades long.
This started back in like the 1950s, gay program.
We're gonna do this.
And what we're gonna do is we're gonna identify these kids
and then we're gonna wipe their brains
and turn them into total losers as adults.
That's our plan, us Illuminati dudes.
That's actually conspiracy theory that's going around that.
The program is set up to dumb down the future generations.
Here's the problem with that.
One, it's completely illogical,
but here's the problem with that.
If we follow that core,
fluoride's already supposed to be dumb on us down.
Chemtrails are already supposed to be dumb on us down.
There's already all these conspiracy vaccines
supposed to give us autism.
There's already all of these other conspiracy theories
that are supposed to accomplish the same thing.
Why would a private organization go,
"No, no, no, we want some of that.
We saved some of that brainwashing for me."
And set up this program that started back like in 1954
to do the same thing that's already happened to the gen--
I don't believe it's happening.
I don't believe that the chemtrails and the fluoride
and the vaccines are doing this stuff.
But if you believe in the conspiracy theories,
which most people don't believe in just one,
most people believe in multiple ones.
There's like a shared universe.
Why would a private group try doing this on their own?
There's way easier ways to eliminate the leaders of the world.
It's the way they eliminate the current leaders of the world,
which is through assassination or just buying them out.
That'd be way easier, right?
Than trying to start this huge program
where people are gonna fall through the cracks
and stuff like that.
And there are people who go out of gate programs
and go on to be successful.
This conspiracy theory points towards the people
who went to gate programs and aren't successful.
See the reason why they're not successful?
'Cause the Illuminati got to them.
So we'll finish, we'll go back to that one
'cause that's a very interesting conspiracy theory.
But there's another conspiracy theory
and this was so interesting
'cause I was researching this back in March
before coronavirus shut everything down.
Back when I was able to do Jiu Jitsu,
I would pack up my computer, go do Jiu Jitsu,
go to a coffee shop and just read nonsense
for three or four hours.
I read this website called barbarism.net.
They keep this guy wrote this article called
conspiracy theory gifted and talented
equals product research and development.
This is written by an author, he writes this article
and he says, "I remember going into..."
And this article was back in 2009
so it actually predates the Godlike production thing.
And he writes this article and he says that
his theory was that gate was run by private corporations.
So not like private non-profits,
but for-profit companies.
And he tells a story about this kid.
It might have been him.
I'm having a hard time remembering
and we'll get to why I'm having a hard time remembering
in a second, but we'll say it's him
for the sake of argument.
He is in a gate program when he's a kid.
And these people come in and there's like
his normal gate teacher there,
but then someone else comes in,
starts talking about the hula hoop.
It says, "Do you guys like hula hoops?"
And the kids are like, "No, boo, hula hoops, relay."
And this is like back in the 80s.
Hula hoops suck.
And the guys like starts crying.
It's like, "Okay, well, maybe don't be so mean next time,
but how could we make the hula hoop better?
Let's all come up with an idea to make a hula hoop better."
So the kids get around and they start thinking about it,
doing like these gifted kids,
putting their brains together and they go,
"What about a hula hoop that counted
how many times it went around you?
You put a little counter on it."
And the man's like, "That's stupid."
And he leaves.
And then a couple of years later,
this guy said he saw on television
advertising a whammo hula hoop that had a counter on it.
So his conspiracy theory was that these,
'cause some schools don't have gate programs
'cause you do have to have an extra teacher,
an extra facility, all this stuff.
His theory was that the gate programs exist
and they're funded by private companies
and they do product testing.
So all of these mental games and stuff like that,
it's a way to refine toys or products for kids.
That makes far more sense than the Illuminati.
It makes less sense than the government wanting to identify
and nurture the smartest of their population,
but it kind of falls right.
It's definitely more believable
than the Illuminati trying to ruin your life.
Now the thing is, is like I said,
I was researching this before March.
When I was getting ready for season 10,
I go, I'm gonna do that story.
I really like that story.
The website's gone.
The article still exists.
You'll see links for it floating around.
I have the link, it's in the show notes.
I have the headline of the article.
I read the article.
It took my notes.
The article's gone.
It's not even in the wayback machine.
I went to the wayback machine, it's not there.
You're like, Jason, obviously a conspiracy.
Well, the website had been around since 2009.
He abandoned, the article was from 2009.
And the last article he wrote was still a few years ago.
And it was like, I'm moving to medium.
It's been a hard time hosting this website.
So in that article, it wasn't written.
It wasn't written.
Oh no, they have a gun to me.
The coronavirus is coming and I'm deleting my site
'cause I know too much about WAMO.
I think it was a website that he had.
That particular page didn't get indexed
by the wayback machine, which happens.
The website is now gone.
And it was just a weird timing thing.
It's one of those things that had I not researched
the story before the site really disappeared.
I would have just thought, oh, it's a dead link.
But because I was able to do it,
and then the site goes down.
It does make it a little more conspiratorial,
but I don't remember if he was the one in the gate class
or he was reporting on a friend or a friend of a friend
and stuff like that.
I just remember reading the article, taking the notes,
obviously not very detailed notes,
and then the website disappearing.
So that is where we stand with that.
Now, my belief obviously is that it is just
a government-run program that has a financial interest.
And finding the next generation of geniuses out there.
But that's not a super sexy conspiracy theory, right?
And neither is the WAMO one,
even though that one again is more realistic.
If I was a private company, I would totally do that.
If I was a company that made products for kids,
you would totally, it's free focus group.
It's 100% a free focus group.
Well, it's not free 'cause you pay the school,
but you have unfettered access to the brains of kids.
And not even a mad scientist has that.
You can honestly go, what do you think of this product?
What do you think about this product?
But let's take a look at the real meat
of the conspiracy theory, and that's the fact that
this controlling body is using it
to neutralize future leaders.
That is extremely egotistical, right?
You were in Gates or TAG or whatever program you were in.
A teacher identified you as being gifted.
The principal, you're sitting there with your parents.
The principal is talking to them,
saying what an amazing kid you are.
How special you feel, and you should feel special.
We should all, we are all special inside.
But when an outsider's saying it,
this person has gifts, we wanna put 'em in this program,
things are set, right?
But then as life goes on, we realize
that's just not the way the world works.
And even special people, even gifted people,
make mistakes, unfortunate circumstances happen to them.
They get lazy, a combination of the three.
And you go, oh man, I really wish I could be an author.
Really wish I could write that book.
One, you can, you totally can write that book
or write that song or start that podcast.
There's nothing stopping you, but you.
And definitely what's not stopping you
is not the Illuminati.
You're brained and getting raced when you're in the sixth grade
and that's what's keeping you in your dead-end job
that you're in right now.
You just work, work, work, and there's no longer any,
this is the big trick with being an adult or being older
because it gets the same thing.
No one cares to help you out
until you're successful already.
Now of course you'll have family and friends
that help you out, but nobody cares
that you're thinking about writing a novel.
Nobody cares that you're thinking about starting a podcast.
You have to do those things, work really, really hard,
get successful, and then the world will care.
But until then, you're just like everybody else.
And you have to work super, super hard at it.
I've been doing this podcast a daily show,
Bustin' My Butt, 449 episodes.
I'm seeing growth.
Or we could go back in time two years.
And I go, well my brain got wiped
when I was in the sixth grade.
I had this weird experience
where I was in this bizarre school program
that I don't remember.
The reason why I'm working dead-end jobs
and I wanna be an author but I can't write my books
and because the Illuminati is keeping me down.
I could have had that mindset, right?
Or I could have said, you know what?
I'm a creative person.
Nobody cares.
Everyone's a creative person.
You have to put out product.
Start my podcast.
Start my podcast two years ago.
We are here now.
You're listening to me.
You never would have heard me before this moment, right?
You have to work incredibly hard.
When you're a kid, it's different.
A teacher will say that kid's gifted.
Boom, he's gifted.
You get this label gifted.
You're in the gate program.
You're meeting other kids who are smart.
You feel special as an adult.
That doesn't happen until you're already successful.
Neil deGrasse Tyson would just be a guy
writing stuff down on a chalkboard somewhere.
If he didn't work super hard
and eventually gets successful to the point that now,
they're like, hey, we wanna do a show about science.
Let's get that dude.
He didn't just wake up one day and go famous, successful.
You got to work super hard at it.
And this conspiracy theory says,
no, you don't.
This conspiracy theory says you were destined for greatness.
And the reason you're not great
is because an outside organization stole that from you.
It absolves you of your sin.
And the greatest sin that humans can have is laziness.
There are a lot of people who are trapped in the rat race.
They're just doing the same thing every day.
They wake up, go to work, come home, watch TV, go to bed.
Wake up, go to work, come home, watch TV, go to bed.
They do that all the time.
And I think a good chunk of the population,
although they aspire to do better,
they don't know how to go about it.
Or they don't think they're good enough to do it.
I think a good chunk of the population,
they're not happy with that existence,
but they don't know what else to do.
Everything else involves way too much chance.
So they just keep doing it and hope for the best.
Then you have a smaller part of the population
who strives super, super hard
to realize their dreams.
That's the part that everyone else looks up at
and goes, "I wanna do that.
"It looks too hard, too chancey.
"What if I do it and fail?
"What if I do it and I'm successful?"
Nah, too scary.
And then you have people that were told as children
that they were gifted and special,
and now they're working at a coal center,
or Jiffy Luga, or they're a teacher.
And I'm not knocking those professions.
If you work at Jiffy Luga,
when someone brings their car in,
you're the most important person
that dude's gonna meet that day.
They need your help.
They need your expertise.
So I'm not knocking those jobs.
But you have a group of people who have no idea
how to achieve their dreams.
You have people who work really hard
to achieve their dreams.
And then you have people, a smaller group of people,
who are told as children,
"You will be the future of this country."
But for whatever reason,
either because of personal decisions,
unforeseen circumstances,
these future leaders of the world
didn't fulfill the potential that their teacher saw
and their parents saw
and their principal saw in all this.
For them, waking up, working, coming home, watching TV,
that is a prison sentence.
It's a prison sentence
because they were promised so much more in life.
So you could easily say,
"Listen, I made some decisions early on
in my teenage and college years that weren't smart.
And I think now, it might be harder
now that I'm 34, but with hard work,
I can start working towards my goals."
It's gonna be hard.
I might have to change my job.
I might have to move.
I might have to do these things that are scary,
but I want to be the person that I thought I would be
when I was in the sixth grade.
I have these dreams to be, I wanna be an author,
I wanna be a musician or a scientist or whatever.
Or you could say, "I'm stuck in this situation
because my brain was wiped by the Illuminati,
that I was supposed to be a leader of tomorrow.
And I was such a threat to the power base
that it took me into a room and wiped my memory clean."
The second scenario obviously sounds completely insane.
But there's a group of people who believe that.
There's a sizable group of people who believe that.
And the thing is, is this conspiracy theory
is going to get bigger every single year.
Because every single year there are gonna be people
who are hitting 25, 30, 40 years old.
And they're realizing that they're not gifted and talented.
They're just like the rest of us.
And they're gonna be looking for answers
as to why life didn't work out the way they thought it would.
They could take the answer that,
"My life can be as awesome as I think it is,
but it's gonna take some hard work,
it's gonna take some risk."
Or they can say, "My life sucks
'cause I was too great for the powers that be
to allow to move about unrestricted."
Living a life that is unfulfilling
is the scariest story of all.
But if you can give yourself an excuse
for why your life is the way it is,
you will continue down that gray path until the end.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is gonna be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
Twitter is @deadrabberadio.
And DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
(upbeat music)
Buy four tires and get up to $175 in savings after rebate
or even more when you finance a bell tire
during our huge Memorial Day sale.
May 18th through the 27th, buy four tires
and get up to $175 in savings.
May 18th through the 27th, all tires, all brands, any budget.
If you want up to $175 off a set of four tires,
then come get the lowest tire price, period, at Bell Tire.
Buy online, save time.
See storebelltire.com for details, restrictions, apply.