Today we take a ride on a ghost train that is still seen plowing across the deserts of Arizona
then we meet the
Unluckiest man in the world until he wasn't and
Then finally we look at an interesting conspiracy
And one that has a bit of backing to it was Marilyn Monroe killed
To cover up the truth of UFOs today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*Music*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carvin
Or I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. We got a lot of stuff to cover
So I'm gonna spare you the Star Trek jokes this episode. We're gonna jump right into it. Jump! Weeee!
Arizona, the state that never sleeps because it's so hot there you can't sleep. That's where we're at
Arizona. It's just one giant flat state. Every so often you see a giant stump of a tree. Ah, you thought those were amasis?
No, those are tree stumps, but we're here. We're in the Dragoon Mountains
Which sounds dope. I think that's the name of French soldiers who shoot guns
Well, they all do now, but back in the day the Dragoons, I think were the first armed
French soldiers, but anyways it doesn't matter.
Between Dragoon and the town of Wilcox, Arizona. This has been spotted multiple times by multiple people over the years.
A phantom train. Sometimes you just see the light on the train. Not just the light like the sun
But sometimes you just see like the front of the headlight. Why do you put a headlight on a train? It's not like it can turn
I guess they could break. By the time the beam of light hits whatever in the
train's way
You cannot be able to stop it. I mean how how many lumens did they have back in the 1800s?
Like I bet you that train that headlight on the train. Oh, oh, I guess it's so other people can see the train coming
Never mind. So anyways, you learned something Jason. You taught yourself something the train
Actually, what a ghost train make noise actually a ghost make noise so it makes sense
Tickets, please you get off the train hobo
Ghost hobos are getting thrown off the train. They're like just evaporating in nowhere slimmers back there. He's eating all the food slimer
Anyways, this ghost train's coming through the desert. People have seen it over the years. They've heard it over the years
They're like why is all these hot dogs just in the middle of the desert?
The weirdest thing is if the ghost train with hobos and slimer on it aren't weird enough
There's never been a train laid in the area where the train
is seen
Now all the articles I read about the ghost train were like there's a ghost train
People have seen it and heard it for years, but here's the weird part
There's never been a train
Where the ghost train seen and I'm thinking
So it's not like the train has a ghost. I have a better point better question here. Let's say that
Okay, so let's say the ghost train exists and it's chugging along in the middle of nowhere a place where train tracks had never been laid down
Did they see trains like in 600 ad in that area where like the native america?
That's a bigger question to me not there's never been a train there. Well, who cares if there's not go ghosts don't have trains
Don't leave ghosts
So whether or not there's a train there is totally irrelevant to the fact that there is a ghost train
but
I think the more interesting question is
600 ad you have native americans live in in arizona
I don't know why it's super hot down there and there's no animals, but they're down there
Was the ghost train there then?
Would they have seen this thing and they'd have no concept for the noises it made for the size for the speed
They're like why who are all these ghost hobos? What's a hobo and then everything just vanishes like
What did they see in that area?
The apache do consider the area sacred
Now I will say this I say trains don't have ghosts
But if there was a train that got lost or derailed and to this day people still say they can see
The ghost of the train coming down the tracks whatever but this train is in the middle of nowhere
When did they start seeing it?
Did people see it before they knew what a train was and the reason why this is an important question?
If that's true
If that train has always been there and no one could recognize what it was until other people who and it invented the train
Saw the train and go oh, that's a train. That's what that is
Do ghosts work in any sort of time?
time
Chain what's timeline?
Or are they just there?
Whenever like the ghosts that we see are they people who have died before or is it possible that there are people who will die?
eventually
Like if i'm looking at a ghost, how do I know if okay if a ghost train can exist in the middle of nowhere?
And i'm looking at a ghost in my living room. It's possible that that guy won't die until 50 years from now
But when he died his soul is trapped in this timeline or it's appearing in this timeline
But he may still be alive 2 000 years from now. Does that make sense? Like i i
That's the thing that I always get kind of squirrelly with ghosts is
Living people measure stuff on a linear timeline because our lives are on a linear timeline
but to a ghost to something who exists for eternity
A linear timeline is
Doesn't make sense
Does that make sense because technically infinity would or eternity would doesn't it go both ways?
I don't know man
You know people always accuse me of smoking weed before I do this show and i'm like
This is always my response. There was no way I could do a daily show if I smoked marijuana. Absolutely not. I think
My i'm just perma stone because I did spend a lot of time in my 20s partying
And my brain just can't stop working sometimes ghost train. What are the serious ramifications for?
Don't do drugs kids by the way. Um ghost trains
What would be the serious ramifications if it if the oh my god, it's blowing my mind
If the train was never there
But there's a ghost of a train if we accept those two things as facts
Then you also have to extrapolate that to say that every ghost or a good likely amount of ghosts that we see
Are not tied to that physical location. Our linear timeline is looking at a ghost and saying I know Mary queen of scots died here
Therefore that ghost looks like Mary queen of scots. However, that ghost could be a cosplayer
From 80 years in the future who died wearing her mary queen of scott uniform. Bam, dude
I just answered every ghost sighting ever. You can thank me later. Don't do drugs kids. Okay, so let's go ahead and move on to our next story
Okay, now we're going to go to
Croatia now
If you want to go quickly, there's only one way to get there. It's all cleaned out, baby
We got the carboner copter hop on in
Isn't it nice through and I got it. It's all clean. I got all these air fresheners cut the doors wide open
So hold on to something
If you don't get the reference a bunch of people pooped in it a couple episodes ago
We're in Croatia. We also had to go back in time during our flight
We are going to watch the life and times of a man. Tell me this doesn't sound like a star trek character
I said I wasn't going to do any star trek jokes, but this guy sounds like a star trek character
His name is frayne selec
Don't fool me. That's a star trek character. You're a time traveler, but anyways, we land
In frayne selecs yard and he's like get out of here your kids in your wacky contraption because we're back in
Oh, I guess they had helicopters back in 1962. He's like get out of here kids with your contraption that I'm vaguely aware of
He's shaking a pitchfork at it. Actually frayne seems to be a pretty nice guy. So he's like, I'm just kidding
Come on in. Let's hang out for a bit. We don't really want to hang out with him
Now if you haven't seen the movie final destination, it's the movie where death tries to kill you
You escape and I love final destination 4. That's one of my favorite movies
The series is good, but final destination 4 called the final destination is one of the bests
One of the best horror movies. Absolutely love it. But anyways, that's the setup for those movies
You escape death and then death tries to get you again until you eventually die
Let's look at frayne selecs life
First off, he was a romulan officer on a warbird. No, I'm just joking. Okay. Okay in 1962
He was in a train
Another train no ghost hobos nothing like that the train however flips off the tracks crashes into the river
17 people drown. He swims the shore one year later 1963
He's flying in a plane the door of the plane
Malfunctions pops open. He is thrown out of the plane. I don't know what height but not super high
He's thrown out of the plane. He lands in a haystack plane crashes killing 19 people
He never flew on another plane three years after that. He was in a bus
Slid off the road into the river. He swims the shore four people drown four years later. So now we're in 1970
He's rocking the bell bottoms harry chest huge medallion. He's driving a car
Car catches on fire. He jumps out of his car and gets away before the car explodes three years later 1973 drive in a car
A malfunctioning fuel a lot of malfunctions a malfunctioning fuel pump begins leaking hot oil onto his engine
Flame shoots out of his heater vents into his car burns his hair off
But he survives and then nothing until 1995
He gets hit by a bus
minor injuries
One year later this I think all of that's bad, but this I thought was quite chilling
1996 he's driving on a curvy mountain road
And a united nation's truck comes out of relatively nowhere and now they're about to have a head-on collision
He swerves into the guard rail to avoid the truck the guard rail gives away
Now because when he swerved the impact of the car
He wasn't wearing his seatbelt and when his car hit his door swung open
He flew out of his car grabbed onto a tree
Car plummets down a 300 foot gorge and he's just standing there
All of these had been documented throughout his life the you and truck I hope stopped and helped them
They're like no we only help nations not just you
But anyways fraying selec
survived death multiple times
2003 two days after his 73rd birthday wins a million dollars in the lottery
buys much houses buys a boat gives a rest to his friends and family
Died peacefully 89 years old. Can you imagine dodging death that many times in your life?
Like I mean at a sur after okay
I've had some pretty scary run-ins with like car accidents and like sketchy situations in places
I shouldn't have been things like that but after the fourth time I got in a vehicle and it either exploded or drove off the road
I I'd be like i'm done. Actually, that's kind of what I have done
I've been in seven car accidents and I'm like I don't need to drive. I'll just walk everywhere
So like yeah, I mean, but this guy's like oh my my car blew up
Good thing it's fully insured time to buy another car and it catches on fire
I don't know crazy, but luckiest or unluckiest man
I mean it's pretty lucky to win a million dollars
But it'd be even more lucky if he won a million dollars when he was younger
But he had it and he said you know his his view was I bought what he wanted and then he's like
I'll just give the rest of my family and kids luckiest or unluckiest man
You decide I guess luckiest really because he survived the whole time
I found that story when I was looking up the farthest falls
He was listed as one of the people who survived the plain fold
But I mean he fell into a pile of hay like a loonatoon character
He doesn't even see how high the plane was
But I thought I was like oh this this guy needs to just get his own little segment
But let's go ahead. Okay, so we're gonna say buy to frame
Buy frame sell like he's like buy and then we notice he talks into his calm and he's like
Let the tal shia know that the romulan's well. He's a star trek character
It's a star trek name
But anyways, we'll leave the star trek romulan infiltrator behind
But we hop into the carpenter copter
We're on our way to Hollywood the land of glitz and glamour
Everything's beautiful in Hollywood everything's I have a friend who went to Hollywood to be an actor
And I go how are the women down there and he looks at me like I'm an idiot
He's like, how do you think dude? They're all gorgeous. I was like, yeah
I guess that was kind of a self answering question
But anyway, so hey, Jonas if you listen to the show so we
Are in the carpenter copter now we do have to make a quick stop
I got to get some ampm hamburgers because I love those gas station burgers
Oh, wait. I'm on keto. Damn it. Ah, I just have to fly over the amp. I'm gonna be like, uh, damn it
We fly over
But we got to be careful we're gonna put on stealth mode
Not super stealthy
But because we know
The cia is listening to a very intriguing phone call
Marilyn Monroe famous movie actress
Singer I think I think she was in some musicals
She had been sleeping with
Both the president of the united states and his brother
Attorney general robert kennedy. I don't think I could share a woman with my brother
Maybe maryland Monroe
But I don't think so so anyways or british fierce, but no, that's gross dude
They'd be getting all dna mixed up and stuff in there. Anyway, so
That that aside that aside maryland roe was sleeping with both president kennedy and
Attorney general bobby kennedy
But they had kind of ghosted her at this point. They were like, no, I wouldn't want to talk to you anymore
And she was starting to lose her luster in hollywood
Marilyn Monroe was no longer the big star that she had used to be
august 3rd
There was a phone call that the cia recorded because cia had maryland Monroe's phone tapped
Because they knew she knew stuff about the president kennedy and
Robert kennedy
And they had the phones tapped of maryland roe's friends now
That's the thing whenever people talk about conspiracies and they're like, well, you know
That's not true that we find bits and pieces of true conspiracies here and there
There's the conspiracy that maryland roe didn't commit suicide that she was murdered people are like what no
There's no way she had all these drugs in her system only people who commit suicide do that
There's no assassin wouldn't make you take drugs
But then we have recordings of phone call. We know her phone was being tapped in this wiretap
Which was found during a freedom of information act request
It is regarding a conversation between a reporter dorthy killigan
Sorry, not killigan dorthy kill glenn and her close friend, howard rothberg
And I believe that when they're saying her close friend, they're referring to maryland roe's close friend
Government talk isn't always the most specific. I'm going to read this to you. This is an actual cia document
Rothberg discussed the apparent comeback of subject with maryland roe with kill glenn and the breakup with the kinities
Rothberg told kill glenn that she was attending hollywood parties hosted by quote-unquote
Inner circle among hollywood's elite and was becoming the talk of the town again
Rothberg indicated in so many words that she has secrets to tell no doubt arising from her trists with the president and the attorney general
One such secret and what's weird secrets and air quotes secrets and quotations there
One such quote-unquote secret mentions the visit by the president
So before I get on the next part the cia is listening in on this phone call and maryland roe's friend is talking to a reporter
And he's like yeah, you know, she's she's making the rounds in hollywood. She's really trying to get herself back out there
She's talking to the high and mighty the elite in hollywood. She's trying to get back into show business
Cia agents like, you know, listen into it. This is the next part that comes out and this is what the cia agent typed up
This is their official report one such secret mentions the visit by the president at a secret airbase for the purpose of inspecting things from outer space
Kill glenn replied that she knew what might be the source of visit in the mid fifties kill glenn learned of secret effort by us and uk governments to
identify the origins of crash spacecraft and dead bodies from a british government official
Kill glenn believed the story may have come from the new mexico story in the late forties
Kill glenn said if the story is true
It would cause terrible embarrassment for jack and his plans to have nasa put men on the moon
So you have this conversation between maryland roe's friend saying hey, she wants to get back into show business
Yeah, she also told me this weird story how the president went out to some secret base and
To go look at stuff from outer space and the reporter goes
Hmm. I kind of I know a little bit something about that
I talked to a british official a couple years ago back in the fifties
And he told me that we have been in contact with a small race of beans
And we believe that they crashed at some place in new mexico. I don't remember and
We're worried that they may be some sort of
problem
Dorothy kill glenn is a reporter, but she's known as a gossip columnist as well
She reported the findings of the ufo of the british guy
That was from back in the
So that story that she had written
Was from 1955 so it was a good seven years before this meeting
She had written up in this gossip column basically saying that
The british government has encountered a ufo. They don't know what it is
They actually have the wreckage and they know the body's like they're a little they're little tiny people and all that stuff
Stuff that we commonly know as grace now. There's two separate statements
One is someone who's close to marylandman row saying marylandman row says that the president said he went to a base and
Went to go see things from outer space and then the reporter interjects. Oh, I know what you're talking about
I know a guy who who believes aliens are here
She never named the name of the british official, which I mean can be a sign of deception or it can also be a sign
of the guy doesn't want to be called a kook
so
What in the world are we supposed to glean from this cia document?
if there's so much weird stuff in this because
If jfk is willing to tell
marylandman row about the secret trip and if he did see aliens
She would know that as well. She would she would have revealed that to her friend or would she
Kilgill in who did do a story on aliens back in the 50s talking to an unnamed british official
She kind of threw in her own two cents, but even if we knew that there was aliens out there
Why would she make the final phrase it would cause a terrible embarrassment for jackness plans to have nasa put men on the moon
Why would would it be embarrassing because our technology was so limited?
Would it be embarrassing because it wouldn't work because the aliens would destroy it now at this time?
Yuri gargan has already floated around space like russians have already launched the first man's space capsule
He orbited and came down normally
There was a theory that jfk visiting the objects from outer space
Was actually remains of soviet technology that has shot up into space and fell down
I don't really know if that washes with this
Because that would also be something marillon row be like if jfk told marylandman row this stuff
She could say yeah, he went and saw some space junk from the russkies and but it's so vague
To see things from outer space and to make it even more puzzling. This isn't the whole report
There's a single page from the cia that includes that story
And then phone taps from marillon row's own phone where she was calling up
bobby kennedy calling up jfk's brother. This is what again, it's it's not the exact transcript. It's what the cia notes say
marillon row repeatedly called the attorney general and complained about the way she was being ignored by the president and his brother
Marillon row threatened to hold a press conference and would tell all
Marillon row made reference to bases in cuba and knew of the president's plan to kill castro
Marillon row made reference to her diary of secrets and what the newspaper would do with such disclosures
Now it makes sense that they don't say exactly what that is because the cia doesn't want to put that information
It's information that they know and they don't want to put it in a report
two days after that
memo was created
marillon row was found dead
suicide drug overdose
again
If the cia was completely covering up the existence of ufo's that would they have included that first part in the document?
They could have redacted it so we would have never seen it
The fact that they leave in the part about the bases and the plot to kill castro
We know about that so it makes sense that that part wasn't redacted
I mean it's a mind boggler because you have this document that really makes it look like
She was ready to release all this information
We don't know what it is
We can assume that when she says she's going to tell all that it relates to
UFOs and et's and all this stuff or it could just be i'm going to tell me have a tiny dick
We don't know exactly what the conversation was and what she was threatening to reveal
I think just this document alone makes it look like she was murdered to cover up her from blabbing her mouth and pro tip
Don't run your mouth and second pro tip if you're going to don't tell anyone you're going to
Ever because this is what happens
But her threatening we hear her words to bobby kennedy saying this is what i'm going to do this for other second conversation
Is all hearsay it's two people repeating what another person has been told
Did marillon row know about the ufo's?
Did was marillon min row killed to cover up something and possibly that's something being alien life
There's a third possibility
That this document is fake
We don't really have a provenance on the
ci
Document it's turned up in someone else's collection. I believe you can order it yourself
But until I do I can't say for sure that it's 100 accurate, but other people have vouched for it
I mean, you know ufo allegis, so I don't you know take it with a grain of salt
They're saying that the cia is never specifically denied that this document is fake
And it was this weird thing where someone said I want the actual transcripts released and the answer was kind of like
Well, you already have that so in a roundabout way and I'm really like shortening the little legal battle that went on but
In a roundabout way, it's been confirmed to be accurate
But we don't know
It could easily be a forgery. I did read an interesting thing and they said this guy goes
I've read a lot of forgeries in my life about ufo stuff and he goes normally he goes if this was a forgery
This is how I think they would have done it
They would have said marillon min row said that she saw aliens and she saw a flying disc and they always hype it up
When you're making a forgery for the ufo community you make it even more hype
And make it really like throw some green men. Yeah, yeah, put the pleidians in there like they make it more
And he goes this one's actually doesn't seem like a hoax just because it's so down to earth
It's very vague. He goes they never actually even really use the word alien or ufo in it
If it's real if this is a real document
That's really creepy
These phone calls are being recorded two days before she dies
That's you know, that's a really big coincidence
But who knows
Yeah, I always thought that marillon min row. I always figured marillon min row was killed honestly
That's a conspiracy theory. I believe and that she didn't commit suicide
I've always believed in that
But I always thought she got killed because she knew too much or she got too deep in the mob or
Something like that. I I never would have thought she knew anything about flying saucers
But according to this document if it's real she knew something and what she knew
May have sent her to the grave
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio
Twitter is @jasonocarboner
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
But I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
(upbeat music)