British special forces do a daring raid on an ISIS bomb factory.
A shaman in Russia begins his quest to end the reign of Vladimir Putin.
And then who or what is destroying Iranian jets over their power plants?
All this and more today on the military special of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm a wild big doll.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I know we were going to do the dimensional merge story today but I came across some new information on that one.
And that honestly is a very very complex topic. I've tried recording it before and it's just really really hard to go over.
There's a lot of weird ins and outs. So I gotta figure out a good way to put that forward.
But anyways let's go ahead and we're gonna do this. We're gonna do military day instead.
And actually all of these stories I've discovered fairly recently.
So they're all pretty brand new. I've never heard of them before. They're totally obscure.
And they're just so...
That was a biplane. That was the red baron at the ending.
But anyways just imagine a montage right there.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
I'm not a military speech person. There's a reason why I'm not in the military because I give bad speeches.
I would be really good at the marching because I walk a lot.
And I'd be really good at carrying like 80 pounds and stuff like that because I lost 80 pounds so I know I can do that. Duh.
But like if they... if I ever got became a general. Like if I ever got promoted to general.
And they're like you have to give the speech. Because that's what generals do apparently.
And Jason's mind generals just give speeches.
I would stand in front of the assembled troops and I would say...
You're doing great guys. And I would salute them.
And they'd be like "Oh yay that was an easy speech."
Go out and blow stuff up. And they're like "Yay that's what we love to do."
Not me, not me. I blow up. So anyways it's a reason why I'm not in the military.
I actually thought. I actually to be fair.
I went to enlist in the military after 9/11 and they said "You're too fat. You can't roll."
Or enlist is what we mean. You can't enlist in the military. You're too fat.
And I was like "That's fair." Because I was quite fat.
And then as the war drug on it was basically like "Would you like to enroll?"
And I was like "Nah I'm good. I wouldn't mind going to Afghanistan."
But "You guys are on Iraq now? Blech."
I actually... my dad was in Desert Storm. He was a chaplain during Desert Storm.
The first Iraq War. I had a buddy who was in the Battle of Baghdad. The second Iraq War.
And he told me. This isn't one of the stories. This isn't one of the stories for them.
But my buddy said that he was a tank driver. And he goes "It really sucked because when you go to the military
one of the reasons why a lot of people join is so they can get free job training."
And he goes "I was a tank operator. How does that translate to the real world?
You can't even drive a big rig. It's totally different."
So anyways he's a tank driver. Battle of Baghdad.
He says they're one of the first tank divisions in the city.
And some dude hopped out with an AK-47.
And they're kind of looking around the tank and they're like "What?" "Pfft!"
Lit him up, right? Shot him with a little machine gun.
Lickified the dude. And they're "Nnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn
Liquidified the dude. And they're driving through the neighborhood.
And another dude jumps out with an AK-47.
"Pfft!" Light him up. Just shred him, right?
And that goes on for a while. And they're like "Why do these guys keep jumping out with the AK-47?"
He goes "Eventually we captured one of them."
We were able to get him to drop his weapon. We captured him.
And we asked them "Why are you shooting at us?"
And what had happened is that Saddam Hussein or the Information Minister had told the people that one
of the US was never going to invade Baghdad.
But if they did, because they weren't really going to do it,
their tanks were going to be made out of plywood. You could shoot right through them.
So the government of Baghdad was lying to them to the very end and telling them
"Oh no, no, you can shoot right through those hulking steel monstrosities.
You'll be okay." And it was just a way to kind of slow down the forces.
But nah, he's like "Yeah dude, we killed quite a few people shooting us.
We were totally protected. But what are you going to do?"
So yeah, war is hell, but we are going to look at some interesting war stories now.
Going here. And all of these stories have a...
The first story is just kind of a really cool army story.
But the other two are dead-rap radio related.
Let's go to... We're in Baghdad. This story takes place in Baghdad.
We're in Baghdad though last year. Still, it's still not a good place to raise your kids.
So anyways, Iraq 2018.
MI6 agents. Those British Secret Service dudes.
So James Bond has noticed that this particular building has an awful lot of bomb material going into it.
And no, there's not like they're selling fireworks. He's like "That's weird."
They're bringing a bunch of gunpowder into this particular building.
But none of it's coming out in the form of snakes or bottle rockets.
So let's put this on our map for bomb making facilities.
So they call in the SAS, the British Special Forces.
Second best special forces in the world. USA.
USA. So anyways, the SAS goes "Okay, keep an eye on this building. Thanks James Bond."
But now let us real people take care of this. You go off on your fictional adventure.
So they're keeping an eye on the building. And they start to get word in the neighborhood.
That multiple suicide bombings have been planned very, very soon.
SAS is like "It's time to show these ISIS people our guns."
I'm bad at making speeches. So anyways, the SAS, it's morning, right?
And the ISIS dudes have just gotten done doing their prayers in the morning.
Which to be fair, would be a horrible time to get shot.
So the SAS waited till they were done saying their morning prayers.
And they started loading stuff up into this van.
And then, here's where we get to the cool part.
Well, cool depending on whether or not you enjoy stories of bad guys getting blown to pieces.
You may not like that. So skip ahead. A couple seconds.
It's morning. These guys, they're legitimate bad guys, okay?
These are ISIS members planning a suicide attack.
Yes, they are human beings with mothers and fathers and siblings and stuff like that.
However, I understand the empathy to it. They were building suicide vests.
I just got to say that because I know I'm going to get some email about this story.
ISIS members are in the house. SAS is outside.
Door gets kicked in. Pfft. Or maybe opened. I don't know.
Maybe it's not so dramatic. Maybe ISIS forgot to lock the door.
They open the door. They rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
They open the door. They reeeeerrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
[SAS Dude]
I don't know.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]