A new upgrade to Apple phones has free speech advocates and perverts very very worried.
Is there any truth to the story that people who suffer from severe dementia return to
normal hours before their death?
Then we take a look at a new conspiracy theory that's making the rounds.
Is it- after those first two stories are so serious- is it possible that the clowns we
all know and love today from Bozo to Ronald McDonald are actually wearing the faces of
the half human half demon Nephilim today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too I hope all you clown lovers have tuned into
today's episode.
First off let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter coming to Dead Rabbit Command
right now.
It is!
Get your hands ready start clapping.
As I pull up my notes Abysmal Boyo!
Abysmal Boyo everyone give a round of applause.
Abysmal we're gonna go- how did it get so bizarre you guys have the weirdest names.
Abysmal you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't support the
Patreon I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show really really helps out a lot.
Help spread the word out there talk about it online talk about it to your friends really
really appreciate it.
Abysmal I'm gonna go and toss you the oars to the Dead Rabbit Robot we are leaving behind
Dead Rabbit Command we are headed on out to wherever Apple is headquartered I don't
know where Apple is at.
Is it in Seattle aren't they all in Seattle we're just gonna row around in the boat for
a while I think it's in Seattle but I didn't research that.
The reason why we're headed to Apple Headquarters is because there's a bit of a controversy
right now and I kind of want your guys feedback on this because I have some this intro is
very very interesting topic I'd like to see discussion from you guys.
Apple has recently announced that they're gonna start doing this program.
Apple who famously when the San Bernardino shooter when that I think it was a couple
a man and a woman who just drove into an intersection started shooting people and then it was killed
the police wanted access to the shooter's phone and Apple said no that's private information
we're not gonna reveal that and the government was constantly trying to subpoena them here's
my conspiracy theory with that you want to you want me to drop a conspiracy theory on
you I think that was all staged I think that was all staged I think it was staged I think
the government either has access to the information that could crack that iPhone like a coconut
falling on Gilligan's head or Apple completely cow-towed to him that's my conspiracy theory
and I think they made a big show of it so people would constantly go oh Apple's the most secure
phone and the government had way to crack it so quickly like I I'm a read in that article
and I was like that this is a made-up controversy but for years Apple's like no we're not gonna
reveal this information and government's like why you why you bastion of free speech I didn't
believe a word of it I believe that either Apple was complicit or that the government
had the tools to break into it but anyways that's a conspiracy theory what's going on
right now is Apple who does stand for free speech they say they do this is such an interesting
complex topic they're going to enact this new feature if you have an iPhone and you
upload a photo to the iCloud which can be an automatic process if you don't want to
have all these photos on your phone you have to I think you have to switch it on or off
I believe it might default to off but I'm not an iPhone user if you have photos in the
iCloud if they match known child porn photos or child sexual abuse material is the terminology
that's being used more commonly now if it matches child sex abuse footage Apple will
report you that that's what's being re that's what's being talked about in the media and
let's really get into it that's not so much the case what it is is that you're every this
is it's actually a little more bizarre than than I just stated so here is here is actually
how it's broken down because a lot there is a lot of misinformation about this the idea
is you have child sexual abuse material on your phone and it gets uploaded iCloud you
will be reported to the police this is what actually happens there's going to be a series
of hashtags assigned to all of known images of child sexual abuse it's going to be like
this algorithm that you don't necessarily see and if you have a photo that matches that
algorithm a human reviewer will then look at the photo you uploaded to the iCloud and
after that human reviewer has verified that this is child porn they don't report you
to the local police which i think is how a lot of people are saying this they report
you to the national center for missing and exploited children who they will then report
you to the police so apple gets to say we're not calling the cops on you we're calling
the people who call the cops on you and they say listen our system is so foolproof they've
done tests on this they said the chances of you being falsely flagged for this is once
a year you have a one in one trillion chance of this accidentally going off and again this
is based on known child sexual abuse material so people are like what if i take a photo
of you know i'm playing with my kid in the pool am i going to get flagged for that and
blah blah blah it's known child sexual abuse material which there's a ton of it out there
unfortunately in matches it has this algorithm based and then a human has to review it i
feel really bad for that human so there's that there's a ton of controversy about this
you have a bunch of free speech advocates rallying against this not because they're pro child
porn that's not the case Matthew Green had this really intro he's a cryptos he's a cryptography
researcher at john hopkins university he had this awesome quote i was reading in this article
on the ap he said what happens when the chinese government says here is a list of files that
we want you to scan for does apple say no i hope they say no but their technology won't
say no unquote and that's the slippery slope that i think people are worried about is fine
who no one is pro child sex abuse material other than the perverts who produce it and
use it no one else is and you but you have to look the next step down like what how yeah
because we know what would happen if china came to them because microsoft has already
done it and google's already done it and they've already done all sorts of like changes to their
algorithm and change the search engine to kowtow to the chinese government we know that and
they do it with the american government as well they're just not as vocal about it that's
a very very interesting question my my thing is on the one hand well here this is what's
actually so interesting because there's a lot of free speech advocates on about this
and normal people as well but at the same time don't we all know that our devices are
spying on us at all time now i just realized that like you can't be a free speech advocate
and have a cell phone or smartphone at least you can't it 100 spies on you all the time
all the time so now that i'm thinking about it why are we up in arms about this particular
thing because if i keep talking about ramen noodles near my phone i'll start getting asked
for ramen noodles like we've given up the free speech that argument doesn't make any
sense anymore we've already given up the free speech thing the second the second generation
of smartphones when they started started having all these algorithms built into it that makes
it so much more convenient to get the news we want we've given up the free speech argument
so actually i dismiss that now if you're drawn your line of the sand for the free speech
argument because of this the battle is already over we gave up the free speech argument unless
you're using like a brick phone and duck duck go or whatever go go duck whatever it is and
you're using some weird email service you already given up the the privacy argument because
we have no privacy anymore we've given that away my thing is how do we stop this guys
this is an epidemic this child garbage it's out there and it just seems to be getting
worse every year like you'll see of these raids and they're like we arrested 44 people in
this thing and it's just like how do else do we stop this now i'm not one of those person
who wants to keep giving up liberties for a little bit of safety i'm not that guy i don't
use i don't use an apple phone anyways i think i'm not a fan of magnetize or apple in any
of that so it's not even my friend but i would be shocked i know i would be shocked if android
doesn't have something like this already built in and they just never announced it i'm an
android guy i just how what do we do to stop this because i don't think the answer is nothing
i don't think the answer is the government coming into my apartment every single day
and ruffling through my couches and talking to my neighbors and all that stuff either
like you don't have to have this total police state and i don't think the other answer is
you don't do anything and let people do whatever they need to do to get off because they're
a bunch of perverts so what the my question you guys is what do we do how do we stop this
and i don't know and you know the weirdest thing is to is this is what makes me a little
sus of apple in the first place is they announced this and then they announced at the same time
this protocol for kids like it's on the same site they say kids listen if someone says
you sends you a nude photo you don't have to look at it we're actually gonna block the
photo and then we're gonna ask you do you want to look at this nude photo and if you
want we've actually included this button you can hit and they will send a message to your
parents saying someone sent you a nude photo okay if you have the technology to block a
nude photo being sent to a child don't let them click on it they shouldn't be looking
at it that's that was super weird to me and they put it in the same thing as they were
talking about this they're allowing their they are acknowledging they will allow your
children to look at nude photos if they want nude i'm not talking about a biology exam
a textbook picture from a textbook i'm not done these are images that people send them
via the messaging is very very specific if someone messes you a photo and the algorithm
picks up that it is a naked person it lets the child know it's okay if you don't want
to look at this naked person but if you do this is a sensitive picture you can click
here don't let them look at it if you have the technology to block a child from looking
at this stuff in the first place block it and say we cannot send this message this user
is under the age of 18 and then you go look the kid can easily just lie and say they're
over 18 sure but but it's so bizarre they kind of like are like by the way we're gonna
let your kids get nudes and send nudes if you go to send a new to goes you know maybe
you don't want to send this but it still allows them to send it i didn't know that iphones
could tell how old the person was using them you should just shouldn't be able to send
if you can tell that it's a nude photo don't let them say absolutely bizarre so in the
same part where they're talking about this is the way we're gonna stop child porn from
being out there in the same page they go listen this is the way your children can produce
child porn more safely we're gonna say are you sure you want to send this nude absolutely
bizarre weird just stop it if you guys can stop it stop it that that segment went on
a little bit longer than i had planned so we're gonna skip the story about the dementia
patients it's a weird one we're gonna save that one for tomorrow let's go ahead and move
on to our last story abysmal i'm gonna go ahead and toss you the key so that world famous
carpenter copter go ahead and take us up and out of this apple headquarters building as
they're getting raided by the police we are headed on out to biblical times that's a
location you didn't know that i did a story a long time ago it's one of my favorite episodes
i know a lot of you guys love it too about the book of giants it's the apocryphal story
about what happened when angels and humans enter bread and it's supposedly a lost book
the bible it's really really interesting episode i'll put it in the show notes and just a quick
overview of what the nephilim is it is that it's that they're mentioned briefly in the
bible and then there have been other books like the book of inoc and like the book of
giants that goes into more detail but what it is is i think they're originally mentioned
in genesis angels came down to earth god sent them down there to kind of be the stewards
of men but then they found out how bootylicious our women were started banging them their
children became these great heroes these great legends of old that's what we see in the book
of genesis but what we see in the book of giants it kind of goes on from there it's that these
angels kept interbreeding with humans and it was polluting the genetic bloodstream of
what humans were because you started having these super humans for lack of a better word
some of them were giants some of them just had giant personalities they're really cool
to be around some of them had superpowers and so god was like okay this is what i thought
this is what i thought when i created adam and eve so we got to go down and take these
out and there was a great angelic army actually i think it was just four dudes but they pretty
much wiped out all of these nephilim and their angel fathers and even the human mothers
and to finally put the nail in the coffin of this half breed human race god flooded the planet
so it's an interesting story i love doing that episode it's always very fascinating i get a lot
of requests to cover it even more so it's a very interesting story whether or not it's true
because it's not in the bible it's kind of an apocryphal book but even dismissing all of that
the nephilim are mentioned in the bible ever so briefly as these people who are half human
half angel there's this new conspiracy theory coming out and when i first read about it and
i'm sure when you guys saw the title of this episode you kind of chuckled and it's an interesting
journey let's let's hold judgment on this real quick there's been about three different youtubers
over the course of five years who have made this same point with different intentions but this is
in a nutshell the nephilim the half human half angel offspring looked like clowns looked like what we
would consider a modern day clown they had red hair that sometimes came up in a point like a
jester's cap they had a bright red nose and they had white skin and the logic behind this
i mean it's kind of hard word to use of this and the logic behind this is they take two cases of
known giants in history and point out that they have these features as well we've covered both of
these one of them was the giant of kandahar he was a giant who supposedly came out of a cave
in kandahar afghanistan and fought a bunch of us special forces he was pale faced or he was white
and he had red hair and he came out the spear i did an episode on him and i if i remember correctly
i disputed i said that probably didn't happen if i remember correctly the second story they point
out i also covered on this show and it did happen we do have proof of this the question is what do
you consider a giant i think when we think of giants we're thinking at least when i think of
giants i'm not thinking of shack or lebron james or something like that like to me they're super
tall dudes when i think of like god level giants like the offspring of like humans and angels i'm
thinking like 13 feet or taller but anyways we covered this it was a group of giants in nevada
they were cannibals they were eating other natives in the area and all these tribes had to get
together to kill them and that was a really cool episode i did these giants this is like old timing
nevada before any westerners got here they were described as having red hair and pale skin
so this idea that we have now two stories of giants one of them is easily dismissed the giant
of kandahar but the giants of nevada there is some archaeological evidence to show that they were
taller than normal if i remember correctly taller than normal people but still would put them around
like six foot two again it's been a while since i did that episode but i could be off on that but
the point is is that we have those stories that are kind of tied into the white skin red hair
and in locations where you wouldn't expect those genetic traits you want to expect to see a pale
person with red hair in the middle of nevada long before any europeans settled there also i had to
look this up because i didn't believe it but on easter island there are statues that have red
caps you know those giant statues on easter island of the dude's heads some of them have red caps so
they've been brought into this conspiracy theory as well that those were images of these great giants
that once walked the world so that's the first piece of evidence that we see put out by these
youtubers the second piece of evidence is this is so because when i when i saw this first youtube
video i had a chuckle i just saw the title was so interesting let's get in so i saw a recent video
from a channel called conspiracy are us and they were doing this topic about clowns look like the
nephaline i was looking through their channel and it was a very entertaining and very educational
video they do a lot of mudflod stuff which i did an episode on the mudflod i think that's been
settled i think we know what was caused there it was cities were being raised because we needed to
make room for our sewage lines cities had existed for thousands or hundreds of years with open
sewage and all of a sudden there's a population boom so we raised the city or simply raised the
roads and we just kept like first floors then became basements so we could put sewage lines
underneath the streets i think that's pretty settled at this point but the mudflod still is a very
popular conspiracy theory and i'm not he can definitely investigate that i'm not the guy who
tells people what to do but conspiracy rs did this video about clowns look like nephaline they got it
from understanding conspiracy a youtube channel called understanding conspiracy theory they started
out in 2017 they no longer put out new videos they put out those 17 episodes all saying the same thing
the nephaline looked like clowns and it's just kind of the same thing over and over again again
it's fairly well put together a youtube channel i didn't listen to all of their stuff but it he
does his research it's an observational conspiracy theory they're looking at stuff like why do these
giants have red hair and white faces and what does that look like that looks like clowns what's
interesting though is understanding conspiracy didn't originate this they're the most prolific
and conspiracy rs admits hey i found this on the understanding conspiracy channel
understanding conspiracy gets very upset that this was actually originally brought up on youtube
there could be an article floating around there somewhere but the earliest example i could find
on youtube there's a website called the epic conspiracy and they put out a video in 2015
called new evidence the nephaline are interdimensional killer clowns and it was a joke video they're
just kind of joking around and making these observations their other videos seem to be the
same thing i don't think they're putting out anything else either but so you have these youtube
channels mostly understanding conspiracy putting out this stuff and when you look at that when you
go okay so we have giants that i guess that's clown like white faces red hair but then the
conspiracy and so when i saw that again i was like oh it's kind of interesting but it's an
observational conspiracy theory the world's full of them then we go into a little bit deeper and
again i'm getting all this information from conspiracies rs and understanding conspiracy
they go into the fact that dmt users when people use the drug dmt it's mostly no people go you
take it and you see the mechanical elves you see like past reality i've never done dmt it doesn't
really interest me but people talk about the mechanical elves and and that seems to be a
weird thing that when you do the drug to me that's that is bizarre like if i'm smoking weed i'm
usually having a different experience than anyone else around me and a different experience than
everyone else who's ever smoked weed when drugs like dmt when they go you see the mechanical elves
like people who've done it over their decades they keep seeing the same thing that's weird to me
it makes me think that dmt is tapping into something and i've always heard about the
mechanical elves i think i first heard about it from alex jones but another thing dmt users
often see are clowns that's a that is a regular thing they see clowns they see gestures they
see jokers and all these dmt trips a lot of times it's reported they go to a dimension
that's nothing but a giant circus or an endless carnival that that doesn't that doesn't make
me want to do dmt like the mechanical elves whatever but dude could you imagine like winning
prizes in an alternate universe that'd be dope you're like throwing balls and like you're winning
these eight-dimensional teddy bears you do dmt a lot of times they go to these universes that's just
the giant circus or a giant carnival sometimes a casino as well you win some money in another
universe that'd be dope i wonder what the exchange rate is like but they're seeing these clowns and
the question that's put forth by these youtube channels is so now we have not only do we have
giants having attributes that are similar to clowns but people who do dmt are seeing clowns and i
came across this article in my research by sam wolf called why do gestures and tricksters appear in
the dmt experience it's this long article so long and the answer who knows sam wolf because i don't
know i think it might be some sort of yungi and archetype but i don't know who knows he goes on
and on and on he says yeah it archetype it might be here to teach us lessons like the gesture of
like the native americans and then it just goes on and on but the answer is he does not know he does
have this quote when he's talking about his best answer is a yungi and archetype quote but it may
not resolve the mystery of why dmt as a as a specific substance has a propensity to bring
these entities to the surface unquote so yeah why are they seeing if it is an archetype fine but
why is it dmt that does this and why does it keep bringing people back to the circus back to these
carnivals and why is it full of clowns and it does it it does make you think because there it's so
funny we know who created the modern clown clown is actually a character from a play or a performance
called the harlequin aid and there was a character named harlequin there was a character named clown
there was a character named columbine which i'm honestly surprised there's no conspiracy theories
about that like it's all a performance and if you knew there was only four characters and they were
no no no i'm surprised there's nothing like that but um columbine there's a character named columbine
there's a character named pantaloon but back in the 1860s there was a guy this very very famous
performance this harlequin show was very famous there was a guy named joseph grimaldi and he was
got the role of the clown he'd been clowning since he was a kid and he did the white makeup the red
nose the red hair like the face design he created that before 1861 i don't know people were just
walking around there like hey everyone i'm a clown he was the one who put on all this makeup
he took clowning so seriously he was a famous clown he basically was the johnny noxville of
clowning he clowned so much i love this quote from this newspaper called the times back in the 1860s
quote grimaldi is the most assidious of all imaginal buffoons and it is absolutely surprising
that any human head or hide can resist the rough trials he volunteers serious tumbles from serious
heights innumerable kicks and incessant beatings come on him as matters of common occurrence and
leave him every night fresh and free for the next night's flagellation unquote it really didn't
mean to the story i just like the idea of this guy getting beat up so much he couldn't be a clown
anymore he did end up retiring but on the one hand we do know who invented the clown makeup but on the
other hand why do clowns speak to us so much like we we can figure out joseph grimaldi invented the
makeup but why do clowns terrify people so much some people say it's a relatively new thing
and it didn't exist say before john Wayne gasey or before pennywise the clown
but it's such an intrinsic fear in people like i remember once i heard a long time ago that
people the the clown the idea of the clown makeup came from people who would run out during gladiator
games and drag the bodies off and they wore this garish makeup and they were like the souls of
the dead claiming the brutally slaughtered people who just been eaten by lions or stabbed i go
and i'm not reading that and i go maybe it turned out to be true but the idea was like maybe maybe
that's why people associate the clown face with terror because there's a good there's a good
segment of society who are afraid of clowns and i i don't think it's proportionate like people who
are afraid of ghosts like in general or people who are afraid of of sharks in general that's fine
but the clowns is such a specific phenomenon and people are terrified by it terrified by the clown
so it always makes me think that yeah we know joseph grimaldi invented the clown but does
is the clown tap into something deeper and darker in the human psyche
because people are afraid of it the same way they're afraid of a shark that can actually kill you
or a dog people have fear dies so it's fascinating so this is one of those conspiracy theories that
i came across i kind of chuckled i was expecting a haun's level take on this stuff but um i'm a
bit i i'm not gonna say i believe in it but i'm a fan of it i honestly am i think it would explain
i think the fact that the clown did i i'll give him this i think i honestly do i think the clown
interacted with us at some point in human history and i'm not talking about the jester spirits
because we see those all across cultures i'm talking about something with the white skin and the red
hair and the the red just the disproportion body types the ultra colored clothes i'll even go that far
i think something in our past very clown like interacted with humanity and we still have a
natural fear of them i'm personally not scared of clowns i i'm not scared of clowns but i
understand why people are and i think it i think when people are afraid of clowns it's not like
the same way i'm afraid of samara from the ring i know samara from the ring is completely fictional
the movie really really scared me and i'll have nightmares about it occasionally but i understand
that that i think it that's just me being scared of ghosts in general people who are afraid of
clowns they have the same fear the same way that people who got bit by a dog or snapped at by a dog
when they are a kid or watch the dog attack someone has a fear of a dog it's based on something real
or even just the teeth because our evolutionary brain says gnashing teeth are bad those are fangs
stay away but their brain is misfiring and they're not just saying stay away from a mean dog they're
staying away from all dogs they have a phobia of dogs i think that's something clown like interacted
with us i think on a previous episode i said it might have been an alien i think it's that level i
think something interacted with us and people have still in the evolutionary brain stay away
from something that looks like this so why not the nephilim could that be i mean the the disproportion
body would make sense because again if you're half human and half angel you're not probably going to
look like a normal person so the the the body the big body the giant i'm actually i'm gonna go to
each detail and i'm gonna be like if you walk into a nephilim and honk their nose it goes
but you know i mean i'm not gonna say they had to have big feet and like
giant car it's like yes just like the nephilim but i think like there probably was something
sinister in our past that looked like a clown pale face red hair
it's not the irish it's not the irish do you know what i mean it's not i'm not gonna hang my hat
on this conspiracy theory but i actually it makes sense to me whether it's the nephilim or it was
some sort of interdimensional spirit or it was some sort of alien lifeformer who knows but i
i am a fan of the belief that something evil appeared as a clown or clowns in the past and
humans still have an evolutionary memory of them and some people love them some people love them
some people still think clowns are hilarious and they invite them to their parties and
everything like that and they're like oh joseph grimaldi that's the best invention your face and
they still love clowns and maybe that's also tied into the evolutionary system as well maybe if you
go back in time they're great great great great great great great grandma was getting banged
by a nephilim what if it turns out that's the case if you love clowns you have your
your part angel if you can't get enough of clowns you actually are a descendant of the nephilim
your genetic line lived through the flood and if you hate clowns you're just a boring you're just
a boring old human very very interesting conspiracy theory it starts off very goofy
and it kind of makes you think an interesting conspiracy theory and one that should send
chills down the back of any clown hater it may turn out that your aversion towards clowning around
may not simply be some weird hang-up you have it may actually be an early warning system
you may be trying to tell the rest of humanity these things are evil but no one will listen to you
no one will listen to you until it's too late and the world has the world has been taken over
clown faces are marching through the streets you're hiding in your bedroom but it doesn't stop you see
you see two two big old shoes standing outside your bedroom door you run in your closet you're
hiding you're sweating you're sweating as much as jason has recorded this podcast and you hear
a meow meow meow as the clown gets closer you're like jason they're just making clown you don't
do they look like clowns or are they clowns like now you're getting confused the point is is that
you you who are afraid of clowns who shut this podcast off a half hour ago the closet door opens
and then you see a big old hand come in and grab you and the next thing you know you have like a
drill you have a drill in your hand i was gonna say you got a drill going through your head but no
you have a drill in your hand you're helping them build the clown headquarters and because you're
real handy and then after you get done doing that they're like you did a really good job dude
and then they take the drill from you put a hole in your head and they give you lobotomy and now
you're just a clown soldier walking through the streets of your former town there's like balloons
everywhere like jason are they clowns or do they look like clowns there's balloons everywhere
and every day is a new child's party but all the children will lobotomize if you're not one of
the nephaleme if you're not one of their clown loyalists you just sit there all day long uh
we just sit there in captivity all day long brain dead pale white face red hair glued on to you
all patchy and stuff you're like jason i don't care what i'm like i have a lobotomy i'm not like
oh no look at my clothes these are so unfashionable oh my hair oh i'm having a bad hair day i have a
hole drilled in my brain all humanity has holes drilled in their brain apparently i'm no more
oh no i got mustard on my shirt i'm brain dead you're right but anyways the clowns have now taken
over the planet and then they look up into the night sky and they go what else is out there
and then they build a huge clown they build one spaceship one tiny spaceship and every clown
gets on board and they take off to go invade another planet and you're just sitting there
and then actually there is no end everyone on the planet has a lobotomy it's there's that's the end
the end
i hope you guys like that end you know because that is it that is the end
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com it's so hot in here i have the door open i'm still sweating
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be an email address you can also do stuff at facebook.com/dead
rabbit radio tick talk is at dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day i'm glad you listen to it today
have a great day guys