Uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
a guy who's knowing, for doing inappropriate stuff, stuff not me, another guy, another
guy, another guy.
We're gonna meet some other ghosts, one that likes to haunt an unusual place, and then
just some other stuff I found on Backpackerverse.
Today on the Afterlife Special of Dead Rabbit Radio.
Radio.
Actually, I'm a walkway girl.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
So this is part two of episode 333.
If you didn't listen to episode part one, it's totally fine.
It's just a health update.
If you don't want to hear that, you just skip past it.
It doesn't matter to me if you're a new listener.
You're not missing anything.
I basically had a heart scare.
Everything's fine.
I was just reassuring people that everything's fine.
Let's go ahead though and talk about some spooky, spooky ghosts.
Now little asterisks next to both of those spookies.
Probably an asterisk next to ghosts.
Oh actually, I do have two shout outs to do here.
So first off, back when I did episode 300, Crispy Bacon.
The Patreon supporter, Crispy Bacon says, "You know what?
Since we all talk about numerology and stuff like that, episode 333 should be
a special episode.
Because it's halfway to 666.
And I said, "You're right, sir.
You are right."
And originally it was supposed to be a special episode, but then I ended up in the hospital.
But technically, it's kind of special because it's the first two-parter.
It's not.
I think I've done other two-parters.
Have I?
I don't think I have.
So Crispy Bacon is the father of our first two-parter episode.
I've done other two-parters and I don't think about it.
But I've never split them up like this.
So all it took was my heart to go out of rhythm, Crispy, to get your wish.
Secondly, let's say hello to our newest Patreon supporter.
We have C. Knowles.
C. Knowles, C. Knowles Patreon supporter.
And I feel bad about this because I wanted this episode to come out on November 11th.
Instead it's being recorded on November 11th.
But his son Casey, it's his birthday on November 11th, 2019.
Ooh, spooky day, 11/11.
I actually saw a movie called 11/11/11.
It was a really low-budget horror movie and it was quite spooky.
Don't let your kid watch it.
But it depends.
If your kid's 25, go ahead.
But because it is Casey's birthday, we're going to let Casey drive us around.
Casey is going to be the man behind the wheel of the...
We'll bring out the Carverter Cofter.
I originally was going to use the Jason Jalopy, but since we have a guest pilot...
You're like, "Jason, he doesn't know how to drive a helicopter."
"Ah, come on, kid.
Get inside.
Here's the keys."
So while he's getting it all set up, let's go ahead and prepare for our journey to these
ghost people that I met when I died.
I should also say right now I didn't die, but I should also say right now, originally,
this episode was going to be about near-death experiences where people have come back from
bad near-death experiences.
But I didn't want to talk about that after spending five and a half hours in the hospital.
So instead we're going to talk about the aftermath of near-death experiences.
Death experiences?
We're going to go hunt some ghosts.
So fire up the copter, Casey, and right now we are headed to El Cerrito, California.
That is a pretty good pilot, man.
He knows his way around a cockpit.
Is that what they call it in a helicopter?
Oh!
I say this too before I get started.
Speaking of aerial aircraft, I get out of the hospital at 5.30.
I go to the hospital at noon.
I leave at 5.30.
I leave in the middle of a chase scene in the Fat Fate of Therias.
And I was supposed to be at the movie theater by 6.25 to see Terminator Dark Fate.
I walked about a mile from the hospital to the movie theater and got there in time to
see Terminator Dark Fate.
And it sucked.
But I will say this.
The action scenes are really good.
It was just the plot was a mess.
The plot was a real mess.
The action scenes were decent.
So anyways, if you like watching people get clawed in the face with a metal hook, every
fight scene, a guy just gets a hook to the face.
It's basically saw franchise in action form.
On the poster, the lead character is holding a hook.
Use another weapon.
It didn't work the first seven times.
Action scenes are good though.
But anyways, there's this ridiculous aerial plane thing.
We're not doing that.
Casey's flying a helicopter.
We're just flying around.
We're not looking for dead franchises to crash into.
Casey's totally just trying to concentrate as I'm just going off on these rants.
He's like, "Dude, I've never flown a helicopter before on Petrified."
I'm like, "You can do it, kid."
Slap him on the back.
We're landing in Richmond, California.
[imitates helicopter landing]
Sound like a transformer?
Not a transformer.
I wish.
Helicopter lands.
I'm going to get off.
I hope you guys brought your beach gear.
Not beach gear.
I hope you guys brought your pool gear, which is probably the same thing, honestly.
Hope you guys brought your shorts and nothing else.
Unless you're a woman, I guess I should have.
Or you have a nice bathing suit on.
I personally prefer one-piece bathing suits.
Okay, maybe that's not true because I do have a lot of sports illustrated posters around
my apartment.
But I think in the wild, in public, I prefer one-piece bathing suits.
I don't know what it is.
On a poster, I prefer a bikini.
There's nothing to do with the story.
Anyways, forget that.
So we're at this pool in El Cerrito.
It's called the El Cerrito Swim Center.
Very original name.
Now apparently, this pool, this is an interesting one.
This is interesting.
Apparently, the pool is haunted.
A haunted pool.
Now you go, "Jason, isn't that what happened in Poltergeist?"
The pool was haunted.
Technically, the house was haunted.
The bodies just came up out of the pool.
But this pool is haunted.
Supposedly, this pool was built on a...
I don't actually know.
I don't think there is ever a reason why it was haunted.
But here's what it's haunted, okay?
According to multiple websites around the web.
What happens is they hate a crowded pool.
These ghosts hate a crowded pool.
So basically, the ghosts are just people who are alive.
Nobody likes a crowded pool.
You're in a pool and you're swimming around, splashing.
Now these ghosts, if the pool is too crowded, the water gets cold.
That's a sign that the ghosts are mad at you.
Now that's also a sign that the pool is closed or that the pool...
They're trying to save energy.
The manager of the pool is like, "Oh man, my electric bill is so high.
This one turns out..."
Everyone's like, "Oh, it's cold in here.
What are you going to do?
It's ghosts.
It's dead people."
They're like, "Ah!"
Or that it's in California and their energy grid sucks to begin with.
I can say that as a longtime California resident.
This all happened during the Gray Davis administration, during the rolling brownouts.
Everyone's like, "Why is the water so cold?
It must be ghosts."
Also, there are reports that if you're in this pool, the ghosts will grab your feet
and try to pull you under.
Which again, is any living person in a pool.
Now not any.
I've been in a lot of pools in my life.
I don't know why that's...
I'm not bragging.
Everybody has.
But when you're in a pool, they're actually quite boring.
Like you're like, "Oh man, I can't wait to get in the pool.
Everyone take your shirts off."
I take my shirt off now, but I was one of those kids who didn't take a shirt off.
And then I got to the point where I was like, "Why don't I take my shirt off?
It makes me way heavier.
When I'm already heavy, I get in the pool and now I'm even less buoyant."
Because I have to take my shirt off.
I don't care what people think, so I started taking my shirt off.
But I used to not take my shirt off, probably until I was like, I don't know, 13, 14?
I was a chubby kid.
I'm still chubby, but I don't take my shirt off.
I don't care.
I take my shirt off walking down the street.
But anyways, you get in the pool and you're like, "Oh yeah, woohoo."
And then you're like five minutes later, you're like, "Sucks."
Unless you're hanging out in the pool with your buddies, but even then it sucks.
It totally sucks.
Being in a pool is actually quite boring.
So what do you do?
You start horsing around.
You start pulling people's feet.
You're pretending to drown them or actually drown them.
Play chicken, stuff like that.
So these ghosts are basically just doing what humans do.
Which to be fair, you're saying, "Jason, isn't that what all ghosts do?"
Eh, not necessarily.
Like if you go to a haunted baseball park, you don't see balls flying around, which
would actually be pretty dope.
What I'm saying is it's most likely probably people you can't see.
Non-visible people.
It's probably just people directly underneath you pulling on your feet.
Now, we do have a first person encounter from El Cerrito Swim Center.
This comes courtesy.
Now, you may go, "Hey Jason, do you really have to talk about this website?"
I thought you stopped talking about Backpackerverse.
I almost died yesterday, man.
I didn't, I didn't.
Just so.
But for the joke, I almost died yesterday.
Give me some more Backpackerverse.
I also, while I was watching Terminator Dark Fate, I thought I might have died if I hadn't
gone to the hospital and my heart just wouldn't stop beating.
Most likely wouldn't have.
But for dramatic effect, as I'm watching Terminator Dark Fate, I go, "It's quite possible that
this might be the last movie I ever watch."
And it was not, it was not up to snuff.
But I could have seen Midway.
So, I mean, you know, I don't think that movie would have been much better.
I'm gonna see you later this week.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Feeling kind of... bummy.
Because my heart rate can only get so high.
It can only get up to like 89 or something like that.
Anyways, you're like, "That's a normal heart rate."
I'm like, "Yeah, but not for me.
Not for me.
I'm an exciting man."
We have a first person encounter from Backpackerverse.
I'm gonna read you this quote and you tell me if you know what this first part is.
A young man who happens... puberty started all of a sudden.
A young man who happens to be a video psychic, used to train in the swimming pool center,
had such a terrible encounter with the angry spirits that he decided to change pools.
What's a video psychic?
First off, I'm gonna say, since I've gone back to Backpackerverse, and to be fair, I
don't go to Backpackerverse.
I'm always looking for ghost stories and they constantly pop up.
I'm not going to them.
They're coming to me.
Their site has taken a huge dip in quality recently.
Now I'm not gonna attribute it to my exposés on them and they realize, listen, we're caught.
If we write good stuff or bad stuff, we're gonna get caught by this illusive, wait not
illusive, intrepid journalist, dead rabbit, radio, Jason Carpenter's actual name.
Let's just pump out poorly written stuff.
Because when we do good written stuff, it's still fake, so let's just do fake poor written
stuff?
I don't know.
But it's taking a huge dive in quality.
What is a video psychic?
That's someone who's like, "Okay, without even looking at the case, I can tell you what
movie that is."
It's a guy with no shoes on running through an office building.
He's all, "That's Die Hard, isn't it?"
Everyone's like, "Whoa, how did he know?"
He didn't even look at the case.
He turned the case around and said, "That's Die Hard."
He's like, "Yeah, huh?
Yup."
What's a video psychic?
What is a video psychic?
Anyways, he said that one day he was swimming in this pool and he heard a voice.
Here's the quote.
I started hearing angry voices of men whispering to my ears, things like, "Get out."
Now it could be that he was swimming in this pool and there were ghostly people going,
"Get out."
Or it's possible he was swimming in this pool.
They were trying to close and it was the lifeguard yelling, "Get out!"
But he's underwater, so it all sounds muffled.
And he's like, "It was so weird.
These mysterious men, these phantoms in red shorts began grabbing me and I'm wrestling
with them."
And they dragged me out and the next thing I knew, I was sitting outside the pool near
my car.
What horrible fate awaits someone who goes to El Cerrito Swim Center.
One star on Yelp.
Actually has four stars on Yelp.
So that should tell you how unhaunted it is.
But yeah, if you're in a pool and people hear voices going, "Get out!"
There's most likely someone who works there.
They're like, "Look out, dude, someone peed in the pool."
You're swimming in there, it's turning blue.
It's already blue, it's turning green.
I heard that's a myth.
I heard that they don't actually have a thing that makes urine.
Well, we have a thing that makes urine.
It's called our body.
But there's not really a chemical in a pool that causes the water to turn green.
I don't know.
Urban Legend?
Who knows?
Also, before we leave El Cerrito, let me tell you, I'm going to read you this last
thing here.
This isn't on backpacker verse.
I'm not going to waste all your time on backpacker verse.
I'm going to save that for later stories.
This is a first person submission from a young woman named Monica.
Here is her and her family's experiences with ghosts in El Cerrito.
And if you are a resident of El Cerrito or Richmond, California, get ready because this
is a representation of not only the spirits that haunt you, but the people who live in
that area.
Here we go.
In El Cerrito, the post office on California Drive, as well as Ontario and Grand, so I
don't know if that's, I'm assuming that's two different post offices.
But anyways, my aunt and cousins have seen giant owls flying around.
One even stood and stared at them.
That is, who cares?
Who cares?
Giant owls.
Okay, but anyways.
This next part works.
I've had family members see goblin-like creatures in El Cerrito.
Lead with that next time.
Don't lead with the post office and the giant owls.
Just start off.
Hey, my family will live in El Cerrito?
Goblin.
Also, what's a goblin-like creature?
Goblin-like creature is just an ugly human.
A goblin is a goblin.
A goblin-like creature is a human who looks like a goblin.
Imagine that you're a ghost investigating.
You're walking around talking to people and you're like, "Hey, man, have you ever seen
any ghosts in El Cerrito?"
This woman walks up to you and says this, this actual quote, "My uncle said he saw a
man on a horse."
Was it a ghost?
Man, was it just a regular dude on a horse?
Oh, no, that's the whole quote.
My uncle said he saw a man on a horse.
Was he at a dude ranch?
Where?
Was it in the middle of the city?
Was it in an office building?
Did it appear before him?
Or was it just a man on a horse?
And he's never seen a horse before.
That is so confusing.
And that comes right after the goblin-like creatures.
But let's wrap it up with this.
My female cousin said she saw a man with money bags at her house.
Did he have a lume?
Did he have a lume uniform on?
Was he walking out of a bank and loading up an armored car?
These details are important.
She does go on to say that she's picked up weird conversations about money and thieving,
like she's heard it in her head.
She finishes her comment, "This is the wild west and wild it is.
Don't walk around late at night."
Submitted by Monica.
So, giant owls, night time, sure.
Don't walk around at night.
An owl might stare at you.
Goblin-like creatures, you might see ugly humans in El Cerrito.
You might see a man on a horse.
And it might see a man walk around with money bags.
Don't walk out.
None of those pose any danger to me.
It should just be don't walk out at night.
This is California and the crime rate is insane.
You're gonna get stabbed by a methodic homeless man.
He may or may not be holding money bags at the time.
Most likely will not because he's a methodic homeless man.
Maybe on a horse?
Who knows.
That would be interesting.
A homeless...
I guess all cowboys were technically homeless.
The home was the range, right?
Maybe homeless people are just reincarnated cowboys and they have no cows to wrestle.
They just feel the pull of being outdoors and sleeping under the stars and severe crippling
drug addictions.
Let's go ahead, hop back on the carpenter copter KC.
We're gonna fire that guy back up and I hope you guys are aware now this is gonna be a
long episode because it's a special.
It's the halfway to hell special.
We're going to Sutter Creek.
Sutter Creek, California.
All this stuff takes place in California by the way.
So he's not flying too far.
I don't know how far away Sutter Creek is from El Cerrito, but we're allowed in case
that you do some loop-de-loops and stuff.
Oh, you're like Jason that wasn't part of the deal.
You bought a bunch of marbles when we were in El Cerrito.
They're going everywhere.
Every time, every time.
Can you even do a loop-de-loop?
You might.
Casey can.
The helicopter keeps spinning around and around.
You're like oh no I bought yogurt.
Everything you bought needs a lid.
Like I'm sitting there with pizza.
Technically doesn't need a lid.
I guess it comes in a lid.
I'm eating just a hamburger patty, so I'm good.
I can put it in my mouth and it just flies up into my teeth and automatically I bite
it like I'm a cartoon character apparently.
Whatever.
We land.
The circus is over.
I don't even know if physically that's possible.
If you could hold, think about it.
Let's figure this out.
Okay, special episode.
Almost died.
Bear with me.
If I held a piece of meat in my hands, which that is not an if.
I do that every single day.
If I'm holding a piece of meat in my hands, when I'm holding a piece of meat in my hands
and I go to eat it, I go "Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
and I go to eat it, I go "Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
to my hands, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like,
"Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh,
I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm
going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going
to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be
like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like,
"Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh,
I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going
to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like,
"Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm
going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to
be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like,
"Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going
to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like, "Oh, I'm going to be like,
to be like, "Oh, what? This is pretty dope. I'm poking people with my pike." People are
like, "That's weird. We always knew Jason was into podcasts and bad movies. We didn't
know he was a Napoleon War rain actor. It's quite odd." But anyways, ghost and old
timey clothes walking around. We have a story from, of course, Backpackerverse. This hotel
supposedly really is haunted. There's a lot of stuff about this hotel, but Backpackerverse
tells a story about this dude who checks into the hotel with his girlfriend or wife. It doesn't
matter. Same thing. Just a contract after that. Ring. No biggie deal. His girlfriend/wife,
he's hanging out at the hotel with, and then he gets into bed and she's like downstairs
doing something. And then the ghost gets into, oh, he doesn't know it's a ghost. He feels
a lump in his bed and he's like, "Ooh, baby." And he's like cuddling up with his lump. And
then his girlfriend comes in the door and he's like, "Ah!" And he throws back the blanket
and there's a woman with pale white skin and black hair laying in bed next to him. And
she vanishes. So that didn't happen. That story is totally made up. Multiple reasons why it's
made up. One, let's look at it factually here. Okay, so first off, one of the main things
that human, and you may not know this, I mean, I'm sure you do. I'm not calling you guys
idiots, but it's mostly subconscious. One of the main things we use to identify people
is smell, even if we don't know it. There is no way that you are, if you are sober, there
is no way you are getting into bed with someone who is not your significant other and not
immediately recognizing it not as your significant other. But Jason, maybe the ghost is able to
replicate the human smell of his wife. Okay, fine. Then you want me to believe that she
believes a lump, that he can wrap his arms around her and snuggle up to a non-caporial
intensity. So this would have to, like if there is a power level of these things, a ghost
walking down the hallway, like you see in a phantom walking down the hallway, would be
fairly low on the power level. It picking up an object or throwing it or knocking over
an object would be higher. Turning electricity on and off would actually be probably easier
to do than moving stuff over, unless it's actually hitting the lights, which it never is, conveniently.
It's always something happening in the wall. But to be able to manifest as a spirit that
can not only misshape the blankets, be a full bodied apparition, because you can spoon it,
wrap your arms around it and not notice it's not your wife or girlfriend. That is basically
gozer level power. That would mean that this ghost is basically the most advanced ghost on
the planet. And it's not, it's totally made up. And he pops out of bed and his wife's like,
"Oh my god, what are you doing about that woman?" And then the ghost disappears. Now to be fair,
that actually is a great way. If you have a girlfriend/wife or boyfriend/husband and you
want to cheat on them, make your lover cover themselves in head to toe white makeup. It
might make some chafing during the actual act of love making, but have them cover their
body in full body white makeup or baby powder. Or, and I mean dye their hair black. And then
that way whenever you get caught with them, you shouldn't because you're cheating on them.
But if you get caught with them, you could then go, "Oh my god, it was a ghost." And then they
could hide under your bed or something like that. And go, "Don't look under the bed. He's a
spooky monster now." And if your significant other is an idiot, they won't realize that the
ghost looks exactly like their cousin. But that's why you fell in love with them in the
first place because they're an idiot. And you can convince them that your lover is a ghost.
So we are not done though with the Sutter Creek Inn. We see Casey looking through the
helicopter window. He's like, "Are you guys done yet? It's getting kind of cold out here."
I'm like, "It's just the ghost. It's just the ghost making the helicopter cold, bro. Just
chill out. Get it, chill out. It's like 30 degrees out there." And C. Knowles is like, "Dude, that's
my son. Just tell him how to turn on the heater. Hold on, hold on, hold on." We got one more ghost
to look at and then we'll go out. We'll turn on the heater. We are here for the main
attraction. We've covered tons of ghosts. We've talked about tons of ghost types over this
show and there are sometimes you run across a ghost that's quite unusual. And this is one
of them. This is why I brought you to here. We're going to meet a ghost. He doesn't have a
name. We'll call him... It doesn't matter. I don't need... He doesn't have a name. Okay? He
just... He doesn't need a name. This ghost has been spotted multiple times. And while you're
hanging out in the little dining room, you're drinking your tea or soda... I don't even
think I drink either of those anymore. While I'm drinking water, lame. Like a nerd, like
a caveman. I don't smoke. I don't drink. I don't do drugs. I gave him nicotine and now
I can't even have caffeine. And I can, but just not... Not eight gallons of it. But still,
I'm not supposed to have for a while. As I'm complaining about my own lifestyle choices
that I've made, you're like, Jason, okay, the pity party's over. Ooh, your heart got out
of whack. Now you guys are making fun of me as I'm drinking my water. You keep trying to
slip a slip tea into it. I'm like, no, that'll kill me. It'll kill me. You guys are all laughing
at my weakened state. A ghost shows up. And I'm like, oh, everyone, shh. What's making
fun of me is I wipe a tear away from my eye. What's making fun of me? Look, watch this.
And the ghost is standing in front of us and we're standing. We're not standing. We're
sitting in front of the ghost. And then the ghost drops his pants, fully exposing himself
to us. And then he disappears. Now that's unusual even in the world of the paranormal.
There's not many cryptids. We talked about the "gurning man." Quite a few episodes back,
he seemed like an exhibitionist, spirit or alien or demon or something like that, who
would only appear to women of a certain age group and rub his chest and have this creepy
smile on his face. But we don't see many exhibitionists as ghosts, which is interesting because
if you think about it, so many people have weird hang-ups that you think they would follow
them to the afterlife more often. This one's dead, so he's a ghost that must have been a
flasher if it exists at all. Let me back up here. If this story is true in any way, shape
or form. And this is a famous ghost out this place. I found this ghost mentioned several
times, especially in the book National Directory of Honder Places. This ghost will appear in
front of women and we're a mixed company, but it's all good. He'll appear in front of
women and he'll pull his pants down, exposing himself to us. Now, there's no specification
that he's not pulling his pants down and there's nothing there, so I believe that we're
actually seeing his ghost junk. That's why we left KC in the helicopter, but that's why
we left him in the helicopter because he was not supposed to see this. However, we all
saw it. And that might be the first ghost flasher that we've actually ever covered, or a ghost
with some sort of bizarro hang-up. Like that. Like he's still in the afterlife, still finding
a lot of amusement, pulling his pants down in front of women and exposing himself. I did
tell you guys about this, but I'm going to repeat this story again. When I was in the
Stanley Hotel, which was the hotel that inspired the shining, they had a closet that, I went
on this ghost tour and the tour guide was like, "Now everybody!" She was this really, really
hot chick in this colonial outfit, but I'm going to make fun of her voice anyways. But
people, here you go. Now she sounds like Rick or Morty or both of them. Here's a closet,
okay? And if you go inside, there's a creepy old, forget the voice, she explains to us
that there's a closet in this room where there's this randy old ghost who will like feel up
women if you go in there. And she goes, "Any volunteers, any woman want to go into this
dark room and be groped by this supernatural spirit?" Now I'm sitting there and I'm like,
"And this is fake, obviously." And so the woman goes, "Any volunteers?" And this girl,
this girl, she's probably about 12, goes, "I'll do it." And the demeanor of the tour guide
completely changed and she looks straight at the girl and she goes, "You have to be 18
to go into the room." "Any volunteers?" And we're like, "What in the world?" So that makes me
think, and I think I explained, I did an episode on the Stanley Hotel, it was on my birthday
episode last year. But anyways, so we do have records or stories, is probably a better word,
of these spirits who have these weird type of hang-ups, but I wanted to expose you,
unattended to this one, and you're like, "Boo, boo, you're holding me down, you're shoving
caffeine right into my throat of a...Waaaaaah." So, you guys carry my lifeless body in a Christ-like
pose, back to the helicopter, throwing me in the back, turn the heater on, flying me to
the hospital, five and a half hours later, I'm sitting in the hospital, you guys are
like, "Are you ready to go? Are you done?" I'm like, "Hold on, hold on." So, let me get this straight.
Dom Toretto turned against the family because his girlfriend, and you're like, "No, just
shut the movie off, just shut the movie off." You guys pull me out of the hospital room,
I'm like, "No, no, no, wait, I need to see more Hobbes and Shaw before their own spin-off
movie." You guys drag me out of the hospital room. We are going to one last place here.
We are going to Sonoma County, flying through the night sky, rotor blades cutting clouds.
Don't think that happens. Carivers are getting knocked out of their house. I'm like, "Casey,
fly through those clouds." You're like, "But isn't that carolot?" I'm like, "Fly through
those clouds." These rainbows are getting destroyed. There's a carobare with no legs. He's like,
"Why? Why? I'm like, "Hehehehe, care about that." Blood going everywhere. Anyways, we eventually
land the helicopter case. He's like, "Oh, my childhood heroes. I really loved Sherlock
Bear." I'm like, "Yes, he can share in the misery of losing all of his friends now."
Ceno takes his son home. He's like, "That's son relieving." Casey's like, "I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, carobares." Anyways, no, they come back. They come back. They're good people.
Casey gets over it very quickly because he doesn't know who the carobares are. He's like,
"What's a carobare? I've never even heard of that before." If he was flying through
like bay blades or something, he'd probably be more emotionally raw. Anyways, we're going
to a couple places. These are going to be brief. These are all from Backpackerverse.
So we're going to end on the absurdity. I guess I should say this for new listeners.
Backpackerverse is a stupid website that just makes up stuff about ghosts. You're like,
"Jason, why are you really going to do this?" "Yes, I'm going to do this. I almost died yesterday.
Let's talk about this. We're in Backpackerverse. This is from the website or this is from the
web page, 10 Sonoma County hiking trails with insane paranormal activity. First off,
we're going to Laguna de Santa Rosa Trail. Let me read. I'm going to read this to you
because that's the best way to explain this stuff because then you go, "Jason, you're
just making stuff up." And I'm like, "No, let me read exactly what they wrote to you."
Beware. This is the Laguna de Santa Rosa Trail. Beware. You might encounter someone
wandering aimlessly in the middle of the woods and that someone is not necessarily a human
being. Numerous stories have reported the bizarre sighting of a body roaming while bending mid-waste.
What does that even mean? What in the world does that even mean? Does that mean, honestly,
that somebody walking down the trail saw another human roaming around bent over and assumed
that was not a human being or sorry, not necessarily a human being? Because if that's the case,
if that is the litmus test we use for the paranormal, then the world is surrounded by ghosts. You can go
to any place where there's a penny on the ground and someone's like, "Oh, you're like,
"Oh, no, the invasion has begun." Go to an old folks home. Just walk by a yoga studio
and see a bunch of people bent over. When this guy walks by the yoga studio, he thinks it's full
of ghosts. He thinks paranormal activity 8 is taking place. There's a bunch of people bent over.
Maybe it was crawling, but again, that was the end of the story. There was more to it,
but that was the end of it. And the more didn't explain any of that. Now let's go to
"Pigme Forest Trail" at Salt Point State Park. Let me read this verbatim to you.
"Because I think it has a great setup. There is a little known story," i.e. I just made it up
for the sake of this article, "There is a little known story of a small girl who looked exactly
"like the doll she owned." And I was like, "Ooh, cool. A story about a girl turning into a doll,
"or the doll wanting a twin sister, or the doll is her twin sister. Trapped." That's what I'm thinking.
Rumors say that years ago, she got lost in the forest while carrying her doll. Oh, maybe the doll's
going to help her find her way out, or maybe when rescuers show up, there's two dolls. Or the doll
takes over the girl, so the girl is still trapped in the doll for whatever. Let's move on to the quote.
"She never made it out and died alone. Now her spirit wanders the forest, doll in hand, seeking
"aid from hikers. Will you help her?" What? Why did you--that's the whole thing for that one. Why would
you build up the fact that the doll looked like her? Am I wrong to be disappointed in that? A girl
has a doll that looks exactly like her. She gets lost in the woods one night. And then she just
never gets found, and she still carries the doll around. That's stupid. That's dumb. I was so
insulted by that one, because it actually set it up to be kind of creepy. It could have said, some
people say that the doll is the kid. That's okay. So maybe it's a little convoluted, but let me
do this right now. There's a little known story of a girl who used to carry a doll around that looked
just like her. And one day, the girl got lost in the forest. A couple days later, the little girl
was found by rescuers. But she didn't have her doll. They didn't think anything of it. But when
they brought the girl home to her mother, her mother swore, "That's not my daughter. That's not
my daughter." Bam. There you go. What was that, like five, six sentences? It makes it a little
more scary, like you're thinking, did the doll possess her, or did they change places, or whatever.
Not, she still has the doll. And I love this last, okay, now her spirit wanders the forest.
Doll in hand, seeking aid from hikers. Will you help her? Yes. Yes, if I am in the middle of
the woods, and a little girl shows up and says, "Oh my God, I haven't eaten anything in days. I've been
lost. Will you help me?" I'll say, "Yes, I will help you." What type of old, and it doesn't even say
that she kills you if you don't help her, or if you do help her, whatever. She's just a little, yes,
who reads that, it goes no way. Because even if it's a little ghost girl, with a little creepy doll,
you go, "Yeah, I'll help you out." And you take her to the edge of the forest, and she goes, "Thanks,
stranger." And then she disappears. There you go. There you go. Now, if they said she also has a
collection of G.I. Joe action figures that are in the shapes of the hikers who tried helping her in
the past, creepy. Again, then I go, "No, I don't want to help this girl, because I don't want to turn into
Shipwreck." Shipwreck was actually my favorite G.I. Joe character. So funny. There was this episode of
G.I. Joe about Shipwreck, and this is going to trip some of you guys out, because this is a true
Mandela thing, or Lost Media, however you want to put it. One of the best two-part episodes, and I'll
talk about this because this is my two-part episode, one of the best two-part episodes at G.I. Joe,
because they always did like five-part episodes and stuff like that. They added this episode, and this
totally fits with the podcast too, so I'm not just going off in a rant. They had this episode where
Shipwreck, who was like the sailor G.I. Joe, so Shipwreck is involved in this huge battle against
Cobra, and something happened. He gets knocked out or something like that, and then he wakes up
it's 10 years later, and he goes, "Whoa, like what's up?" And then he's like, "Have I been in a coma for
10 years?" He said, "No, no, no, no, no. You've been in a coma for like three days, actually. You did
get injured in that battle, but then G.I. Joe actually defeated Cobra, and you're instrumental
in that, actually, but you've lost your memories. Like you just recently had this new head injury,
and you've lost the last 10 years of memories. You have a wife and a kid. I think you had two
kids, and the world's at peace. Cobra is destroyed." And so he goes home, and it's like this perfect
suburban life, and he's like, "I don't remember any of this." This is a really good episode. He's like,
"I don't remember any of this, but his beautiful wife, beautiful kids." And he's meeting other G.I. Joe's,
and he starts to catch on. It's kind of a Truman Show type of thing that he is a prisoner. He starts
to kind of figure out that this life is not real, that he's a prisoner, and it must have been Cobra
who are trying to get information out of his head. Now his buddies are saying, "Shipwreck, no, you're going
insane. Like you need to go to the doctor." Like this is reality. We've defeated Cobra, and he's like,
"No, no, no, you guys, I know for a fact that something is not right here." And what happens is,
I don't remember what the impetus is for him to finally realize that everything is fake, but he decides to try
to break out of town, and all of a sudden everything goes to chaos. And it did turn out that Cobra did
kidnap him during that last battle and had created this whole world for him. It was on an island,
and gave him a fake family. But the people on the islands were basically like bio-robots. So when they
were killed, they would melt, and it was like their eyeballs would fall out of their head, and they would
look like an action figure was being lit on fire. They would just kind of melt. And at the ending, he still
hasn't fully grasped how much, how many bio-androids are on this island. He goes home to get his wife and
his kids, because he's still having a hard time starting this out, and they both pull, all the kids
have these automatic rifles, and his wife has this automatic rifle, and they're going to shoot him, and a
fire breaks out. Now this is the thing. The first time they aired the episode is different than every other
airing of the episode, because I love this, it was one of my favorite episodes of G.I. Joe. I just thought it
was a great storytelling thing, and I saw it back in '85. So I was like nine years old, and it just like
blow in my mind that this story is going on. But in the original viewing of it that I remembered, a fire
breaks out in the house, and the bio-androids of his family have rifles on them, and they melt. He watches
his wife and kids melt in front of them, and their eyeballs fall out of their heads, and he's like,
"No, he's totally freaking out that they just melt." Like they were going to kill him, but the fire got to
him first, and you're just watching these two kids and this wife that he thought that were real, really up to
that point, melt. And the episode ends with the Joe's laying siege to the island, because they figure it out,
and they save him, and he's just like heartbroken. He just can't, like he's still trying to figure out, because he
was on this island for a while. It wasn't like two days. He was on this island for a good amount of time, and he
was being told, "Oh no, you've been here for ten years," or whatever. Really, really good episode in the
ebb and... 1980s cartoon. GI Joe had a couple episodes that... I think that was probably the best episode of GI Joe.
They did tell some really good stories, but yeah. Why am I talking about that? What were we talking about?
Helping people? I was talking about, like, saving a little girl from... Oh, oh, appearing as a GI Joe character.
Yes, yes, Shipwreck was actually one of my favorites after... So I would be happy to appear as Shipwreck. He was
actually one of my favorites, I think before that show. I really liked that character. Anyways, everyone's just
sitting in the forest. The little girl with her dolls just sitting there super bored. She was like, "Okay, Boomer, we don't
care about your 80s cartoons and your Carabaire references." I'm like, "Ugh." So anyways, I'm like, "Okay, girl, you can
head back to the forest." She's like, "Thank you. I will head back to my eternal torment, as long as I don't have to
hear about 80s cartoons anymore." 80s cartoons were great, by the way. So, better than, like, your slug tarot.
Slug tarot nowadays. But anyway, so we're walking through... We're leaving. There. We're going to our last trip on
our special episode, Halfway to Hell special episode. Thanks, KrispyBacon, for making me realize the significance of 333.
So we are headed off to our last destination of our special episode of Dead Rapper Radio. We are going to West County
Regional Trail, Sebasto Pole. That's in California, apparently. Sebasto Pole. Stupid name. Anyways, West County
Regional Trail. No, nothing about the place. Just dumb name. Don't want to go there. West County Regional
Trail. Again, I just got to read you this quote, because you can't say it any better than this. But while I'm reading
you this quote, I want you to imagine we're going on this journey together. So, "Cold night air through the very famous
haunted forest of Sebasto Pole." Everyone knows about Sebasto Pole. "Marked by a wooden bridge." Don't know why there's
a whistle there, but there was. There's a little slide whistle there. "Marked by a wooden bridge." It takes you on a short
journey into the mesmerizing horrors of old structures. Who knows what you will find under the piles of rotten
wood? So we're walking through this. We've crossed the old creaky bridge. I reach for the slide whistle. You're
like, "No, that joke." It's dumb the first time. Don't do it again. We walk off the bridge. We go on a short
journey into the mesmerizing horrors. We're like, "Ugh, tripping out." You're like, "Chasing, chasing. That's an acid
plant. Don't touch it. I'm all tripping out." Anyways, we're walking through the woods and we see old
structures. So old, spooky, broke down buildings. Just wood everywhere. Which is what forests normally have in
them, but this is processed wood. This is cut and planks of wood. And then what was it? Oh yeah, the next part was
"What will we find under piles of rotten wood?" So brown recluses. Maybe the body of a homeless man. Who knows.
Probably those two things. Or both. And then we get to this last sentence. This might actually be one of the best
sentences I've ever read involving the paranormal. If not one of the best sentences I've ever read, period. So move out of the way.
Hymning way. We have backpacker verse. We're walking through this forest late at night. We see a pile of rotten wood.
We're moving it aside. And then we have this quote. "Some hikers report a strange apparition." Here's the first part, which we need to
figure out. A face without a body. So, "Some hikers report a strange apparition of face without a body." Now, you go, "Jason, that's
not unusual." Okay, but here's the thing. Is it a head or is it just a face? I would assume because of the terminology, it's
simply the face not a head. But wouldn't you just be able to say a face? Like a floating face. Why do you have to add without
the body? That's how all faces are. There's nothing unusual about that. You're going, "Jason, you're getting totally into the weeds
on this one." This is why this is important. Because it's obvious it doesn't have a body from the rest of the sentence. It's almost
like they got paid by the word and they wanted that. They get paid a penny every word. They wanted that extra three cents.
Because they did not need the term without a body because of what comes after this. We're moving the wood around. We go back to the
sentence. "Some hikers report a strange apparition of face without a body stitched into the headrest of a brown leather chair."
Okay, so now you see why... First off, first off, that's not... First off, let's be clear. That's not true. That never has happened
in the history of the world. At no point has ever anyone moved a log, seen a pile of rotting wood, began moving the rotting wood
and found a brown leather chair. That part is untrue, totally. Secondly, removing the wood and then seeing a human face
stitched into a brown leather chair. Without a body, by the way, because that would just be someone sitting in a chair.
What is the point of this apparition? What is the point of being a ghost if people have to remove garbage to find you?
That's not really even a ghost. That is... Okay, here's the thing. Let's play our game. This is either completely made up. It is completely made up.
But let's say that the story is true. Let's figure out what it is. If you were a ghost, if you were a ghost, you would be like
"Woo, floating around." Maybe you're trapped in a particular location, but unless this guy died in a lazy boy factory
and he possessed the body of a brown leather chair, there is no way also, let's talk about this too, there is no way that a brown leather chair
would survive more than a few nights under a pile of rotting wood in the middle of a forest. It would be completely trashed.
So, you're like, "Taste this neither here nor there. We're talking about ghosts." My point is that you're a ghost. Are you really going to be a ghost under garbage?
Like, wouldn't that be the most ridiculous place to just be a ghost?
Two, let's say that it's my worst nightmare. Let's say that a man was magically transformed into a lawn chair. Or a leather chair.
A big old recliner. And I hate, I've talked about that, I hate stories where people are transformed into stuff against their will.
So this guy is turned into a brown leather chair. The thing that scares me about that is that you're transformed into something and you're just sitting there
and you're observing the world around you. Like, that locked-in disease doesn't really scare me as much because you're still like a human.
But like, if you had locked-in disease and you were an ottoman or you were like a lazy boy, that terrifies me.
So he's trapped in the form of a recliner. I'm assuming it's a recliner. In the middle of nowhere.
But, and then he could like watch the birds fly around and be like, "Oh, I wish I could pet those birds. I wish I was fast enough to catch a bird to pet it."
It doesn't scare me if you're covered, again, if you're covered in garbage, because then you don't know what's going on in the outside world.
You can't influence it anyways. You're just a leather chair covered in garbage. You're just a leather chair covered in garbage.
So you are a garbage ghost. That might be the worst ghost. That might be the worst ghost we've ever covered.
Now, I'm sure someone could email me and show me a worst ghost, but being a ghost in the middle of nowhere, that's spooky actually.
Little girl ghost walking around with a doll can be spooky, but at least she's mobile.
I wish she can like follow you and when you're in your tent a little like, you see the zipper move up a little bit and you see like a little eye poke out.
Like look out from underneath the flap. And you first you just think, "Oh, maybe that was a deer. Maybe a deer got super close and evolved thumbs and undid the zipper."
But you would like brush it off and then in the middle of the night you'd be on your cell phone late at night and the blue glow would be filling up the tent.
And you would think you see like the outline of something outside your tent. You're like, "Ah, the deer's back."
But then you realize it's like only four feet tall and happen to be carrying a two foot tall version of itself.
And then in the morning you wake up and your own kid is missing and there's a doll that looks exactly like your kid.
You're like, "Ah, it sucks. What are we going to do with this dumb doll?" That's scary.
I mean, obviously that involves child protection, but any part of that, the little girl looking in your tent or seeing something run by your tent.
Obviously your child being replaced by a doll. All that stuff's scary.
Now you're camping in the middle of the woods and 50 feet away from you is a pile of garbage.
And the wind blows and you think you see something outside your tent and you look and it's just a pile of garbage 50 feet away.
No big deal. You're like, "I should have probably picked a different camping spot." But whatever.
And then later on the night they're kind of on your phone flipping around and you think you see something move outside but you're wrong.
You're just tired. You're just saying stuff. And then next morning you wake up and you pack all your gear up and leave.
And your kid's totally fine. You're like, "There's not a little brown leather chair with your kid's face on it."
You're like, "No, this sucks." You just leave with your kid.
There's a pile of garbage that nobody ever looks in.
What a hiker. Let me just say this too and I'm sorry, I might be being a dead orange.
What a hiker. It's like, "Hmm, what a beautiful nature romp." I love nature.
Ooh, pile of garbage. Let me start rooting through this until they find a brown leather chair with a human, not a body.
A face without a body stitched into the headrest of a brown leather chair.
That is our tour of spooky, spooky little asterisks next to those.
Ghosts, asterisks next to that one as well. Of California.
Now, I want to end this episode with, again, a thank you to you guys for all your support and all your love.
I find it so bizarre that less... it's a little... the show started in June of 2018.
So we're a little over a year later. And I've been to the ER before and I've had issues where I've had to go there
and I've sat in that room for an hour or two or more while I'm getting tests done and things like that.
And then they come back and say, "Oh, it's just an anxiety attack." Or, "Ah, you know, your ankle's not broken."
But never have I sat in that hospital and been able to laugh at all of the great comments
and feel very proud of all the support you guys have given me.
This show's really changed my life. Like, I was thinking about that. I was like, "This is really awesome.
Like, this is a community of people." And I really want to make sure that you guys know how much you mean to me.
You guys really do mean a lot to me. And that's why I wanted to get this episode out. Not feeling 100% still,
but I wanted to get this episode out for you guys just to acknowledge how much you guys mean to me.
The show's really changed my life. And I'll end it with this.
I almost didn't do the podcast. We've talked about this a couple of times. Like, I was a writer before this,
and I had some other projects before this. And I just kind of fell into this one day.
And I implore you guys to find those projects that are going to change your lives as well.
You may fail a couple of times. I failed a couple of times in other projects.
But find that thing that will change your life. That sounds like a big goal.
And you may not know what it is at first, but find that thing so a year later, when you're feeling down and you're not feeling good,
you have that community around you. And to let you guys know that you guys do have this community around you as well.
But, um, yeah, find that thing if you can.
Because it's weird. I mean, again, my life has radically changed since I started doing this show.
I really, really appreciate all you guys, all your support, all your love, all your jokes.
But it also wasn't Veronica the Honenthal had nothing to do with this. It's totally fine.
I love you guys. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at Facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day. But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]