Humanity prepares to touch the sun.
And when Hollywood gossip becomes true crime,
today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
(upbeat music)
Hey everyone, welcome back for another episode
of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
It's a Monday, it's 103 here in Hood River.
I'm actually recording a little bit earlier in the day.
I normally do this at night, but you know,
I had some free time.
I had the day off, so I figured I'd see what it's like,
recording during the day.
There's a couple cars,
there's a little more traffic outside than normal,
but we'll see how it goes.
Also this week, we're gonna do something
a little bit different.
Every day we are going to feature a food-based story.
Food-based conspiracy, weird stories about food,
'cause I actually found a bunch of them
when I was just looking.
Because I actually found a bunch of them
when I was just kinda looking at conspiracies this week.
The first thing that I have to say right away,
we actually bumped this up.
The story, originally I had slated for Tuesday,
but it's so important.
You need to know it now.
And then we'll get into the intro and everything,
just in case.
I have to tell you this, just in case,
you have a spoonful right now.
The CDC is telling people, do not eat honey smacks.
The delicious, supposedly delicious cereal,
I've never eaten it before,
but the delicious cereal with the wrap-in hip-hop frog
honey smacks has been linked
to a multi-state salmonella outbreak,
which is second to at least two people in Oregon.
And I'm from Oregon,
a lot of the listeners here are from Oregon.
Since July 12th, 12th, however you say that,
100 people since March, that doesn't make sense.
Okay, since March, 100 people have gotten sick
after eating honey smacks.
Apparently there's some sort of salmonella outbreak.
So, first off, I just stumbled across this story.
Again, I was kind of looking up conspiracies,
and this was just an alert on some website about Oregon.
Oh, I was looking up Oregon employment laws,
what I was doing, and I saw this story.
This story should be everywhere.
It's, can you imagine buying a box of honey smacks
and you're like, gotta dig 'em honey smacks?
Gotta dig 'em, I'm ribbit the rabbit,
whatever his name was.
Anyways, some little 10 year old has this bowl of honey smacks.
He's getting ready to watch some slug-tara on Netflix,
and he's just digging in, digging into that stuff.
The next thing you know, they have to chop his hands off.
Salmonella's actually like, paralyze you.
It can get really, really bad.
So I got a couple questions about this.
One, why isn't this bigger news?
I mean, I guess they probably sell,
hundreds of thousands of boxes
and only 100 people have gotten sick,
but you would still think that a story of something
that appeals to children is making people sick.
Actually, now think about it.
It says 100 people were sick.
How many of those people were children?
Are a bunch of adults eating honey smacks?
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't eat cereal, I don't, well, okay.
First off, I don't eat anything for breathics in general.
I'm not, I don't eat stuff when I wake up.
But I'm not a big cereal guy, even.
I have a couple boxes of cereal here
that are at least five years old.
I just never bought 'em and never ate 'em.
I actually have a box of microwave popcorn bags
and that's about six years old
'cause I never eat that either.
And I don't throw it away.
I think it'd be funny if someone came over
and it had some.
I wake up and there's someone in my kitchen
making some cereal and I will not say anything
as she sits there and eats it and then leaves.
I guess that's kinda cruel.
But anyways, they'll probably get salmonella.
My point, my second question is how does cereal,
what in cereal can cause salmonella?
I thought that was like eggs or cilantro.
I thought that had to be some sort of produce.
Isn't that just kind of like dried corn
with like a honey glaze on it?
It's kinda crazy how susceptible our food supply
is to illnesses.
You would think that something this basic,
just basically like corn starch
and high fructose corn syrup
and whatever would be relatively free
of any sort of like virus or bacterial infection.
But who knows, it's apparently out there.
If you're eating the honey smacks
and I just caught it in time, you can thank me later.
Send me an email telling me that you now owe me a life debt.
A la Chewbacca and Han Solo or Brady Bunch.
Pick your nerd culture.
And then as I was looking at that,
I came across a bunch of other food-based conspiracy season.
We're actually gonna talk about another one of those
in just a second.
But first, I thought this story was interesting.
I came across it a couple days ago.
And it's just one of those kind of really cool science,
the advancement of humanity,
just the way that we're going
and the way that we're exploring things.
And of course, the whole idea of it
is this amazing leap in human technology,
this great step forward.
And the journalist makes a joke in the headline.
Which again, like I said, I appreciate that.
I was a journalism major, my degrees in journalism.
And I love it when there's a little bit of like,
smarmy-ness or there's a joke in the lead
or something like that.
But it's always, it sticks out more
when it's such a serious subject.
So here's the headline.
This is on CNET.com, links below, links in the notes.
Headline is NASA Ready's probe to touch the sun
with cutting edge heat shield.
So they're gonna build this probe
that's gonna get closer to the sun
than anything humanity has ever built before.
And they've come up with this amazing heat shield.
It's gonna get within 29 million miles of the sun.
Wait, no, take that off.
So this probe is going to get
within four million miles of the sun.
Mercury is around 29 million miles away from the sun.
And that place is a hellhole.
I mean, I've always been told
if you landed anything there or just melt immediately,
it's super just like, it's just blasted by heat all the time.
It's a horrible, horrible place to be.
Not like Venus that is capable of having life on it.
But this ship will get within four million miles.
So it'll be closer than the planet Mercury.
We're gonna get all this amazing readings
and this amazing technology.
So the headline, like I said, NASA ready probe
to touch the sun with cutting edge heat shield.
And then the sub headline is it's getting hot in here.
So protect all your probes.
Now, I appreciate the pun.
I think it's definitely a generational pun.
And if you don't get it, that's that Nelly song, "Hot In Here."
It's getting hot in here.
So take off all your clothes.
I am getting so hot.
It's getting hot in here.
So protect all your probes.
It's a very clever, it's a very clever.
So Jackson Ryan, the writer, you know,
sometimes writers don't come up with their own headlines.
Sometimes it's the editor staff.
That song is so catchy.
And again, it's a generational thing.
I never, I'm not gonna tell that story.
Let's move on to the NASA story.
So this probe is gonna come
within four million miles of the sun.
It's never been visited before by manmade spacecraft.
I'd probably say by any spacecraft really, you know, generally.
So this doesn't necessarily go into how the shield works.
And even if it did, I probably wouldn't understand it.
But what's amazing is they're saying that
outside of the shield,
it's gonna be exposed by 2,500 degrees Fahrenheit.
2,500, yeah, 2,500 degrees Fahrenheit.
Just blasting this manmade piece of metal
floating through space.
On the other side of the heat shield.
So it will protect all of the gears
and all of the reading, all of the instruments
and the engine and all that stuff, 85 degrees.
That's, I mean, and the thing is this,
like if we're to this level of technology in 2018
that we can fly this close, if this works,
we can fly this close to the sun
and it's that comfortable inside.
We, this is completely breaking new bounds.
All of these things about going to these planets
in our solar system that we're gonna be more hostile
to us, if we can get this close to the sun,
we can put a base anywhere.
We can put a base on a, you know,
a one of the asteroids orbiting Saturn,
or we can put a base on the dark side of the moon.
If we can control the climate this close to the sun,
then I don't foresee us having any trouble
doing it the other way.
This probe is most likely disposable.
I don't think we're getting it back.
I think we'll probably just get the readings,
but there's just an amazing advancement
in human technology.
So that story is relatively short,
but again, I mean, I just like the idea of it.
You know, who hasn't wanted to get that close to the sun?
My little brother, he has an interesting thought experiment.
He said it to me once.
He said, "Close your eyes and picture the sun.
"As close to the sun as you can get."
No, we'll do this, we'll do this exercise now.
"Close your eyes and picture yourself
"as close to the sun as you can get."
What is going on?
And it's funny because my answer was different
than most people's answers.
I'm kind of, I really like reading stuff about the sun,
but so my little brother, he'd done this
to multiple friends of his,
and when he asked him to describe what was going on,
they all said it was too bright to look at.
And it's funny because it's your imagination.
Your imagination, technically, you can imagine anything.
If you imagine staring at the sun,
you should be able to stare at the sun
for an unlimited amount of time.
There's no actual light rays coming into your eyeballs,
but if people imagine staring at the sun,
sometimes they'll imagine it that it's too bright
to look at, even though it's simply in their imagination,
'cause our brains have been trained so much
to not look into the sun.
It's funny, one thing,
I've always been able to look into the sun.
Ever since I was a little kid, I can look right at the sun.
I don't do it for long, but other people are like,
"Oh no, don't look at the sun."
I don't know if you're not supposed to look at the sun
at all, or if you're not supposed to look at the sun
for a long amount of time,
but I look at the sun all the time.
When I did that experiment, my little brother goes,
"What's going on?"
I told him, "I could be close to the sun.
"The brightness wasn't the issue, but the noise."
Like if I really got into my imagination,
the noise was deafening.
So it was the same thing, like it's my imagination.
I should be able to control it on any level,
but the sun is just millions of,
I just imagine millions of nuclear bombs going off
every minute, just the noise that it must create
if you're close enough to the sun that you can hear it.
So a little thought experiment, it's interesting
because yeah, our imagination,
technically we should be able to be like,
"Oh yeah, I'm walking on the sun and it's totally fine."
Do, do, do, do, do, but there's a human walking on the sun.
It's one thing 'cause we can't do that,
but we have heard really loud explosions
and we have looked at really bright lights.
And if you imagine yourself looking at a bright light,
you may find yourself flinching to that,
even in your imagination, kind of holding your hands up
'cause you're looking at a light that's so bright.
Now, there's a website.
This is gonna be moving on to our next story.
And this is also food related.
This is very interesting.
So I go to this website.
I'm a celebrity gossip geek.
Like, I always read, and I don't read like
Kylie Jenner's new boyfriend bought her a purse,
but it was China Black's.
I can't believe I even know the character's names,
but no, it was China Black's brand.
So Kylie got all mad because they don't like China Black
and so on and so forth.
They don't really follow gossip like that.
I like the more kind of sinister dark Hollywood gossip.
And there's actually a lot of websites like that.
I'll link to one below.
AGC Web Pages is the website.
It kind of coalesce other Hollywood gossip
into one easy to read page.
And it's funny 'cause the page looks like it was made
in like 1992.
It's just very simple to read.
Tons of information.
So in the month of June, these two pieces of gossip popped up.
Now, the way that these, these are called blind items.
The way that this gossip is structured is that it gives you
a brief description, not really using names
of the people involved because it's gossip.
They don't want to get sued.
And then other people can try to figure out the names.
And you know, you can credit it or discredit it
as much as you want.
That's fair.
But so in June, these two blind items popped up.
And then today I woke up and on Drudge Report
was a very, very interesting article.
So I'm gonna read the first blind item here.
It was from June 8th of this year.
She didn't, she didn't go.
It was supposed to look like a murder suicide.
That had been the plan all along.
The plan that had been in place since March.
Then as she began to get more and more attention
and the claim, suddenly her schedule was too busy
and she couldn't make it.
What to do, what to do.
Improvise, do what they always do.
Make it look like all the rest they have done
but also make sure they send a message to her.
Apparently they sent her a picture with no words.
Just the picture.
I'm guessing she got the message.
In the next few weeks, we will see if she ignores the message
or continues to be brave and fight the good fight.
Then on June 24th, so about two weeks later,
here's another blind item.
This gives a little bit of clues to who it is
and I'll reveal who people think it is too.
But this was the one from June 24th.
This foreign born, illiterate celebrity
has been taking no chances.
She sleeps in a different place each night
and makes sure she is always with at least one person
if not two or three.
She might get that new guy in her life killed
if she doesn't get this thing settled once and for all.
They are still out there until they are called off.
So those two blind items specifically refer
to Asia Argento and Anthony Bourdain.
The first one is basically insinuating
that Anthony Bourdain was murdered,
that she was sent a photograph most likely of his body
before anyone knew about it.
And the reason why they've been targeted
is the Me Too movement.
And Anthony Bourdain, I've also heard conspiracy theory
before today about Anthony Bourdain
having issues with the Clintons, Bill and Hillary Clinton,
which they're really tied into the Me Too movement.
Obviously Hillary Clinton's had was best buddies
with Harvey Weinstein, Harvey Weinstein,
he was one of her top campaign donors.
Bill Clinton goes without saying,
raped and sexually assaulted multiple women.
I'm not trying to get political here,
but these are the very least he sexually harassed women.
And then there's allegations that he's raped
and sexually assaulted women as well.
There was another story that just came out last year
that Hillary Clinton's faith advisor,
kind of her minister in her campaign
was caught sexually harassing one of her female staffers.
They moved the staffer, but kept the faith-based
advisor for her.
After the campaign, he went to another group,
I think it was Chair Blue or something like that,
where he sexually harassed a third person,
he was fired on the spot,
and that's when the new story came from.
So she's been really linked to these issues
with sexual, harass your sexual assaulters.
Like I'm not saying that Trump is 100% innocent
and I'm not trying to get into that.
That's a totally different story.
But in this particular story,
these are things that have been allocated or proven.
Like the faith-based guy,
that's no one's disputing that story.
Even Hillary Clinton has come out and said,
"Yeah, I knew about it, but blah, blah, blah."
And you can, I'll see if I can find the links for that.
That was pretty much mainstream news.
So not getting political.
But so I remember reading those blind items.
And I was like, you know, it's always,
suicide is always tragic.
Generally when people commit suicide,
people are always looking for answers.
I've heard, what's interesting, so all that being said,
so Asia Argento is a big critic,
a big outspoken advocate,
I guess I should say of the Me Too movement.
Anthony Bourdain has had run-ins with the Clintons before,
but again, I was, I'd see that stuff and I was like,
"Yeah, you know, it's tragic that he killed himself,
but I don't think it's necessarily part
of this Clinton murder machine."
You, I saw these two blind items and they're like,
these people were killed to cover up a bigger crime.
So his last interview with the journalist,
he's trashing on Hillary Clinton, Bill Clinton,
calls Bill Clinton rapey,
goes on to say that Hillary had a part
in destroying women, destroying sexual assault victims.
And he just laid it out.
And he called the former president a piece of shit
entitled rapey, gropey, grabby, disgusting.
He condemned Hillary saying that she destroyed these women
when they came forth through the allegations.
Here's a quote from him.
He is a very speaking of Bill Clinton.
This is Anthony Bourdain on Bill Clinton.
He is a very charming man.
I met him, he's fucking magnetic.
As is Hillary.
When you're in the room, you think,
wow, she's really warm and nice and funny,
but the way they efficiently dismantled, destroyed,
and shamelessly discredited these women
for speaking the truth.
So basically like these victims had came forward
and both Bill and Hillary just decimated them.
And then he goes on to talk about how
when Harvey Weinstein was first caught,
when he first came out, Hillary tweeted,
basically if Hillary's tweet at the time was,
it was something, or Hillary said at the time,
it was something that was intolerable in every way.
And you know, like so many other people,
so many people who've come forward and spoken out,
this was a different side of a person who I
and many others had known in the past.
So basically Hillary saying, I didn't know anything.
This is totally something that I didn't expect.
And then Anthony Bourdain tweets that she,
that her response was shameful in its deflection
and its disingenuanness.
So he doesn't believe what she's saying at all.
He, here's the thing, she probably knew.
He, Hillary Clinton was surrounded
by secret service agents.
From 1992 till today, she always had security.
And you can't tell me that those security agents
hadn't done massive background checks
on anyone in her circle.
And you can't tell me the secret service
didn't know that was going on.
And she was completely unaware.
People will tend to make excuses for access and power.
And I believe that's what she did, honestly.
So anyways, he tweets that.
And then he gets slammed.
And this is his quote, which kind of goes
into this whole conspiracy.
"I will tell you that as frightening as that was
at times," talking about the backlash
when he called Hillary disingenuous.
"I will tell you that as frightening as that was
at times when I sat there with Asia
and she texted her sisters,
watching the Clinton apology on Weinstein
and watching Asia watching that statement,
there was a lot of anticipation.
People were really hoping she'd come out with a,
I don't know, let's just say with something different.
I immediately tweeted my disappointment,
very much shaped by what I saw around me.
And I will tell you, that was really fucking frightening."
The reaction to that.
You know, I voted for her.
So what happened behind the scenes?
So that's a very telling comment.
So Asia Argento was one of the young ladies
who first accused Harvey Weinstein of rape.
She's the daughter of Dairy Argento.
She was in Land of the Dead.
That was the first movie I've seen her in,
but I knew her as the daughter of Dairy Argento.
He's a big Italian zombie, filmmaker, zombie or movie maker.
So anyways, he's saying that he's getting ready
to watch Hillary Clinton make comments
on Harvey Weinstein.
She comes out with that, "Oh, I just didn't know.
We all don't know who people really are
in their private lives."
He responds to that.
And the reaction that he gets,
he describes as fucking frightening.
And then he says, "You know, I voted for her."
So he's a supporter of Hillary Clinton.
He doesn't have a dog in this race,
but he was frightened by the response.
He got back from her camp.
So it was interesting.
He then goes on to say that basically it was turned on him
like he was defending Harvey Weinstein
or he was accusing her of being in league
and all this sort of stuff.
And he goes in the interview.
He totally calls out Jared Kushner as a snitch
and basically says that he'll never
be able to keep his mouth shut about any sort of crimes he's
committed with the Trumps or the collusion.
So again, this isn't a political hack job.
You can tell he's not really happy with anything.
And then he goes on to say that his dream is to watch
Harvey Weinstein have a stroke and then fall into a bathtub.
And as he's drowning, trying to figure out which
of his friends to call.
And he realized he doesn't have any friends
and so on and so forth.
So very angry because his girlfriend-- he was dating
Asia Argento.
His girlfriend had to go through all this.
Then it was all brought back up into the public eye.
So did the Clintons or somebody else
involved with the cover up of the Me Too movement
have Anthony Bourdain killed?
Was he really that big of a critic
of this group of men and women who have protected sexual
assaulters in Hollywood and around the world?
[SIGHS]
You know, the sad fact is that he's either way he's dead.
So there's no changing that.
Obviously the best version-- I mean,
I've watched this show once or twice.
I can't-- he was kind of just a figure that I knew of.
The tragic thing is that he's passed away now.
The noble story.
The story-- he's dead.
We can't change that.
So the story that makes everything makes sense.
The story that gives us some sort of hope
is the story that he was murdered.
And I think that's sometimes what conspiracies do.
You can get the facts together, and you can connect one, two,
three, four, and you go, OK, I don't have five and six,
but I can assume what seven and eight are going to be based
on the pattern before that.
So I don't think that he killed himself.
I think that he was murdered by operatives,
and Asia Argento is on the run now
because she'll be next.
That story is nice because it doesn't involve a depressed
and lonely man taking his own life.
Do I think it's possible that he was killed?
It's possible.
Technically anything's possible.
Unfortunately, I don't necessarily think it's likely.
And I think that's the same thing.
It's funny, as I was doing this episode,
I was like, I probably won't do the Chester Bennington.
I hate that I don't remember his name,
but the Chester and the Chris Cornell story,
because I think it's kind of the same thing.
You want to believe that these young men, these young people,
didn't warrant just at the end of their no pun intended rope
and took their own life because they were just so depressed
and so distraught, or just had some sort of chemical imbalance,
or just had a day that was off and they couldn't
get it together.
It's better to believe that these were soldiers.
These were martyrs for a greater fight
against a shadowy conspiracy.
But is it likely?
No.
I think it's an interesting article.
I think it's an interesting theory.
But I think when we look at those conspiracy theories
like this, we minimize talking about suicide in and of itself.
So I could talk about this conspiracy theory
and say, yes, he didn't kill himself.
This is an ongoing war between the forces of light
and the forces of dark and so on and so forth.
But really, the discussion we need to have is no more suicides.
How can we as a society and we as individuals
not promote that, not hide it, to talk about it as an actual thing?
Again, there's always a lot of options out there.
If you are having those thoughts, there's always options out there.
Talk to a friend.
Talk to a stranger if you have to.
There's always the suicide prevention hotline 1-800-273-8255.
They even have an online chat option.
I'll put that in the show notes.
So I think that's an important--
I think that's honestly more important than the conspiracy
itself.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe it will come out that he was actually
killed by this shadowy conspiracy and Aja Argento is next.
Or maybe it's something people made up to make sense of the world
because they knew him.
And it's easier to believe that your friend or your role
model or your television show host that you watched every week
and you bought all of his shows on DVD
and he was your friend.
He was your virtual friend.
It's easier to believe that he was murdered
than that that man took his life just like it's hard
to imagine any of your friends or family taking their lives.
And so a little bit of a depressing ending,
but don't let it be because there's always hope.
There's always hope.
And we can always reach out to the people who need our help.
And if you need someone's help, there's
always going to be someone out there for you.
It may not feel like it, but it could just
be someone you meet online.
It doesn't have to be this amazing thing.
It's going to be something that you never even
really know their real name.
You're just talking to them.
Reach out.
And here's another reason why.
This is what I always say.
Think of your favorite television show,
your favorite movie series.
Whenever you're really depressed and you're--
I mean, you're not just having the occasional thought
about suicide.
You're planning it out.
I've run into people like this online.
They're ready to go.
I'll ask, what's your favorite television show?
The guy said, it's always Sunday in Philadelphia.
And I said, you know what?
Why don't you just wait until the run of the show is over?
Wait till the show's canceled or they quit making episodes.
Because that's your favorite show.
And that's one of my favorite shows, too.
I've watched it multiple times, the whole season through.
You're going to miss all those episodes if you kill yourself.
And sometimes little things can have big meanings.
Someone is a huge Star Wars fan.
I can't imagine why nowadays.
Let's say someone is a huge Avengers fan.
And they're just ready to indents.
They say, well, give it a couple-- give it two more movies.
Let's buy some time.
Let's watch those movies.
We'll talk about them.
Oh, OK.
Doesn't work for everybody.
But when you throw out general stuff like, oh,
you have so much to live for, people go, no, not really.
Tomorrow, you know, just be happy.
That doesn't work.
On a side note, they actually say, if you're being mugged
or someone has a gun on you, don't say.
I have a kid and a wife at home.
This is actually old police advice.
If someone ever pulls a gun on you,
don't talk about your family.
Because it's possible that that person doesn't
have any sort of family connection,
or you may remind them of their crappy family,
their crappy childhood.
I have a kid at home.
And that may actually make them matter.
So if they had a horrible family life,
or they don't have kids, or they're in a horrible place,
and they have a gun on someone who they perceive
has a better life than them, don't say anything.
You really should not try to engage
with a armed criminal at all.
My wallet, here's my wallet.
Oh no, I have a wife and kids at home.
That person may go, you know, I don't have a home.
I'm living in an alley.
Pop!
Yeah.
So anyways, that's kind of a bit of a tangent.
But hopefully that saves your life too.
Also, another piece of advice, never get in the car.
Anyone ever wants you to get in the car?
They have a gun on you, they have a bazooka on you,
they have a flamethrower?
Don't get in the car, because guess what?
Well, gunner probably, if they, right there,
they'll shoot you or set you on fire,
and you're in the middle of a neighborhood.
Or people will know you're walking along that trail,
or whatever, and they'll be able to get you.
If you're shot in a neighborhood,
you'll start to bleed out, and someone will come out.
If you get in that car,
you're going to someone's torture dungeon.
Don't ever get in the car.
Take the bullet, take the flamethrower,
take the bucket of acid in your face,
because trust me, it's going to get 10 times worse
if you get in that car.
I guess that's going to do it
for this episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
You got a little bit of life advice in the ending.
I think the Anthony Bourdain conspiracy
is really interesting.
Obviously, I'm going to keep following it
because there's a lot of info on it.
And if anything changes, I'll let you guys know.
But right now, I think we just need to think about
his life, his legacy, and how we can prevent
that from happening with other people again.
I think that's kind of the more important story
than the conspiracy theory.
So I hope you guys had a great time listening.
Dead Rabbit Radio is our website.
We have the fastest growing podcast in Wasco County.
It's pretty good.
It's a pretty big size county up in Hood River.
@jasonocarpenter is my Twitter.
We have our email address, that's deadrabbitradio@gmail.com.
We now have a Facebook that is facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
And that is going to be it for tonight.
Actually, I think we did a pretty good job
recording the afternoon.
We got our kind of depressing story out of the way.
I think most of the stories are going to be more lively
for the rest of the week.
They're all going to have a food.
Every day, we're going to talk about a new food conspiracy
building up to one of the most bizarre
and hard to find conspiracies that I've spent
time looking for in the past 30 days.
I found some stuff on hard stuff,
but I've really been looking out this conspiracy theory.
I don't want to build it up too much,
but on Friday, we are going to touch one
of the main conspiracy theories on our conspiracy theory list.
It is related to food.
So get your forks, get your knives,
watch your calories, and come back tomorrow
for another episode of Dead Rappity.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]