Even more demonic rap conspiracy news, and apparently Michigan can be the last place you'll ever be today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, this is Jason Carpenter for Dead Rabbit Radio on back.
It's Monday the 25th, it's not Monday the 25th, it's June 25th.
The weather is beautiful, so I don't need any fans, that's always good.
I'm always happy about that.
Hope you guys had a good weekend, I had a great weekend, it was actually a lot of fun.
But here I am back looking at the most ridiculous news possible to have an entertaining podcast.
And you know, sometimes it's easier than others, sometimes I find some great topics, and other times it's a little rough.
I did though, before we get started, I think I have stumbled upon the secret to evolution.
I think that, I can't really phrase it correctly, but I think I've stumbled upon something that could change everything.
It's almost like a glitch in the matrix, and that kind of leads into another story we're going to do.
So I was thinking, and it's kind of weird, so we hunt, let's take deer for example.
We hunt deer, because they're first pretty, and they have like big antlers.
And what if deer started to be ugly? What if they started to evolve to be like modeled fur, and busted like their antlers look all sucky and janky?
People would be like, "Yeah, I'm not hunting them anymore."
What would happen is you would go to shoot a deer, and you'd look at its fur, and it would be all disgusting, it would look like a hobo deer.
And you'd be like, "No, I'm not taking the shot. I'm not what am I going to do with that?"
And its antlers all busted up.
And so that deer would go home, and theoretically have more deer babies.
And those babies would be all like busted up.
And over time, the big beautiful deer would get shot, and I'd put their head on my wall, but the one that looked like it was all cracked out,
I wouldn't shoot, and it could have more babies over time.
Now, I know what you're saying. Jason, that's really smart, but female deers wouldn't date a male deer or a buck.
I think it's the scientific term, does and bucks.
A doe would not date a buck if he looked like he was a meth addict.
And that is true. However, I think that they would if those were the only ones alive.
And I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
And so, I'm not eating like my species. I'm going to taste gross.
I'm going to start to evolve, so I'm gross. Groser.
So when a wolf bites me, he's like, "Ugh!"
And then runs away, and then I live to have other babies.
So you can have it both ways. You can have a busted up looking deer that no one wants to hunt,
or a beautiful deer that tastes disgusting, and then they wouldn't have to worry about natural predators.
I don't know if that either disproved evolution, why animals taste so good,
or actually proved that we can make evolution better. That's one of the two.
I was thinking about that the other day. I told my friend she didn't get it,
but she did have a headache, so I'm going to chalk it up.
Not to any faults in the argument itself, but the fact that she had a headache.
Because we were sitting in a really hot theater for a while.
Okay, there was more to the story than that, but anyway, so she had a headache.
So, speaking of glitches in the matrix, which kind of is evolution.
So there is, like I said, I like to cover conspiracy theories that are fairly obscure.
There are the classics, the ones that I like. I like Bermuda Triangle.
I really like disappearing when conspiracy theories or paranormal events, stuff that disappears.
Ghost stories are okay if they're out of the ordinary.
Like I want to do one on ghosts that have murdered people. I find that fascinating.
Just ghost sightings. I don't find necessarily that fascinating.
But when ghosts murder people, there's been a few cases where that may have happened.
But overall, I like to do conspiracy theories or paranormal events that people don't know about.
And one of them is, we did Dublin, Wisconsin.
Another one is Michigan, Blue Hell.
So again, I saw it. They have this huge image, a graphic of conspiracy theories.
And we talked about this before. It's like an iceberg.
So like, the most common ones are at the top as you go farther down, they get more and more obscure.
Some of them are made up, obviously. Some of them, I mean, and when I say made up, a lot of them are made up.
They're not real. They didn't really happen. But people think they did.
There's ones at the bottom are stuff that people just spout it off like, let's put three words together and see, you know, like, John Tash Nipples.
And people will be like, oh man, what's John Tash Nipples? I got to look that.
And it's just, they just threw random words together.
Michigan, Blue Hell. It may be one of those, but it's actually, because I've Googled a bunch of them to see if there's any credence to them.
And some of them, they have, you know, a couple pages dedicated to it. It's still being nonsense.
But Michigan, Blue Hell, I find fascinating.
So first off, what the term Blue Hell is, it's a video game term.
It's the Skybox. So when you're playing a game, and it looks like it's a 3D game where you're walking through, let's say you're playing Halo, whatever,
and you're kind of walking through the valley and there's mountains on either side, you can clip through the mountains.
So you can basically move through the mountains, through some sort of glitch in the game,
and then you pass through what you thought was a 3D object, but it's actually just like a graphic on either side of you.
Now you're in what's called Blue Hell. It's basically like the Skybox.
It's the parameters of the game. So now you're outside of where the developers wanted you to be, and you're kind of just in this void.
It tends to be blue, because what happens is they paint the sky blue and they just basically program a big blue box,
and then they put the assets inside of it, and you're supposed to walk that path.
But most games, you can glitch out if you're persistent enough.
So the idea behind Michigan Blue Hell...
Sorry, I'm a little parched.
The idea behind Michigan Blue Hell is there is a place in Michigan, in an abandoned building,
that you can clip out of our reality.
Now there's the theory that we are living in a simulation, that everything we see is actually kind of like a matrix type simulation.
It's being programmed on the fly, and that's why things don't make sense when you look at a macro level and a micro level.
That's why the universe seems impossibly far.
It's just constantly rendering.
There's nothing... Once we start going out there, things will appear, but since we're here, nothing's ever showing there,
because we haven't really gone there yet.
But anyways, that's one of the theories.
The other theory is that the world is just how we see it.
But the Michigan Blue Hell works for either one, so basically you can fall out of our reality.
This is the main thing.
And you end up in basically the skybox.
It does fit more with the simulation theory, but...
However, so is that likely?
Probably not.
I do always find it fascinating.
I find as much as creepy as I find caves and forests, and I find both of those very creepy.
There's also something very creepy about buildings.
You have a... You build a skyscraper, you build a... Even a small...
You build like a three-story building with ten offices, and knowing that some of those offices are just empty
and like the sun rising and the sun setting and just it being...
That's creepy too.
I think I find emptiness creepy, but I also find forests full of animals creepy.
No, I find forest full of animals dangerous, but an empty forest is terrifying.
So a building full of people, I'd be like, "I don't have any problem with these people."
But being in an office complex by myself, being in a library by myself, that's really, really spooky.
So, yeah, the idea that you can just... There's a random building in Michigan that you can walk into
and just kind of fall out of our reality by no... You know, you didn't mean to do it.
You know, there's talk that Michigan Blue Hell is related to the elevator game,
which is something we may go over in another episode, but we won't.
I'll just tell you right now. Elevator game, you can Google it, I'll link it, whatever.
It's a game where if you hit the... If you go in on elevator and hit the buttons in the right order,
you can end up in an alternate reality. Like, you step off the elevator and you're in this alternate reality.
They did a short film of version of it, I think, in VHS 2 or 3 or whatever.
But anyway, so that's the same thing. It's basically a way to leave our reality,
which, again, is another conspiracy theory or paranormal event that I find fascinating.
I'm going to do an episode. I'm going to do a story on a couple of people who have supposedly come from their realities to ours.
It also kind of plays a Mandel effect.
Anyways, where I'm going with this is that apparently also in Michigan there is a story about a native...
Okay, I'm going to... Okay, no, no, no.
There apparently there is a story in Michigan that in their Native American history,
they had a evil snake god there and they actually trapped him in this Michigan blue hell area.
So it's one of those stories that one may have preceded the other.
Either there was the old legend about the evil snake god that was causing trouble in the Michigan area
and was trapped into this void and then someone read that story and they said,
"Oh, that's a cool idea, but let me modernize it and call it Michigan blue hell."
There's the other possibility that the Michigan blue hell story was made up first
and then someone went back and made up a story about the tribes because I really don't know.
I'm just reading this on the internet.
The most fascinating answer, though, is that they're both true
and that is that there was a giant snake god thrown into a void in Michigan.
There's a lot of people sitting on it and they're still like a frayed area of reality
where you can walk into your office building and fall out of the skybox.
I mean, obviously two of those are far more likely than the third one,
but again, I think the third one is interesting.
I think that's kind of an interesting concept and it plays into my whole office buildings are creepy
if there's nobody in them.
Abandoned anything is creepy because you think,
"Why did people leave this whenever I read books or stories about like, you know,
like Mary Celeste or whatever where people go on to a boat and like it's totally empty
and you can't use anything but you're imagining."
You know what? Actually, let me do a side story right here because this kind of plays into it.
There's actually a story I was reading about the other day.
The Sarah Jo. The Sarah Jo was a little boat back in the 1970s.
Okay, 1979. I'm not, I don't have a photographic memory.
I got the article pulled up here.
I'm sure you guys know how brilliant I am with me knowing, never mind, that joke failed.
So in 1979, these five dudes hopped on a fishing boat off of Hawaii and they said,
"I'm going to go fishing." And a huge storm came.
There's like 40 foot swells and people are like,
"Oh no, that boat totally like sucks. It wasn't built for any sort of inclement weather."
So of course, the boat goes missing.
They're like, send, they're like, people are walking along the beach looking for them.
They can't go out to the ocean to find them.
It's storms too big. They search for them for weeks and weeks and weeks and weeks and weeks.
They never found them.
Now, fast forward about, what was it, 10 years, 10 years later,
there are these nerds from Hawaii doing some sort of science thing.
They're from the Western Pacific.
This is, this totally sounds like a bunch of nerds hang out here.
Western Pacific for the National Marine Fishery Service.
That sounds, that sounds pretty nerdy.
But anyways, so they're walking along this island and they find the boat.
Oh, I should have said the boat was called the Sarah Jo.
I don't think I said that in the beginning.
So anyway, they're walking along this beach.
They find this little uninhabited island and it has like just like shrubs on it.
Maybe some trees. I'm looking off in the distance here.
They find this boat. They find the Sarah Jo.
And they're like, oh, oh wait, no, they didn't know.
They didn't know about the boat. They're from something related.
But anyways, they see the boat and they're like, oh, it's from Hawaii,
according to its license plate or whatever is on a boat.
And then they saw a grave and the grave had like a mandible.
And it had a piece of paper and a little piece of tinfoil and a piece of paper
and a little piece of tinfoil, a piece of paper, a little piece of tinfoil.
And so they reported the findings and investigators came out to the island
and there was five people on the boat.
And the jawbone belonged to one of the guys.
So the question to me is, you know, well not just to me.
Everyone was wondering where did the other four people go?
Did they make it onto the island and die and like just kind of float away?
Were they killed during the initial storm and this guy was in the boat by himself
for a month or two?
And you know, it was floating around for 10 years, as far as they know,
because what happened was a previous team came onto the island before
and didn't record that there was a boat there.
So it's just weird and you think about like where, what happened to the other four?
The most likely thing is that they got thrown off the boat
and this dude was just floating on the boat for whatever reason.
He didn't get thrown off the boat and he crash landed.
I think it's possible that all five of them crashed on the island
and one of them died, who they buried.
And then the other four just went off and had like some jungle adventures
and just like, you know, died off one by one.
I would hate to die of old age in a cave, but if I was on an island
and there was like fruits and stuff, I wouldn't mind dying of old age on an island,
even a deserted island.
You know, as much as I hate abandoned stuff, I think it's different being abandoned on an island
because it's like half the worst stuff on an island is in the ocean.
It can't really get you.
But yeah, you know, and that always, whenever I think about people getting trapped on an island
or in a cave, all those miners got trapped in that cave,
you think, how long would you have to be trapped on an island
with three other guys before you started being gay with them?
Like, I think that's the, that is a legitimate question.
Like, at what point do you say, we're gonna be, we're gonna start having sex with each other?
Like, the answer is not never.
Whatever the answer is, it's not never.
You could say, well, and here's, you know you're not getting rescued.
Like, maybe if you were only on an island for a week,
it's not like I'm gonna start hitting on you within a week.
And then like a rescue plane shows up.
But you know at a certain point you're not getting rescued.
It's been two years.
You're not getting rescued.
You're gonna start having gay sex.
That's just, you can't, people do it in prison?
There's consensual gay sex in prison?
I don't think it would be that long.
I'm, again, I'm saying don't go on a trip with me
because the car might break down and we have to wait for AAA.
I'm not saying that.
But I think any man would, you're not gonna say,
"Oh, I'm never gonna have sex again for the rest of my life."
Think about it, mull it over, consider that.
And we're gonna move on to this last story, which I want to talk about quickly
because I don't want these episodes to be too long.
And so our friend from a couple episodes back
is continuing his conspiracy theory about XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX
and we're gonna talk about the story of the murder of a man
who was killed by a black man.
He was a black man.
I can also picture this 16 year old kid
wearing his mom's
like big black trench coat.
Why would the mom have a trench coat?
Basically, he's dressed
I just imagine him in clothes that are way too big
for his skinny little body
with a candle, a mirror
and something scribbled with lipstick
on his hand as he's
evoking the spirit.
Then he just imagines stuff.
I do not think that the grand architect
of hell
and Pontiff of hell is coming to this kid
so he can post on 4chan
of all places
that black dudes shot a rapper
in Florida.
This is ridiculous.
However, I will give him credit.
He's not asking for money right now
which is a lot different than a lot of the conspiracies
we do cover.
But this is ridiculous.
I do not think
that anything that this guy is saying
is legit.
I think that this guy is going to grow
into a real conspiracy.
That is weird.
That shows what's wrong
with the conspiracy theory community.
This is going to be just as legitimized
as
today it was just revealed that the NSA
has concrete
high rises in cities
where they funnel all their information
to process.
That is going to be that is a legitimate
conspiracy. That is a legitimate
conspiracy.
That is going to be what is going on
and right next to it is going to be
X was killed by Balbarath.
Ridiculous.
Well, I think that is going to be it
for tonight's episode.
I don't think we ran. No, no, we did pretty good
on time.
I want to thank everyone for downloading the episodes.
We are actually exponentially getting bigger.
The show is just getting more and more downloads
each and every day.
I really appreciate that.
I'm going to be doing a podcast
on the podcast.
I'm going to be doing a podcast on the podcast
I'm going to be doing a podcast on the podcast.
That's the main thing for me.
My computer can't really handle video processing right now,
so that's why we're not doing that.
But again, I love podcasting.
I think it's great.
I listen to it while I'm out walking and so on and so forth.
So, deadrabbitradio.com
I mean, sorry, deadrabbitradio@gmail.com
if you want to get ahold of me.
My Twitter handle is @symbol.
I don't know.
Jason O. Carpenter if you want to hit me up on Twitter.
That'd be great.
Thanks for all your support.
I'm having a ton of fun doing this.
I hope to see you tomorrow.
I still don't have a sign-off.
I'm afraid that my sign-off is going to become.
But we are through here today.
I will be back tomorrow with some brand new
crazy weird news out of this crazy weird world.
Have a great day.
[Music]