When a young man takes his dog for a walk through the forest, he thinks it's just going to be another great way to start the day.
But when he hears a voice calling out from behind the trees, he realizes that this day will be anything but ordinary.
And then we're going to meet two resident care workers, two young women who spend their nights taking care of those who cannot take care of themselves.
But when a mysterious event strikes the home that they're working in, we are forced to ask the question, are aliens from another world targeting the disabled?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenterner, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too, I hope you guys are having tons of fun.
We're getting ready for spooky month central October.
Will I do anything different? I always go eat this year, I want to review a movie each episode or this year is going to be a ghost.
This show is so hard to do, this show is so hard to put together. It's so hard planning anything, but I'd love to do spooktobular spectacular something like...
Hopefully something I can pronounce. We'll figure it out.
But someone who never needs to figure stuff out, someone who always has all the life mysteries solved, walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now, give it up for our newest Patreon supporter, Michael Knight.
Yeah, woohoo, come on in, come on in, Michael Knight walking into Dead Rabbit Command.
Michael, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode, if you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it, I do.
Just help spread the word about this show that really, really helps out a lot.
You can even help us, right now a big thing we're trying to do is to fill out the Dead Rabbit Radio wiki that Germ started.
Thanks for that Germ, so get the word out about the show, help us with the Wikipedia page, or support the Patreon, all of that stuff totally helps.
Michael Knight, he's walking in with his cool sunglasses.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jollopy. We're trading in Kit the Talking Car for this hunk of junk, for this hunk of junk, this jitty jitty bang bang car.
Michael, we're leaving Dead Rabbit Command Drive us all the way out to a forest.
Bang bang!
We're headed back to September 12th, 2022. That's very, very recent story, right? What is that, just a couple weeks ago?
I found this story posted online, we don't have a location of it, it's just a small, I imagine it's an area like so many areas are.
You have suburban housing and then you have a nearby green belt, a nearby forest that has been untouched by the developers so far.
We're about to meet a guy, we don't have his real name, we're gonna call him Charles.
And Charles has this routine. Before he goes to work, he likes to take his dog, we're gonna call the dog Rufus, he likes to take his dog on a nice little walk, right?
That's actually Charles' painting, the dog's quite silent. He takes his dog for a walk around 5.45 in the morning so he can get it done, he can get it out of the way so he can go to work.
He gets the exercise for the puppy and then you gotta go do your own thing. He's a professional dog walker, he thinks his dog's super nerdy.
He's like, "The dogs I walk are cool, Rufus, you're not cool enough to hang out with them so I walk you all alone through the forest."
He says, you know, for the past few months it's been nice 'cause the sun's been up at 5.45 and he would take his dog on this walk, they would take him down a trail through this nearby wooded area.
But recently it's been getting darker, right? Everything's kind of changing.
So at 5.45, even though it's always been the same time, it's just a little darker outside than he's used to, that he's comfortable with.
Now like he said, Charles likes to take the dog for a walk before he goes to work so he can get the energy.
The dogs need walking, right? It's a good time to do it.
He gets him up moving, gets some energy burnt out on the dog, they're going for this little jaunt through the woods.
The reason why he specifically chose the woods is because Charles also likes to get stoned before work.
So hopefully he doesn't do anything more serious than a professional dog walker.
He's like, smoking a weed, he's like, "Oh, now it's time to go to my job, professional construction worker."
He likes to get stoned before work and he does it in the woods so nobody can see him.
So he's walking, when now it sounds a little less altruistic that he's taking his dog for a walk.
The dog's mostly just a cover story. If he gets caught, he's like, "What? No!"
The dog was smoking the joint. It wasn't me, I swear, officer.
He takes his dog on a walk through the forest.
Yeah, that's the good stuff. Mmm, yummy, yummy, yummy.
We love it all. He's super loud. He comes to the least complimenting how strong his weed is.
He's like, "Charles, we can hear you. You're not being discreet at all.
You're making orgasmic moaning sounds and you're naming the brand of your weed. Ah, yes, Cherryberry.
The best. He's smoking this weed in the middle of the forest walking his dog."
Now, to say, I'm making him turn out to be a huge stoner.
I have to say, if you're waking up, the first thing you're doing is smoking weed.
That's the definition of a stoner. But he says he just smoked a little, right?
Which is obviously like a little to me would be like a puff.
There we go. That's the good stuff.
But to a professional stoner, they're like, "Why don't we smoke three joints this morning?"
That's barely getting me high. So we don't know what it means when he said he smoked a little bit.
But he smoked some weed, smoked some Mary Jane, and then he continues on his walk.
And he's getting ready to exit the woods when from behind the nearby tree, he hears a voice.
"Hey, Rufus. Come here, buddy."
Charles kind of stops when he hears this, right? He looks over.
He can't see anything with the trees, right? He doesn't see anyone.
But he clearly heard someone say, "Hey, Rufus. Come here, buddy."
And then the sound of someone tapping their knee like you would when you were calling over a dog.
"Hey, Rufus. Come here, buddy."
Now he's stoned, right? I mean, according to me, he probably just smoked a little.
But you know what? He's inebriated on some sort of drug. It's psychoactive.
And you could just write it off, right? Hallucination. He's smoking weed in the forest at 545.
It's getting darker. He's not comfortable in the dark. He's definitely a little more paranoid.
What's interesting is he noticed when he heard it, he looked over and he wasn't for sure that he heard it.
But he noticed that Rufus was also now looking in this direction.
Like, they both turned and they were looking from where the sound came from.
So now he realized, it's not just the hallucination. My dog's looking over there as well.
And I heard someone say, "Hey, Rufus. Come here, buddy."
I just couldn't believe that that would be coming from there.
But when my dog turned and looked at the same time I did, like, what could that possibly be?
And then as he's staring out into the trees, trying to figure out what could possibly be going on,
he hears, "Come here, Rufus. Come on, boy. Come here."
Charles is standing there, peering into the darkened trees.
Can't see anything.
But what he realized was the energy was kind of changing, and the sense that Rufus, who originally turned and looked when it heard the voice,
is now not in a curious mood.
It's not tugging at the leash. It's not trying to check out what's over there. It's not angry.
It's not trying to figure out what's over there.
Rufus is in a protective state, as Charles described it.
Rufus senses danger and wants to protect the leader of his tribe.
Rufus wants to get out of there.
And so Charles puts on his headphones and hurries out of the woods.
Now, they were almost out, right? He was getting ready to exit the walk.
So it's just a short walk for him to end it. But they do get out of the tree line and they hurry home.
It's an interesting story. This is one of those stories where it could totally be made up.
I've been fooled before this stuff happens.
It's interesting, though, the element of them putting in the headphones, which sounds counterintuitive, right?
You spoke before as someone's calling your dog.
You think you might be in some sort of danger or you put in headphones to walk away.
That is this element that makes the story really believable.
Because people do stuff like that. When they're in a threatening situation, they will block off their senses.
It's the same thing when you're in a room and you think there's a monster in the room and you close your eyes.
Or you cover yourself with your blanket. And you're like, Jason, that's what eight-year-olds do. It's a human thing.
It really is a human thing. If I close my eyes, it'll go away.
If I stop listening for the voice, I won't be able to hear it.
Now, I think a rational thing would be to have my ears working in case someone's up running up behind me.
But Charles goes, "I don't want to hear anything, so I'm going to plug my ears and we're going to get out of there."
That's a really interesting little tidbit that makes me think the story's authentic.
And again, when you read it, when you're looking at it, when he's getting stoned and hearing voices,
I would have totally just written the story off. It's interesting, but I would have written it off and go, "Well, he's stoned."
So, of course, he's hearing stuff.
But the idea that his dog was reacting to it as well is what makes me think there could be something there.
And then what would it be? How did this thing know his dog's name?
Because obviously there's two options. One, it's a real human who was trying to lure.
There's that word again. I had to use that word a couple times earlier on the podcast.
There's the possibility that it was a real person trying...
There's the possibility that there was a real person trying to lure Charles into the woods for some sort of nefarious reason.
And then there's the other possibility that it was some sort of creature or cryptid or spirit or ghost,
also trying to bring him into the woods for some sort of nefarious reason,
because they want to hold a birthday party for you, right? It's always some sort of horrible thing.
But what was it? What could it have been? It's funny, I'm going to segue to another story here real quick.
It's related... Michael Knight, let's go ahead and actually drive your car. The Knight Rider.
Was that the name of the car? It was Kit. Drive us out all the way to somewhere in Oregon.
I heard this story a while back from my good friends, Sabine, who she doesn't believe.
She is one of those hippie-dippy girls that is all spiritual, she does all that goofy stuff.
She also is super pragmatic, right? We'll be watching a movie. We saw The Northman, which was all about Norse mythology.
Odin is a character in it, and there's constantly this magic being performed, these weird miracles.
And I saw it as a paranormal movie, and she saw it as like, "Oh no, those were a bunch of coincidences."
Like, none of that was paranormal. When that woman was tied up with another man's intestines, that was just somebody did that.
It wasn't some sort of paranormal act, and I was like, "What?" She's super pragmatic.
She's the type of person that could watch a teacup...
She's the type of person who could witness a teacup floating across the room, and 100% believe there was a valid answer for that, even if you ruled out every possible valid answer.
It's weird to be f-
[door opens]
[door closes]
Somewhere in some gray alien scientific laboratory
are notes taken that night.
Biological samples, cataloged and put away,
that was taken from that residence on that particular night.
Surveys and scans and experiments that these otherworldly beings
perpetrated the night these young women lost seven hours.
And while that thought is terrifying,
we have to ask the question,
how many times did they visit that care home?
Are they still visiting it now?
Are they doing this in such locations all over the world?
Attacking those who are the most helpless, attacking those who cannot cry out for help.
[music]