your soulmate may be living in Brazil, although she's currently a headless horse.
And then we take a look at what happens when a love of horror movies collides with real life
today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carvener. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. So we got some cool
stuff to cover today, so we're just gonna go ahead and slide right into this. First off,
we're going to... So first off, we're taking a trip to Brazil. Sunny, sunny Brazil. Home of the
Brazil nut and was featured in a documentary called Brazil about an office worker who becomes an
angel. I don't know, never saw the movie, just saw the cover. But anyways, that's all I know about
Brazil. And they have a UFO problem. We've documented that in other episodes, but in this episode
we're going to Brazil specifically to meet Mula Sem Cabaca. Mula Sem Cabaca. Fluent in Spanish.
Oh wait, no, is that Portuguese? Which one's the Portuguese country? I think that's Brazil.
Anyways, and Portugal. But, or in English, the headless mule. Dun, dun, dun. Now, generally
animals that have their heads chopped off aren't threatening because they're dead. But this one is,
and you're thinking, oh okay, it's just going to be a headless horse running through the fields
of Brazil. But don't jump to conclusions because this is far, far more than just your average
headless horse. There's three types of headless horses. There's ones that are just dead in some
sort of slaughterhouse. Those are the sad ones. There are ghost headless horses, which those aren't
very interesting because again, they're just a horse. I guess it's more interesting than a
dead headless, I don't know why I keep calling it a headless horse actually. It's a headless mule,
which is when a horse and a donkey have sex and oddly enough, a mule can't have offspring itself.
I learned that from an Isaac Osmob novel. The headless mule, not horse, headless mule is this
creature that lives in Brazil. But it's more, it's so much more, it's so much more than that.
This is its origin story. Apparently there's a lot of them because they had a serious problem
with this in Brazil at some point. Back in the past, there was a beautiful young woman who fell
in love with a priest, which you're not supposed to do that. Rule number one, never fall in love.
But she didn't listen to rule number one. She fell in love with a priest and she actually is able to
use her witchy woman powers to seduce this man of the cloth and they have sex. And all of a sudden,
she's like, "Oh no, I did something totally wrong." What's funny is that so her, what happens is she
runs out into the forest or the jungle, whatever's down there, or both, I'm not entirely for sure,
but she runs off into the foliage of Brazil and her body, like her bones, start breaking and her
legs grow long and she's like, "Oh, that's not good." And then her arms are getting long too and her
fingers, her perfectly manicured fingers are turning into gnarly horse hooves and she's like,
"I thought I was a mule, gnarly mule hooves." She's like, "That's better." And she realizes she's
not running now, she's galloping, her clothes are ripping off, her body, she's swelling up,
her bones are getting thicker. She's like, "Uh, this is not the normal, this isn't that time of the
month. I don't normally don't bloat around now." And she realizes that's her voice, she's nane,
because she's turning into a mule and then her head falls off and flames shoot out of the stump
of where her head used to be and she gallops off into the night air. Oh, and for people who have
a weird fetish, also a tail pops out of her butthole. So I mean, I don't know if you're into that
thing, if I don't know if there's any bronies going on, but if there are, you have a beautiful maiden
who's turned into a mule, which to me, the word mule is far less sexy than the word horse. I guess
it's kind of the same thing, but if someone was like, "Hey man, I'm dating someone," I'm like, "Really?"
They're like, "Yeah, but she kind of looks like a horse." I'd be like, "Ugh." But if that same person
says, "I'm dating someone," I go, "Really?" And they're like, "Yeah, she kind of looks like a mule."
I'm going to be like, "That's, you break up with her right now. You can date the horse chick, date the
horse chick." But if she looks like a mule, that's a stage too far. Does she look like a headless
mule or are there flames shooting out of her neck? He looks down to the floor, he's like, "No." And I'm
like, "Yeah, you just got to break up with her." So anyways, she turns into this headless mule,
but for all intents and purposes, it's a horse. It's a galloping thing. But what I find funny
about that whole story is nothing happens to the priest. The priest who made an oath to God
to never have sex, to take a vow of celibacy, bangs this chick and then she jumps out of bed
and starts transforming it into this hell beast. He just goes back to like, reading the Bible.
He's like, "Oh yeah, I forgot, headless mule. Shouldn't have done that." There's a bunch of headless
mules running around his yard. He's like, "I should probably stop banging all those peasant girls."
So this mule, this flaming headless mule is running around. Despite its lack of a head,
it makes a lot of noise. It nays really loudly and like totally like, scares you. A lot of times,
it also moan like a woman is the description given. I'm like, "Okay, that's oddly sexual."
But so it can both nay really loudly. It can moan like a woman. And I keep saying loudly because
one of its key characteristics is how loud it is. It's almost deafening. You can hear it from miles
away. When it's getting closer to you, it's getting louder and louder and louder. That sounds
sound normally words. Its horseshoes themselves are made of like iron and they're very loud. It
sounds like giant drums are just bump bump bump bump bump bump bump bump bump bump bump bump bump
as it's running towards you. So there's almost no way you don't know this thing's coming at you.
But there are people out there who don't want to avoid this hellish creature because it will kill
you. It can stop you to death and get mad. It can shoot flames out of its neck at you, set you on
fire. But in where its mouth should be is a bridle. There's like a red hot metal bridle.
Bridal's a little thing that goes in the horse's mouth. In this case, a mule's mouth. So this legend
is akin to a werewolf where during the day she is a normal woman but at night transforms into an
extremely loud beast who can trample you to death. I.e. just like she's your wife. And she will destroy
anything in its path. This horse is just a ramp. This mule is just a rampaging beast will destroy
anything in its path. And the one thing that attracts it more than anything is shiny things.
So if you have like a little gold nugget on your mouth, I don't know why you do that. You just
spit in gold nuggets everywhere. It'll come after you. But let's say you don't have any metal on
you, anything shiny. Your fingernails and teeth are shiny enough. If it sees those, it'll come
towards you and try to trample you to death. You have to lay down on the ground face first,
cover up your pearly whites, cover up your fingernails. You'll just look like a lump
in dirt and the horse will walk past you. Now that's the advice they give you. I'm a little
iffy on it because one, laying down in front of a demonic mule is never a good idea. I'd rather
take my chances running and the chance that it may see one of my fingernails than laying down on a
dirt road where a fiery mule is headed towards me. They're saying the reason why this trick works,
because it doesn't have good eyesight, which is kind of a given because its head is gone. It
shouldn't have any eyesight at all, but apparently it's able to see shiny things and come after them.
But during the day, it's a normal woman. It's like a werewolf-esque curse with these things.
So the problem is, is that she can go about her daily life, but as the sun starts to set,
she's going to go through that horrible changing process again. She's going to feel her bones
break and her body weight shift and all that stuff. There's a bunch of fetishists sitting in the
village eating popcorn. They're like, "Oh, this is a real good part." Some of the tail pops out of
her butt. Everyone's like, "Yeah, yeah." So anyway, she turns into this monster every night. But if you
are looking for love, gentlemen, if you are looking for love, there is a way to tame this beast's heart
and get a little something, something for yourself. See, there's a couple of different ways to cure it.
You can take a needle and when they're in mule form, you poke them and they'll start bleeding.
Obviously, that's what needles tend to do. Or you can tie her to a cross. Now, when I read that,
I realized that one of the most curculean tasks that could ever be undertaken would be tying a
horse to a cross. I just don't think their body works that way. But if you can somehow take a mule
and tie it in the form of a cross, you can cure this thing. But it has to be done where the sin
was committed. Answer, basically in the priest's bedroom, you're like, "Hey, sorry, sir, here.
We're wrecking this giant cross in there." He's like, "I already got like 10 of those." He's like,
"Yeah, but this one's specifically horse-designed." And he's like, "Oh, great." And then he sees you
leading this headless mule and he's like, "Hey, Betty, you can do that, but she will only be cured
for that night." So it's pretty useless. So I don't even know why they came up with that part of the
legend. They're like, "Yeah, we have a way to cure you, but it'll only last for eight to ten hours."
If you really want to cure this woman, what you have to do is you have to reach in and grab the
hot bridle from, is it bridle or brittle? You have to reach in and grab the what the, the, the, the,
the, you have to reach in and grab the metal mouth thing from where the mule's head would be. And
it's red hot. It's super, super hot. Maybe white hot even. But you have to grab it and take it off.
If you do, this is your reward. This is a quote from the website where I got this information.
"Removeal of the curse is a great relief for the woman because the curse includes many trials."
I'm assuming that's the horrible shapeshifting pain that happens every night. And probably just,
you'd probably get tired because you'd be running around Brazil every single night and then you
got to go home and like do dishes. Sorry, let me go back. "Removeal of the curse is a great relief
for the woman because the curse includes many trials. So the grateful woman will usually repent
her sins and marry the benefactor." So you can find the woman of your dreams by removing this red
hot bridle from this creature's mouth and she turns back into a woman and says, "Thank you.
So many trials. My legs hurt. I have been able to poop because there's a tail sticking out my
butthole. It's been an awful, awful couple years. Let's get married." So you do get that. However,
I do like that they included the word usually. Usually. So imagine a man chasing down this
haunted mule looking for love and he finally is able to trick it. He covers up everything shiny
in his pocket. He's a goth teen so his fingernails are already all black. That's not a giveaway.
He just wears a mask over his face. A goth mask. And anyway, so he is able to take down the headless
mule, pull the bridle out of the mouth and she looks at him and goes, "Thank you. Thank you,
good gothic traveler. But you're like a brother to me and I can't imagine you not being there for me.
I'm gonna go back to town. I'm gonna go talk to that priest again. I think the idea of getting
friend-zoned by a cryptid might be the worst possible outcome ever. If you and your buddies
got kidnapped by bigfoots and your buddy gets dragged off and becomes like they're breeding,
starts impregnating all the female bigfoots and you just get to watch, that might honestly be the
most humiliating fate ever. I mean, if me and my buddy both got abducted by aliens and he's the
only one getting anal probed, I'm gonna feel a little left out. I'm gonna feel like it's me.
I'm gonna feel like I'm not good enough for them. Getting friend-zoned by aliens or ghosts or cryptids
might actually be the worst thing that anyone will ever have put on their tombstone. So you go
through this whole process. You grab the hot bridal out and she just walks away. It goes finds a
hot young man. Get it? Hot? Actually, I didn't plan that fun. She goes into town. She finds some hot
dude and you're stuck there with horrible burns on your hands. But before you go, Jason, that's
worth the risk. I am willing to burn my hands. I'm willing to get friend-zoned by a Brazilian cryptid.
Let me tell you a little bit of what happens after she turns back into a human. She's totally naked.
Yeah, Jason, you didn't even have to tell me that part. I assumed all of her clothes ripped off.
She's sweaty? Yeah, double good. Double, double good. Got this naked, sweaty woman standing
in the middle of the Brazilian jungle or forest, whatever's out there. It's just me, her, and the
horrible scars and burns I have all over my hands and wrists. She's naked, she's sweaty. She also
smells of sulfur. That might be the biggest boner killer of all time. I can't imagine
finally meeting Brittany Spears and her smelling like rotten eggs. She could have B.O. She could smell
bad, but if she actually smelt like hell, sorry, Brittany. Sorry. Not still do her, but the point
is, is that you would really have to overcome that horrible, horrible scent and it doesn't necessarily
say it goes away either. So you could have little babies that have smell half like sulfur and half
like you, whatever you smell like, hopefully better than sulfur. And before you guys get too excited
and go, okay, so you have this horse that bangs a priest, so that means she's good to go, and she
turns into this horse and then I horribly scar myself or just wear oven mitts. I'm sure there's
a way around melting your own hands. I pull the thing out of her mouth. She turns back into a
hot sweaty woman who stinks, but you know, I can deal with that. And I'm banging her. That's good,
but to be fair, yes, that is good. I do agree with you on all those points. That's why I presented
the story that way. However, one other twist, you don't necessarily know how the woman became the
headless mule. There's actually several ways this can happen. One of them is banging a priest.
Okay, again, that just means she's DTF. She can also become this by infant side. Look, I personally
couldn't get with a woman who killed a baby. I mean, your mileage may vary, but that's kind of,
that's, that's a bridge too far. That's like on the third date, she tells you, oh yeah, I have kids,
well had kids, and you're like, what does that mean? And she's like, oh, that's a fourth date
conversation. We're not getting to the fourth date. Unless I mean it was like a core accident or
something. But I mean, no, and she, you can also become this thing. That was dark. That was a dark
moment, dark moment for an otherwise lighthearted show. She can also become, this is fairly more
lighthearted. She can also become this thing by engaging in necrophage, which is eating corpses.
So that's disgusting. Like that's another thing. But to be fair, if a girl told me when she was in
college, she ate somebody's thumb, probably be able to look past that maybe. Well, actually,
this is a corpse. So if I met a girl and she said, oh yeah, about 10 years ago when I was in college,
I went into a morganate, ate a thumb. I don't know why a thumb, any part of the human body. I guess
the thumb's like the most innocent thing. But if I was with a girl and she goes, oh yeah, no, I, I
ate some of the corpse once that, that would probably be a deal breaker. Yeah, that would, yeah, that
would be a deal breaker. But it would be, if I had a choice between necrophage, girlfriend, or
never mind, never mind, never mind. There's no choice. They're both gross. If I had a choice between a
woman who banged a priest, I wouldn't even consider. I'd be like, oh yeah, and would you do the next
day? Like that wouldn't even pop up on my radar of red flags. But infancyed and necrophage. So
just letting you know, yes, this segment ended fairly darker than it started, but just letting
you know, before you book your ticket to Brazil, until you pull that metal piece out of that mule's
mouth, you don't know if you're getting a hot chick who's banged a priest or just some disgusting
women who've done some disgusting things. But to be fair, you're the one who went to Brazil
to bang a mule. So let's go ahead and move on to our next story. Now our next story is going to seem
a little out of place because I didn't expect that segment to get as lighthearted as it was.
But it's a story that I've wanted to cover actually before I even started doing the show.
It's one of those true crime stories that I've come across in my years of looking at true crime
that is always just kind of stuck with me for some very particular elements. The crime itself is
actually, and I hate to use words like this, but it's actually fairly mundane. So I'm not going
to spend a lot of time talking about the crime itself. But what we're going to look at is this
happened in 2006. You had three teenagers. You had Brian Lee Draper and Tori Michael Atomic.
They're both 16 years old, and they had a friend whose name was Casey Jo Stoddart, and she was 15.
That should tell you where we're going with this because she was 15. And what happened was these
two kids get together, they'd only known each other for about six weeks. Brian and Tori had only
known each other for about six weeks. They immediately become good friends. They're really
into movies and movie making. They went to Pocatello High School in Pocatello, Idaho. So that's
where this story takes place. So in the year 2006, for six weeks, these two people meet, and they just
really bond very, very quickly. And so one of them was idolizing the Columbine killers,
and the other one was a huge fan of Scream and horror movies in general. And both of there's a
little bit of bleed through with the two. They both liked horror movies, but one loved Columbine
more than the other, and one loved horror movies more than the other. But they started getting
it in their mind that they wanted to be famous. They wanted to kill someone, and they specifically
wanted to reenact Scream. They wanted to be those cool edgy teenagers who are going around
killing people in town, because it wouldn't make them famous. It wouldn't make them powerful. It
would make them somebody. In a world full of invisibles, they would be somebody. So they
hatched this plan, and they begin going out, and this came out after the trial, but they begin
going out, and they surveilled eight people, eight different people, eight different times,
waited outside their house, looking for the perfect opportunity, but every single time
there was multiple people in the home. So they always had to kind of brush off their stuff. Now,
they video, they were huge into movies and huge into making films. So they videotaped a ton of
their stuff. So we have basically videotaped confessions of them sitting outside these people's
houses and planning the murders and stuff like that. But what happens is they eventually find out
that Casey Joe Stoddard, who wasn't just some average girl, it was their friend, and Brian had
a crush on her, but she ended up dating somebody else. And he says, "She's my friend, but she has to
die." They needed their victims. So, and I'm not just, I'm paraphrasing that, but here is an actual
audio clip that I'm going to play of them discussing the murder of Casey Joe Stoddard.
So what I'm going to do right now, because they recorded a ton of the stuff, I'm going to play
you an audio clip from one of their video recordings where they are discussing the murder of Casey
Joe Stoddard, because they're basically making a documentary about the crime they're about to commit.
There should be no odds against killing people. I know it's a wrong thing, but
hell, you restrict somebody from it, they're going to want it more.
We found our victim and as it may be, she's our friend. But you know what? We all have to make
sacrifices. Our first victim is only to be Casey Stoddard. She's going to be alone in a big,
dark house out in the middle of nowhere. How perfect can you get? I mean, like, holy shit, dude.
I'm horny just thinking about it. Hell yeah. I was 950, September 22nd, 2006.
We know there's lots of doors and there's lots of places to hide. I locked the back doors. That's
all a lot. Now we're just going to wait. So what happens is they find out, like they said in the
clip there, and that was all recorded. It was recorded at different times during the day,
but that was all recorded the day they committed the crime. They found out she was house-sitting
for a relative and she was going to be there with her boyfriend and they originally thought,
"Well, just kill them both." But because they're friends with these people, they're actually invited
over to the house and they sit around and they watch a movie for a bit. And then Brian and Tori say,
"We want to go see a movie at the movie theater." So they leave, quote, unquote, leave. And then the
power goes out of the house. And KC is freaking out, obviously, because, you know, they're in the
middle of nowhere. It's late at night. They're in this house and they look around and the power comes
her and her boyfriend are kind of looking around to see what happened. And the power does end up
getting turned back on. But at that point, that was Brian and Tori killing the power so they could
sneak back into the house. So they're in the house now, unknown to KC and her boyfriend. And at one
point, the boyfriend calls up his mom, because these are like 15-year-olds, 16-year-olds. The
boyfriend calls up the mom and said, "Hey, can I spend the night with KC at this house?" And the
mom's like, "Of course not. I'm coming to pick you up." So the mom comes and picks him up. So now
KC is alone. KC, Kassie, I think it's Kassie. I'm sorry if I've been pronouncing it wrong.
Kassie is in the house alone by herself. Well, she's not because they're those two teenagers.
I just killed Kassie. We just left her house. This is not a fucking joke. I stabbed her in the
throat and I saw her life. This body just disappeared. Dude, I just killed Kassie.
Fuck. That felt like a foot name for real. I mean, it went by so fast.
Shut the fuck up. We gotta get her out of the street.
Now, that audio clip I just played was Brian and Tori driving away from the crime scene.
It's fairly self-explanatory. They ended up stabbing her 30 times.
And from what they can gather is they chased her around the house a bit and she was totally
freaked out. Now, they had said during their trial that they were simply trying to scare her and
things got out of hand, but stabbing someone 30 times is really getting things out of hand.
So she died. She was found by her 13-year-old cousin. That horribly mutilated body was found by
Kassie's 13-year-old cousin when they came home from wherever they were at. That's where she was
house-sitting. And Brian and Tori were arrested five days later. It's a very, very short amount of
time because her boyfriend, they immediately go to the boyfriend and say, "Hey, you're the last
person with her." And he's like, "Oh, yeah, me." And then these two other dudes came over. So then
the cops went to talk to them and they totally cracked. Now, this case, again, that's a fairly
standard true crime story. There's a lot of video evidence for it. I'm like, people talking about it.
What I think is odd is I've never heard, because I followed this story pretty closely for a while,
I'm surprised they didn't videotape the murders. I'm glad they didn't, but I'm wondering if they
didn't. It's just that it's never been revealed to the public because they don't want anyone
filling out Freedom of Information acts or something like that to try to get that videotape.
I find it odd that they videotape for weeks and weeks leading up to the murder and then start the
video camera as they're leaving the murder, but we've never seen that they videotape the murder
itself. It's considering they were into videotaping everything. I've always thought that was kind of
odd. They did both get sentenced to life without parole. And this case actually went to the
Supreme Court. And the Supreme Court ruled that in 2012, the Supreme Court ruled,
minors cannot be sentenced to life without parole. You cannot do that. So this case ended up changing
the law. And I think they haven't really had their sentences reduced yet because the state's like,
no, no, no, there's no way we're letting these dudes out. They're like, no, we're not letting
these guys out. So that's still going on. But it's all a fairly mundane thing. But the reason why
this story is always kind of stuck with me is because there's a documentary called Lost for
Life, and it's about minors who are in prison for the rest of their life. And these two guys are
featured in it because their case ended up going to the Supreme Court. And in the documentary,
they're talking to Brian in prison. And I've read true crime stuff all my life. And I've never
heard such a description from a killer before, the aftermath of a crime. Brian and Cassie were
friends. They knew each other. And most murderers know their victims. But here's his quote. This is
what he says. "After it happened, I had horrific dreams. Bad dreams where she was there and just
graphic, gruesome dreams about her dying. I would wake up in the night and I'd be scared, terrified.
Now I have dreams of her at school and everything's good. She's always smiling. But I always know in
the dream that I killed her. And those dreams are the worst." And I find that absolutely fascinating.
I find that absolutely fascinating because you have this young man who killed this woman and
almost a... They'd been planning for about six weeks, but for the most part it came out of nowhere.
Like it wasn't this, he was killing cats for a long time, doing all this stuff. He takes this
woman's life. And you could hear how panicked they were in that second audio clip. He takes this young
woman's life. And then he has those normal nightmares of guilt where he's like reliving the
crime and he's like... He can't... He's not in control of his body. When he falls asleep, he sees himself
committing the crime over and over and over again. And no matter how much he mourns during the day,
no matter how regretful he is during the day, when he falls asleep, he has no control over his
dreams and he's back and he can't help but killing her. But that's not the dream that terrifies him.
The dream that terrifies him is when he's in class and Cassie is sitting in front of him and she
turns around and she smiles. She goes, "You gonna do good on the test today?" "Oh Brian, I can't wait.
I can't wait till summer. I'm gonna do so much stuff." "Yeah, I actually just got... I'm going to that
horseback riding camp. I know it's kind of lame and very little girlish, but I don't know, it's just
gonna be fun to get out of the area for a while." And in those dreams where she's just talking about
life and her hopes and what they're gonna have for lunch and the new movie coming out, and in those
dreams Brian is just sitting behind her in class, no knife, no blood, just knowing that all of that
is over, knowing that he's already murdered her. Those dreams are the worst because in those dreams
she's still alive and she's still happy and full of life and has a future and he knows the truth.
She's already dead and he killed her. Whether or not his sentence is reduced from life because he
was a minor when he committed the crime is irrelevant. He will always be a prisoner in his head of this
crime. Those dreams will always pop up. People really seem to idolize killers to the point where
they will openly brag to someone that they barely know that they could take a human life.
Because we can argue whether or not you could physically actually kill up someone.
We can argue that point. But mentally, no. Mentally you will be imprisoning yourself for
the rest of your life. You'll always be having those dreams and those thoughts and they will haunt you
until the day you die. It might sound like a bit of a downer way to end an episode,
but just think about that the next time you engage in some risky behavior that can get somebody else
killed when you decide to start a fight with someone or finish a fight that didn't need to be a fight
in the first place. When you find yourself with your back up against the wall and you can't stand
it anymore and you just want to go across the street and teach that punk kid some lesson,
think about it for one extra moment because that extra moment may be what spares you
from a lifelong nightmare.
[Music]