The following episode of Dead Rabbit Radio contains crimes of a graphic nature.
Listener discretion is advised.
What would you do if one day you walked out in your front yard and a tree had fallen down?
But the next day, it falls up?
And then we meet a disgusting criminal with horrible crimes on his mind.
Is it possible that someone will stop this man before he does the unthinkable?
Or will his fantasies become a reality?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garbiner.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had an awesome weekend.
Let's go ahead and get this episode started by inviting in one of our legacy Patreon supporters.
He requested to be on a gross episode.
Here you are, buddy.
Everyone give a round of applause for Rabbit Fish.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in.
Come on in.
He's looking around.
He's like, "Oh no, what did I ask for?"
Hey, you did ask to be on a gross episode.
Rabbit Fish, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the show financially.
That's fine.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That really, really helps out a lot.
Dead Fish, hop on out of your portable fishbowl device.
I'm going to toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're going to drive all the way out to Ghana.
Should have taken a boat.
I figured that halfway across the Atlantic Ocean, but here we are in Ghana.
Specifically, we're in the community of Dambi in Ghana.
And it's earlier this month, July 2022, is when this story takes place.
So we're walking around Dambi and we're like, "Oh man."
And this storm starts to roll in.
We're like, "Ah, we're running for..."
It's not that bad of a storm.
It's not acid rain or anything.
But anyways, it's a rainstorm.
It actually is pretty windy and things like that.
And the next day, people are kind of out walking around trying to figure out what got knocked
down, what needs to be fixed, right?
Picket fence, got a couple things blown off of it.
Baby carriage.
Baby carriage flew off a bridge.
People are kind of licking over.
"Ah, there's no baby."
And this woman named Mary Boma, Mary Boma, comes out of her house and she sees this pretty
large teak tree completely ripped out of the ground.
So you know, that's a pretty big storm, right?
Ripping out trees and stuff like that.
And Mary's like, "Well, you know, you gotta make milk if you spill milk."
I guess they were all saying, "Right?"
Isn't that what people always said?
So this tree's knocked over and she goes, "You know, what am I gonna do?"
I'm gonna chop off a couple branches to use for firewood, right?
I mean, it's in the middle of summer.
Do people really like firewood in the middle of July?
I don't know.
But she starts cutting off branches and she takes them home and she's like, "Well, I'm
sure got a lot of firewood.
Now I just need a place to put it for 10 months."
And then a week later, another resident of Dambi, a man named Abraham Sapakou, is sitting
at home when he hears a "Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
down and she's like, "Oh, and behold, when she gets to the tree, it's standing straight
up again."
She's like, "What in the world happened?"
That tree was knocked down.
I have proof.
I cut off all these branches.
I took them home for firewood.
Now a week later, that tree is standing back up straight and the branches are removed from
it.
The branches I cut.
There's a photo of this tree.
There's a photo of a tree standing up, right?
That's proof.
There's a photo of a tree standing up and the report is this tree got knocked over and then
somehow it re-rided itself.
What's interesting about this photo is it does look like it was uprooted.
All of the ground at the base of the tree is churned up and you can see most of the roots
of the tree.
Ghana News Agency was the one reporting on this story and it's such a weird thing.
Ghana News Agency is talking about this and then there's a footnote going, "This isn't
the first time this has happened."
I'm like, "Really?
Can't tell us about the other times."
Apparently this isn't the first time that it's happened that a tree has been felled
and then fixes itself.
Mary, just to be safe, has contacted a local spiritualist.
You know, "I would probably not burn that wood, right?
I'd rather spend a couple nights kind of chilly than burn possibly cursed wood."
What a bizarre story.
Last week we covered a hobo whose car was magically repaired one day.
He walked out to his cousin living in his car and apparently he left his car for some reason,
probably to eat, right?
And then when he comes back, part of his car had brand new parts put on it and he didn't
do it.
And he questioned whether or not the Mandela effect had anything to do with that and that's
really when you look at this story, like what could be the possible causes.
We know why the tree got knocked down.
It was a storm.
But what would have been the possible, like from a logical point of view, right, you're
just going to say the photo, they just took a photo of a tree and the thing with being
a skeptic is sometimes you do really have to think of a logical excuse and that doesn't
make sense.
Well, maybe a construction crew needed to move a vehicle, by the way, so they towed
the tree up and sat it there and left this teetering giant tree.
It's quite large.
It's probably like 20, 30 feet tall.
They just left it there.
They didn't replant it or anything.
I've never ever heard of a tree, a fallen tree being put back in its position and they just
kind of left there.
Right now there's a bunch of people going, "No, Jason, that's what they actually do with
fallen trees."
I don't think so.
I've always seen them carted away, right, for firewood or paper or pencils or whatever,
right?
To get rid of, because you can't have this giant tree just laying there.
But yeah, so maybe there's a totally reasonable explanation.
I'm going to get an email from some forestry major being like, "No, that's what they do."
But I think if it was a reasonable explanation, they would have just put that in the article.
Coast to Coast AM's website is where I found this originally.
And they're really, really good about including, well, you know, experts say this or experts
say that.
They'll constantly...
Sorry, there's a card driving one.
I'm recording in my living room instead of my closet like normally because it's just
too hot.
Coast to Coast AM's good about the other side of things, right?
Not like the other side, i.e. the other side dead people, ghosts and stuff like that.
But just like, this is what experts say.
They're really good at providing balance.
This one even there like, "What in the world can have caused this?"
You could say the large sound was a construction vehicle rewriting the tree, but then you also
hear the rumbling of a construction crew nearby.
So this happened, right?
I mean, unless they're, again, faking everything, which they could, but it seems to be going
out of the way for kind of a goofy fake.
You do have to look at stuff like Mandela Effect.
Ghost?
I have no idea.
Why would a ghost even want to do this?
They're like, "Ah, it's time to flex my ghost muscles.
I've been dead for 400 years.
Time for a workout."
I mean, like demons maybe?
Magic?
I mean, I have no clue of why a tree...
And you know, and again, you could go to maybe something that I personally find very boring,
but a lot of people like nature magic, right?
The tree was like, "Oh, I'm not supposed to be dead."
And then like, he did it himself.
Which if I saw that event, I would not find it boring at all.
I would be completely dazzled, but I'm not a huge fan of nature magic.
I'm not a huge fan of like fairies and little gnomes and stuff like that.
Again, if I see them, I won't be like, "Boring."
But just, I don't like reading about them.
I find it kind of lame.
I mean, I'm talking about this tree that fixed itself.
I'm like, "Come on, man.
Where's the UFOs?"
I have no reasonable explanation of why this would happen or why someone would fake it.
But according to Ghana news agency and Mary Boma, two very, very well-respected names,
this tree fell down.
She chopped the limbs off and then re-rided itself.
And what's interesting is she does have the proof.
Like when you look at the photograph, there are limbs chopped off the tree.
You're like, "Jason, come on.
There's always limbs chopped off trees."
Why would they make this up?
It's so dumb.
Why would they make it up?
And it's also so fascinating because I can't think of a legitimate reason outside of some
lame old nature magic that this would even be a thing.
Ghosts don't care.
Aliens don't care.
Demons don't care.
Bigfoot wouldn't do it.
I don't even know if there's a Bigfoot in Africa actually now to think about it.
That's interesting.
I know there's a bunch of cryptids, but a Sasquatch-esque creature in and of itself.
I don't know.
I should look into that.
But yeah, why would this have...
Mandela effect really is the biggest thing, right?
But then why are the tree branches removed?
Fascinating story coming out of Ghana and it's fairly recent.
Ghana news agency also, if you do say, "This paranormal event has happened more than once."
Include those.
Include those notes.
I'd like to see those.
Now, rabbitfish and the rest of you are probably thinking, "Whoa, that wasn't that gross.
You were thinking did the tree fall on someone?"
No, you sickos.
You're like, "Get to the gross.
Get to the gross.
We're getting to the gross."
Rabbitfish.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonar character.
We're leaving behind Ghana.
We're headed somewhere within the United States of America.
This is a story I've had ready to go for a while and it's actually one of those stories
that's so creepy and disturbing that I've actually gone back and forth between like,
"Should I do it today or should I never, ever cover this story at all?"
Because what we're going to be looking at is the story of a man who was on a mission.
Well, according to him, not on a mission, but we're basically, when I tell this story,
you're going to see this clock in front of you and you are going to realize that it is
counting down to something very, very, very disturbing.
There's a subreddit called "Incessed Confessions."
Incest Confessions.
And if you've got to say anything about this subreddit, for the people who are listening,
they're like, "No, I'm good, dude.
Good happy Monday, Jason."
Incest Confessions, truth and advertising, right?
It's people talking about incest confessions.
Now there's a debate even within the community about how true the stories are, which I would
hope that none of them are.
I'm hoping that none of them are.
I actually came, I stumbled across them because I was covering another story where someone
was posting, saying some crazy stuff and I want to say, "What else is this lunatic up
to?"
I don't remember what that story was.
It was nowhere near as crazy as this one.
I got wondering what this guy's up to and he was in, one of the subreddits he was talking
about in was incest confessions.
And these people sit around and talk about either things that really happened or things
they want to happen.
And again, you don't know what's true.
Some of this stuff, because I didn't have to read some of this stuff, I'm like, "Ugh."
Some of this stuff is obviously like, it seems fake.
Again, I hope it's fake.
Let's take a look at this guy because this guy, he is in love with his daughter.
And when I say love, that's probably not the right word.
Obsessed would be a better way to put it.
He's very, very cautious about what information he gives out, obviously, because he's getting
ready to commit a crime.
The only information we have is that he has multiple daughters.
And according to him, someone specifically asked, "How old is your daughter?"
And he goes, "18."
I actually read that comment in that voice.
I don't know if she's actually that old.
He knows well enough that if he said she was any younger, even the people of incest confessions
would boo him.
She might be 18, but we don't know.
So you're like, "Jason, okay, you found a guy talking about wanting to have sex with
his daughter on Reddit."
Yeah, it's way worse than that.
That is just something in passing.
This guy, again, what I find so fascinating about this is like with any criminal, there's
an escalation to it.
You can always chart a through line.
So let's take a look at this guy.
He didn't wake up one day.
Well, he might have woken up one day and said, "Oh, I want to have sex with my daughter."
But let's take a look at this escalation of events.
And you tell me if you think there should be a race against time to identify.
I'm not saying Doc's the guy.
Let's take a look at this.
Here I am again, 12 is his username.
Here I am again, 12.
Why did he pick the number 12?
Don't know.
Don't want to know.
What he does is post on incest confessions and we find out that he is the father of multiple
daughters and he enjoys going to happy ending massage parlors, which is the massage parlors
where basically you do not get a massage.
They just want to get you in and get you out.
The people there, the masseuses, masturbate you and then you leave, right?
If you go and then you're like, "Man, I sure didn't have a stressful day at work."
Then you start off on my back and then work my calves.
You'll be like, "No, that's not what we're here for."
Happy ending massage parlors.
And he's very clear about this stuff and he goes, "One day I was getting a happy ending
massage and he asked the woman, "Do you mind if I look at pictures on my phone?"
This gets rough, guys.
From here on out, you're like, "Jason, it started off rough.
It started off rough."
He said he's having this done.
He's having this happy ending massage.
He's getting masturbated, right?
He's getting jacked off by this woman.
I don't want to use all these euphemisms.
He asks, "Can I look at my phone while you do that?"
She doesn't care.
Yeah, anything that'll get you off quicker and get you out of here.
So he pulls up a photo of one of his daughters.
Now he kind of plays it off like maybe he didn't plan on doing that in the first place,
but he's looking at a picture of one of his daughters in a thong bikini.
And he said that it was hard for him to even last.
As he's looking at this photo of his daughter, I'm already second guessing about releasing
this.
As he's looking at the photo of his daughter, he goes, "It was so hard.
I was so turned on, I couldn't even last that long because of it."
And then after he was done, the masseuse kind of looked over at his phone and saw the picture
of this girl on his phone.
And she said, "Very pretty."
He's complimenting this random girl, and he responded, "This is an actual quote from him.
Thanks.
She's my youngest."
And then the last quote of this post was, "The look on the masseuse's face when she realized
what I said was priceless.
I can't wait to try this again."
I saw that post, and I was like, "Oh my God, this guy's a monster."
And I really kind of thought that would be the end.
I really kind of hoped that would have been the end of it, right?
But later on, I think I was planning on just mentioning that briefly about something.
So I went back to this account, and I saw that he had posted more.
And I was like, "Okay, whatever I was working on before, we've got to follow the trail of
this villain, right?
This man who he says his daughter's 18, which doesn't make it right.
It doesn't mean, "Oh, well, she's over 18.
You totally have sex with your daughter.
She still doesn't make it right."
But I don't think she's actually 18 years old.
I mean, maybe, right?
If that's his youngest, then he has multiple daughters, then maybe he's in his 50s, right?
50s, 60s, years old.
I don't know.
He legally knows that even, morally, that even the Reddit incest confessions, I think,
has a line, or at the very least, they rule.
You know, you can't say anything.
So let's go ahead a month in time.
When he posted again in the same subreddit, he said that he's gone back to the massage
parlor several more times.
Whatever, right?
The dude is getting happy and beans.
That's not my beef with this guy, right?
But then he says that he's starting to feel, quote, "extremely tempted by his daughter."
He says the weather's been hot recently, so she's been wearing less clothing around the
house.
That makes me mad, right?
That's her house, too.
She's feeling comfortable there.
Her guard's down.
She doesn't know her father wants to have sex with her, so if she's walking around, she's
like, "Oh, man, sure is hot."
And she throws on a pair of boxer shorts and a tank top.
It's because she doesn't think that there's anyone around who is going to judge her sexually.
Her guard is completely down.
And as she's wearing this casual clothing, see, this is where we get to this dangerous
stuff.
He's seeing it as, "Oh, maybe she's trying to turn me on."
See, his neurons are starting to get rewired.
This is what we talk about when fetishes become obsessions.
Your neurons start getting rewired.
Your pleasure sensors change.
He actually posted one point on the incest subreddit.
He posted one of them was, "Maybe I've read too many of these incest stories."
Like, he even knows that this is changing the way he's looking at his own flesh and
blood.
He never once mentions this as a stepdaughter.
Again, not that would make a huge moral difference.
But she's wearing clothes that are comfortable in the heat.
Oh, man, she's tempting him, right?
So he has been going to these happy ending parlors.
That's doing pretty good for him, I guess.
I mean, he keeps going back.
Five stars on yelp.
His daughter is tempting him at home, but he knows that he can't do anything.
Now, according to him, this was all an accident.
According to him, he accidentally hired a prostitute who looks like his daughter.
On accident, right?
Didn't mean it at all.
He was going to the escort website, and he closed his eyes, and he scrolled his mouse
and goes, "You!"
He puts this, he says this in this post quote.
She definitely looked different.
But, when he had a butt to that, she definitely looked different.
But her eyes, nose, and hair were uncanny.
And from the back, I couldn't even tell the difference."
Unquote.
Then he says, just so all the other perverts on the board know what his intentions are.
He says, quote, "I wasn't planning on asking her to pretend to be my daughter."
But, and then he goes on to tell the story.
He said, "She asked, the escort asked what fetishes I have.
I believe they're meeting up at a hotel room at this point, or maybe her place, but I think
it was a neutral location.
She goes, "Do you have any fetishes?"
And he said, "Well, since you asked, I want to have sex with my daughter."
According to him, he accidentally chose an escort that looked like his daughter.
And he didn't want to, he didn't come in with that intention.
She asked, so I told her.
He's with her.
He doesn't want to do anything with his daughter until she brought it up.
It said, "What fetishes do you have?"
He goes, "Well, I've always wanted to have sex with my daughter."
And then, that's a bomb to drop in any conversation, right?
She said, "Why don't you call me by your daughter's name?"
And they keep this thing going.
He's now having sex with this escort and calling her his daughter's name.
And the escort looks like the daughter.
He's like, "Jayson, you don't have to review it.
Please just continue.
Just continue."
And he has this thing where he keeps putting it on the other.
It's not my fault.
My daughter's tempting me.
I didn't want to do this with the escort, but she brought up the fetish thing.
And this is when he says, "Am I taking this too far?"
Like, at this point, he realizes that maybe the fantasy is going a little too much.
Am I taking this too far?
The escort, though, before he's able to rationally think about that, the escort said, "Hey, next
time," because obviously now you've got a hook in this guy, right?
Next time, why don't you bring some of her clothes?
Why don't you bring some of her clothes?
And he ends this post by thinking, "Oh, yeah.
I can grab one of her bikinis, her cheerleading uniform, maybe her underwear."
He's excited about this thought about what he-- again, he didn't think about this.
She brought it up.
He didn't think about this.
And he's already thinking about this, cheerleading uniform.
So he's done this now.
He's had sex with this prostitute and pretended it was his daughter.
And then he thinks, "Am I taking this too far?"
And he ends the post again by re-asking that question, "Is this taking it too far, though?
Part of it feels like it's good because it's helping me resist my temptations."
That is used a lot in sex criminals, right?
They go, "Well, I'll watch this really, really graphic pornography because it won't make
me want to go out and do that."
But that's never that-- we've never seen that throughline, right?
Playing violent video games doesn't make you more violent.
We know that that exists.
Watching violent movies doesn't make you more violent.
We know that exists.
But watching depraved pornography that feeds into your fetish, there's a reason why pedophiles
get caught with large amounts of child porn.
There's a reason why people who commit necrophilia get caught with necrophilia porn.
We see that throughline all the time.
"Is this taking it too far, though?
Part of it feels like it's good because it's helping me resist my temptations.
Not I know that it's only making my lust for my daughter stronger."
I don't think I've given you a time scale.
This is taking place this year.
This next post was posted on May 27th, 2022.
So really, really recent stuff.
There's still a chance to stop this.
I don't know why I think Sherlock Holmes is listening to the podcast.
He's like, "Indubitably.
Let me figure out who this guy is."
May 27th, 2022, he goes to see this prostitute again.
And this time, remember, he had all those choices.
He had all those choices.
Cheerleader uniform, bikini, underwear.
What he brings is actually now the reason why I thought she was younger.
Now I remember.
I didn't wasn't originally thinking that sicko.
I was thinking that sicko.
This was the clue that I go, "Oh, she's not 18."
What he brought was his daughter's prom dress.
So again, it's an icon of high school, right?
Cheerleading uniform icon of high school, but also icon of college.
You're not going to proms in college unless you're a dude and you're going to some senior
girl's prom.
He brings the prom dress, an icon of not only high school life, but high school, like
the ending of being a girl and becoming a woman is the prom dress.
Cheerleading uniforms, they have them all the time.
They're something about a prom dress.
It actually seems really, like totally fluffy and stuff.
That doesn't seem like the best dress.
You write that to the escort and she's like, "Okay, it's going to take me two hours to
get in and out of this thing."
He brings the daughter's prom dress and it was the hottest sex he'd ever had in his
life.
Being sex with this escort in his daughter's prom dress was the best sex ever.
Oh, and I should add, he said it felt so real.
He's still completely fantasized.
Just because he's like, "Oh, I love this prom dress.
Satin on silk?
This is beautiful."
It's because he was still imagining his daughter.
So then a little bit of time passes and he has two weeks of the house to himself.
The rest of the family is gone and he has some money set aside.
He has some money that I don't know if he's in that...
Again, he doesn't give us a lot of details.
Was he saving up for this event or did he just happen to have a lot of money set aside?
He decides with the family gone from the house.
You guys are like, "It's been a while to ride so far."
With his family gone from his house.
He decides to hire the escort for three days to live with him in the house and pretend to
be his daughter.
So for three days, that would be a couple thousand dollars, right?
I don't know, a lot.
For three days, I'm like, "You're like Jason Rowe."
He can fixated over the weirdest details.
You're like, "Oh, you're having my little calculator I'd have on that little accounting
visor from those old 1940 movies."
I'm like, "Wowee, that sure is a lot of money."
Because I'm doing, he's paying an escort that looks like his daughter in his house and they
would do it in her bed.
So he's hired this woman.
She only wore his daughter's clothing.
She called him dad the whole time.
Dad, daddy, they're walking around.
He says this, he goes, "By day three, I almost forgot that she wasn't really my daughter.
It was amazing.
She would be wearing cute outfits of my daughters and I was finally able to live out my fantasy
of ripping every one of those outfits off of her."
I'm assuming she, the daughter, would come home and go, "What happened to all of my clothes?
Why have they been shredded to pieces?"
Apparently, he turns into a werewolf.
And then he adds this quote, "My favorite place to have sex was, of course, my daughter's
room to really make sure that you know how sick he is."
And then, so you're like, "Jason, listen, man, people have fetishes.
He's not actually, what do you want me to look at the photo of his daughter?
They have any parlor.
You forgot that part, huh?"
Okay, okay, so, but he's not doing anything to her, right?
It's that he's having this fantasy and he's not engaging in the reality.
I mean, ignoring the first part of the story where he's looking at the photograph, ignoring
the story of where when the daughter's walking around just being herself, being comfortable
at home and their dad's like, "Ugh, she's tempting me."
This is, this is really, like, I can't think of another way to end this.
The doomsday clock is ticking.
We're to this point, we're to the zenith of this man's sickness.
Has this escorted over for three days?
They're having sex in her bed, wearing her clothes.
This is where you're just like done, right?
You're done.
Now, one of the hottest experiences was looking through old photo books of her and talk about
how much she's grown as she lightly teased my cock.
So whatever debates we had about how old she is now, now he's referencing younger photos
of her and sexualizing her at a younger age, whether she's 18 or 15.
Is it relevant at this point?
Because now he's looking at young photos of her while he's with a prostitute.
It's kind of mind blowing if you think about it.
While he's with a prostitute dressed as his daughter looking at childhood photos and talking
about how much she's grown.
This is vomiting, this is so rough.
And the reason why I think it's rough is because this isn't a true crime story where we have
this guy locked up in jail or he's on the run and there's been this trial and there's
all this stuff or whatever.
This is happening now.
That was posted on May 27th, 2022.
I just checked his posting history before I started recording this episode.
There is no additional parts to this saga.
He's just posting on gross subreddits, meaning like, yeah, give it to her baby.
Yeah, that's so hot.
I wish I could do that.
That's what all of his other posts are.
We don't have any addition to this story.
Did he make a move?
Is he still planning on it?
Is he still seeing this escort?
Have things escalated so much he doesn't even feel comfortable talking about it.
A subreddit full of incest lovers.
But this is a true crime story.
We covered a story like this before, right?
A true crime story, but we have not seen technically the crime happen yet.
We have unsolved true crimes.
There's usually disturbing, right?
There's a serial killer on the loose that's never been caught.
Then we have solved true crime where the person's currently in trial or the person is already
in prison or the suspect is dead or whatever.
This is a true crime story in the making.
This guy's a villain and he's going to cross the line.
This guy at the very, very least will cease having a healthy relationship with his daughter.
The very least, right?
He will see her as a sex object.
He may not have seen her as a sex object all of her life, but he definitely sees her as
a sex object now.
And every time she makes a funny joke or every time she leans her head up against him as
they're sitting on the couch or every time she giggles at one of his stupid puns, he's
going to read into it the same way that a guy does when he's talking to a cute girl at
a coffee shop.
She gives him that bright smile and goes, "Oh, I wonder if she's into me."
But the difference is this is not my daughter at the coffee shop.
I have no power over her.
I'm not in charge of paying for her college.
I'm not in charge of any sort of emotional support.
I'm not in charge of any part of her life.
And if I was, if I was the boss, that'd be sexual harassment, right?
If I'm doing things untoward, is that a thing?
I'm doing things I shouldn't do to my employees.
At the very least, he's going to have an unhealthy relationship with his daughter.
That's the very, very least.
And you got, I don't really have to say what the worst thing to happen is, right?
Like in his mind, I'm going to, I'm going to, but in his mind, if he successfully seduces
his daughter, they'll have this super hot, "How do we want to go into it?
I'm not saying it's hot.
I'm saying for him, right?
They're going to make whoopee and it'll be this lust filled journey.
All of his fantasies will come true."
We know that's not how this stuff works out, right?
It would completely devastate the family.
You go, you're just shredded in half.
But, you know, he's the hero of his own story and he's rewired his brain to think that this
type of stuff is normal.
Even though in almost every human civilization, it's not, I mean, unless it's a survival situation,
it's not.
So he, he, he's just looking at the world through a porn sick point of view and he's
on this subreddit.
Again, that's why I hate Reddit, because these people can congregate and cheer each other
on.
And the posts that they leave stay there pretty much forever.
The mods very rarely delete stuff and the people don't delete their accounts.
They're proud of this stuff.
So best case scenario, he just has a completely unhealthy relationship with his daughter from
here on out.
And even when he's 80 years old and the rest home and she comes in and brings in the grandkids
to visit him, he's still going to have these weird messed up things floating around in
his head.
At the worst, he's going to try something.
He's going to make a move.
He's going to misread the room.
And then the whole fallout from that, right?
A true crime story when technically the crime hasn't happened yet.
I mean, technically going to escorts and going again, having any miscarriages or all crimes.
People get arrested for those all the time.
But you know what I mean?
Like the thrust of the crime, the narrative here hasn't happened yet.
So we don't know how it ends or if it will ever end.
Again, will this be something that just carries on through the decades?
He becomes insanely jealous of her husband or any boyfriend she brings home like this.
We've seen this stuff happen in true crime stories, right?
We can trace these things back.
And this is how they start.
A man becoming obsessed with his own daughter, obsessed with having a sexual relationship.
Not very loving, right?
Again, not that it would matter, but again, he's viewing his daughter as a solely a sexual
object.
Absolutely terrifying.
Again, this is, we want to think this is an aberration.
And I do think for the most part it is an aberration, but there's a lot of aberrations
out there.
This guy is just going to keep on having these fantasies.
He's not going to stop.
He's going to keep fueling it from reading more of these foreign posts and from watching
incest pornography and just building this up in his system until he either completely
abandons the whole thing before.
I mean, he's gone pretty deep at this point, right?
He hasn't crossed that line, but paying the hooker to come to your house for three days,
dress up as your daughter and have sex in her bed.
I mean, that's, I won't say you're past the point of no return, but you're getting
there.
You're getting there.
Your foot's on that white line.
You're coming close to stepping over.
It's just, it's creepy.
It's creepy because we don't know how the story ends yet.
This story's going on right now.
We don't know if it's going to happen for no one intended a happy ending or if it's going
to be an absolutely tragic ending.
We don't know.
We just can sit and watch, not even watch, wait for the next post to come out.
Don't subscribe to this guy.
Don't be like, all right, I'm bored.
I wonder what's going on.
This dude sickos life.
But again, like a true crime in the making.
Will he make the ultimately disgusting decision?
Will he back off and realize that this was wrong?
Will he try to thread the needle and say, I love the fantasy, but I don't want to actually
have the reality because I know how devastating that will be.
Or does he jump 10 toes into it and make a move on his daughter?
Only time will tell.
But that doomsday clock is ticking.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also do stuff at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
TikTok is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
[Music]