A man meets an untimely end at the worst and possibly most fun place you'll ever work.
And then we travel to Oswego County in New York State to find the remains of a town once
known as Happy Valley.
Locals say the area is haunted, cursed, everyone thought it was rumors until the skeletons
appeared today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a ton of stuff to cover so let's go ahead and give a shout out to one of our
legacy Patreon supporters, Bryce Dawson.
Bryce Dawson, getting a round of applause as he's walking out of the room and what is
he holding?
Yep, that's right, he's holding a turkey, a dead turkey, a cooked turkey.
He's not just carrying around a corpse, he's carrying a cooked turkey because we did this
last year, it was super successful.
We're in the planning stages right now, so give me your feedback if you guys want this.
But I'm looking at doing another Thanksgiving livestream.
We did it last year, I took the whole episode, I uploaded it onto the podcast providers as
well so you can listen to it there after the fact.
We do Patreon livestreams once a month for the Patreons and I'm going to do one with
them and then on top of that I'd love to do a live episode for everybody on Thanksgiving
and we can chat and eat and you can watch me eat with my mouth full talking as Bryce
is feeding me food.
So Bryce, let's go ahead and put you at the helm of the Dead Rabbit Dreadnaught, our
massive battleship.
We're not going to war, but we just have you in a while and it starts to get rusty, you
gotta scrape the barnacles off.
Bryce, you are navigating this massive warship out to the United Kingdom.
Specifically, we're going to Red Roof that's in Cornwall in the UK.
It's November 2017 and the Dreadnaught docks that we're walking around and we see a big
building, I don't know, could be meeting size, they didn't say in the article how big it
was, there's no dimensions involved.
H&A Recycling.
At H&A Recycling there is a young man named Dave McClellan, he's 23 years old and he's
currently training Kyle Harvey on how to fix a jammed garbage compactor.
Garbage compactors jammed and Dave's like, "Okay Kyle, it's time that I show you how
to fix this thing."
It actually jams all the time, it's kind of a piece of junk.
Electionally he says, because that wasn't in the article either, but anyways.
So Dave goes up to the top, so it's like a two-story garbage compactor.
So he's on this walkway and Kyle's down below and Dave opens up the compactor and Kyle
kind of is walking down, he can't really see what's going on up there, but he's like,
"Well, okay, enough time is passed, I guess I'm going to start hitting this button."
He hits the button and he hears, "Ahhh."
He goes, "Oh, that's cool, he must have unjammed it, but," because I heard that monster's noise,
"Ahhh."
But now it's jammed again, it stopped.
He's like, "Oh, great.
Hey Dave, Dave, it's jammed again.
Whatever you did, it didn't work."
And Dave doesn't answer and he's like, "What?
That's weird.
Dave probably just went to a break.
He probably just took a break in the middle of fixing this thing."
Oh well.
So Kyle goes to the other coworkers, he's like, "Hey, the big green compactor's jammed."
Everyone's like, "What?
Again?"
So there, I'll start working around with their life.
We don't know how to fix it, you got to call Dave."
And he's like, "Yeah, Dave was working on it, but Dave's not up there anymore."
And the coworkers are looking at each other, they're like, "Oh yeah, it's break time, right?
You just leave in the middle of doing the job, totally makes sense."
Let's call Dave's cell phone and ask him, one, to bring us back some crisps.
And two, to let him know this compactor is broken.
Again.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
It's in Britain, so there's more numbers.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do.
They're sitting there on the phone, all of them, all the employees, they're all like
girls gossiping on a sleepover, they all have their ear to the phone.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do,