Two topics from the conspiracy iceberg
one the height of
human ingenuity
The other one the lowest point in human depression today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you're having a great day too
I'm having a great day now man after I recorded the ghost of the haunted apartment episode
I ended up getting I don't know if I got food poisoning
I don't know if I got a touch of the flu, but man
I was out of commission for about two or three days. I record most of my episodes on the weekend now
So I have more time to research
but from Sunday evening to
Today's Wednesday from Sunday evening to Tuesday night man
I was I was done and it's so funny because
Well, it's enough I was super sick
But I was just like I had recorded that ghost episode and I had all those creepy experiences and I was like well
I need to sleep in my bedroom. I can't really sleep with the light on in my bedroom
Because there's only one light bulb and it's right above the bed
But I'm sick and I have to like lay down and I ended up grabbing my tablet that I got for Christmas from my mom
Watched a couple episodes of Star Trek and then I thought you know what I need something comfy to watch
And it's so weird. I've talked to other people about this
It's almost like the show the office is
Like probably one of the most comfortable shows ever created and never gets super loud
Well, Michael yells a lot, but it's just one of those I watched all of season 5 and about two days
And it's so funny because I'm watching I've seen it multiple times before
But I'm watching it and I'm sick and I'm hearing these familiar voices from you know
10 years ago when I was watching the show when it was brand new on NBC and it would help me sleep
It's so funny and what's funny is I knew I was starting to get better
The office was on and I wasn't watching it like I just had it on and I was on my phone doing research
I was like, oh, I must be feeling better. I don't have to be staring at this television screen for hours on end
Oh, it was so terrible. Not the show my sickness
Yeah, I think the office might actually be the most comfy show
I've met people who absolutely hate that show though because they hate seeing people being embarrassed
Like they can't watch comedy where people are embarrassed. I've met a lot of people like that
I think it's hilarious watching other people be embarrassed, but other people are like I can't watch it
I can't watch people in awkward situations, but anyway, so yeah, if you're ever sick and you have Netflix
Well, I actually tried looking for X files first, but that's not on Netflix anymore, man
Whatever man pretty soon everyone's gonna have to have 10 streaming options
It'll be just as much as cable in the end. So let's go ahead and get started with the episode here
I am feeling better. So I'm happy about that
So I have two topics from the conspiracy iceberg today and like I said in the intro one is
wonderful
One is a wonderful conspiracy theory
It's one of the ones that I like because it's very happy and enlightening to who we are as a species
Now on the conspiracy iceberg there is the phrase
Amazon forest is man-made and I was like, oh, it's just gonna be like
Mountains are trees like are they gonna say that the trees are holograms or they're all metal and whatever
But I was like, you know, it's it's an evocative phrase. So I typed it in a Google and
page after page after page pulled up
showing
from scientists
That the Amazon rainforest is indeed
Man-made
Let's travel back in time
Let's go. We're not gonna get in the carbon decopter because I'm still a little nauseous
I don't think I can take the flight. You know what we're going to the Amazon rainforest
So it's been gone through some rough stuff. Let's go carbon. Let's go. I can't even say that word with a straight face
Let's go carbon neutral
with
the hoppy hang
The hoppy hang glider is we each have our own so it's not we're all not hugging on each other was flying over
It's basically a hang glider in the shape of a rabbit and somehow it still stays afloat
Doesn't just have a picture of a rabbit on it. It's actually the shape of a rabbit. Oh, oh, I wanted to say this too
I got some fan art from gray of PTA from on YouTube
He sent me a picture. I'll put it in the show notes. He sent me a drawing of Pinko
The the tolpa slash communist infiltrator. It's amazing. Thank you
Thank you. Thank you. I'll put that in the show notes, but anyways, so we're in the hoppy hang gliders. We each got our own I
Played a lot of pilot wings back in the day. So I know how to use these things
But we're gonna fly not only to the Amazon rainforest, which is in South America. He didn't know
But we're also the gentle breeze is going to take us back in time
We're going back hundreds of years
We're going back to basically
Prehistory well, I guess not prehistory because they're they were right and stuff down, but we don't know the history is modern day doesn't know the history
We're in South America. We're flying over the rainforest and what's interesting is we look down
First we think there's some sort of Mandela effect going on. There's there's not a rainforest here
It's it's just it's just a bunch of bamboo. This isn't what we expected
We expected lush green jungles and
Jaguars and
Anaconda and anaconda to search for the blood orchid, but none of that stuff is down here
We just see bamboo and this is what so this is what's interesting. This is 100% it's a theory
It's a theory, but scientists believe that this is true the Amazon rainforest that
Landscape used to have a ton of bamboo which does grow naturally in South America
and at some point
a
Leader or a group of leaders in that area. They had their tribes said, you know what let's build a supermarket here
Let's cut down all this bamboo
Let's burn it
Let's burn it all and we are going to reshape the landscape and plant trees
That we use we don't use all this bamboo
So they burned it all down
And the smoke saw coughing us as we're flying in a hang glider. I lose a couple of you. Sorry. No
And you don't listeners I can get as you disappear into the dark smoke below
But anyways, we eventually do catching up drafting get back up to us
so they burned down the bamboo and they begin planting trees like palm trees and
trees that provided nuts trees that
they could use for food and
A shelter like they would have the right bark for them
trees that were actually useful to the indigenous people and because now they no longer had to travel out to find these
supplies
The population in and around the Amazon rainforest boomed
Was massive and I'll get to the proof behind this real quick
But because you're like chasing just making this stuff up
But no so the populate now they had all their resources in one single area
So people started coming to the area. They had tons of food. They had tons of material. They could start trading at other groups
What's interesting is that when?
The conquistadors came to South America and the early reports of the conquistadors
They said to there's like these massive amounts of people here in the Amazon area
huge cities full of people and
As more and more conquistadors showed up. They're like, uh, there's not that many people here anymore
And so when modern
Researchers were looking back when they were looking at the first
Instances of people like of conquistadors of the West coming to South America. They're like, we think they exaggerated
We really don't think they came across the a tribe of ten thousand people
We think there was probably thousand people historical records are usually exaggerated, right?
but now what they think happened was
They basically when the conquistadors came the natives left that area
Either they were killed off the disease got them or they just left because they knew bad stuff was coming down the pipe
And once they stopped cultivating that land stopped working in that supermarket
nature took back over and
The rainforest exploded with all sorts of trees all sorts of plants and vegetables and
Fruits did have fruits down there. Is it a mango fruit or mangoes from South America? Anyways, so
The and that created the Amazon rainforest we see today where it's just a bunch of foliage and it's not necessarily completely useful
So this is the proof behind that
tons of resources on this one when they started burning down the
Forest recently the Amazon rainforest recently to make room for cattle grazing
They started to notice these huge geoglyphs in the ground which are basically giant shapes
Either mounds or trenches and they're absolutely massive
It's not like just someone drew it, you know, like made a trench in the ground and like rolled around in the dirt
Like these are geometric designs and stuff like that and they go oh there must have been like a city center here
Or this was a religious site that got swallowed up by the jungle
researchers started to notice there was a lot of
charcoal in
the soil and they go
It looks like there were a lot of burns in this area in the past
Like not just like lightning strike burns. It looks like somebody was burning the forest to make room for something else
But the kicker is this when they look at the Amazon rainforest, which now is completely wild and untamed and it
I'm gonna do a follow-up episode on this
But there's a ton of cryptid sightings there and like lost cities and things like that
but
When they look at the Amazon rainforest now, it's just just jungle
But along the Amazon River basin
There are
85 different tree species that
The natives absolutely used and needed to prosper
And they're like this isn't by chance
If we look along the basin here and the Amazon rainforest, we will see stretches basically a supermarket aisle of
Trees that would be useful to the indigenous people
So the theory is this that yes, there were massive populations in the Amazon up to 8 million people
Who live they basically clear cut all the bamboo
planted the trees that they needed and
Basically would say you know what I really need I need a couple papayas and people are like
I don't think those grown South America
Well, I'm gonna go down to the old Amazon and check it out you go down there to pick them
Strip off some bark and grab some coffee beans
Whatever and then you go to your tribe
They basically they did to the Amazon rainforest what we're trying to do now
When they're doing the clear cutting and using it to produce food for other people they did that already
It's a man and I'm not saying that yeah
We should clear cut the Amazon so McDonald's can sell cheap beef
But I'm saying like it's the same idea and I always think it's fascinating when we can look back in history and
See people come up with these plans and it makes you think what other natural
Phenomenon do we see and we thought always thought that the Amazon was this pristine virgin jungle when in fact
It was basically railies or Bel Air or Safeway or any other grocery store to them
But once they stopped cultivating it it overgrew back into the jungle and I want to end on this note too
It's so funny. I heard a conspiracy theory a long time ago
That in Vietnam this is well
This is a good segue because we're gonna get dark with the next topic
But I heard this good
It's conspiracy theory that in Vietnam the Viet Cong used to grab USG eyes
They would dig a hole and they would put sharpened bamboo shafts
At the bottom of the hole like they could grow they're like I don't know how to bulb on the bottom of them
I don't know how bamboo grows but anyway, and that's why conspiracy works on people like me because I don't have all the facts but
They dug a hole and they put the sharpened bamboo shafts in there and they put the gi and they buried him up to his neck
And then the bamboo would grow through him because bamboo grows incredibly quickly
It can grow like a foot every couple hours
so the idea was was that you would basically be sitting there and the bamboo would grow through you and it would be super painful and you
would die and
Other GIs would find a soldier buried up to his neck and a bunch of bamboo coming out of his brain
Now what's funny is I it's when you get older you meet all sorts of interesting people
I met a bamboo expert on my vacation
I met a girl who specializes in all sorts of stuff
but one of the things that she was an expert on was bamboo and I of course were at the
Practice dinner for my brother's wedding and I go she tells me
You know what she's talking about, you know, what are you doing? She goes?
Oh, you know that she starts talking about ecological stuff and I don't remember all of it
I just remember her saying the word bamboo and I was like, oh
Have you ever heard the conspiracy theory about and I told you the story I just told you and she said you know
It's funny because I never heard that before but no, that's not how it works
She goes plants take the path of least resistance
So even if you sharpened the bamboo once it started to hit flesh
It would start to move out of the way the bamboo is actually not going to pierce through flesh
It's actually if it wants to grow it will move
It'll start to curve past his leg and then just go straight up
So you may have found a guy surrounded in bamboo buried up to his neck
But it wouldn't have killed him bamboo does go quickly
But it would just touch him and then go it would grow the path of least resistance
so first off I went home and freed all my prisoners and the bamboo traps I made for them and
Secondly, that's the thing again coming back around at the Amazon rainforest. It's the path of least resistance as far as just the
Digitation grows these people had totally cultivated the soil
for
These tropical trees used to be bamboo
They totally cultivated the soil and tilled it and made it great for the trees they needed
But once they left that fertile fertile soil was overtaken by any plant that came by that could survive in there
So who knows what other mysteries are in there?
We'll be covering the Amazon rainforest in a future episode
But again, I just think it's fascinating when we can look at human ingenuity like that and go
They were far smarter than we thought they were so let's go ahead and move on to our second story now
Second story is a little more. Well, it's a lot more grim and it was a request actually
It was on the conspiracy iceberg and this this was a request from Wesley on YouTube
I'm gonna go ahead and read you off a couple incidents here from this chart. These have been verified incidents. They're all gonna be
I'll tell you when they're separate. So I should actually make you choose a number between 1 and 26, but that's quite grim
Case number one woke up boyfriend started beating him attempted suicide
Well jumps case number three punch a stranger to bowling alley
Case number five irrational and aggressive thoughts melt down at work
Case number seven nightmares mood swings attacked fiance with knife
Case number nine threatened mother with shotgun locked self in bathroom
Case number 10 became aggressive and odd attempted to kill self with shotgun
But survived
Case number 11 nightmares anger and depression felt would kill someone
Case number 12 punched policeman threatened others
Case number 15 wanted to get key to gun cabinet to shoot husband
Case number 18 wanted to run off porch and hit neighbors in the face and start killing them case 16 screaming and kicking and sleep
Suicidal feared might attack boyfriend with axe
Case number 20 uncontrollable extreme irritation felt could kill someone and have no remorse
Case number 21 beat her friend broke doors in her own home beat on side of truck
Case number 24 choked his wife in a fit of rage and hung himself
Case number one woke up boyfriend started beating him attempted suicide case number two agitated angry acts that patient could not control hung
self in closet
Case number 13 started hitting daughters came out of room yelled at them shot herself
So couple suicides a lot of violence. These are 26 cases now. Obviously. I could say
26 of anything and the read off the worst of them and you go. Oh man, that sounds dangerous
But it's it's it's quite sad. There was the funny one of
There would I think I skipped it
But where was that funny one that I kept laughing at?
Confronting colleagues at work overturning furniture. So that kind of reminded me the office
but anyway, so what we're talking about here is chantrix now chantrix is a very successful
smoking cessation drug and
The topic on the conspiracy iceberg and the topic that Wesley suggested was chantrix psychosis. So this is the theory
there's a lot of
Debate on what's going on with this chantrix is a drug that helps you to stop smoking. It is the most successful
Thing that you can use to quit stop smoking is chantrix
FDA did a study on it to see if it was healthy
They originally said yeah, it's totally fine when they're steady. It was a fairly small sample group and
The only listed side effects that put you in the hospital other people though kept steady in the drug over the years and
Said depression doesn't that like you can have severe depression and not put you in the hospital
You can overturn furniture at your workplace and it won't put you in the hospital
So they didn't think that was a correct
Assessment for the FDA other people looked into it and they've said that out of all of the anti-smoking options
Chantrix raises your risk of suicide by eight eight times
it octuples
Your chances of killing yourself versus the patch or nicotine gum or any other
Stop smoking drug or method. There was a study that was done saying no no no no the risk of killing yourself is
Actually the same as a placebo that study was sponsored by Pfizer the makers of chantrix
It also raises the risk of heart attacks and seizures so other than having like this
Basically psychosis delusions possible suicide killing yourself and stuff like that
People still use it now at a certain point the FDA said you know what we're gonna put a what we call a black box warning on this product
And it's only on products that have like super severe side effects
So they're like yes. Yes, this is a really good way to quit
But we need to put like basically like you know, they have a black box warning on nicotine say and this can cause mouth cancer
This can cause lung cancer, whatever but in 2016
This is super rare for the FDA to do in 2016. They removed the black box warning from chantrix
And they said listen the risk this is their quote risk of serious side effects on mood behavior and thinking is
lower than previously suspected
5 million people take chantrix
And I know I'm just reading off a bunch of facts here, but we're gonna get into some interesting
I think that's all interesting but 5 million people take chantrix and as far as we know
Reportedly there's been 400 cases of suicidal thoughts and 30 people have killed themselves
So the FDA has said we it's that the yes
It can do that
But if 5 million people take it and we have such a small amount of people just thinking about suicide and even small amount of people
Doing it. We're gonna take off the black box warning. So a couple years ago probably like five or six years ago
I was depressed. It was funny because I was more of like a mix between anxiety and depression and
It got to the point where I was like, you know, because I was moved up here. I didn't have any friends
I was new in town and stuff like that and I'd kind of been battling with
Depression for a while, but not just I didn't I'm a laze. I guess would it be a big term for it?
I remember going to the doctor and I was like, yeah, you know, I just get anxiety a lot and stuff like that
They said if you ever thought about taking anything for it and I go well, I guess it wouldn't hurt
I had it and I don't remember what they put me on I was either
Prozac or a smaller version of Prozac
Because he was like a half version or something like that was like an off something
Because he's like you're not to pry you're not gonna hurt yourself or anything. I'm like no no
I just feel like
Empty it's not like a scary depression. I just felt off and a lot of it had to do so funny cuz he was talking and I go
He goes, what are you depressed a lot about? I'm like, I'm depressed a lot about money
But you know taking a pills not gonna help, you know, paying my rent
He kind of laughed but what it was was I was having normal stressors
But I just was not really dealing with them. Well, I just kind of was ignoring everything
I guess or or I let little things really bug me and it only lasted a couple of months
But he's like, you know, maybe we should try taking this stuff
Maybe we'll see what see what you do with this stuff and it's so bizarre. It's super bizarre
I took it and you deaf your brain chemistry definitely changes now some people
Definitely need to be taking anti depressants
Absolutely like they have a chemical imbalance. I didn't have a chemical imbalance. I was just having depression through life stressors
But I could tell that my brain chemistry was changing
I live alone at this point for the majority of my life and one of the benefits of living alone is you're constantly talking to yourself
You're very introspective as long as you don't have to television on all day long
You're playing video games all day long. You're constantly
Dialoguing with yourself your brain is basically working. You're very just introspective
And so I know who I am and I know how my brain works and how my thought processes are and things like that
So for the first time in my life, I
Felt something it was so bizarre. I remember talking to the doctor. I told everyone this story
It was so bizarre because I'm so aware of who I am as a person as an entity
That once I could tell
Within a few days that this thing in there was basically changing my brain chemistry felt really weird
Felt super bizarre
It would be like if you kept coming home to your house and every day
Little things were moved and I'm not talking to your car keys
But you come home and your television is in the corner of your room and you're like watching your room get rearranged
Over the course of time. That's what it felt like and the dreams were
insane
Absolutely insane
I'm not I hate hearing people's dreams, so I'm not gonna tell you about them
But I remember one dream I woke up and
I was a hundred percent sure that my parents had killed my stepsister
I woke up and I was a hundred percent sure that I helped cover up the murder of my stepsister
And it took me a half hour wide awake
To realize that that never happened
But I was a hundred percent sure that that had happened. It was bizarre
It was that that would be considered a delusional thought. I remember just waking up and being like, oh my god
What if I ever get found out?
And then I had to sit and I had to think no no you saw joy
You you saw her a couple years ago. She didn't get murdered when she was a teenager
To step dad and your mom didn't do it
Super bizarre and here's the thing if you don't have
a strong sense of self. I think
Drugs that mess with your brain can be absolutely devastating and I think that's why they affect people under 18 even more
When we look at people who do you know, they say don't take
Prozac or any of this stuff and that's what chantrix is chantrix. I'm not necessarily isn't necessarily an antidepressant
But it does change your brain chemistry
And the benefit is to quit smoking and I'll get into that in a second
But when you take this and again if you're if you're if you need it absolutely take it
I am not saying in any way shape or form do not take this stuff
Because after I got over the two or three weeks and all of those cases that I read to you
Most of them happened. The longest one that happened
Was 42 days after starting the chantrix most of them happened within the first week
To the first month so very very short incubation time
If you need to take it definitely take it
Just be prepared for that wacky wacky wild ride in the beginning
And then you know that I have a good doctor they warned me about all that stuff and dreams are great
I ended up though eventually saying you know, I don't need this stuff
I took it for probably like five or six months and I go, you know what?
I'm just gonna work out and that worked for me. I said, I think the fact is that I moved up here
I am not active. I'm not walking everywhere like I used to
Don't have any friends. I you know just I don't have any friends and I'm dealing with money problems and stuff like that
I'm just gonna work out more and I remember I saw my doctor the grocery store and he goes, how you doing?
And I was like, well, you know, I quit taking that medicine you gave me is like really I go
Yeah, I go, you know, I'm just gonna work out and he goes you can do that but
You have to treat your working out as your medicine. He goes do it every day
Take a treat it like taking a pill because he knew he was also on the thing that he goes
I really don't think you need this but we'll try it
We'll see what happens. So yeah, he was like, yeah, I totally agree. You probably didn't need that stuff
But you got to work out every day, dude
Because you are you are struggling with with some stuff and I'm sharing that story with you guys in case you guys ever
You know experience this or our experience in this about, you know, my personal journey with it
But anyways, it's also more into this chantrix thing. You take this stuff. It changes your brain chemistry
They say the benefit of stopping smoking outweighs the possibility of you killing yourself
And when you look at the wrong numbers, that's true
5 million people taking it 30 people killed themselves now
They had the four what was it four or 500 people who had suicidal thoughts
It's I don't see in that with the violent outburst or the yelling at your loved ones and stuff like that
So it's they're mostly just looking at the suit the FDA and all that's looking at the suicide stuff
But if you take that out and we start looking at violent outbursts and things like that
Is it really worth it to quit smoking? The FDA says yes smoking is so terrible
Nicotine is so terrible, which I think nicotine is fine
But you know smoking and chewing and all that stuff's unhealthy, but it's so terrible
It's worth taking this drug that at the very least maybe just stop smoking
Or you start punching people overturning furniture or you might kill yourself
Notably absent in all of this stuff. They remove the black box warning
They have these steadies these dueling steadies that are coming out
You cannot take it as of tooth that this really should be the end of this argument really
And they should put that black box back on it and say listen
Okay, maybe you won't kill yourself, but it can make you a little crazy
Maybe you should try every they don't give you lap band surgery right away
They want you to try all sorts of different diets before they cut you open
And again that works for some people have to have that some people have to have that
But they should do the same thing with chantrix. I have no problem the drugs out there people can take it
But there you go. You should exhaust everything possible before you take this
as of 2008
This should be the end of it the FAA the federal aviation administration
Does not allow pilots to use chantrix at all
If you are flying a plane
You cannot take this drug that should be the level of how dangerous this can be
May not make you kill yourself, but it may make you incredibly angry
Or depressed or sobbing. I don't want to pilot overturning furniture
It really should just be the end of it, but
They took the black box warning off the chantrix
People are taking it every day, and I'm glad that it works for most people
But before you decide to take any sort of drug that does affect your brain chemistry
My advice to you would be
How well do you know yourself?
So when those intrusive thoughts those alien thoughts come into your head
Can you deal with them?
Or will they sneak in and trick you into thinking they are part of you?
How well do you know yourself?
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @jsonneauxcarpenter
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great day
You
(upbeat music)