In 1956, a young woman in the Soviet Union is having a dance party with her friends.
Everything's going great until she turned into a statue.
And then what happens when you take ancient demonic rituals and combine them with modern
technology?
The answer will frighten you.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had an awesome weekend.
First off, riding into Dead Rabbit Command on a massive caterpillar.
Blamber!
It's one of our legacy Patreon supporters, Platinum Piss.
Everyone give a round of applause to Platinum Piss.
Eventually that caterpillar will turn into a beautiful butterfly but for now it's just
a big old caterpillar.
It's eating everything green at Dead Rabbit Command.
Platinum Piss you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or if you don't eat plants, that's fine.
Everyone eats plants but if you're not a wolf, if you're not a carnivore, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Really really helps out a lot.
Do wolves eat plants?
I'm going to look that up because I think they do.
Not all the time, not by choice, but I think if a wolf was really hungry he'd be like
I'm eating those berries.
Because dogs eat lettuce and stuff.
If you throw a lettuce at a dog, if you see a dog walking on the street, just throw a
head of lettuce at them and they'll go "Argh!" and they'll eat it.
Don't throw heads of lettuce at dogs but I'm pretty sure like if you gave a dog a hamburger
that had a lettuce on it, it would eat the lettuce.
Everyone's like "No dude, the dogs are allergic to lettuce.
It's worse than chocolate.
I'm all feeding the dog lettuce right now."
I'm pretty sure dogs and wolves eat plants.
That's the episode for today, Platinum.
We got a ton of stuff to cover today so forget that segue.
I'm not going to edit it out but forget it.
I do want to say this though, before we get started on our adventure, I have something
coming up this weekend so I want to be taking a long weekend off.
It'll probably be like a three, maybe four day weekend really depends.
There probably won't be any episodes until Tuesday of next week and I'll do some reminders
through the rest of the week.
Sorry about that guys, I just got something coming up that I can't avoid.
I gotta take care of it.
But everything's fine.
I'm totally healthy.
It's nothing like that so don't worry.
It's something though that I need to take care of.
You're like Jason, that's more mysterious.
I thought it was medical and now that it's not medical, don't worry about it.
If you see any news, if you see anything pop up on the news, that wasn't me.
I wasn't there.
Platinum piss, Platinum piss is my accomplice in this adventure.
I'm going to toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command and we are headed out to the Soviet Union.
And as we're headed out there too, this is a really short story that I'm going to squeeze
in here real quick.
I want you guys to watch this video.
I planned on doing a whole segment on it but I just couldn't, it just wouldn't fit for
time.
And really I want you guys to watch the video.
You guys are going to be chasing me listening to the podcast because I don't like watching
videos.
They hurt my eyes.
There's a video right now on a Facebook page of a Sheriff's Department in Florida.
I'll have the links in the show notes.
I'm going to make it brief.
It's a police officer.
It's Sheriff Deputy Royce James in Edgewater, Florida.
He gets a call about a missing 13 year old girl and he has very, very limited information
at go on.
He's looking for this missing girl who her friend says she went to a hotel with someone
whose name starts with T. He might be Tyler.
He's from Orlando.
And you just, it's this body cam footage.
It's like five minutes.
It's edited together.
This body cam footage of him visiting different motels and asking the manager's questions
and then he gets the one, the manager's kind of like crumpy, kind of like, oh yeah, I'll
get out of bed because he's like, lives on site.
He's all sleeping on the job.
People are trying to check and he's like, go away, go away.
He gets up, he goes and he's like, yeah, this guy checked in earlier, you know, and
he hands the ID to the cop and the cop's like, yeah, I want to know where this guy's at.
I want to know what room this guy's at.
And it's really, really cool.
Like just based on that little bit of information.
And it's also, he goes and he pretends to be like the maintenance crew or the manager
or something to get into the room.
He knocks on the door and he's like, oh, I need to get in a pipe burst.
And the dude's like, there's no pipes in here.
This is a motel six.
There's no running water.
But the cop does get into the room and the dude is absolutely petrified and the cop keeps
asking the dude, how old are you?
How old are you?
Because that's a big point in this with the missing 13 year old girl.
And while he's asking this guy how old he is, you see a blurry shape moving in the background.
It's not a ghost story.
It's not Samara crawling out of the television.
He said, they blur the girl out for privacy because she's underage.
You just see this blurry shape move out of the bedroom and hug the officer.
Because whatever was going through her head when she arranged this date, she got in over
her head.
You know what I mean?
Like you may be thinking, oh, it'll be romantic and she was in over her head.
And the second that police officer showed up, she knew that things were going to be
okay.
And he keeps asking the dude, how old are you?
How old are you?
And the guy is not saying anything.
And he goes, if I have to ask you how old you are one more effin time, I'm going to
lose my mind.
And the guy tells him that he's 22.
And he goes, you effed up, bro.
You effed up.
It's really, and that's the whole story.
I mean, obviously he's going to go to trial and all that stuff.
The evidence is he's in the room and I was looking through the charges and it doesn't
look like anything happened to the girl.
Anything like gross, anything.
I mean, other than, you know, being in that situation in the first place and she wanted
the officer to be with her throughout the whole process, but he's not being charged
with anything sexual.
So that's good.
So after the trial scene video, I recommend you guys checking it out.
I told you the ending, but it's still neat to see it from that perspective without all
the flashy lights.
Except for the police lights.
Those are flashy lights.
Except for all the, like, the Hollywood stuff.
Just literally knocking on doors with very limited information.
This police officer saved a 13 year old girl.
A plurri Bobby 13 year old girl floating in the back room.
So thank you, Sheriff's Deputy Royce James.
It was really cool and I recommend you guys watching that.
Not you, Platinum Piss.
You have to find the world watching the video.
And it's like, oh, that's really cool.
Platinum Piss is crying.
As he's flying us out to Russia, you have a job, bro.
That's why he signed up for the Patreon to not watch videos.
I want to give a shout out for this story.
I got this story.
I did other research, but I found out about this story from a YouTube channel called Obscure
Lodge.
But I want to give a shout out to them because I didn't know the story existed until I came
across it from them.
It's January 1956 and we're in Kubišev, Russia.
Now nowadays, you're like, Jason, I don't know if it's down like that.
I don't think that's pronounced right at all.
Well, maybe not.
But nowadays it's known as Samara Russia.
But as we're walking through the city of Kubišev, the streets seem empty.
There's like tumbleweed.
There's like Russian tumbleweed rolling down the street.
And then there's like birds.
You know what that means?
There's always birds.
There's no people around.
There's birds there.
The place looks empty, but we see everyone in town is gathered around a house and everyone's
like, get out of the way, man.
I want to look through the window.
And like dads are holding up their kids and the kids are like, papa, papa, this is a miracle.
This is miraculous.
And the dad's like, I wish I could see.
I wish I didn't have kids.
I wish my kids were so strong they could hold me up.
The reason why everyone's staring at this house is because inside this house, there's
a statue.
Not just any statue, it's a human statue.
Not just a statue that's shaped like a human, because there's tons of those.
It's a human frozen in place.
Oh!
Now let's go back in time a week.
The crowd fades away.
The statue is not a statue.
It's actually a young woman named Zoya.
And she shares this house with her mother.
And Zoya is a party in girl.
She's having lots of fun.
As much fun as you can have in 1956 Soviet Union.
I'm sure it wasn't a ton of fun, but I'm sure you find something to do, right?
Well she did.
Zoya found something to do.
I'm turning her into a statue, but she found something to do.
The mother went to church.
The mother would go to church and one day, Sunday in particular, Zoya's like, yeah mom,
I'll go to church later.
She's like, well there's only one service.
That's not the way it works.
And Zoya's like, what?
What?
Can't hear you.
And so the mother, I don't know if they had that type of relationship.
I don't know if she out and out lied to her mother.
But the point is, is the mother went to church one day and Zoya stayed home and she decided
to have a party at the house.
Zoya was engaged to a guy named Nicholas.
And Nicholas was supposed to come to the party and Zoya's like, oh girls, don't you just
love my fiance?
He's totally awesome.
I can't wait to dance with him and all the other girls are just dancing.
And Zoya is so desperate to dance with Nicholas.
Any Nicholas at this point.
She grabs an icon of St. Nicholas off the wall and proclaims to the whole crowd.
If there is no my Nicholas, then I will dance with St. Nicholas.
She starts dancing with this little statue.
Now her friends realize this is a bad idea.
I think we would all laugh, right?
I mean, I don't know if you're Eastern Orthodox.
Sorry, if you are.
And you'd be super upset by this.
But I think if someone said that and they're dancing with little statue, am I wrong?
Am I wrong in that?
Like, people are on sound subscribing to the podcast.
No, if you saw someone dancing with a little statue of St. Patrick, would you be like,
I'm sure people do that all the time.
Is that offensive?
But apparently in the Soviet Union it is.
It was and might still be.
But she's dancing with this little statue of St. Nicholas.
And her friends are like, stop the music, stop the music.
Quit doing that.
She's like, do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do