Did Jeffrey Epstein kill himself? Commit suicide? Or was he cloned? And then a young woman leaves
her house one day and someone throws a bowl of blood all over her. And then things get
weird. Today on Dead Rava Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rava Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
or I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys
had a great, great weekend.
Two quick things I wanted to talk about. One, I have a listener, a personal friend of mine
I know her personally. Robin, it's Robin's birthday. Let's give her a hand even though
she won't listen to this episode being recorded on her birthday. But she's a really cool kid.
She's a professional fashion person. Like people pay her to dress them. Like she comes out
and she talks to them for a while and goes, "Where are you at now? Where do you want to
be in five years?" She picks out their clothes. She goes and she buys all their clothes. She's
a really, really fascinating person to talk to. So happy birthday Robin. I've been on
her for quite a few years. She's really cool. She listens to the show as well. And you'll
notice the art is different for today's episode. That was provided by John from the Scar Group.
Oh, mysterious. He seems to be a really cool guy. I don't know him as well as I know Robin,
but I've talked to him a bit online. Great. That art works amazing. It was a hand sketched
art. He was posting versions of it on Instagram as he was doing it. And it's just amazing.
And it's funny because I sent it to Ash Black. Ash Black drew the normal logo we use on the
show and I'm like, "Someone made fan art based on your art." The original logo, he just made
when he was listening to Dead Rabbit Radio. I had an old version of the art. So it's
just interesting to see how this community works. And Ash Black was like, "Dude, that's
totally awesome." And I was like, "I know. It is awesome." So yeah. And it's funny because
eventually I think someone will sketch something from John's art and come up with a new image
on that. So I think I might flip the images back and forth every once in a while just
to change things up. But Ash Black, that's still our official art for the show, but the
John art is just this amazing gritty reboot, gritty retcon, however you want to put it.
It's funny because I never noticed the teeth on the Dead Rabbit logo until John drew them.
And I was like, "Oh yeah. I guess he does have teeth. I guess he does have things." So
thanks to Ash Black, thanks to John from SCAR, the SCAR group. And thank you to Grant Scott
as well. He does our, as above so below, image as well. Just an amazing artist that I've met.
So let's go ahead and move on to our first story. Now I want to say this. This is actually
a second draft. I originally recorded a 15 minute segment on the ins and outs of the
Jeffrey Epstein case and all of the ties to the different political factions and the rumors
of this and that and everything. And I edited it and it was about 15 minutes long and when
I got to the end of it, I go, "This is boring. This is really, really boring." It's nothing
more than what you can read in the newspaper. I try to cover conspiracy theories that aren't
mainstream and this one has gone mainstream, which is odd because I predicted a couple
of videos ago that conspiracy theories are going to become incredibly mainstream. Both
sides of the political aisles are thrown out accusations that the Clintons did it, that
Trump did it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. So I recorded all that stuff and I was bored editing it
and I figured you guys would be bored listening to it. And again, it's nothing more you can't
learn by reading any series of websites. So I took it out. It was just, it's not one,
it's not a story that I particularly have fun talking about because of the subject matter.
If you don't know, Jeffrey Epstein was a pedophile who quote unquote killed himself. I personally
think, because I maybe you guys want to know what my personal opinion is, I personally think
that it's that he may have killed himself. Obviously, that's the obvious answer, but
it's very, very, very, very, very suspicious. And I kind of just went on for about 15 minutes
talking about different facts of the case and it was super, super boring. But all that
being said, because I know people are going to say, Hey, how can we get in common on the
case? That's, it's boring to me personally, but I, it's very, very suspicious that, that
he died when he died. But what I find fascinating about it is you have the both sides of political
aisle throwing out different conspiracy theories at each other, which may or may not be valid.
We don't know is the has to go through this whole investigation thing, but like most, most
criminal acts do, but like that, like that, remember when 9/11 happened? Of course you
do 9/11 happens. And then people start saying there was control demolitions and that inside
job and all this stuff. And then people said, no, no, no, you guys, you guys are wrong. You
guys who believe the planes brought down the buildings, you guys are wrong. And you guys
who believed it was an inside job are wrong. It was actually holographic planes or space
lasers or time loops or whatever. There's always someone out there who wants to outweard
both sides of the conspiracy and it's happened already, already. There are reports online,
just flittering whispers actually, just see them pop up here and there. I wasn't able
to actually find a particular website because I would just read them and then it would just
disappear in the wind like dust, right? Because people realize how stupid it is. But trust
me, this will gain traction. This will gain traction. Jeffrey Epstein was cloned. Do you
see the body that was wheeled out on the gurney doesn't look like Jeffrey Epstein. Did you
know that? Look at these two pictures. I'm going to show you a picture of Jeffrey Epstein's
mugshot photo and then I'm going to show you a picture of a corpse. Now, I used to work
in a crematory. I think I've told you guys about that before and that aside, I've seen
a lot of dead people and you don't generally look the same when you die. One, your soul's
gone. So that's a really weird thing to look at a body when no soul, but your blood settles,
your bloat in certain weird places, fluids collect and all sorts of stuff. You're not
going to have the same rosy cheeks you had in your mugshot photo when you're laying
down lifeless on a gurney. But people say no, no, no. See, they cloned Jeffrey Epstein
and put the clone on a gurney and then they let Jeffrey Epstein out because he's so good
at providing the elites with these kids that we need him on the outside. So let me ask
you guys, anyone who believes in that theory or when you come across, because this theory
will take off, trust me, I believe this is a very, very up and coming conspiracy theory.
This is why I want you to ask those people. You can run into them, you're at Starbucks,
you're drinking your coffee. So I'm going to walk, say, with a shirt that says, "I cloned
Jeffrey Epstein and all I got was his lousy t-shirt." And you go, "Hey, hey, can I talk
to you about your conspiracy theory?" And they're like, "Someone's paying attention
to me?" Yeah, and they sit down next to you and they're taking a bunch of Splendor packets
and putting it in their coffee. That's what I do. I don't know why I attributed him that.
I just take like five Splendor packets. But anyways, he goes, "Yes, yes, here, you want
to hear my conspiracy theory?" "Jeffrey Epstein was cloned and then he tells you the whole
nonsense that I just told you." These are your questions you should ask. First off,
who cloned him? When did we get cloning technology? How did they sneak the clone into the jail
and him out of the jail? Those are all valid questions. If he was cloned, why didn't they
clone him on the outside and have his clone get arrested in the first place? Why would
you need him to get young girls when alone America has a huge human trafficking problem
and a huge subset of that is children? So it's not like there's just one guy in the
country who can do it. You can go to pretty much any major city, talk to three or four
pimps and find what you're looking for. That's not a selling point. It's absolutely tragic,
but America has a huge human trafficking problem. Why would you need this guy? If you had the
ability to clone people, let's go with this. At this point, the guy's getting a little
nervous. He's slowly stirring his coffee. He's looking from side to side trying to plot his
escape. If you can clone people, why would you clone the pimp? Wouldn't you clone the
prostitutes? Wouldn't you clone the victims and then you wouldn't ever have to worry about
anything? You wouldn't have to have a new pimp go out and find a new girl. You'd have
a hundred versions of the same girl. I think one of the big problems with conspiracy theory
is that it's not questioned enough. Most people, when they hear ridiculous conspiracy theories,
they just let them stand. They go, "Ah, what? You're an idiot." And they just walk away.
And then the person is allowed to exist in their echo chamber and stuff never gets questioned.
Sometimes we should take our time out to actually argue these things down. Really, we really
should, even if it's just five or ten minutes a day. I used to do that all the time. I used
to debate people who didn't believe we landed on the moon. I'd debate them until the cows
came home. I thought it was the funniest thing in the world to debate people who don't believe
we landed on the moon. It's one of the easiest things to debate. And here's the way to do
it. Just ask questions. If you start presenting other facts, which is generally how we win
arguments, and someone says, "Hey, we never landed on the moon." And you go, "Well, we
took photos. Like, there's photos of the moon." And we were up there and people were bringing
back rocks, explaining the rocks and stuff like that. And there's like, you're presenting
them with facts. The best thing to do is, what I always do is go, "Who would make it
up?" And they'd answer that. And there's obviously a logical flaw in it, because it's not true.
We did land on the moon. Who would make that up? Well, NASA's a satanic organization that
said, "Oh, okay." And then you can start to take apart their argument. You don't want
to present an argument to them, because they will have an argumentative book. They've already
talked to all their friends, so they know how to argue stuff like, "Why are there no stars
on the moon?" You know why there's no stars on the moon, like in those moon photos? Because
they were taken during the day. But they'll say, if I presented that fact to them, they'll
just be, "Oh, no, NASA airbrushed out the... I don't know how I got on the moon land."
And they're talking about Jeffrey Epstein. But the point is, is like, if you present
a fact, they'll have a counterfact for you, and they'll just disregard the fact. The point
is, is to make a conspiracy theorist's brain start to work. You're basically the jumper
cables trying to get that car started. Why would they make it up? Why didn't the Russians
cover it up for them? They say, "Because we paid the Russians off in wheat, because they're
having a huge food shortage." And I go, "Yeah, that normally works with other countries,
when we pay them off with money." Like, if North Korea says, "We won't build nukes if
you give us money, and we give them money, and then two years later they're building
a nuke," that works, right? But before I let them answer that, I'll ask them another question
about what they're talking about. And you just are getting that, their brain to start
to think, "That is a little weird." Like, let's say we did give the Russians a bunch
of wheat, so we'd union a bunch of wheat so they would lie about the moon landing. Why
would they keep that secret for the next 60 years? And they start, you know, get those
gears turning. Why is NASA a, if NASA is a satanic organization, what about India's
space program? What about China's space program? You can do that with any conspiracy theory.
When someone presents a ridiculous conspiracy theory to you, simply ask questions. Simply
just ask question after question after question, and then you're allowed to walk away at any
point. When you're a time is more valuable than talking to that lunatic, but it makes
them think. If you present them with facts, they'll just shut down. They'll be like, "No,
no, it's a satanic conspiracy." Okay, give me some names of people who started this satanic
conspiracy. Where did this person get their satanic training? Where did you get this information
from? And you just keep asking them questions, and eventually they'll get to a point where
they don't have an answer. And that's the ultimate weapon against ridiculous conspiracy
theories like Jeffrey Epstein being cloned. A lot of times people who put out conspiracy
theories go, "Hey man, I'm just asking questions. I'm not being disrespectful to 9/11 victims.
I'm simply asking questions." So that's what we can do too, is ask questions as well. That
thing right there was infinitely more entertaining than 15 minutes of me going through the Jeffrey
Epstein case. So we're going to go ahead and jump back into the story. You're going to
hear me go, "Blech!" as I finish up the Jeffrey Epstein story, and let's go to Bolivia. Let
us hop on board the Carbonercopter and head to Bolivia. But first, you're going to hear
this. "Blech!" We're done with that story. Which I'm sure you guys are all relieved of.
I mean, you know, no one likes talking about this stuff, but it's such big news. I had
to cover it. So let's all hop on board the Carbonercopter. Let's get on board. We are
flying out to Bolivia, and we are about to explore probably one of my new favorite stories
that I've found. I never knew this story existed until probably Thursday, and I was immediately
like, "This is dope, dude. This is really cool." So we are flying to Bolivia. So we're all
on board the Carbonercopter. And as we're flying out, we're going to go back in time
as we usually do. Then we reappear, and we are in Opalco, Bolivia. Very, very poor region.
At least back then. I don't know. It could be bustling metropolis now, but it used to
be really, really poor. Okay? And there was this girl named Valentina Flores, 24-year-old
mom, mom, single mother. No, she wasn't single mother. She just had one baby. That's what
I meant. She's not walking around one day. She leaves the house. She's kind of just walking
around. She has no friends. There's no one else living in the area. Her husband's off
doing work for the government. Because they're super poor, and she stays home in farms, and
he goes and basically the government's like, "Do this," and he'd get up and go do it,
and then get paid. Not a lot of money, though. They're poor. And she's walking around outside
and someone throws a bowl of blood at her. And she's like, "The worst prank ever." I
mean, I get cream pies, her little cliche, but a bowl of blood is a tall escalation.
So she gets covered in blood. She's like, "What?" And when she finally wipes the blood
from her eyes, she's like, "Aww, you knucklehead!" She's getting ready to bonk him on the head.
No one's there. No one's there. And she's like, "That's weird." I mean, the blood part
was weird, too, but the disappearing act, quite odd. Now we're going to jump ahead. That
happened a few days before this event. Now, your skeptic alarms are going to be going
off this whole story. This whole story, because mine were two. So let me get into this real
quick. I've tried really, really hard to debunk this. There's basically two types of made-up
stories when we deal with the show. One, the person who's telling the story totally made
it up, which is possible, obviously. And the second one, which is more troubling, is the
internet made it up. That was something we came across when I covered the Lone Pine Devils.
And then a listener, I don't remember their name, I'm so sorry, but I mentioned it on
the episode that I corrected it on. A listener said, "That story is completely made up.
It's based on this YouTube video." And sure enough, there was not a single mention of
this story of the Lone Pine Devils before the YouTube video. So when I started to look
into this, I go, "I can't prove whether or not she made it up. That's pretty hard."
But I can assure you that this story is not created by the internet. I tracked this story
came out in 2001 from a Spanish book, and the first mention of it online is like August
2001, and it was mentioned in this context. So she could have made it up, but it's not
an urban legend that was made up on the internet that everyone just repeats and passes around.
I'm shocked this story isn't more famous, but let's go ahead and get into it. So I want
you to put peace of mind that I've done my due diligence to see whether or not this is
fake. She could have made it up, but we'll accept her out of her word as we tell this
story of Valentina. So it's May... This is going to set off your skeptic alarms, too.
It's either May 10th or May 14th in the year 1967 or 1968. So that, again, set off my skeptic
alarm. But considering it's such a rural region, she's illiterate. She's from an indigenous
Indian tribe known as the Kuikua tribe of Indians in Bolivia. So it's not like they
have a farmer's almanac hanging out. I'll accept that the dates differ from different
versions of this story, but most of the details are the same. Okay, so we got all of that
out of the way. Now you can take off your skeptic hats and enjoy this story. So Valentina
Flores is 24 years old, and her husband's off again working for the government. So she's
there, and it's her job to, one, take care of their precious little infant baby, little
baby on her back. She has like a... One of those things that wraps around your front,
and then there's like a little baby chilling in the back with a bow and arrow. What were
those things? Weren't there bamboo shkas or something like that? I don't know. Anyways,
this one is called a manta in this part of the world. But anyway, so she's hanging out
there, her baby's on her back, and she has 64 sheep and a bunch of llamas. And this is
how they make their money. They have to have the sheep for the wool, and they make stuff
or sell the wool or whatever. The sheeps are a big part of their livelihood, so are the
llamas. So this is basically what would be the equivalent of, you weren't going to bank,
but your money can walk away at any time or be eaten by wolves at any time. So she's always
constantly having to keep an eye on her business. There's a bunch of livestock. So she's walking
around with her baby on her back, taking care of farm stuff, right? I've never been to a
farm. I don't know what they do, but anyways, she's doing stereotypical farm stuff. She's
throwing hay, building houses, watching sheep. But then she realizes, she turns around and
she realizes all the llamas are gone. She's like, "Dagnabbit, if I ain't never seen nothing
worse than that." And so she starts stomping on, she gets into her jalapeno. And so the
llamas are completely gone. She throws her hat in the dirt, she's stepping on it. And
so she starts trying to find the llamas. So she starts walking all over, it's like a real
hilly region. She starts walking all over the hills, she's like, "Llamas." It's a 45-minute
walk before she finally finds her herd of llamas. So at this point, she's very, very
upset. And she herds them back, she brings them all back, and she's like, "Let's get
back to the house. I got 64 sheep to take care of." But as she starts to come over
a hill with all of her llamas, she notices something really, really weird. So she put
the sheep in this stone corral before she left. But as she's coming over the hill with
her army of llamas, she sees something covering up the stone corral. And she noticed it looks,
the way she described it was, there was a pipe sticking out of the top, and then this
plastic web-like coating, almost like a circus tent coming out of the top of the pipe and
covering the entire corral. So she can't really see what's in the corral. And she's
like, "I didn't leave that there. That's not mine, right? Who is messing with my sheep?"
So she kind of like puts down, she's like, "Llamas, stay here." She holds her hand up
so they all stop. And she's like doing the army belly curl. She comes around and she
looks into basically a tent flap of the tent, of the big plastic thing that's covering
her corral. And what she sees is shocking. So she looks in, she's like a little boy,
like a little boy sneaking in the circus. She like peeks in, trying to see like an elephant.
She sees a three-foot-tall man in there, this little white dude, this little white guy with
blonde hair, blue eyes, and a giant red mustache. He's described as chubby and young. So imagine
me with a mustache for the rest of the... Imagine 12-year-old Jason, I wasn't three feet tall,
I don't think, but imagine 12-year-old Jason for the rest of this story, the giant mustache.
The little chubby boy, sitting inside this tent. But it's not just me and a tent. What
she sees is me and a tent surrounded by 63 slaughtered sheep. Just guts hanging out, jaw
bones missing, eyeballs gone. It looks like a horror movie, except this horror movie is
her livelihood. And as she's looking in, she sees chubby little man have a chain attached
to like a belt. And on the end of the chain is this large hook that he's been using to
cut the sheep open. And on both sides of the boy, he had two plastic satchels filled with
sheep guts. Now, again, let's put our skeptic hats on for a second. I don't care how big
the satchels are or what you're pulling out of sheep. I don't think you can fit 63 of
anything, anything's guts, in two side satchels. I just don't think that's possible. But let's
take our skeptic hats back off. And he's about to kill her last sheep. And she flips out.
Right? She totally loses it. So she picks a rock up and she throws it at little dude
and hits him in the head. And she's throwing rocks at him and he's yelling at her in a
language she doesn't understand. And she just, she doesn't care at this point. She's seeing
all of her sheep killed. She begins just picking up rocks and throwing them at her. And the
little dude's like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. And eventually the little dude's had enough
of it. He goes and he starts winding this thing up there. She said, look like a radio,
like just basically was a box. And as he's winding it up, the plastic tent over the,
I know the story sounds insane, but I love it. The plastic tent over the corral basically
winds up and gets sucked into the metal pole that was sitting in the middle of her farm.
At that point, she sees a second three foot tall chubby little boy on the opposite side
of the corral that was blocked from view because of the tent. The second dude sees her, sees
what's going on and books it, dude. He just goes in the opposite direction, starts running
away as fast as his chubby little legs can take him. Then he sits down in a chair and
hits a button and these propellers start going off. And the chair goes, and she just
flies away, leaves his dude there who's being assaulted by this woman. So the dude looks
at her and she looks at him and he's in this stone corral surrounded by dead sheep, gutted
sheep and the sheep he was going to cut open and run away at this point. He's like, thanks,
gives Valentina high five, books it hangs out with the llamas who must be terrified by this
whole situation. Little dude's looking at her, she's looking at him, she goes, let's
rock. And everyone's like, yeah, yeah. Just like episode of married children, this one's
a little more violent. She ends up pulling out a club. She keeps a cudgel with her, right?
She like pulls it out, spins it around in her hand, spinning it over her head like an
ninja. It's a wooden club that has a iron tip to it and she steps into the corral, stepping
over sheep carcasses, flies must be everywhere at this point. Little guy's looking up at
her and he's like, uh-oh, this is not going to end well. And she bashes this dude over
the head. Now I should say right now, it wasn't actually two chubby boys who had wandered
into her carral and just started getting sheep. It wasn't, so yeah, it was just two little
boys were hanging out on their property killing sheep, which would deserve a butt kicking.
But the implication of these kids are aliens. I hope you guys picked up on that as this
next part starts. She picks up her, she has her cudgel and she bashes this dude right in
the face and he's trying to talk to her the whole time in this language that she just
doesn't understand at all. Well, no matter what he was saying, we're trying to cure,
we're trying to help the environment with those hippie aliens that are trying to help
everything. No, we have to kill 64 sheep or your world will be doomed. It wouldn't matter.
It was her livelihood. She bashes him in the face and he just starts leaking. He just starts
bleeding all over the place and at this point he's screaming at her and she goes for another
blow, right? She's just brain this kid and the hook thing he has attached to the chain,
he picks it up. It was originally designed to kill sheep, to gut sheep. He throws it
at her and she tries to do a matrix dodge. It doesn't work. It actually hits her and
cuts her chest and then as it's like going up, he throws it and it flies back to him because
he pulls it on the chain. But as it's making that arc, it basically hits her chest, cuts
her chest, cuts her face and then comes back to him and then he's like spinning it and
he's like, you want to go again? You understood that, right? You understood that? And she's
standing there. She's all cut up and she said, "I think it would have went straight into
me if I wasn't wearing the manta that was holding the baby on you on the back." And
I'm assuming the baby is wide awake and screaming at this point because basically everything
that could go wrong is going wrong. As he's getting ready to do another throw of this
thing, she takes her cudgel and she smashes his hand so badly. Again, this isn't a put
on a skeptic hat for a second. This is something that if you were an alien, you'd have to be
pretty weak. She hits his arm, his right arm so badly that it begins bleeding and is immediately
immobilized. Like, I can imagine getting hit so hard in the arm it gets broke and then
you can't use it, but I've had quite a few broken bones. I've never bled, to be fair,
I've never been hit with an iron cudgel, but anyway, she just smashes his arm. He's screaming.
His face is bleeding, his arm is bleeding. He's like, "I'm out of here." He runs, he
gets in a chair as well, hits a button, flies off after his buddy. Her husband comes back,
"Where's all of her sheep? What you do?" And she's like, "You won't believe the day
I had." She's in there drinking whiskey. He's like, "That's all the whiskey we have."
She's like, "Yeah, well, I need it." She tells him the story. Eventually the
blivvy army gets notified. They come out and they collect the carcasses of all the sheep
and they also scrape up the ground where these weird creatures had been to get the blood.
I shouldn't have that. They weren't just scraping up dirt. They scraped up where the
aliens' blood had dropped and then they left. Now, this incident devastated the farm so
badly that Valentina and her little baby and her husband had to move away to another
town. They couldn't be up here anymore because they didn't have any reason to be up there.
All of their sheep had died. Alamas, they're just like, "You're lame. You're not good
enough." And that all happened in 1967. In 2001, a famous Spanish author and UFO investigator
named JJ Benitez found out about this story and was able to track her down. She was in
another region and she's like, "Oh yeah. Come and take a seat. Talk to you about this
stuff." And she's telling him the story and he goes, "Oh yeah. You know, cattle mutilations
are a thing and these are..." Which is funny because I talk trash about cattle mutilations
all the time but I love this story. He's like, "You know, cattle mutilations are a thing
and UFOs come down and they abduct them." And as he's telling her all this stuff, she's
just sitting there drinking tea. She goes, "I don't care. I don't care. I don't care
about UFOs. I don't care about aliens. All I care about is that all my sheep got killed."
She was illiterate. The whole family was illiterate. The baby was illiterate, obviously. And even
in 2001, she had never looked into UFOology. She didn't care about aliens. She thought all
that stuff was just like whatever. I don't care. Don't tell me about it. It means nothing
to me. Which is an interesting thing because we've covered stuff like that before where
people who've had close encounters with alien life who don't have any idea of what aliens
are or flying saucers and stuff like that. So is this a genuine case of cattle mutilation?
I'm not for sure. I think it's fascinating because most cattle mutilation takes place
out of sight. They just find cows or find human bodies or whatever it is and they're
like, "Ah, aliens." But this is a story. This is the only one that I've ever seen of someone
actually watching the aliens mutilate livestock. Which is an interesting spin on it. But I
find the story fascinating. I find the story fascinating nonetheless. And that's one of
the fun things about doing this show is I'll talk trash about all sorts of stories that
have tons of sources. And every show often I'll come across a very intriguing story that
has one source that was, you know, 50, 60 years ago. And I'm just like, "Oh, the story's
awesome." Stories where people beat up aliens might be my favorite. This is the second one
now I found. A couple episodes ago we did the Finland special and that involved the
lumberjack chasing an alien away with a chainsaw. Which I found infinitely amusing and this
one's even better because she totally beat it up. And I have to add, actually, I forgot
to add this. This is another thing. You know, the beginning I had to add in later. I realized
I forgot this. The bucket of blood. The bowl of blood, right? I started off the story with
that. She doesn't know, even after all the stories, she doesn't know, nobody knows who
threw the bowl of blood on her. It's a total mystery. Was it related to the aliens? Who
knows? Was it alien blood? Who knows? Was it some sort of portent? Was it some sort of
foreshadowing that she was going to have this alien encounter and drenched in blood? Nobody
knows. I like to imagine that somewhere out there in the cosmos, there's a race of chubby
little, chubby little alien people on the planet Chubbular. All the buildings are made
out of sheep guts. They're walking around and eventually these spaceship goes lands,
right? Two flying chairs come out of it. No, one flying chair and it's soon on a flying
stretcher. Everyone's like, "What happened? What happened to you guys? Did you guys bring
our new building material?" The dude's like, "Oh dude, shut up. I need to go to the doctor."
So he goes to the doctor and eventually all their scientists, military officials are
talking to Tiny Jason. You won't believe it, man. I'm standing there. We have the best
technology in the world. We can travel the cosmos. He just gave me a hook to defend myself
and they're like, "That's all you should need, sir." Not sir. You lost. You got demoted,
private and he's like, "Uh." And then they're like, "So what happened?" He's like, "Well,
there's this woman. She's an average sized woman, so she's like five foot six." And they're
like, "Oh my God, they're all giants there." He's like, "They are." She begins picking
up rocks, throwing them at me. That was the extent of her skills. And then she beat me
up with a big old stick. Big old stick. And they're like, "A stick did this to you."
And he's like, "Yes." A stick wielded by a giant. And then he's like, "Give me more
pain medication. I'll tell you more." You give me a little bit more of that delicious
alien pain medication. I'll tell you more. But eventually her story would have become
legend on Chubb Ular. This feisty young woman with a baby strapped to her back beat back
alien invaders. The moral of the story is don't mess with earth. The moral of the story
actually is don't be afraid of aliens, because I have a lot of friends who are afraid of
aliens. Because aliens for all their spaceships and their psychic powers and their big old
reptilian bodies or little gray bodies or chubby bodies in this case, they're still flesh
and bone. And flesh can be torn and bone can be broken. Earth. Earth. Earth. Or I want
you to say with me, I want you to know that you do not mess with planet earth. Because
at any point in time, we can reach down and pick up a rock. It's on. Aliens. I challenge
you. Every so often I do an episode like this, I think, "What if I get abducted by aliens
tonight?" Like, what if they're like, "Okay, we're done with this. This guy's talking so
much trash about us." The intergalactic war may have started in 1967 when a woman bashed
an alien's head. And if that story is true, we're well on our way to victory.
[Music]
(upbeat music)