A baseball mystery that's lasted decades.
Who shut off the lights.
I'm making it sound super dramatic, but it is an interesting mystery.
And let me take a look at the story of the stone clad.
A race of people that may have lived among the Native Americans.
They were 12 feet tall, their skin was hard as stone, and they feasted on human flesh.
Did these creatures actually exist?
And if they did, where are they now?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[MUSIC]
Yee-haw!
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
The reason why I'm Yee-hawing is because we're on Jason's farm.
[MUSIC]
There's like pigs walking around and stuff like that.
They work there.
They're not the livestock.
They're fucking in.
They're just such a cow getting ready to get milk.
I just posted that YouTube video.
A lot of people didn't expect it.
A lot of people didn't know what it was.
It was me working at my friend's farm.
And also working at my friend's farm.
Let's bring in our Patreon supporter for today.
It's SqueezeGod.
SqueezeGod.
We're clapping.
We don't see him.
We're looking around.
We see a pregnant cow.
A cow's giving birth to SqueezeGod.
Coming out.
He's learning to walk.
Little legs, little legs.
I'll get covered.
Why am I supporting your Patreon, dude?
I'm covered in embeotic fluid.
Oh, we're going to clean you off.
And we're going to give you a job.
You have to immediately have to get to work.
You're late.
You should have been born five minutes ago.
SqueezeGod, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't
support the Patreon or if you're not half cow, that's fine too.
Just helps spread the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
I posted some YouTube videos of me holding down a pig as this dude was clipping its nails.
I wanted to give you guys some background for that because YouTube videos just kind of
popped up in people who was like, "Dinner time," and people go, "What's this?"
And it's just the sound of this pig screaming.
First off, the pig's totally fine.
This is a routine thing.
Secondly, I want you guys to feel good about these pig-os in this farm.
These are, there's four pigs here.
Joy, the one we are clipping the nails of.
She's 15 years old and she and all of her other pig friends there actually came from
research laboratories.
They actually were rescues.
So basically after the research was done, after they taught them telepathic powers and
they're floating around the room, they're like, "We must destroy these pigs."
My friend, every show often she rescues two pigs from this local research facility.
She doesn't like breaking the window.
They're like, "No, the rescue pig bandit's back."
She has an agreement with them that they let her take the pigs home.
And it's really cool actually, she found out that out this research facility, I don't know
exactly which one it is, so I'm not going to say.
It's like Cyberdyne or Waylon, Utahnee or something like that.
No, it's a local facility here, but they treat them really nice.
Like they are doing experiments on them and they know they're going to have to kill them
after the experiments over, but they have like enrichment hours and they get special
toys and they get like red books.
They're freeing them with the wind and the willows.
The pigs are like, "I don't understand this.
I don't know English."
But it's the thought that counts.
So yeah, Joy, she's 15 years old and then there was Waylon in the video.
He's maybe like 10 years old, he's 500 pounds.
So go check out that video on YouTube.
I think it's really cool.
It's basically me holding a pig dance close up of a pig's back in my hands going, "It's
okay, Joy.
It's okay as I'm rubbing her little bristles."
And she's screaming, but immediately, she was in no pain whatsoever.
It was fear.
It's okay, right?
You can be in fear, wasn't it?
Immediately afterwards, she just laid down to go nap.
So she's totally fine.
And she is walking.
She wasn't walking before.
We were like, "Jason, this is an agricultural podcast.
Just get to the goats.
Get to the goats."
I just want to say that she's doing totally fine.
All the other piggoes are doing fine.
Chickens and goats and everything like that.
Look at SqueezeGod.
SqueezeGod is now milking himself.
That came out wrong.
Everything.
You have this farm is fine.
But check out those videos.
I think you guys will have a bowl.
That was a really long introduction, but I thought it was an important part of the Dead
Rabbit Mythos.
Me at a farm.
SqueezeGod, let's toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgable.
We're leaving behind Jason Farms.
We are headed out to Baltimore, Maryland.
Specifically we're going to Camden Yards.
That's where the Baltimore Orioles play.
Dude is on a pitcher's mound and he's like throwing the ball and the guy's all sweaty.
He's just a big sweaty guy at home base and he swings that bat, crack, and hits it and
the ball sails away and the first baseman is trying to grab it.
He's leaving the base.
They're like, no, no, that's for the outfielders.
And then he bumps into a bunch of outfielders and it ends up on the highlight reel and he
loses his job.
Typical day at a baseball stadium.
People are constantly getting fired for leaving their stations.
We're back in the year 1997.
The reason why we're here is infielder Cal Ripken Jr. is about to set the record for
the most played consecutive baseball games.
Originally, Luke Gehrig set it in 1939.
That record existed from 1939, the most played games in a row, until September 6, 1995.
That was when Cal Ripken beat the record.
So now we're in the year 1997.
It's August 14, 1997 and he is still just blowing this record out of the park.
August 14, 1997, the Orioles and the Seattle Mariners are facing off in Oriole Park.
Things ready to go.
Someone brought the ball.
They forgot that the last game.
They're like, oh no, we can't play baseball without a ball.
Everyone had to go home.
They brought the ball this time.
Everyone has their bats ready.
And just before 7pm when the game is about to begin, a bank of lights behind the first
base dugout goes out.
So they go and they fix it and the umpire goes, play ball!
And everyone's like, yeah, yeah, that's what we came here for.
The bank of lights goes out again behind the first base dugout.
So let's fix it.
Fixing it.
Play ball!
Bank of lights goes back off.
This goes on from 7pm till around 9pm.
Every time they fix the lights and they turn it back on, a circuit breaker is thrown and
it kills the lights again.
At 9.15pm, finally the ref comes out and it's doing all the hand motions and stuff like
these thrown up game signs.
Arrival gangs are driving by, cheating them.
He's doing all the hand signs.
Game is off.
We can't play the game without these lights.
We probably could have started it back at 7pm when the sun was slightly still up, but
now no go.
Also Bloods for Life.
So calling this game actually puts the Orioles at a disadvantage because that means tomorrow
they'll have to play a double header.
They'll have to play two games in a row because you have to stay on schedule with this thing.
But what are you going to do?
You can't play without this Bank of Lights.
So there's a conspiracy involving this.
There's a conspiracy involving why the lights kept going out.
So let's go back to earlier in the afternoon of August 14th, 1997.
Cal Ripken Jr. is getting ready for the night's game.
He's driving home.
He just got done playing a game for the Chicago Bulls.
He's playing the most games ever in a row.
They didn't know that.
Not just baseball.
He pulls up to his house and he's walking up and he hears a "e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e
He's starting to put stuff together.
He knows that that is the sound of a mattress moving.
And the mattress move was not supposed to be here until tomorrow.
So it sounds like someone's having sex.
And it's not him, but he's in his house.
He's not the smartest guy in the world.
He's like, "Ugh, what's going on?
Someone's having sex, but it's not me."
His wife is at home.
And so is his best friend, Kevin Costner.
And he opens the bedroom door and there is Kevin Costner straight up delivering the mail
like the postman to her water world.
It's about time he pulled out his tin cup.
I don't know.
It's the only movies I know of Kevin Costner.
He made her dance like wolves.
That's it.
What else was he in?
It doesn't matter.
It beats up Kevin Costner.
Kevin Costner's like, "No, no, I got a movie tomorrow.
Doesn't matter.
Punch, punch, punch."
Cal Ripkins punching him.
Kevin Costner is crawling out of the house.
I'll show you a tin cup.
He just happened to have a tin cup.
He picks up a tin cup.
He's throwing it at Kevin Costner.
Anyways, the point is that Cal Ripkin beat up Kevin Costner and then he called up his
coach and goes, "I can't play tonight."
Coach is like, "Why not?
We need you in the game."
And your world record.
We don't want it to break.
Like, sure, you've beaten Luke Garreg, but we want to make the record even longer.
We want to make it even longer.
And Cal Ripkin's like, "I can't.
Listen to what happened.
I came home, squeaky bed, Kevin Costner, tin cup."
And the coach is like, "Say no more.
Say no more."
I can pick up those phrases.
The visual is in my mind.
Coach goes, "Tell you what.
I'll take care of it."
And so later that night, the lights wouldn't work.
The game was cold.
And he played a double header.
Cal Ripkin Jr. played a double header the next day.
His record stayed intact.
He actually ended up playing a total of 2,632 games in a row.
Luke Garreg's record was only 2,131 games.
So he just blew it out of the water.
That's the conspiracy theory.
And it's a really interesting one, except for the fact it's 100% not true at all.
This is a really, I actually really love this conspiracy theory.
Because back then, and probably still today, but I remember as a kid, Kevin Costner had
a huge reputation as being a womanizer.
He's constantly sleeping around.
So he's the perfect foil for this story.
And Cal Ripkin and Kevin Costner were friends.
And there are photos of Kevin Costner and Cal Ripkin's wife.
And Cal Ripkin and his wife had some marital difficulties around that time.
So you have all the elements of this.
There's a key problem with this story.
Cal Ripkin was at that game.
Cal Ripkin was 100% at that game.
This story is huge.
This isn't some weird conspiracy theory that's floating out there.
Where it is, well it is.
But this is addressed in like sports media.
Cal Ripkin was there.
He goes, he's done interviews about it.
He goes, I was at that game.
He goes, there's footage of me coming out of the dugout and looking at the lights.
He goes, I was there.
I was trying to help figure it out as well.
He was the main guy, he's the main electrician.
He puts away his bat and ball, grabs his electrician belt.
He's like, I'll take care of this.
He's there.
He's on footage of being there at that game.
Now you could say, Jason, maybe he did show up, but he also beat up Kevin Costner.
And then he just showed up a little bit late.
Maybe but doubtful.
It's not going to be one of those things where you're going to say, boss I can't come into
work, but I can come and just sit there in case anyone starts a rumor later on, I'll
sit there and be really sad in the dugout.
That doesn't work.
The idea was that he couldn't leave his wife, he was so heartbroken, he just had to stay
there and process everything.
I'll just go there and sit in the dugout.
And the story was, he didn't show up at all.
There's video footage of him there.
But this rumor, even though we have physical evidence that this story is not real, this
rumor is so pervasive in 2001, in June of 2001, Fox Sports Radio told this story.
They reported it.
It was a couple of years later.
They're like, Hey, Barry, did you hear about that thing with Kevin Costner banging Cal Ripken's
wife?
No, Joe, what happened?
Well, he gave her the old postman into her water world.
And they're like, Arrrrg, no, no, no, no, no.
Sound effects.
It's only a step.
It's only a step down from what I do.
They just have better sound effect board.
Kevin Costner called him up the next day and threatened to decapitate both of them.
He threatened to take their heads off.
Kevin Costner, star of four movies, only four.
He threatened to chop their heads off.
So it's definitely a really touchy subject.
I mean, if you find my body, if you go to Jason Farms, my body is being devoured by the hogs
and my head is missing.
I don't assume the hogs ate my head.
Assume that Kevin Costner has it on a mantle somewhere and he's sitting there drinking
wine, drinking wine out of a tin cup.
Renee Russo dressed all sexy standing next to him and he goes, That's what you get for
spreading the rumor, Jason Carpenter.
That's what you get.
That's him drinking wine.
He makes that noise.
He has a little sippy cup, but it's made of tin.
You know who else likes taking off heads?
Your woman?
I don't know who she does, but she has a sword.
Superman got killed.
He got stabbed.
And then the earth was like, aww, they cried.
They all made a big baby noise at the same time.
And across the universe, a bad guy goes, Yes, now is my time.
That guy's name is Darkseid and him, along with Granny Goodness, are headed to earth to
destroy us all.
It's up to the Justice League to fight back.
That's Batman.
And Wonder Woman shows up.
She's shot people's heads off.
And then the Flash and Aquaman and then maybe some other dudes show up.
And then Darkseid shows up and he has his arms crossed and he's shaking his head.
And he goes, Uh, uh, uh, this is my planet now.
Is it?
Find out.
March 18th people are like, I'm not watching this movie because of these ridiculous problems.
March 18th available only on HBO Max.
Watch Zack Snyder's Justice League rated R.
I can't wait to watch this movie.
I'm really excited for it.
I've been excited for it for years.
I'm a huge Zack Snyder fan.
I already have my little score sheet.
Wonder Woman shop off.
It's rated R. So maybe it's a lot.
But I'm super excited for it.
I hope you guys watch it as well.
Justice, Zack Snyder is very important.
Is Zack Snyder's Justice League?
I actually watched the first one in theater.
It was decent.
It wasn't great.
It was better than in game.
Squeeze God, let's go ahead and leave behind Baltimore, Maryland.
We are headed out to New York.
And squeeze God as we're flying out there, I want you to go ahead and hit that time travel
button.
We're traveling back in time to the time when the indigenous people of the continent
ruled the land.
And when we're in the area that will become New York, we're hanging out and we start to
hear stories of the stone coats or the stone clad, different tribes to different names
for them.
But what they were were they were 12 foot tall warriors with skin made of stone.
Some of the stories actually say they were simply wearing armor.
But it doesn't matter if you're trying to kill this guy with a bow.
If you're trying to shoot arrows at this guy and they're bouncing off of him as he's getting
ready to club you in their brain, you're like, hmm, the distinction between why these arrows
aren't working is very, very important.
It was just bashing your head in.
No human weapons work against these creatures.
They live in cold areas and they love to eat human flesh.
Now as you moved farther north, these guys started to be known as windegos.
And just like the windego legend, some people believed that the stone clad were humans who
had committed evil acts, namely cannibalism, and turned into these monsters.
That's not really a punishment, right?
Someone's like, don't eat human flesh.
You're going to turn into a 12 foot impossible to kill man.
You're like, what?
I'm totally, I'm going to eat all the flesh now.
I'm going to eat your flesh just because you told me that story.
No, it's not a punishment.
The Iroquois, that's kind of the version the Iroquois have of them are just these giant
warriors.
The Iroquois natives also had a version of them.
Pretty much the same thing.
You could only defeat them though.
These guys actually had a named weakness.
You could defeat them by stealing their powers or exposing them to a menstruating woman.
So just bring a bunch of those along.
Just have a bunch of them and then you can eat them afterwards and become a monster yourself.
We covered a story, I don't remember which story it was.
We covered a story not too long ago where like the menstruating woman, the monsters tried
to raiding the indigenous people's tribe and then they just put a bunch of menstruating
women by the river and the monsters are like, ah, no way.
We're headed over this way.
We're headed to the tribe where all the dudes hang out.
We're going to eat them.
So that's not only in this legend, but we do see that menstrual, I bet you didn't know
that.
You learn something every single day, menstrual fluid can be used as a weapon against a particular
species.
So always carry some with you.
Carry a little jar of it.
The Seneca tribe has a legend about what happens when a human actually encounters a stoneclad.
So squeeze after that little introduction, land this carbonicopter.
We are on the outskirts of a tribe in ancient America.
There was a young man standing there with his wife and he's getting his weapons ready
to go.
He is a hunter like everyone else in his tribe.
We're going to call him Joey and he's standing there and he goes, you know, it's really cool
hunting with you guys and stuff like that, but I kind of want to eat.
He's super skinny.
He's like, you kind of want to eat.
The problem is we are all hunting the same thing.
Sure we get to like share elk and moose and whatever else we're shooting, but I want to
eat more and I want to get really good game and I want to be a better hunter.
So I'm actually going to head up north and I'm going to go hunt there and people are
like, dude, you can't do that.
The reason why we hunt in this area and not up north is because that is where the stone
clads live.
And he goes, yeah, I hear all this stuff about the stone clads and I believe they exist,
but think about it.
They only eat humans, right?
Everyone's like, yeah, that's why we don't go up there.
He's like, but follow me on this.
If they only eat humans and there's no humans living up there, the game must be dope, dude.
There must be like giant elk.
Hopefully they're not made of rock too, but you know, there'd be like lots of deer.
No one's hunting these things.
So I'm going to go up there.
They're like, dude, that's the stupidest plan.
He goes, you will see.
You guys will see.
He gets his wife, we'll call her Monica.
He's like, Monica, I want you to come with me.
He goes, are you menstruating?
She's like, I do it once a month and he's like, good.
Well, plan it for that month just in case.
So they head up north.
They make camp.
He goes to hunt and he was right.
The game is amazing.
He has all these dead elk.
He's shooting moose.
He's shooting animals.
He didn't even know he existed.
He's shooting Komodo dragons and pterodactyls.
No one else hunts up here, but his wife's back at camp and his wife is just hanging out
and a stone woman shows up.
So she bounces.
She's out of there and she goes down river and she tells her husband, hey, you remember
that whole thing about you saying you could totally kill these giant monsters that eat
humans?
The dude's like, yeah, is this how she's from side to side?
He's like, oh, I really didn't think those guys existed.
She's like, one of them just showed up in my camp.
So we got to do something about these things.
I get it.
We're going to eat like kings out here, but they made us.
So Joey sits there and he sharpens his hatchet.
Sharps his knife.
And he sharpens his wit.
He's just reading detective novels.
He's like, oh, Sherlock Holmes.
Because he knows to fight these guys, he's going to have to outthink them.
He sets a big bonfire.
He wants to draw attention to himself.
He's basically puffing his chest up.
He puts on a puppet show.
He puts on a puppet show with a bunch of dead elk.
Hey, everybody, I heard the stoneclad suck.
Oh yeah, they're totally lame.
And throughout this whole production, it's like a trilogy.
He does this full on director's cut.
He has the extended director's cut of how much the stoneclads suck in the musical.
Eventually a stoneclad is standing across the river and he's like, uh-uh-uh.
We don't suck.
You suck.
Well, we do suck.
We suck the marrow out of your bones because I'm a giant cannibal.
And Joey goes, hey, okay, come over here, bro.
Let's fight.
So according to this legend, I love this part, according to this legend, the stoneclad warrior
is looking around.
There's a big river separating him and Joey.
The stoneclad warrior starts to walk into the water.
And Joey's like, oh crap.
I was hoping, I knew he didn't have a boat.
I was hoping he'd be like, I'll be back in three days as I walk around the river.
No, he's a giant and he's apparently able to breathe underwater.
He starts walking into the river until eventually the water covers his head.
And Joey's like, uh-uh-uh.
But then he had sharpened his wit and he remembered that a tree had fallen down across the river.
That's a big tree.
Maybe it's a small river.
I don't know.
He runs down to the tree, crosses the tree bridge, and then runs along the other side
of the river.
And as the stoneclad comes out of the river, now Joey's standing on the opposite side and
he goes, dude.
Did you get turned around underneath there?
And the stoneclad's like, what?
What are you looking at?
He's seeing a smoldering fire pit.
He sees all these elk puppets.
But he turns around and Joey's on the other side of the river.
Joey's like, dude, you got turned around.
Like I thought you were going to fight me.
Are you scared?
Ugh.
The stone giant turns, walks under the river, and right when his head goes under the river,
Joey runs back to the tree, crosses again, and then standing back by the time the stoneclad
gets to the other side of the river.
And now Joey's back on his original side.
He's like, dude, come on, man.
What is going on down there?
Is there like a whirlpool?
There are a bunch of mermaids, a bunch of sirens turkeying you?
What?
Yeah, dude, I'm right here.
This goes, according to legend, this one happened several times.
The guy kept trying to cross the river.
Joey just ran to the opposite side.
This happened multiple times.
Then eventually, according to this legend, Joey goes, okay, I'm done for this.
Like this was super funny, but it's really not a tactic.
Like eventually, I'm going to get tired or I'm going to fall off the bridge and I'm
floating down the river and he's just going to grab me.
At this point, the stonecoat walks out and Joey's standing there and Joey's like, finally.
The stonecoat's ready to smash this dude's head in a putty.
And Joey's holding up his hatchet and he's kind of like making it look super mysterious.
He has like a silk blanket over it.
He's like, what's under here?
Dance of the Seven Veils.
To the point that the stonecoat goes, I've never seen one of those.
What is that?
Can I see it?
Then he goes, oh, this is a hatchet.
And he hands it to the stoneclad.
And the stoneclad takes the hatchet and he runs his finger along the blade and he goes,
hmm, interesting.
We don't need these.
We just rip people's heads open with our teeth and hands.
I haven't seen something like this.
And as he's running his finger along the edge of the hatchet, he's actually sharpening it.
He hands the hatchet back to Joey and he goes, show me what you can do with this.
Joey takes the hatchet and swings it and smashes it into rock.
The rock splits in half.
The stonecoat goes, oh, that's what I'm made out of.
That rock is what I made out of.
Maybe you humans can kill us.
We've eaten a bunch of you over the decades.
But this is weird.
We've never seen anyone smash a rock open.
Tell you what.
I'm going to go home and I'm going to tell my people to stay away from you.
And you can hunt this elk and you don't have to worry about us eating you.
And Joey goes, that sounds like a great idea.
That sounds like a good con.
I don't even compromise.
That's just Joey getting whatever he wants.
And then the stonecoat goes, how do I get back home?
And then Joey tricks him 100 more times underwater.
No, he just lets Stoneclad walk under the river and go back home.
And for a while, everything is fine.
They don't go back to the tribe.
They're just enjoying all this hunting.
They're all just, everything is just meat.
Everything is just super yummy.
They're devouring the entire forest.
And then one day a stone woman shows up at the camp and she's like, oh, she sounds just
like the dude.
She sounds exactly like the dude.
The stone woman goes, Joey, Joey of the forest.
I have heard tales of your bravery.
I heard about her one time you smashed a rock.
I need your help.
And Joey goes, okay, what's going on?
She goes, listen, me and my husband are having a fight right now.
And eventually we're going to murder each other.
And Joey's like, what?
That's a horrible story.
And she's like, I know it's quite terrible.
But I'm also very lucky.
She's like, sounds very lucky if you're about to get murdered.
And she's like, no, no, no, I will bring you luck.
I bring myself bad luck.
But if you hang out with me, you'll get even more game.
You'll get even more deer than you could possibly ever eat.
But when my husband shows up to murder me, you must help me.
He goes, that's fine.
I'll totally do that.
He's afraid of hatchets, right?
And she's like, he doesn't know what a hatchet is.
But for a time, she's hanging out with him in the woods and even more deer, even more.
But what are they doing with all this meat?
I guess they were probably turning it into jerky.
They have to invent the canning industry just to be able to put all this stuff in 10 cups.
Kevin Costner is like, hey, everybody.
This episode's gone on way too long.
I'm starting to lose my mind.
He's hunting with the stoneclad woman.
Even more animals are showing up.
He's getting the most game.
But one day everyone's sitting back at the base camp.
The base camp is now just beef jerky everywhere and they see the stoneclad man, her husband,
moving through the forest.
And she goes, this is it.
This is it.
Now is the time for you to help me in this fight.
Now, I'm going to give you a little hint on how to kill us, which is good.
Because even though he was able to pull that trick with that axe, could that axe have actually
killed the stoneclad?
She goes, we have a weakness.
It's being poked with fire, being poked with a sharp, fiery stick.
So we're going to fight.
And if I kill him, that's totally dope.
We'll have a celebratory dinner.
I'll eat Monica and we'll sneak away together.
And he's like, I don't know about that.
She goes, OK.
She goes, if I kill him, then I'll leave and your debt is repaid.
But if he is about to kill me, if I'm on the ground and he's standing over me, take a fire
brand, take a hot stick, take a hot stick out of the fire and jab it into his abdomen.
And it'll actually go right through our stone armor and drop him on the spot.
And eventually, the stoneclad husband gets there.
And he looks at his wife.
And his wife looks at the husband.
The husband looks at Joey.
Joey looks at a squirrel walking by.
He's like, oh, I'm supposed to pay attention to this fight.
The stoneclad woman and her husband both tear trees out of the ground and just start swinging
them.
Oh, oh, just smashing them into each other.
Just hitting each other with these giant trees.
Because Bounce Monica is gone, she's like, I'm going to watch this from this cliff.
Joey's standing there.
And unfortunately, the stoneclad man really starts to get some blows into this stoneclad
wife.
And she falls to the ground and her log rolls into the river.
No.
The husband stands over with this tree ready to bring it down upon her.
And Joey grabs the fire brand out of the pit and drives it into the stoneclad man.
Oh.
Stoneclad man dies.
You think that would be the end of the legend, right?
I mean, I don't know what the moral of that story is.
It's a bunch of weird, conflicting things.
But that's not the end of it.
The woman pushes her dead husband away and she goes, perfect.
Thank you.
Do you have anything to eat?
That took a lot of energy.
And luckily, Monica's gone.
And the stoneclad woman goes, I'll go find someone else.
But thank you so much for saving my life.
And you got one more mission, Joey.
Remember when you showed up and you smashed the rock and everyone left?
He's like, yeah, I do remember that.
She goes, when everyone left, one of our people left their kid here.
You need to raise him.
He's like, what?
That wasn't part of the agreement.
You're going to help me hunt.
I was going to kill your husband.
Now I'm a dad.
Now I'm a dad of a giant cannibal.
She goes, you got to do it.
Because you're the one who pushed us out of the area in the first place.
And he was like, yeah, that kind of makes sense.
So she said he's up on a cliff.
He's like, what?
How old is this kid?
He's like 18 years old.
Like who leaves a kid on a cliff?
Eventually Joey and Monica meet back up and they go through the woods to this cliff and
a kid.
Like I imagine him like the rockbiter, like the little baby from Neverending Story 3 is
swinging on a swing between two trees on the edge of a cliff.
And this kid's giant.
I mean, sure he's not the full 12 feet, but he's this giant guy.
So Joey goes, okay, the only way I can get him down and this is going to be super dangerous,
but not for me.
It's going to be super dangerous for him.
I'm going to chop the trees down that he's swinging from and then he'll just kind of
fall to the ground.
It is on the edge of a cliff.
So it's pretty dicey, but what else is he going to do?
So Joey chop, chop, chop, chop, chops the trees down and they say the boy actually like
swings, he's swinging, right?
He's on a swing.
And then he goes, he just swings down.
He's still doing the back and forth motion like he's on a swing, but he's like hovering,
almost like a leaf falling.
And they said he's singing the whole time.
And then finally he gets to the bottom of the cliff and he's like, ah, Joey's like,
dang it, now I got to climb down this cliff.
They take the boy back to the village at this point.
He's like, I can't raise this kid by myself.
And like they always say it takes a village.
He just wants to raise the kid.
He's hoping someone else will adopt it.
He takes the kid back to the village.
He shows back up with all of this meat, all of this fur and everyone's like, dude, everyone's
clapping, everyone's giving him a round of applause.
Everyone's like, he did it.
Everyone's like, oh, we didn't think you could do it.
Everyone shows up.
Kevin Costner's ghost is standing there.
His blue ghost is like giving him a thumbs up and Joey gives him a thumbs up as well
and the ghost fades away.
This was a successful mission.
The problem is, is that he brought a giant cannibal baby back to the tribe and the baby's
like, me want to play, me want to play.
And he's playing with the other kids and he's instantly killing them.
He's like, that's my Bob-O.
The dude gets his arms ripped off.
Let's play tag.
I'm it.
And he's like touching people in the back and their spines were disintegrating.
He was so strong.
They said every kid he played with died on the spot.
And all he wanted to do was play.
Let's play hide and seek.
He's pulling their eyes out.
He's not jigsaw.
He doesn't know.
He's not like trying to come up with ironic punishments.
He's not doing that.
But eventually Joey's like, okay, I came back as a hero, but this is quickly turning me into
the villain of my tribe.
He sends message back for the stoneclad woman who he saved and he goes, dude, you gotta
pick your kid up.
He's murdering everyone in my tribe.
Eventually the stoneclad woman shows up and picks the kid up and the baby's like, we
see you later daddy.
And the daddy's like, sure, baby.
They didn't even bother to name it.
Sure, baby.
We'll see you soon.
And once the baby leaves, they're like, move, move the tribe, move the tribe.
Let's go.
That's one of the stories about the stoneclad, a race of people who are impenetrable to weapons
and aid human flesh.
I think it's an interesting story.
There's really no moral to it.
Don't bring strange kids home.
Help women in need.
Help them murder their husbands.
What would be another moral?
Oh, if someone ever tells you don't go in that area at Super Dangerous, go there anyways.
You'll probably kill a bunch of animals.
You're showing up at the zoo with a rifle.
They're like, sir, don't go in there.
That lion cage is Super Dangerous.
You're like, I know, I heard this story on Dead Rabbit Radio.
They're like, no.
Pull our bears sneaking up behind you.
You somehow come to the lion cage first.
But I think this episode is interesting for another reason.
We're going to wrap it up like this.
We're running a little long.
On yesterday's episode, I talked about this might seem like a leap of logic, but stay
with me.
Yesterday's episode, I talked about an alien spaceship crashing and the survivor living
on his own and trying to complete his mission of scientific experimentation using old timey
tools, which I thought was a really creepy visual.
But when I was saying that, I actually already had the ending for this episode in mind.
That was kind of an improv ending I came up with on the spot.
But this episode, I kind of went in when I was prepping it with this ending.
So it's a little similar, but it's interesting nonetheless.
I think this idea that we have of ancient aliens, when you look at stories of aliens
coming down and helping humanity, build pyramids, build the Nazca lines and stuff like that.
A lot of that stuff has been debunked, but I'll put a really cool YouTube video in the
show notes you guys can check out.
If you want more information on that.
But even if you're not looking at the big stuff like Nazca lines or the pyramids or
Goblet Tepeke or any of those things, the idea of ancient aliens coming down and interacting
with humans, it's always this idea of these gods in their spacecraft.
They come down, they help us out, genetically engineer us, whatever they're doing, and then
they leave.
Or they still visit Earth, whatever version of the story you're looking at.
But what would be more likely is a single ship, not an entire culture, a single ship
crash landing on Earth.
And those survivors would crawl out of that ship and go, "There's no way we're getting
off this planet."
This was our interstellar vehicle, it's completely demolished.
We need to make the best of it.
And we have human parallels of that on this planet.
Shipwrecks.
People crash on a deserted island and they go, "We're not going to get rescued.
Let's start setting up a society."
Let's Robinson Caruso this.
Let's do this.
So you don't have these wonders of technology.
You don't have these backup ships that can come.
You don't have these anti-grab rays that can build these giant structures.
You just have 30 people from another planet who are crashed on this Earth.
And they have the technology they can salvage out of their ship.
Which would be things like their suits.
So they have body armor that are impenetrable to human weapons.
We actually covered a story not too long ago about a bunch of Russian soldiers.
They find an island, they go into this base, and they massacre all the grays.
There was a bunch of giants working at these control panels and the bullets were just bouncing off of them.
I'll put that in the show notes.
So you have that.
The fact that they're locked into a particular region, they're always in cold areas, could
be that this particular race of aliens needs to be in cold areas.
It's interesting because we have all these different tribes in the same region have these
stories of cannibalistic giants.
My theory is with this story is that a ship crash landed in the Northeastern United States
and they're trying to rebuild their society.
Now were they eating humans?
Was that actually a component of it?
Maybe I don't know.
I don't know what you're listening to, guys, are all the questions.
The story is that they eat people so maybe they did.
Maybe this race of aliens just love to eat people.
But I think it's an interesting story because when we hear about these tribes that seem to
be completely outside all of human evolution seem to be completely outside all of the other
groups in the area.
It could be a myth.
It could be a group of warriors where they happen to be 6 feet tall and the legend grew
and grew until they became 12 feet tall and they used to wear some different type of armor
and people turned the legend into them having impenetrable skin.
That's possible too.
That's the most likely scenario.
But I like the idea of a ship crash landing castaways on our planet and they do their best
to survive.
They move away from human population centers.
And when humans do come in the area they see them as a threat and they kill them on the
spot.
But they do their best to try to not be a part of our world.
So while ancient astronaut theorists believe that aliens would be viewed as gods, coming
down from the sky in their vehicles, helping humanity on its journey, it could be the opposite.
It could be a single crashed ship and the survivors were considered monsters that you
had to stay away from.
Underneath thousands of years of soil somewhere in the northeastern United States may be the
wreckage of a ship.
Its power cells long depleted.
It's been invaded by roots and worms.
And it sits there silent in the dark.
It was built for interstellar travel.
It crashed on the planet earth.
And its survivors lasted as long as they could until they also eventually perished and ended
up under the soil.
All that remains of their story is a legend that the tribes in the area would tell each
other of impossibly hard to kill monsters that stalk the woods.
Instead it was a small group of castaways who would often look up in the night sky and
think of home.
[Music]
(upbeat music)