The Red Rooms. Supposedly on the deep web, there are websites where you can pay money
to watch people get murdered live. This has always been considered an urban legend until
the Italian police investigated one.
Now we take a look at the podcast Dead Rabbit Radio. After so many episodes, conspiracy
theories are starting to pop up. Why does this podcast exist? What is its end goal? And the
answer may lie in your dreams. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope
you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend doing whatever you love doing. We got a ton
of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away. First off, walking into Dead Rabbit
Man. It's one of our legacy Patreon supporters. You know his name. You say his name. It's
Robert Paulson. Everyone give a round of applause to Robert Paulson. He's walking in. Robert,
you're gonna be our captain, our pilot. He actually did some fan art for us as well. You
know what? Actually, let's do that. For Fan Art Friday, let's use his fan art that he
made. He did this. We really, really appreciate it. And then he started supporting the Patreon.
So Robert, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode. And look at this dope
fan art. It's the Ouija board. The Ouija board, Dead Rabbit Radio logo. Looks great. True
classic. Really, really appreciate the work, Robert. And Robert is a Patreon supporter
as well. So you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode. If you guys can't support
the Patreon, that's fine too. I totally understand. Just help spread the word about the show.
Write reviews about it. Talk to your friends about it. Talk to your family about it. Post
flyers. We have flyers in the show notes. If you can't help the show financially, that
is another great way you can help the show and keep the show going. Robert Paulson,
I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the shovel. Let's go ahead and take the carpenter caboose.
We're taking this choo-choo train all the way from Dead Rabbit Command out to Italy.
Choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo-choo. Robert Paulson's one little conductor outfit.
He didn't even know he'd be riding the caboose. It's just his favorite clothes. Robert is
bringing us out in this train underwater tunnel all the way out to Italy. There's just really
interesting story that's happened in Italy recently. But before we start talking about
that, let's back up a bit. So the red rooms. I've talked about them on the podcast. I
don't think I did a proper episode on them. They're on the Conspiracy Theory Iceberg and
this is what it is. We're sitting in Italy and we're in a cyber cafe. If those still
exist and I'm like, "Hey, distract the barista and then you go give me some coffee because
I'm thirsty." And then you watch the door because we're gonna use this public... I don't
know why we're just not doing this in the hotel room. I don't want to use my laptop.
We're going onto the dark web. And supposedly, like again, this was an urban legend. There's
been a lot of debate over whether or not these exist. There's been a lot of debate over whether
or not snuff films exist. Now snuff film, I'm sure you guys are aware of it. I'm sure
you guys have an extensive collection of it. A snuff film, specifically, it's the murder
of someone on camera, but it has to be made for commercial purposes. There's tons and
tons of footage of people being killed. Snuff films have a distinction. This is the way
law enforcement looks at it. It has to be made. The main goal of it is not as a warning
to rival cartels. It's not to scare people. It may have those as secondary goals, but
the main goal is this is commercially produced. It doesn't have to have a $60 million budget,
but the main goal behind it must be to make money off of the footage. Commercially produced
product. That's what makes it a snuff film. Unfortunately, there's gore videos everywhere,
but for it to be a snuff film, when they sat down and they go, "We're gonna murder some
people today, and we're doing it and we're gonna record it on camera for the purpose
of making money off the production of the footage." The FBI has long said there is no
such thing as snuff films. That is what the snuff film is. A red room is even more mythical,
because a red room requires it not only to be commercially made, you still have to have
that thing. A red room is not watching gore videos online. It has to be for commercial
purposes and it's live. It's live footage. So again, a gore death in a red room does
not count as a red room video. The red room has to be made for commercial purposes and
you can watch it live. Whether or not you're walking, you would have not woken up in time,
but people were able to watch it live. That's what the definition of a red room video is.
I'm sure if the room is mauve or red or purple, it doesn't matter, but the idea is some people
could watch it live over the internet. Now, the sticking point to this was that the dark web
is really, really slow. You're using the Tor browser to get there. It's super slow. People think
it has a ton of security. It doesn't. They'll find you. They're constantly busting people on the
dark web. I'm surprised that it still has this reputation of being top secret. But you can't
stream live video on the dark web. The internet speeds weren't fast enough. Well, that's,
I'm using the past tense now. When I did an episode, when I talked about the red rooms,
again on the conspiracy theory iceberg, I talked about it maybe the first year of the podcast,
that was considered the feds go, listen, there's, it's a myth because you can't stream live video
footage over the dark web. It's way too slow. It would be unfeasible to do it.
But like all technology, it marches forward. And now people are saying, well,
they could have gotten better, they could have gotten better broadband, could have gotten better
ethernet cables where this stuff is supposedly taking place. Because in 2019 in Italy, Operation
delirio took place. The Italian police force in one swoop arrested 25 suspects spread across 13
provinces. And they were able to target these people because they were the worst of the worst,
what these people were searching for, finding and hosting on their computers was beyond anything
that these officers were prepared for. And the suspects were shocking as well. Out of these 25
suspects, you had six adults, the other 19 were minors. I think the youngest was around 12,
13 years old, and then the oldest was 17. And this all came out because a concerned parent
went through her son's or 15 year old son's phone and saw illegal content on it. And illegal content
meaning this 15 year old had child porn on their phone. So the parent contacted the police because
what else are you going to do at that point? Parent, it's a little late for intervention.
You got to get law enforcement involved. The parents contact the police and the police
started interrogating him. And they begin to talk to this kid and find out who he's sharing
these videos with, who he's sharing these photos with. And that is when this kid tells them some
of these videos we watched live. The investigators are what? And he goes, what videos are you talking
about? And this kid, this 15 year old kid, now you can say the word of a 15 year old kid in a
police station is probably shaky. But he's now going to be admitting to something morally worse,
I would argue, than child porn. Because what they're watching in these dark web videos is the
torture and murder of children in these red rooms. And he goes, we paid money on the dark web and they
showed the police officers these sites where we pay money and they take these kids from third world
countries. They take them in this room and they torture them and they murder them. And we get
to pay if you have enough money, because I don't know if these kids are funneling their allowance
into this thing, but if you have enough money, you can choose what happens to the kids.
Now I'm not going to go into the gory details of what actually was going. I'm sure you can use
your imagination. You're probably pretty irritated that you have to use your imagination
in the first place. That he goes, people would choose this and people would choose that and
then we would see that acted out on camera. And the police are able to sweep up all these other
suspects and they don't know what to do. I mean, obviously, I think, you know, the child porn,
that's illegal, they're going to be charged with that. Would they be charged with accessories to
murder if they're doing this thing? Now there are red room scams out there too, where you donate
your Bitcoin and you don't get anything, which if you're going to scam anyone, scam people who
want to watch red rooms, I have no problem with that. But that wasn't the case. They had these
videos on their phone. They had this stuff on their phone. And the police just like, how do you
prosecute that? I don't think it's illegal to own snuff. It's obviously, because legally it doesn't
exist. But now the Italian police are saying, well, it does. This stuff was made for commercial intent.
And it was made on the dark web. It's what we always feared. Because even though the law enforcement
said snuff films don't exist, it's one of those things that it feels like they do. It doesn't
feel like they should. I'm not saying that they should exist, but doesn't it when people, I remember
when you first heard about snuff films, they were terrifying. People getting killed on camera,
on purpose. And then I remember reading that they weren't real by the FBI. They released this
document. It was like back in the 80s, because they used to be a bigger thing, the fear of snuff
movies. But when you hear the FBI, when you hear a law enforcement talk about it, you go, yeah,
that makes sense. But it feels like they're real. It's one of those things that would not shock me
if it turns out that they were real in the FBI, botched their investigation, or they were covering
something up because they're weirdos. I don't know. I'm not saying the FBI loves their snuff, but
when they came out and they denied it, which they could be right. They could have been right at that
time. There were no murders shot specifically for commercial gain. But nowadays, where you can
take Bitcoin, and you can do this stuff online, and as streaming gets better and better and better,
unfortunately getting better in this case. I could see people doing this, and they're going,
they're, these children were mostly from Southeast Asian countries. So it's an interesting true
crime story. It's absolutely terrifying. And right now, like you see, because all of these kids are
minors, we have no names. And this happened in 2019. I was looking at the story again. There hasn't
been a lot of movement on it, at least not that's been reported. So who knows if they're still
investigating it. These kids are still facing trial. But as far as I can tell, they haven't
had their trial yet, 2019. And then we rolled into coronavirus. And now I've officially said
enough keywords to get this episode blocked on Spotify. But as of right now, they're just in,
I'm assuming, I hopefully in jail. But it appears that the internet myth is true, that red rooms do
exist. And it's one of those things that even though I covered it before and said technologically,
it couldn't exist in the back of our heads, our collective head. We all have one. You're thinking,
yeah, but unfortunately, it wouldn't make sense if they did. And this operation delirio seems to
have proved something we all kind of believed was possible all along. Roger, Roger, Roger,
Paulson, Roger, Paulson, we are leaving behind Italy. Jason, what is your voice sounds so bad?
Well, because now this is my official carpenter copter headset is my eyeshift from side to side.
It's not that I'm making an edit. And I'm not at home. It's not that I can't clean up my mistake.
I'm wearing this headset officially to let Robert Paulson know we are leaving behind Italy,
hop on board this carpenter copter young man, giving you the keys. We are headed out to
your bedroom. This last topic is really kind of out there. I mean, it is taking place in your
bedroom. We know what a freak you are. This is a really bizarre spin on this show.
Because we've talked a lot about hyper sigils on this show, and how I use the law of attraction
to draw audiences to the show. I think you have to visualize success and know you're already
successful for you to be successful. And you have to do hard work. We've talked about that a lot on
this show. But at what point does the show itself become a hyper sigil? Now this show is, I produce
all this content, I edit it, I research it, I present it. That's it. There's no team on my side.
There's people I talk to from time to time about topics I may or may not do. I talk to the
patreons during the live show about it as well. But as far as the actual construction of the show,
it's just me. There's no other editor, there's no writer, there's no researcher, there's nothing,
it's just me. And this show, it's funny to think about it, has no competitors. As far as what this
show is, it exists in its own space. The closest that comes to it is Coast to Coast AM, where it's
a daily show about paranormal topics. There's, the Ghost Hunters have a daily show, but they mostly
just talk about ghosts. They have a daily podcast as well. But we came into the game three years ago,
and we have more episodes, and I'm not bragging, this is kind of setting this up. We came in three
years ago, and we already have more episodes than last podcast on the left. We have more episodes
than Mysterious Universe, which has been in production since 2006. Their episodes are longer.
Their episodes are longer, but they cover less stories. A general episode of Mysterious Universe
might cover one or two stories, maybe three on the bonus. Last podcast on the left usually covers
one story mostly. And sometimes they'll have four episodes that cover a story. Now, both of those
podcasts are more in depth with their stories. I like to sum it up, give you the information,
just get it done in 15, 20 minutes. But different strokes for different folks, and both of those
podcasts are great, and I understand why they're, I understand definitely why they're far more
popular than this show. 100%, and they're really good at what they do, and the hat's off to them.
But when you have one person focusing, I spend about 20, 25 hours a week on this show.
After we're on episode what, like 740 something, that energy, it's so hyper focused.
Where is it going? And more importantly, what's it doing to the fabric of reality?
Let's say 740 episodes, let's say average two stories in episode, that's 400, that's 1480 stories.
I've been getting weird emails lately. This isn't a bit. I've been getting weird emails and weird
YouTube comments lately from you guys. A while back I got a YouTube comment from Nikolai Mishkin,
and they asked me a question, they go, "Hey, where's that season trailer you uploaded a while back?
That was one of the best videos I've ever seen anywhere. Was it here or Instagram?"
Now I did a season trailer once. I did a season trailer a long time ago, like between seasons
three and four, four and five, something like that. And I didn't know what he was talking about,
because it definitely wasn't the best video that anyone had ever seen. It wasn't a video either.
I think I was posting stuff on YouTube at the time, I'm sure I was, but no video.
So I asked him about it, what are you talking about, dude? Now Nikolai is one of those guys who
came on late to the show. He's only been listening for the past couple months, but he's listened to
every episode. And he goes, "There was this short video you released a while back. It was a trailer
for Dead Rabbit Radio, and it was me playing Fortnite. It was about four minutes long, and I was doing
Mungo's voice, who was a reoccurring character back in the day. And I said, one of the lines he
thought was funny was, "But can he get the girl?" And I was cracking these jokes and doing this
Mungo voice. And the song "Bella Royale," which is the Indian credit song, is playing in the background.
He goes, "I want to watch that video again. It's so funny." That video doesn't exist. I never made
anything like that. I don't have the technological know-how. And I've tried to stream video while
doing anything. Like, video games, I mean. Video games. I've never been able to do that
in any sort of overlay, ODP or whatever that program. OPD. It doesn't matter. I can't use it.
It doesn't exist. And I told him, "I go do it. That video doesn't exist. It was the best video
you've ever seen." And he goes, "Oh, maybe I was dreaming." A long-time listener of the show,
Patreon supporter Tressa, put out a call for an episode. She emailed me, and she goes, "Hey,
I'm looking for this specific episode you did." It's about an author, maybe a professor, who wrote
about the fey. And then he disappeared. But before he did, he said that if he ever disappeared,
he would have a sign at his funeral to prove that he wasn't dead, but trapped in the fey dimension,
like fairies. Do you know what episode this is? Do you even know what I'm talking about?
Now, that episode did ring a bit of a bell, but I couldn't find it. And when I posted it on the
Patreon, they had no idea what she was talking about either. She also came to the conclusion
that she must have just had a dream. Then I got this email from Sean, a long-time listener of the
show. And he said he had this dream. He knew this was a dream from the outset. He was dreaming this.
"I was in my childhood bedroom listening to the show, and he started talking about a homicide
investigation you helped the police with. You said that when you were in college, you found the
horribly charred corpse of a child in a park near Drexel University in Philadelphia. And he took
a few Polaroid photos and handed them over to the police as evidence. But you kept one photo,
because you're into the macabre true crime stuff. You also said the crime was never solved."
Up until this point, you had been telling the story in your usual tone when discussing a serious
matter. But then, and I swear, in the dream I felt the hair on my neck standing up because it was
such a scary change. You became extremely distraught. As though you were breaking down and fighting
back tears, and said that all evidence of the case had disappeared. You said how there was
absolutely no mention of the crime on the Philadelphia Police Department website,
that all articles about it had been totally wiped from the internet. And your one photo of the body
is the only proof that the child ever existed. But you didn't sound like you were alleging a
conspiracy to erase the crime. It was very sinister like you thought you were going crazy.
It sounded horribly real, and I woke up in a cold sweat, shivering in relief that it was over.
I'm not the only one putting out this podcast. When I say it has no contemporaries,
it's more media put out than anyone else. It's a daily show that's put out by a single person on
these topics. I'm not the only one. I'm the only one here in this reality. But I'm not the only one.
There have to be other jasons in other realities. Some of them never started the podcast. Some of
them went on to do other things. Some of them did nothing and continued to dream about being creative
while watching the creations of others all night long, not creating myself. But there are other
jasons out there who did start the podcast. And all of this energy that I'm putting out,
what if Conspiracy Caps fully on that these episodes, these incidents are real
in alternate universes?
I even had that incident where I reported a story about the Zennetti train company
that went back in time. And in that episode, I said, "I know I've recorded this segment before.
I know we've done this story." And I half expected to get a bunch of emails saying,
"Dude, you did do it. You just kind of find the episode. It was episode 352 or whatever."
As I'm telling the story, it sounded so familiar to me that I already recorded it and everything
had been done that what if I did cover it in another universe?
At what point does an artistic project stop being just an artistic project and become a
hyper-sigil, become something else? I'm not telling stories. It is the story. The podcast is
the conspiracy. The podcast is the paranormal event.
And I'm doing it and this Jason is doing it and that Jason is doing it and that Jason is doing it.
And because it's just one person behind the mic focusing so much of their energy and so much
of their time, it's criss-crossing realities. When you have a team doing it, I'm not knocking
teams. When you have a team of 10, 15 people putting together a podcast, that's awesome.
But that mental energy is then diluted against 10 or 15 people. I have to do all the marketing
all the way to the editing. I do everything and I'm so, so grateful that you are here to listen
to this. I'm not diminishing your purpose in the podcast either.
But when one person, I spend so much of my time thinking about the show, producing the show,
restructuring the show, looking for ways to make it better, finding other things to
market it with, promote it with. Are we punching holes through realities and connecting with other
podcasts performed by other Jason's and we're starting to get the streams crossed?
At what point does it stop being a podcast and start to become a portal?
I expect, after doing this segment, that others of you have had dreams like this.
But you just didn't, you were like, "Well, that was a weird dream."
I suspect I'm going to get a few more emails or a few more YouTube comments. People are going like,
"Dude, that is so weird because I've had the same sensation. I swore up and down I heard you cover
a certain topic." And maybe I did. Maybe you just heard another version of me tell it.
And at this point, where 740 some-odd episodes in, we're not even close to stopping,
not even close, the hyper-sigil will continue to grow in power. And I don't see it as a negative
thing. I'm not worried about it. I'm not concerned about it. I'm curious to see where this goes.
As the dead rabbit radio hyper-sigil continues to grow, we may have a new Mandela effect happening.
We may see realities collide in a way we can never expect. And if that happens,
you know the first podcast that's going to cover it.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also
hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend, guys.
Bye.
[Music]
[MUSIC]