More proof that meth makes you go crazy, the resistance movement fails to bring out their
A game, and the biggest conspiracy that has ever happened on US soil.
Who killed John Lennon?
This is the 14 Family Podcast.
Okay everyone, my name is Jason Carpenter, this is the 14 Family Podcast.
Podcast about paranormal, conspiracy theory, true crime, and all sorts of other weird news.
And it's already happened.
This is episode 4, and I'm barely able to record it.
It's funny because I thought I could do a weekly podcast, but I know after probably
about 2 or 3 weeks I'll stop recording.
The neat thing about doing a daily podcast is it's actually more shorter, there's less
work involved, so it's actually easier to do.
But man I've just been dealing with some crazy migraines today, and I was like, "I don't
want to do it, I don't want to do it," and I thought to myself, even though these are
kind of introducing, you know, introductory test podcasts, you got to do it.
You got to do it every day.
We got some good stuff coming up though in the future that we'll be talking about as
we go on.
So yeah, yeah, I'm going to try to keep the energy level up.
First off, you know, last episode I was talking about meth use and just how I couldn't stand
that I thought it was probably one of the worst drugs that I came into contact with,
not personally as a user, but just as the people in my life.
And here's a little tip, if anyone wants to find anything entertaining online, what
you can do is you can Google blank conspiracy.
You can also do it on YouTube.
You can YouTube blank conspiracy.
And what's going to happen then is that you will be able to find the weirdest conspiracies
you probably never would have thought of either, you know, in any sort of way.
So earlier today I was looking at some videos and looking at some good topics to talk about,
and I Googled meth conspiracy.
Now obviously a lot of the stuff that came up was, you know, charges for conspiracy for
distribution and things like that.
But one of the second links that I found was this.
To prep the sample you're about to hear.
It's late dusk.
It's like there's just a little bit of sunlight, but whoever's recording it is completely
bathed in shadow.
They seem to be walking around surprise, surprise.
It's some sort of trailer park.
Anyways, here is the video.
We'll have the audio for you.
The title of it is heroin in crystal meth government conspiracy.
Let's listen to this.
It's getting pulled up right here.
I hope you guys are doing good.
I just have a really bad headache.
Yeah, I hope you guys are enjoying the podcast so far.
I really enjoy doing it.
It's actually getting in like my creative fluids pumping in other parts of my life as
well.
So I'm having a lot of fun.
It is on me.
I just can't see right now because I'm white.
I mean it's dark.
Can you imagine being white and it's dark and you're fucking with blacks and you can't
see them and they want to kill you?
So apparently black people, black people have an advantage to being in the dark.
I think that is probably one of the most old school racist things possible that somehow
their skin color gives them an advantage to dark combat.
To like night combat.
Which you know, I mean I don't necessarily see how that's possible.
You see whether or not someone's skin, and you know this guy's obviously on meth.
Whether or not their skin is white or black, you still see like a six foot figure moving
towards you.
But anyway, so he's afraid of getting stopped because he's, and you know what's weird is
like I said you can't really tell what he, what race he is.
I'm pretty sure he's white, but even that he seems a little unsure of himself, what
color, what race he is.
So let's keep listening here.
Oh yeah, when you're like, that's why the lion don't go into the jungle because he
get eaten for food.
He's like, "Oh, I'm gonna go get some food."
And I'm like, "Oh, I'm gonna go get some food."
And he's like, "Oh, I'm gonna go get some food."
And it's interesting because anyone who's been around meth addicts for, you know, any
period of time, the conspiracy theory thing is really big.
They're super observant.
So he goes on to explain it as he sees people smoking meth and as he's probably smoking
meth himself as it starts to turn brown, he perceives that as truth that there's heroin
in the, in the meth as opposed to simply turning brown when they're caught on fire.
I don't know how he explains a pink hamburger patty turning brown as your cookie man, but
that, that's where he's at mentally.
Methanphetamine that people are smoking.
Okay.
I see it turning brown.
I've seen it before, right?
And there's a quick fix.
What you do is you heat it, right?
Smoke it and when it's still liquid stop and then from the back end, just put a little
acid in it and let it go in and pop and it'll get all that shit out.
Back it out where it came in onto a plate and it'll whiten it and it'll make it so you
don't get dumb.
Into our methamphetamine, it's definitely a cultural problem.
So yes, confirm this guy does smoke methamphetamine.
And to be honest, I had no idea what he was talking about where he was like emptying the
pipe and the liquid and put something in it and it pops because I, not a, I don't know.
But I'm sure if I have any listeners who are a methamphetics, former methamphetics or
just a recreational meth user, don't do it.
Don't do it at all.
But maybe they know more of what's going on.
We're almost done here.
And you know what?
It's a conspiracy to make people fucking stupid and basically fucking brain dead.
Okay.
So, you know, and that's always the amazing thing.
If you type in blank conspiracy, you will find out.
You'll find something you didn't know before.
I did not know that the US government was putting heroin into crystal meth, which is funny
because if you think about it, wouldn't that actually make them less like crazy?
Would that actually, I don't think they're doing it to make people dumb, as he keeps
saying.
But I don't know.
Maybe it helps them come down from it.
Meth is terrible.
Meth is absolutely terrible.
I remember once I was at a party.
One of us was throwing a party and a lot of people who were invited were meth users.
And I knew that, you know, there's a lot of people who weren't meth users, more people
who weren't meth users, I should say, but there was a few meth users there just because
the area we grew up in.
And one day I'm at this party.
I'm sitting there.
I'm drinking a soda or whatever.
This young man sits next to me.
He's probably older than me at the time, but and he goes, Hey, I came up with an invention
like just out of the blue.
And I'm like, great, this guy is totally high.
And he's going to tell me the weirdest invention possible, a meth invention, like something
you would come up with at three in the morning after being awake for two days.
He goes, don't you hate it?
Don't you hate it when you're sucking on a straw and the liquid comes up to the straw
and you're drinking it and you're drinking that.
Dude, actually it's funny because I'm totally about to give away his super secret idea.
But anyways, he's like, when you're drinking a soda and you suck in that liquid up and
you're drinking it, it tastes really good.
But then the second you stop sucking, it goes all the way back down the straw.
And for you to get your next drink, you have to apply all of that pressure again.
You have to suck all of that pressure again into your, into your mouth.
So here's the thing.
Someone who is on meth, that would be the most frustrating thing in the world to be
drinking a soda or whatever and stop drinking and watch that liquid moves down the straw.
Realizing in just mere seconds, he or she is going to have to re-suck that straw and
bring that liquid back up.
That is like a Herculean task.
That is the level of pushing the boulder up the hill to a meth addict having to, to apply
.008 milliseconds of time to suck liquid up into a straw.
So anyways, he's like, yeah, doesn't that suck?
No, no, I've never considered that to be a problem.
Ever.
Ever considered that to be a problem.
But anyways, so he goes, so I came up with an invention.
I was like, okay.
And then he pulls a dye and then he pulls a blueprint out of his pocket of a drawing,
drawing of a straw with, so it's like a standard straw.
He basically just drew a line, but maybe about a half inch from the top, there is a circle,
like a little globe built into the straw.
So it's like a regular straw with like basically a little reservoir near the tip.
And he goes, that's the reservoir.
That way, when you suck up into the straw and you stop drinking, it doesn't go all the
way back down the straw.
It collects in this little globe here, so your next drink is that much faster.
You can't, I can't debate that with him.
Not because I don't think the sciences sound, but the first thing that popped in my head
was straws cost what, a quarter of a penny to make?
They're extremely cheap because it's just a plastic tube.
Once you start putting a little ball on the top of it, now straws are going to cost more
to make.
You're going to have to have different packaging for them.
They're going to be unwieldy at first, like where do you hold the straw at?
These are all thoughts that I'm having instantly after hearing his pitch that I don't think
he ever considered to him the idea of the sucking was the main thing.
It was driving him nuts.
He did tell me though, if anyone wants to rip off this idea, that he mailed himself a
copy of the diagram and it's dated on the envelope.
If there's ever any trouble, he can always refer to that earlier envelope.
Now, here's the thing, that doesn't work.
That's never, as far as I know, because I used to look into a lot of trademark law.
I used to have to deal with trademarks and copyrights and all that stuff from other businesses
that I had.
That doesn't really hold up in court.
You have to go to the trademark office.
You have to have it go to, you know, I do the trademark, do the copyright, the mailing
yourself the form, it's not really going to hold up in court.
That being said, I doubt that he, one, still has the original envelope that he sent himself,
two, that he's still complaining about making the straw he could be, and three, that anyone
would rip that idea off in the first place because it just, on a financial level, it
doesn't make any sense.
But anyways, so, you know, you have these interactions with people who are using meth,
and they're just, it's almost like they're in their own world, because kind of they are,
you know, they're addicted to a drug and that kind of becomes the main thing.
I don't want to rag on meth users all the time, but I do see a lot across contamination
between meth use in particular and conspiracy theories.
You get meth is a big one, marijuana, obviously, is a big one with conspiracy theories.
Those are the most likely.
A cocaine maybe a little bit.
You don't get many heroin, people who are heroin addicts engaging in conspiracy theories,
their main thing is just getting more of the opioids.
So, so I mean, you know, it does, maybe that is a legit conspiracy, the government is,
no, it's not a legit conspiracy, but let's give them the benefit of the doubt.
If the government was putting other drugs into the meth supply, heroin may, maybe not
necessarily make them dumber, but to calm them down, it's, it's possible.
Super unlikely.
The guys probably just burn and stuff and it's brown.
I can just imagine though being this guy's friend and every time I'm trying to smoke
meth, he's like, let me check it out.
Let me check it out.
Let me see if it's brown.
Let me see if it's brown every, every time he would have to be the worst person to share
a meth with.
And that's a really low bar.
So this one, this next story, it's just so, it's just so bad, not bad as in.
Not bad as in a subject matter wise, but here's the thing.
This is, we're getting a little political here and I know people are very divided in
here.
You have people who are Republican and people who are Democrat.
You have people who are pro-Trump and you people have anti-Trump and you have that in,
in the Republicans, you have people who are pro and people anti-Trump.
And then we have the resistance movement.
I've no problem with any of that.
As long as it's not leading to people actually being assaulted or attacked, you can have your
political views, but if you're out there beating people up, you can't be doing that.
That's a totally different form of governments of, and it's not dialogue and it's terrible.
However, if you are going to protest things, do it in a quality manner.
Do it, do it with a little, be proud of your work.
Don't just throw stuff together like this podcast, which I literally just record for
20 minutes, edit for 20 minutes, throw it online.
I love it.
It's great.
I kind of wanted that access television vibe.
But anyways, so I came across this today.
It is a group called Pussy Scouts.
And I just haven't been able to really suss out where they are.
To be honest, it might actually be a troll.
The thing is, is that we have come so far that you can no longer tell if someone's being
actually sincere in their beliefs or if they're trolling because it all seems the same.
This is a group called Pussy Scouts.
You can go to pussyscouts.com.
It's their website.
I found this on YouTube, but it is a music video.
It's a rap song with, because you're not going to be able to see it so play the audio, but
it's only a minute long.
I'm not going to make you do it too much, but it's a rap song with four little girl
scouts rapping about President Trump.
Anti, that obviously should be with the Pussy.
Sexual Soulter, you know, Muslim bands, racist things like that.
They can make those valid points, but just do it well.
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I