We've talked before about haunted video games or how open world games are becoming too smart
This time we're gonna talk about it again
And I've brought proof
And then we finish insanity week by taking a look at the story of Mike Madman
Markham, is it possible that a young man goofing off on his porch with a few scraps of electronics?
Actually built a working time machine today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*Movie about to be played*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carventer. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a ton of stuff to cover so first off
Coming into Dead Rabbit Command in his own personal Pope Mobile. It's all decked out has the bulletproof dome. I'm testing it
I'm shooting at it. It's Father Dovey everyone give a round of applause to Father Dovey
He's waving from his Pope Mobile
Father Dovey step on out of that step on out of that protection even though I still have a gun aimed at you
You're gonna be our captain art pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon or if you don't have a pimped out car
Like the Pope that's fine too. Just helps spread the word about the show really really helps out a lot
And look at this cool fan art Friday. We got something different today for fan art Friday
I got this from the patreon discord server
This is from little graze destiny to clan the Dead Rabbit Society
Isn't that dope look at that little flag that he made oh?
I want to see what you do is running in a battle with that logo and
Oddly enough he posted this on discord. I don't know if he was planning this look how many members are currently in the clan
Spooky 30 if you're driving you're like you're driving and you can't look at the cover art. It's 13
There's 13 people currently in the clan. He's playing on Xbox
So if you're into destiny - he's like - and my clan's gonna get over on if you're into destiny - and you're playing on the Xbox
I think clans are I don't play destiny - I
Don't get to play anything
But if you do maybe little gray, maybe you'll be part of this clan with that dope look at that
That's dope. Those are the battle flags apparently. I don't know if like on they're on the shoulders or something like that
I don't know anything about destiny - other than that. I'm now in it. So thank you little gray
Father doobie, I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the oars to the dead rabbit robo. We're leaving behind dead rabbit command
We are headed out to a little coastline in the middle of
Minecraft splash
Splash
I don't have time to play video games anymore. I really really like them, but I just don't have time to play them
So I'll read a lot of video game websites video game magazines
Because I like the culture and I watch video game streamers. I watch home record do dead by daylight
I watch a lot of Minecraft streamers dream bad boy. Halo George not found. I really like fruit berries. I think he's the most clever
Minecraft player and recently he was taken on alumina who is arguably the best Minecraft player in the world
Don't let your eyes glaze over yet
I know this is like your nephew is cornered you at Thanksgiving and it's telling you about Minecraft unlike him
I have a point this this story actually goes somewhere. I
Was recently watching this really bizarre video clip
It's gonna be in the show notes and I know most of you guys can't stop you're doing like driving or working
To watch a Minecraft stream, but it's queued up. It's in the show notes. You click on it
It'll take you right to where it's going on. This is a server
This is a private server the only people in the game are alumina and fruit berries
Illumina is digging for treasure and he's afraid at any point because this is competitive Minecraft that fruit berries is gonna sneak up behind
Them and kill him so he's looking around. He's trying to watch the six while he's digging for this treasure
He turns he sees fruit berries in full enchanted iron armor again
Do not let your eyes glaze over just yet
He sees fruit berries in full enchanted iron armor jump into the water behind them and this is gonna be bad news for alumina
He's not ready to take on full enchanted, but then the video cuts to fruit berries. He's underground
Mining iron and the camera actually because you can change the camera angle in Minecraft
We see a view of fruit berries. He has no armor at all. He's wearing his default skin
Now alumina goes, uh, did you just jump in the water because they're playing like this game basically of hide-and-go-seek and
Fruit berries is like what no not me and it's kind of coy
But we as the audience saw someone jump into the water
Alumina saw someone jump into the water
This is a private server with two players on it
There was a third player in full enchanted iron armor
jumping into the water
I've watched this video over and over and over again. I've done the slow motion
I actually was taking screenshots of it and magnifying it this
Person this character should not be here. It is not fruit berries
There was a third player there
There was no third player on the server
Someone in fully enchanted iron armor
jumped into the water just as
alumina turned around and
It's not like they go at the end of the video. Whoa, who was that was this some sort of spooky thing?
They talk about it briefly because again, it's like hide-and-go-seek so fruit berries is thinking if alumina is confused. That's totally fine
But it definitely was not alumina and it definitely wasn't fruit berries who or what was this thing?
If it was a lark they would have kept bringing it up
They would have mentioned it in another video
The that's halfway through the video. They never bring it back up because so much of the game is to do misdirection
But we see it too
You might think it's some sort of glitch you might think it's a minor thing and maybe it is maybe it is
But if you guys are if you guys are familiar with Minecraft at all
I definitely recommend you checking out the video and see if you can identify it because it is not one of the two players
It doesn't make sense and this is what creeps me out about games like Minecraft. They are vast infinite worlds
And when you're walking over the hills, who knows who knows what's going on underneath the ground
And when you're underground
Who knows if another lone wanderer is traveling the world above you and you'll never meet them
They're not supposed to be there though. You don't want to meet them
So check out this video if you're familiar with Minecraft. I want you to check it out
You're not familiar with Minecraft. Ask your nephew. They'll talk to you about it for three hours straight and then watch this video
It is creepy simply because it shouldn't exist. It shouldn't be there in the video
There's another thing I want to share with you this one this one actually works for our podcast your driver your car
You're doing your homework like Jason. I can't watch the video right now
It is queued up and it'll be ready to go when you watch it
But I do play video games when I get my two week vacation from the show and last vacation
I played state of decay - that's all I did. I played
50 60 hours of stated decay - and two weeks that I had off
I got really used to the zombies and the maps and the AI of the characters the AI of the zombies
When you really dig into a game for 60 hours over a short period of time like that you really know the game
But it is an open-world game
Stuff can always throw you a bizarre curveball, but not like this
Was on the state of decay - subreddit and it's you
posted a question
Does anyone recognize this sound and I'm gonna play it for you right now
*Birds chirping*
That is not a sound that any of the zombie characters make in that game
At all
The scene is his character at their home base. It's nighttime
And you hear that bizarre creature sound now
I want to be playing that sound if I go hey that sound plays all the time. That's the sound of a barrel
That's the sound of a screamer
That's that is not a sound that is played at any point in the game state of decay one or two
What is that
Now the obvious answer is some sort of unused audio file that got triggered
No one on the reddit knew what it was no one posted no one recognized the sound on the reddit either
But it could be some unused audio file that got triggered in this one person's game
When we have video games when we have these sound even though they're monster characters in state of decay
It's a zombie open-world game
Those zombies have recognized the sounds and the reason why they have recognized sounds and recognize silhouettes
They don't do things that are too unpredictable. So the player knows they're in the area every time a feral shows up a certain sound is given
Makes it scary, but it also gives the player an edge
If the feral's may know noise if you're just walking through a department store and then something one of the most powerful zombies was on top
Of you it wouldn't seem fair
So you have these recognizable sound this is not a sound in the game
This is not a sound that I experienced at any point in the 60 hours that I played no one else on the subreddit recognized it in
Real life you can say this is the sound of a dog. This is the sound of a horse
Ha ha ha ha and that's true. Those are the stereotypical sounds that a horse makes
But a dog in an event like a dog on a ferris wheel is not gonna make stereotypical barking noises a
Dog going down the slide is gonna sound different than a dog on a trampoline. You know what I mean in real life
There's so many variables that'll change the way we make noises
But in video games everything is programmed a feral coming at you in the middle of a field
It makes the same sound as a feral in close combat at your home base. It is programmed that way. What is this noise?
Was there something else in the darkness?
surrounding the space
Making that noise
What I'm getting at is that what if this sound isn't part of the program the language? It's a new sound
It's developed this new creature type in the darkness
You're running this game
Thousands to tens of thousands to twenty thousand hundreds of thousands of times all these different players starting it playing it
Stopping it over and over and over again. It's almost like a fluke in evolution in
This particular game at this particular time. There was a new creature type
outside the fort
One the programmers didn't create but it formed itself and
made that noise and
Then when the game was shut off this evolutionary fluke
Was deleted with it as well and when you bring the game back up it is back to its normal programming
Open-world games are so fascinating to me and I think with the computer processing power we have and the more
Complicated these games get the more realistic these games get we're going to see more and more of these
Paranormal events
Inside our video games. There's also the chance
There's also the chance that someone is going to come along and explain both of these very very easily to me someone goes
Oh, no, no, that is this audio file. It was on this form and stuff like that
That's very possible. It's interesting when we're talking about
computer-based mysteries
They are easier to find answers to so I don't like you guys to kind of dig into these and see if you can figure out an
Answer for them, but as far as I can tell these are both stories. I've sat on for a while. I
Had I found the state of decay thing weeks ago. It's pretty much right right after my vacation ended
So I've been waiting to tell these stories, but yeah, and it's you thanks for letting me use the sound clip as well
Check these out see if you guys can figure out an answer for him because I think it's just terrifying
And I think we're gonna see more and more paranormal events in open-world games
People are always talking about San Andreas GTA San Andreas having Bigfoot having these UFOs having these events and they were urban legends
We may be moving past the point where they're urban legends and becoming reality
Father do be put down that controller. I'm gonna toss you the keys to the Carvener copter
We're gonna leave behind this Minecraft world
I guess technically went to state of decay - after that, but we're leaving behind both of those
We are headed out to
Standbury, Missouri
Father do be land that Carvener copter at Standbury, Missouri. It is 1995
The gin blossoms are pumping out great music third-eye blind is doot-doot doing its way around America
I think is that too early for both those fans? I say link Pearl Jam was still the lead band doesn't matter
Doesn't matter we have our flannel shirts tied around our waist our ripped jeans and our long hair
We're walking through Standbury, Missouri. We're about to meet Mike Madman Markham
Mike is currently in school. He's getting his degree in electrical studies electrical engineering
You're like, there's no such thing as electrical studies. He's not a super villain. He's doing something with electricity
He's also a rogue inventor
So he's taking his two passions putting them together and he's building all these things at home
And one of the devices he puts together is what's known as a Jacobs ladder. You've seen them most likely in movies
There's two metal rods and you have a little bit of electricity
Go and it goes up the rod you guys have seen this a hundred times in horror movies
So he builds one of these on his porch
but what he what he's using to actually make the electricity to power it he's using a
laser from a CD player and
He's running this little test and he's just watching the electricity
And he notices something different he's obviously had experience with Jacobs ladders before
He notices it's producing a bizarre haze as well
He said it's like when there's a hot day and you see the sidewalk kind of shimmer from the heat waves
He's looking at that the Jacobs ladder has formed this little vortex
He picks up a metal screw
He throws it through the vortex
And it would disappear for just a half second a blink in time
But then it would reappear sitting on the ground a few feet away
He looks at that and he goes that I must have not seen something right that breaks all the laws of physics
He picks up another metal screw and he throws it through the vortex disappears for half a second and then reappears on the ground
He thinks I need to grab my camera
Go grab a camera to document this get a camcorder, but the CD player at that point catches on fire
So he had to shut down the whole experiment
What he thinks he's done is invent a time machine
He thinks what's happening is he's throwing the metal screws through the vortex and the reason why they're disappearing is they're moving forward in time
And then teleporting as well to another location. He goes. Okay. This is dope, right? I broke the laws of physics
I've invented a time machine what I need to do now is make it more powerful
So he starts looking for ways to increase the voltage of this thing
I mean he's using a laser from a CD player. He decides he actually needs some transformers some giant electrical transformers
There are 13 thousand dollars each though. He can't afford to get these
Transformers so he actually starts scoping out a local power plant and sees
You know just laying around just laying around six transformers
They're each about 300 pounds and he realizes well, maybe I'll only need three of them
But when he's putting his plan together when he goes to the power plant he realizes I'm just gonna steal all six of them
Let's just take all six of them and let's make this machine as powerful as possible
He takes these transformers back home sets them up
He's getting ready to run this experiment. He basically wants to build a bigger version of this thing
But he doesn't have a lot of money. He doesn't have a lot of resources
He doesn't have enough money to throw parties
So one night him and his buddies are over there. They're drinking beer. They're wild and out as the kids said in 1996
One of his friends is jumping up and down on his couch and goes hey Mike go get me another beer
Mike goes, oh, you know, okay fine. Just get off my couch, right? He goes into the kitchen
He gets him a beer and then when he's coming back
The couch is gone
Mike's like, where's my couch at?
They're like, what do you mean? He goes you were just standing on the couch. Where's my couch? Where did my couch go?
The friends had no idea what he's talking about and Mike goes dude
She was just jumping up and down on my couch my couch. Well, didn't you guys realize that I didn't have a couch and
None of his friends know what he's talking about
Mike thinks this is some sort of practical joke
But he realizes that one the couch is nowhere in the house to the back door the place where you could really sneak the couch out
Is blocked by six stolen transformers and three they never find the couch
He ends up hooking these transformers up to this invention and while he's powering it up
Of course something goes wrong, but not deadly wrong just kind of funny wrong
He ends out knocking out the power to the entire neighborhood
The police are already looking for someone who broke in who stole these transformers the fact that the whole neighborhood went dark
It's a pretty good idea that the perpetrator is there and Standberry is not a big town to begin with so the police very quickly
Zone in on Mike madman Markham. They arrest them for theft
At this point it goes from being a local crime story to major newspapers are picking it up
The New York Times are at an article about this guy a young man who stalled
Transformers to build a time machine. There's a goofy slice of life person of interest story
People loved it and it actually came to the attention of Art Bell host of coast to coast a.m.
The granddaddy of all paranormal radio podcasts. Everyone will always be in debt. It's a good old art Bell
Art Bell invites
Mike to call into the show he wants to talk to him wants to talk to this young kid who claims that he invented a time machine
And Mike tells the story that I just told you
And it's funny because it's a small town Mike's arresting officer the cop who caught him that day
Also called into the art Bell show and was talking to him
It was a really fun story this young kid claims that he invented a time machine
Knocks out the power to the city that sounds great. It's a great prologue to any fun movie
And people really get behind the story of Mike people recognize something of
Themselves in Mike just a guy who has a dream but doesn't have the resources
To make that dream happen because he's on the art Bell show people he gives that he's like
Here's my phone number guys call me. I want to hear all your ideas scientists are calling them and saying this isn't a good idea
This is why I wouldn't work, but he knows what he saw but people believe in him
They begin donating money to him. They begin donating equipment to him
And he's actually able to start working on a larger
Time machine
He calls back in about a year later in 1996. He calls back into the art Bell show and
Tells art listen. I'm about 30 days away from getting this machine working 100%
It's far bigger. Thank you so much to all the listeners who made this happen. I was able to afford a machine
That will allow me to walk inside of
I'm gonna try the time travel thing myself and he said he actually changed it up a bit now
It works on rotating magnetic fields. I'll be able to time travel myself. He goes. I'm gonna bring my phone with me, too
So I'll still be able to contact you guys and our bell goes
Let me know before you go in the machine because I want to be able to document the experience
I think it would just be a once in a lifetime thing or if the time machine works several times in one lifetime
Because you just keep going back and forth
At this point Mike gives out his address as well. Come on down and visit
Let's chat. He's very open guy
He's giving out his phone number. He's giving out his address
He wants to kind of make this a community driven thing
But around 1997 people start to notice that Mike is
Gone
He's not responding to any correspondence. No one can get ahold of him
No one's heard from him
He's vanished off the face of the earth
The story goes that to this day Mike madman Markham is still missing
but after all of this happened a listener called into the art Bell Show and
Told this story. He was going through old newspaper accounts and he found a mysterious death in the 1930s in California a
Man was found crushed in a metal tube
It was unknown who the man was or how he ended up in this metal tube squished
But the officers found an odd device
Laying next to the man
They didn't know what it was but a modern-day person reading that article would identify what they were describing
as a cell phone
Very very interesting story
About a man who was trying to invent something and I found out about this from a new website
They might have been around for a while, but they recently come on my radar called Planet Today
They posted this story. Thanks for posting that I read it and I go very very interesting story
But I could already taste that there was something missing from the story
The ending I go that's not the true ending to the story
It's interesting because we have all this documentation. He was on art Bell twice. There are recordings of him on art Bell
You have to be a coast-to-coast AM plus member to listen to them
They've been taking a lot of their stuff off of YouTube lately, but
He's not a completely made-up figure for the internet. He actually did exist
We actually have documentation that he's working on this stuff. There's news articles about him working on this stuff
And then you think well he went missing but that could be anything did he actually go back in time?
I immediately dismissed the whole 1930s thing and for from a narrative standpoint if you guys are going to fake something
It would have been more interesting if before
We even knew about mad Mike Markham if they had said it's weird in the year
1989 someone called into art Bell and said there was a man squished in a tube and he had a cell phone because if time travels involved
Why would the call take place after?
Mike had disappeared so just from a narrative standpoint if you guys are ever trying to pull a hoax
It's better to add that layer of
Confusion to it because it makes it more legit, but I
Didn't buy that at all. It's not that I didn't buy the fact that he built a working time machine. I actually was still
willing to suspend disbelief for that
But that was just too clean of an ending so I really started digging into this story
When you look up Mike Markham online
You see a lot of forum posts about this and there's a lot of theories about what happened to him because he actually did disappear
That is true
Theories are that it was all a hoax to begin with none of this story was real which we know isn't because there was versions of it in the newspaper on
Coast to coast a m all that the government kidnapped him because they wanted possession of the time machine the government had him killed because he knew too much
They actually did time travel and he died or he did time travel and he was successful
There's a kind of the most common theories going around on my journeys looking into the story. I found a website called paranormalists
There was a poster named Himalayan hermit who said I don't know why this is such a big mystery
Nexus magazine did a write-up on this guy. They found them. They know what happened to him
so I had to find this Nexus magazine article I can't post it in the show notes because
You have to pay for it. It cost me a dollar twenty-two. It was one of the best dollar twenty twos
I've spent doing the show. I'll put the link in the show notes so you can buy the article
But we have an answer to this for years for years
People had not heard of this guy since
1997 and that is where the story ended and to this day that Planet Today article was brand new. That's how they ended it
We don't know what happened to him. He was in this tube
Nexus magazine solved the story of what happened to Mike
Madman Markham and it's it's awesome. Let's move on
This article is written by Jason Offit and I'm pretty sure we've covered him before because he's written about shadow people
He's written about black-eyed children. I tried going through my notes. I couldn't verify it
But I'm sure we've covered Jason stuff before he wrote this article in Nexus magazine. It was volume 18 number five
It'll be in the show notes the to buy the article if you'd like to and again, I suggested it's a really well-written article
Here's what happened
After that first interview with Art Bell he moved away. He moved to Kansas City, Missouri
So all of his friends everyone he knew in school. He'd moved away from them
So right there that would explain one of the reasons why you could disappear so easily if I went missing in my hometown
Hundreds of people would wonder right away. They wouldn't have no I they would immediately realize that something was off
But if I moved away
It could be weeks before it filters back to all my friends and family
What happened?
But he moves to Kansas City, Missouri
The other articles that were saying that he was getting donations to help build his time machine
This Nexus article goes into great detail. Someone gave him warehouse space
He got ten thousand dollars in financial
Contributions and he according to him he was interviewed in this article. He is alive and well
He got millions of dollars worth of equipment from people
So he ends up building this massive machine in this warehouse
It's over 60 feet high
And he has everything he needs to power it
He turns it on and he creates this vortex there's this tube and
It's five feet in diameter and he's up on this cherry picker and he's watching this machine activate
This is a life-size
Time travel machine, but he still has to test it
He's thrown metal screws through it. He's throwing items through it now. He has to test it on
guinea pigs
So he begins dropping guinea pigs out of a cherry picker
into this vortex
Doesn't hit the ground that just disappears
Throws another one in doesn't hit the ground it just disappears
But he doesn't see him walking around the warehouse floor he doesn't know where they're going or when they're going he hopes
They're not just getting vaporized
But he does start to notice
Out in the parking lot around the warehouse
Guinea pigs guinea pigs walking around the parking lot
So he's realizing that he's dropping them in and they're appearing outside of the warehouse
It's successful
This time machine works
I would say at this point
I don't know if you've necessarily invented a time machine, but you may have simply invented a teleportation device either one would be revolutionary
But he still thinks that when he's throwing these things into the vortex
That there is a period of time passing and it seems to be relative to the size of the thing that that kind of is what his thought processes
And he's also thinking sure this works on metal screws in organic stuff. It works on tiny things like guinea pigs
But what about me and is it painful?
But he realizes he has to test this on himself
So one day he gets in that cherry picker
He goes up
It's a 60 foot drop from the top of that cherry picker to the warehouse floor and
He has to fall in a five foot in diameter
Cylinder and he is thinking okay. I'm not afraid of heights. I love roller coasters. I'm a big adrenaline junkie
however
If I panic and I hit the side of this thing
Who knows what's gonna happen?
It's now the year 1998 and he's up in this cherry picker. It is time to test the machine on
himself
There's no camera set up. There's no friends. There's no observers
Just a man and even if there was you think someone would try to stop him, but there's a man in this cherry picker and he
leaps out and
Falls in towards the vortex of this massive machine that he has built
There's a bright flash a
loud crack a
Thudding sensation that almost knocks him back. He says it's like a flashbang grenade going off right in your face
It took him a long time to remember what happened Mike is standing in the middle of a farm
He doesn't know where he's at. He doesn't know how he got here. He doesn't know who he is
Mike is standing in this farm with no memory whatsoever
He just kind of looks around
Just can't figure it out
He's in Fairfield, Ohio the year is
He is two years later and hundreds of miles away from where he started
Mike's time travel machine is successful
But he doesn't know it. He doesn't even know who he is
And because he has no memory of anything he ends up making his way into the city of Cincinnati
Barely scraping by he ends up staying at a homeless shelter
Taking on odd jobs trying to make ends meet and trying to remember who he is
And he starts piecing things together over time. He begins to remember who he is
He remembers a warehouse in Kansas City. He remembers what he was working on now two years have passed
Since he jumped out of that cherry picker. He makes his way back to Kansas City, Missouri. The warehouse is empty
He said millions of dollars of equipment were gone all of his logbooks all of his notes
gone
He says even without the notes I could rebuild the machine, but you don't understand this machine
Costs I wouldn't have been able to do it without all the generous donations of this equipment and
I don't remember who gave it to me. I cannot for the life of me remember who donated
This equipment it wasn't all from one person several people were sending stuff over and I can't remember who it was his memory never fully
returned
He went back to Ohio where he continued to work odd jobs just kind of scrape by he would also Google himself
Look up articles and he said one of the funniest things that he saw regarding this story
Was that some man was found dead in California crushed in a metal tube with a cell phone? He goes that wasn't me
I don't know who that was
But it wasn't me
When this article was written in 2011 Mike was alive and well continuing to work jobs in Ohio scraping by
And he would love to rebuild this machine sometime, but he is just worried on paying rent and keeping himself fed
And he ends the article by saying listen, I would love to rebuild this machine. I remember how to do it
But right now I'm just struggling to pay rent keep food on the table
It's a lofty dream
Maybe someday I'll be able to rebuild it but for now I have more pressing matters in the present day to deal with
Then to look into the future and see
What may be you didn't say that eloquently you didn't say that eloquently, but he said that
That is the whole story of Mike madman Markham
And
It sucks that this version isn't out there
I think part of the reason why it's not is because of the paywall
Everything about that ending is better than the time travel one it turns out to not be a hoax
Like if we trust him out his word right he totally made up this last version of the story
He's the only witness to any of it, but the one where he goes back in time and ends up in the crushed tube at the cell phone
It doesn't really I guess on a sci-fi level it kind of makes sense
But this version's better isn't this version one because it's a definitive answer
It's from the man himself telling the story and it still has the elements of sci-fi it still works and all that stuff
I think it's a better ending. I still have some questions about it though
Why didn't he just call art bell again?
That's what I don't understand when I was reading the story. I thought well, okay, this is interesting
It's very fascinating story. Thanks for sharing it Mike
But how come you didn't call art bell when you came back two years later?
Even if it had been two years later imagine like the melee airheart showed back up and she's like oh
They don't want to hear about me sure I've been gone for a hundred years and I like just as good as the day I left
But I don't want to bug anybody like he should he should call art bell or if he's still alive now
This article is from 2011 he was 22 back in 96, so he's gonna be that much older than me
Why doesn't he contact coast to coast a and why doesn't he contact me actually?
Well, he doesn't know I exist yet. Maybe he'll Google this
But I mean he could contact these people now and clear this up. It could just be that he's kind of over it
It could be that there's a little bit more to the story that we're not we don't know about
Who knows but that was my thing when I was reading the story after I got done
I go he could even though he doesn't remember the people who donated the equipment to him fair. That's fair enough
He knows art bell
And because he references them several times in the article
So why doesn't he call him up again?
But that is a personal decision that Mike is making and it could just be that he does want to build the machine again
But all the attention may have just been a little too much who knows
But for me this was a perfect way to wrap up insanity week because we've talked about a lot of insane stories and insane people
This week. This is insanity that becomes
Creativity this is that type of insanity that borders on the line of world-changing genius
It takes an insane man to jump out of a cherry picker
60 feet off the ground
believing they will be safe and sound in a
Time machine that they invented out of donated parts
But that's the type of insanity that helps people
That's the type of insanity that can actually change things
So I wanted to end insanity week on a high note
Wanted to cover someone who yes, we buy all definition of the word would say they were insane
But this is that type of insanity that the world needs that drives the world forward
But you're also probably wondering what happened to all the parts all the logs all the notes that were in that warehouse
Well, someone cleared it out. It's possible the person who was leasing the warehouse hadn't heard from Mike and
Stopped paying the lease and it was all taken off to the city dump
Or it's possible that a government agency was observing Mike's progress
They watched him jump into the portal and they realized this
thing worked
So with his notes they carefully disassembled this device and took possession of it
It's possible that they rebuilt it, but they needed to test it for themselves a
Government agent got in that cherry picker
Sweat dripping from his brow
They all saw that Mike disappeared into the vortex, but they don't know what happened
Was it successful or he was he vaporized into a billion atoms
this agent jumps and
As he's falling towards the vortex he panics he hits the side of the metal tube and
Both him and the cylinder that holds the vortex
Disappears in an instant
The government agents carefully disassembled the machine and lock it away
Maybe they can figure out its secrets some other time, but for now
It's too dangerous to even test
And what happened to that special agent?
well in the
1930s
There was a crushed cylinder with a man inside of it
Maybe that wasn't Mike
Maybe it was one of the men
Who stole his time machine?
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is gonna be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
Twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great weekend
*Music*
[MUSIC PLAYING]