Can bees live in your eyeballs?
Can mannequins move on their own and then we travel down into the earth as we explore the mysteries of
Bottomless pits today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Garvin or I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. It's the 200th episode of Dead Rabbit Radio
We've almost been out this for a year. We started I think it was in
June June of last year. We're almost at a full year
But we're definitely 200 episodes in that's kind of cool. It's kind of nice
I don't know what I don't know what else to say. I appreciate that you guys are coming back to the show
Listening to it. Our download numbers are always going up. Now the first news story. I saw pop-up
Quite a few days ago, and I thought that's fake. That's absolutely fake
Recently we're in Taiwan. There was this woman named he who goes to the graveyard to go visit her relatives
It's not like they were living there anything they were buried and she went down there
And she wanted to tidy up their graves so she began pulling weeds and then she's like ah my eyeball and goes home
She's like damn ancestors should be protecting me
She goes home and her eyeball keeps hurting and itching and stuff like that
And she can't figure out what it is and so she goes to the eye doctor
I'm sure going to try to pronounce the word but I'm just calling the eye doctor and the eye doctor starts looking in there
And he says not the woman but the doctor the pronoun as in he has the doctor said
It looked like there was an insect leg in there and when he began poking around there was four
Sweatbees in her eyeball like not like actually in the ball itself
But like around the eyeball on the inside
Drinking her tears and I'm like that story is fake the story is 100% fake and
Then I saw it pop up the next day and it was kind of the same thing when I go up fake news spreading around
How would you not know there's I could understand if there was one bee in your eyeball?
Maybe but four bees in your eyeball and apparently sweat bees are really small, but I was still super
I was like that's not true and then finally another article came out today
And they actually included video footage of a press conference where the young woman and the doctor
Gave a press conference with photographs of
The bees in her eyeball now
I had seen photographs of bees on an eyeball and earlier things that I think that's just like some mock-up
But apparently it's real. I mean they held a full press conference and these people are given interviews
I don't understand what they're saying
But they kept cutting back to pictures of bees and eyeballs and it was like this big news deal
I don't think of that. I do think it's real. How do you go about your day with four bees in your eyeballs?
I always heard this urban legend quote-unquote urban legend. It may be true
But I heard a long time ago. There was a young wife a young hot blonde a young beautiful hot blonde wife
Sitting there in her yoga pants and her tank top her tight tank top
Press against her body. Anyways, I don't know what she was wearing the point. That's what I hope she was wearing
She was mailing wedding invitations and she was licking the envelopes
But in the letter you guys know how you stick put a letter in but anyway, she's licking the envelopes
She's licking the envelopes and eventually she licks and she gets a paper cut on her tongue. Ow
Only there was a Jason here to kiss my tongue and make me feel better
But I wasn't there and she just kind of went about her business. It's really hard to to treat a tongue wound
But then a couple days later, maybe a couple weeks later. I'm not exactly for sure of the time period
I was just horrified at the story her tongue begins to throb and starts to like
pulsate
And she's swelling up. She's not swelling up her tongue is swelling up if she was swelling up that would be a different story
That'd be a very very sexy story
Anyways, eventually she goes to the dentist and the dentist is like you need to go to the doctor because that is completely abnormal
Tongues shouldn't pulsate. They shouldn't
Undulate in your mouth. She then goes to the doctor and the doctor's looking at it
And he's like, oh, yeah, that's looks like maybe you have like a really bad infection. She might want to eat in a week
Can you help me doctors like yeah, I can understand you and I can help you and
He cuts her tongue open and a bunch of cockroaches came out now
I doubt that story is true
The the this that was a story that I heard and which the cockroach had a cockroach had laid eggs
That got stuck to the envelope and when she licked it and cut her tongue
The eggs went into her tongue and they fed off of the blood and saliva in her mouth
So they became full-grown cockroaches and the pulse I'm getting grossed out just thinking about it
the pulsating of her tongue where the cockroaches
Crawling over each other and they cut it out and all the cockroaches came out again
I don't know if that's a real story, but that's quite disgusting and whenever I lick an envelope
Which I very rarely do nowadays. I think of that story
But that's enough of cockroaches apparently the bee lady is cool like they got the bees out
But man, that's pretty disgusting
But I wouldn't much rather take bees in my eyes than cockroaches in my mouth and no I'm not gonna make a dick joke there
But I was very tempted to halfway through that story
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story now our next story is kind of weird
Because it's something that I'm sure has a simple answer
But everyone in the neighborhood is being really tight-lipped about it. We are going to a place called Wappenger's
Falls, New York Wappenger's fall. Oh, yeah, that's the only way I can pronounce that word
Wappingers. Anyways, we're going there. We're going to a place with the last word falls in New York
The year is 1871. There's a choo-choo train driving along riding along the rails and there's a horrible accident
*makes noise*
21 people are killed sorry 22 people are killed
That's why I have notes and not only that but the train actually derailed and smashed through a neighborhood
So that was bad, right? That's a bad that's a bad combination of things
1877 so only five years later a massive fire rips through that same neighborhood and all but two buildings are burned down a house
And then I think like a bigger house or factory or something like that
But you're like, okay, what does that have to do with anything jason a train crash fire?
Where you going with this? Does this story involve a sexy sexy bride with something swollen in her mouth?
And no, unfortunately not this story involves something equally sexy in a weird way. There is a house
There is a house that lives that lives there is a house that is in that neighborhood
Known as the john loson house and what makes this house noticeable or
Remarkable is the fact that it is inhabited by only three mannequins
So there's three mannequins dressed up in period clothing. So like older time clothing. They're not wearing juicy couture
You know, they're just kind of wearing like frilly dresses and little sun hats and stuff like that
So you walk by the house and you just see these three mannequins sitting in the kitchen
They're like, that's kind of bizarre. It's kind of weird
You've never seen anyone else in the house
Now that would is just bizarre enough. You're thinking maybe there's a serial killer there
You're thinking all sorts of weirdness stuff, but you're like three mannequins. That's fine
But then a couple days later you walk by the house again
And now you see two of the mannequins sitting on the porch
And one of them inside the living room looking out of the window
And you go, oh, okay. So it's some sort of joke like some guys moving around mannequins in there
Puts them out on the porch dresses them up in old timey clothing
You know, whatever one of them's left out one of them's inside playing solitaire because she's the lonely one
But then you notice that almost every time you pass by that house the mannequins are in a different position
When the weather is bad, they are never outside. That's one one pattern you notice
But a lot of times you'll see them sitting on the porch. Sometimes all of them sometimes just one or two of them
You'll see them inside and they'll be in poses. It's not like they're just leaning up against stuff
They're dressed in different clothing than the last time you saw them. That's all you know
Now neighbors have reported that on occasion there is a light on in the kitchen, but the drapes are closed shut
But other than that nobody knows who lives in the house
Nobody knows who's doing this
There's something creepy about mannequins. It's really bizarre like I remember their twilight zone episode where the mannequins come to
Life and that was kind of spooky that was kind of spooky and like a weird surreal way because spoiler alert
The girl didn't know she was a mannequin and she like escaped and lived her life
Like once a year one of the mannequins got to spend a day out
But this one mannequin went out and then developed this whole false memory
Knit forgot she was a mannequin and then one day she goes shopping in the stores and the mannequins
Adopt her and turn her back into a mannequin that that kind of creeped me out because it was just kind of a weird story
But the fact that they like look like human and they're they're not and they just kind of stand in human poses
And the fact that most of the time they're really really hot. They're really sexy
You very rarely see an unattractive mannequin
I guess the ones that are missing their heads and their arms and their legs are pretty unattractive
But even then they got a little nice little hourglass shape
But generally mannequins are pretty hot now when I was reading about the story
I was it was kind of bringing me back to that childhood thing like oh man
That would be so spooky to like have mannequins walk around. There's something just creepy about that
But of course I kept digging because I'm like logically this is impossible
If there was a house that mannequins were walking around then
One of two things would have happened
One the government would have come in and taken those mannequins and turned them into super soldiers
Or at least found out what sort of phenomenon was happening in this house
Or two this would be the only story that was ever covered on every paranormal website ever
If it was 100 true that these mannequins could be documented moving around
It would be the first ghost story you ever heard as a kid
So I kept digging and it turns out
That the idea that nobody knows who lives there is a bit of a
Misleading statement because as a boggett for a long time that statement was true
But as of now since august 2016 the mannequins are gone from the house
And when people started asking one of the neighbors said
The mannequins are removed out by the person who owned that house
And now they're in another house, but you can't go there and I won't tell you where it's at
So I do know who lived there, but I'm not going to tell you who it was
I'm not going to tell you where they went. I'm just telling you that the mannequins are gone
So that I think still leads us back to our first theory
If these things were real and I believe there are real paranormal things that kind of fly under the radar
But if I'm able to stumble across that one late night while I'm you know just scrolling through stuff
Then I'm sure the CIA could find it
But it leads us back to that theory. What if these mannequins were real and they were being spotted in this area?
And they're in this house moving around and the first thing that happens is the government would come out because they would
Investigate anything that was weird. I got a story prepped coming up for next season as well about
Russia's psychic spies that they just like announced in their newsletter
That's the whole thing. I really have to dig into that but governments do look into this stuff
So if the government came out and found that this was a real phenomenon
They stood out there for a few days in a surveillance van. They saw you walking back and forth going what?
Like golly the mannequins are still moving around
But they're surveilling the place and they don't see anyone coming in they would go in
Examine what was going on and if there was something paranormal going on they would simply take the mannequins
And then they could just have like some CIA agent pretending to be a neighbor being like oh, yeah, I live there
They moved away mannequins everything moved away
And then people go like oh that's the end of that mystery
While really these mannequins are like being trained in some CIA
CIA warehouse to like fight other mannequins there to fight other inanimate objects are these things real?
It's most likely it was an art installation. Some guy was goofing around
It could have been some weird fetish thing too could be that souls of people who died in that train crash
You're like, yeah, why should you mention all that stuff in the beginning?
Could be that souls of people who died in that train crash inhabited those
mannequins
The most likely one obviously is it's some sort of art thing or sex thing
But if these things are real
They're not just at someone's house that this neighbor won't say where it's at
They're being fully examined by government or non-governmental agencies to find out what makes these things work
And how to make more of them
Moral of the story
Do not get lost in a macy's or seers
ever
Because you don't know which one of those mannequins could actually be a spook in more ways than one
For new listeners of the show, I use the word spook and it's meaning as an FBI or a CIA spy
I do not mean it as a racial slur. I'm not saying watch out for black mannequins a long time listeners of this show
I'm sure are well aware of the fact that I use the word spook a lot
That's not a racist slur. Okay. I figured I had to jump in there just in case you're like
My dear that guy's super racist. He doesn't like black mannequins. I love all mannequins
Okay, so let's go ahead and move on to our last story here
The next story is something that I was always intrigued about as a child
I think a lot of people were just because the imagery is so bizarre and it really tests the limits of what's physically possible
We know they exist in space
But do they exist in earth?
I'm talking about bottomless pits
Now, obviously I'm talking about black holes in space, but you know just a pit that goes on forever
Would defy all logic all physics
But it's something that there's just something really like enthralling about that idea
So I started looking into bottomless not literally I wish I don't know if I knew a pit was bottomless
If I knew a pit was 100 feet deep, I don't think I'd look into it like I don't like
Looking into the pitch black abyss
Especially if it's high maybe if it's like three foot and I look down and I see cthulhu
I'd be like oh, it's kind of cool
But I want to want to look down a giant abyss
And see cthulhu even though he'd be farther away. I'd be safer
There's quite a few stories about bottomless pits the stories that I found seemed to center in
America and two of them are actually quite close to each other
But for our stories the first two are actually only small entries that were in this book called weird usa
Which we've had some run-ins with before
They're the ones who talked about spider web gate cemetery, which was just absolutely just
Garbage information, so I'm always a little iffy on weird us books. I'm sure the authors are lovely people
I just had a bad experience with the information from that one. Anyways, first off
Let's hop in the jason jalopy. We're just we're not crossing in the oceans
We're driving our car it looks like the Beverly hillbilly's car, but we got those spinning rims on it
So it's like jeet out. We're going to Hannibal, Missouri
Now down in Hannibal, Missouri
There is a legend that there used to be this pit or I'm sure it's still there
It probably doesn't like fall in on itself
But there is a pit in Hannibal, Missouri, which no one has found
since this happened
But it was this bottomless pit and animals kept falling into it
So I don't know how stupid the animals are down in Missouri
But anyways animals kept falling into this pit and people are like well golly
Better find out what's down in that pit now
That's a bad idea. There's no time frame for this story. I don't know if it took place in 1997 or 1797
Because if it took place any time past the 1970s, you just throw a camcorder down there attached to a rope obviously and see what you get
But back then whenever this story took place the guy a guy said you know what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna tie a rope around my waist and I'm gonna lower myself in
Yee-haw and he goes down into the pit
And then at some time later according to the book sometime later his friends show up and they hoist them out
And here's the exact quote his hair had turned completely white
And he was wildly insane somebody stop me like I mean
It's not somebody stop me that that part I made up, but
The wildly insane it sounds like something you'd put on like a sixth graders t-shirt
Or like a fourth graders t-shirt totally tubular and wildly insane you pull a man out of a pit
How do you differentiate they're like man this guy looks insane and someone else goes no no no
He's wildly insane
Obviously that story is probably not true for a couple reasons one
There's no time period given for it the guy who went wildly insane. We don't have his name
Did he lower himself into the pit?
With his friends not noticing and they just showed up to you know drink some brews and watch the game and they see a rope
Leading into this pit
Was his friend supposed to be there to pull him up and a short time later
He realized they had went and watched the game without him and totally forgot he was hanging down there
Such a bizarre story, but anyways he goes wildly insane most likely a fake story
But it's a legend in Hannibal, Missouri
Now we're driving hot back in the jason jalopy with a wildly insane guy in the back just
She's going crazy quoting Deadpool the whole time. We're like, oh my god. This guy's driving me nuts
We drive up to
Tacoma, Washington
And there this time we have a dude's name
But we still don't have a time period for it and technically we have half a name. His name is johnson
Now his name his first name may be john his last name son
But probably not it's probably just johnson. He finds a hole in his yard. He moves into this house
And he doesn't notice the hole at first, but then one day this dog finds his big old hole
It's a hole that's about four feet in diameter and it's interesting because we're looking at these legends here
Think about the story. I just told you about Hannibal, Missouri. That was pretty much all the information
That was in the book
That's all the information of the legend and now we're moving to this one. Well, you're gonna find more concrete stuff
This one we have the size of the hole. It's four foot in diameter
It has a three foot brick wall around it. So it almost looks like a giant well or medium sized well
I don't know how big wells normally are
But there's like a three foot brick wall surrounding it which makes it a little suspicious
He didn't notice it in the first place, but whatever
And he looks down. It's this huge pit
So he wants to figure out what's down there obviously and now I don't think he did it on the first day
He moved in but one day he's bored. It's Saturday afternoon. He throws a rope down there
He keeps low night. He didn't toss the coiled rope down there
He's lowering a rope down there is what I meant to say and all the rope goes down
And he's holding the end and this does he doesn't feel that he's hit the bottom yet and he's like, hmm
That's weird. He did he throws 40 feet of rope down there. No bottom now
That's really probably to me 40 feet doesn't sound that long
But I guess going straight down it probably is he starts to think it's an abandoned well
And what are you going to do with an abandoned well? He starts throwing old tires into it
Just tossing old tires down there just because he has to get rid of them anyways
I don't know what this guy was doing for a job. Maybe it was like automotive repairman
Maybe just really like tires. I don't know
Eventually the hole starts to fill up full of tires, which is what will happen when you throw tires in there
At a later time he starts talking to his neighbors. He's like, you know, hey, yeah, it's pretty nice area. Isn't it? Yeah
Hey, he goes. Hey, hey, have you guys know anything of previous owners?
Never mentioned to me about the big old hole in the backyard and they're like, oh, yeah
Yeah, that hole they didn't tell you about that
Johnson's like no, what's going on with that hole? I keep throwing tires in it and they're like, oh my god, don't throw tires in it
No, I'm just joking. I didn't say that
Anyways after they gave him a heart attack
They go no, no, it's throw it's safe to throw tires in there
But don't throw marble in it because the previous owners kept throwing chunks of marble in there
Now I'm assuming that they were some sort of like counter maker. Again, I don't think they just really really love chunks of marble
They kept throwing chunks of marble in there and eventually it filled up and then there was an explosion and it blew out everywhere
And then they moved away now. I don't think the two events were connected
But the marble did all shoot out like a shotgun blast and they moved away now at that point if I was Johnson, I'd be thinking uh-oh
I better start getting some of those tires out of there because I don't want a tire explosion
But he doesn't he just leaves them in there
But what he starts to notice is over time he has this pile of tires in the pit and now like you can see the top of the
Tires, they're higher than the pit
Over time he starts to see the top of the tire slowly go down
And after an indeterminate amount of time they don't put it in the article pretty soon
He couldn't see the top of the tires anymore like the pit was getting smaller and smaller and smaller
It was just melting or shrinking or falling into something
And that's all we know. We don't know where he lives. We don't have any other information on the story
If there ever was a tire explosion, we don't know. We don't know what's going on
Interesting story again most likely a local legend, but it's interesting to see the comparison one has far more details
So it's almost automatically more believable. It's very weird. I read the first one
I was like, well, if I don't know who it is and I don't know when it happened
Then it's probably not real
But the second one I still missing some key details like a location and a date
But it's more believable because the character acts in a more believable way. He goes, oh, it's a big pit
I wonder what I'm gonna do with it. I'm throw garbage in it
Not lower myself into it and go wildly insane. It's just kind of interesting how those two things play out
But when I said bottomless pits when I said I was going to talk about bottomless pits
I'm sure a good 30 40 of you go up
He's going to mel's he's going to mel's not mel's diner from happy days. That's dated reference. Did they still even show reruns of that?
No, anyone who really investigates bottomless pits knows the story
Of mel waters mel waters
Is a man who made a phone call
I don't know why i'm talking like that all of a sudden mel waters is a dude so back in back in
1997 mel waters called up coast to coast am with art bell
And told this crazy story over the radio and really sparked a renewed interest in the idea of bottomless pits
He is the elan musk of the bottomless pits
He is the guy who really like got everyone to think. Whoa, this could actually be something
We're going to ellensburg washington. So very very. I don't know if it's near actually
It's in the same state as the coma. We're still in washington
I probably should have looked it up on google maps
But anyways, we're in ellensburg washington and you have a man named mel waters
And what he did was he found a bottomless pit
He found a big they can't say that it's bottomless until they started testing it
But he notices this giant pit in his property. It also has like a little bit of a wall
I think his wall was made of metal just a small like wall
And his first thing is he starts throwing garbage in it, which again is a normal thing
And now you see again the difference. We have dates now. We have a full name and stuff like that
He starts throwing garbage into the pit
And starts to get curious about it and
Can't see how deep it is. He takes a pack of lifesavers wraps a string around it lowers it figuring if it hits water
He'll pull it up and the lifesavers will be dissolved nothing. So he's doing these scientific tests
Eventually, he's able to get 80,000 feet
of fishing lure
string
Fishing string that's what it's called right fishing line fishing line. I never I'm not an outdoors dude at all
Anyways, he's puts down 80,000 feet of fishing lure dammit a fishing line
And doesn't hit bottom doesn't hit bottom
Now people are going away a second this story is okay. Let me finish. Let me finish. He doesn't hit bottom
So now he's like truly
Truly, this is a bottomless pit
He keeps throwing junk in it can't figure it out keeps throwing junk in it
But then he knows these dudes his friends of his these friends of his are basque sheep herders
So rock on basque brothers his basque sheep herders
Are hanging out with him and he's telling them about this hole and they said well
You know if you really want to test this hole we got a test for you. So they take a sheep
This is okay
So let before I get into the sheep story that was a little bit of a teaser because then it gets really bizarre
Let's talk about the fishing fishing line
um 80,000 feet of fishing line is obviously a lot
Of fishing line. I mean that must have cost him quite a lot of money to get that much unless he's a true scavenger
and just like rifling through fishermen stuff
80,000 feet is a ton but
I that's what I thought when I read that I was like there's no way any human could collect 80,000 feet of fishing line if
Unless they worked at a fishing line company and they were like stealing it like Johnny Cash. So
That was my logic
But there was a geologist who said there is no and this is a little more scientifically
Possible than my just like you can't own it. That's impossible. This geologist said
fishing line
Drop to 80,000 feet into the earth would melt
It would just melt because it's just too hot down there. It's not saying the hot lava is down there
But the temperature 80,000 feet down is way too hot
It's impossible the the heat of the planet would just burn the string
And also you'd wonder how does he know that it doesn't hit the ground to just start piling up
But let's give him the benefit of the doubt here for a second
Because assuming the hole is actually that deep at a certain point. It's like not into the earth anymore
It's like almost a portal into something else a a basically a gateway
It's less a bottomless pit carved into the planet and more of a really really deep pit that opens to some sort of abyss
Which is actually where the term bottomless pit comes from so
That aside the geological pressures and stuff aside because we're getting into the weird stuff now
He's back. He's hanging out with the bass sheep herders. They take a sheep and they put it into a crate
And they begin lowering it into the bottomless pit and the whole time they should
They hear it getting less and less as they're lowering it down
They lower it down about 1500 feet and then all of a sudden they hear it and the the ropes start shaking violently
They hear it running around in the crate and screaming and then nothing
The lamb goes silent. You're pulling this
Sheep up this lamb slash sheep
Up to the top of I do in this with my hand motion for some reason like i'm pulling a rope
They pull it to the top of the pit
And the sheep is dead
So they do see it's dead and they do a field autopsy on it. They cut it open and it's all of its organs have turned to like this gelatinous
tumor
And they're like, oh that's disgusting. No one's eating lamb chops tonight
and so
They pull it out
And they see that the tumor is moving and the one dude goes
I'm gonna cut it open. I'm gonna see what's in that the other guys are like, no, no, no, don't don't don't and he does
He cuts it open and what is described as
a tumor seal
Just falls out still attached with an umbilical cord
To something to the basically the mama tumor inside the sheep
So it's basically it looks like a seal
But it kind of also looks like a giant tumor just like a growth
With hauntingly human like eyes is how it's described
And according to this website that i was reading
It says that the seal the tumor seal looked at the sheep herders and mel
And the sheep herders looked at the tumor seal
silently
For two hours at a certain point someone's going to be like you guys are seeing that right like I would say that after the first 30 seconds
But apparently for two hours everyone just kind of looked at each other
And then after two hours the tumor the tumor seal nodded to the men and jumped into the pit
And they're like what in tarnation was that and mel's water's just like I don't know wait
Wait wait a second
I used to have esophagus cancer and now it's in remission
He felt the tumors in his own body disappear going to remission. So bizarre
yes
It's weirder because the tumor seal keeps showing up after that he pops back out of the pits. He's like
I'm back folks. He's doing a little dance like the frog from Warner Brothers
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
Ta-da-da-da has a little top hat now and a cane he shows up just all the time it starts visiting the sheep herders be like what are you guys doing?
Can I play rummy? Yeah, I'm really good at this here. Let me deal. He ended and he's
Playing with the cards
He can also well he can't talk to them, but only veam shortwave radio
So he's like down there on a ham radio
His name is to me. Hey, it's to me coming from the hole. How are you guys doing up there?
And they're like god damn it too. Well, this guy stopped calling me. Hey, to me. What's up?
He can talk to him via shortwave radio
I mean come on. So we're gonna get into how the story evolved in a second. He can talk to them via radio, but
Unfortunately for us whenever they tried recording his voice. It just came out as static
But if we were there, we would have been able to understand what to me was saying
Eventually though people always go were mel. Where's this hole at?
Like seriously, I can get cured of my cancer. I can throw garbage down there
I might even be able to be harassed on various occasions by a talking tumor and he goes well
I can't tell you where it's at because this is kind of the conclusion to the story
The federal government found out about the hole and they either scared him off their property and took the place over
Or they bought it from him or both right now
Well as of really his last communication mel said he was living on australia
On the federal government's dime. They basically paid him off but told him if they didn't take the deal
They were going to find a drug lab on his property
And that place is now owned by the u.s. Military which that pattern does fit
Other weird locations we found when I did that death valley episode all these weird underground spots are all now owned by the government
And they're totally off limits to civilians
But it's a very convenient answer as well. So let's start getting into the nitty gritty here
We're running a little long, but let's get in the nitty gritty here because I just can't leave you with that
There's never been anyone
Oh something that a lot of skeptics go is they say mel waters never existed. There's no record that he lived in that area
However, he could be using a fake name. I'm not going to totally hang my hat on the fact like well
There wasn't a guy named mel waters up there
Then the whole story is fake
Like I'm not going to hang but I think there's other stuff that proves that the story is kind of ridiculous other than that
Using a fake name is not
Musicians use fake names. Like that's just kind of a normal thing
There's other interesting
Things that are about this one. They are used to be a file on all the mel water stories at
A local library that files gone and people have pointed to that being some sort of conspiracy
Although other people could say it could just been a patron who took that
People are still looking for mel's hole today. I don't know if mel is still alive
And if it's a fake name, we never really would know if he was alive
People believe they've narrowed down kind of the area where the hole could be but since they don't know
Who the person was who really made the phone call to art bell
Or owned the property or anything like that. They can't look through property records
So people are still looking for this hole and everyone else is saying your guys are idiots because it doesn't exist
It's physically impossible
And I think they're half right a bottomless hole cannot exist
That goes all the way through the earth just the pressure of the earth would collapse a hole at any given point
So what you can have though, where's it going to get, you know paranormal here
You could have a deep hole
Or it really anything that enters into
Some other realm
So it doesn't even have to be a bottomless pit you could look at the pit and it could only be three feet deep
But when you throw a penny in there, you just see the penny disappear into the ground
Obviously science disagrees with me on that
But I mean when you're looking at the paranormal and the supernatural that's possible
You could come home from work today
Walk through your bedroom door
And end up in raven dale some magical forest full of pixies and a dark overlord trying to take stuff over in a supernatural world
It's incredibly
Small chance at whatever happened, but in a world where you believe in the paranormal and supernatural it's possible
So make sure that you're really good with your bow and arrow skills before you go home
But if you were able to have a static place you could have these weird time slips and portals moving around
But if there was actually a hole
That you were able to go into and enter into this other realm
And that's why it seems bottomless. There's some other fantasy realm
That is just full of couches broken down tv sets in tires and they're like why god
Why are you punishing us as another tire comes rolling crushing their village?
But I think that's the really the only workable way you could have a bottomless pit as described in these stories
Because really that's only the interesting way if someone goes I found a bottomless pit
You're like really and they're like look I can look all the way through the planet earth. You'd be like, yeah, it's kind of cool
But that's not necessarily interesting
I want a bottomless pit that leads somewhere not just a pit that just goes
To the molten core of the planet big whoop. Yeah
Like that's to me is just a big old hole in the ground
I would want a bottomless pit that was truly bottomless like you could throw stuff in forever and it would never fill up
And then that's a paranormal thing
Otherwise you're just throwing couches through and they're getting melted in hot lava
And that's really not bottomless the bottomless part the bottom part is just the other side of the planet
So if we take that scenario I took a little long time to get to this point
This is my point if we take that scenario that could be moved
That could be moved
If you if you were able to identify that here is a hole
And in this hole is a static gateway to another realm
We can either do one or two things we can put a government or a military presence on this hole
And it would be super bizarre because we're in this little part of washington all of a sudden this military base springs up out of nowhere
And maybe there was one there for a time
But it seems like the first thing they would want to do is
Can we move it?
Can we move this hole?
We want to put it somewhere else
If we dig this hole up
Will the unusual qualities remain as scientists are like, I don't know you got 8 000 feet of fishing line and they're like, yeah it's over there
You figure out how deep
The actual earth pit is and where it opens up into something else
And the thing is is you could say well, we could dig it up and we could retain its properties
Or we could dig it up and then it's just a bunch of dirt is the risk versus the reward
And if this agency or this government says it is
It's absolutely where we don't want it here. We want to be able to access this on a regular basis without bringing trucks in
Let's move it
so
Going on that thought mel's hole. I believe if it's real at all
Which i'm highly doubtful of
But if it's real at all
It isn't there anymore
They would have found it by now people have said that they've seen it before
The story actually I forgot to mention the stories of this bottomless pit existed before the phone call
That mel made and some people go no, it was just a really really deep pit. It wasn't really bottomless
But whether or not it's like this portal where you can throw sheep down and then talking tumors pop out
I don't know people have said the dogs have come back to life being thrown in there
People have said black beams have shot out of there or radios will play really old music when you walk by which I think they just have
the oldie station on but
There's lots of other weird phenomenon. So it would be something that the military would or a government agency or a
secret society would want control of
But not there
They'd want to move it
there could be a place
outside of the view of
us of normal people
that
all of these items all of these things
are stored
And you go isn't that the plot of like indiana jones isn't that the plot of that show warehouse 13 predictive programming maybe?
predictive programming
No, I think I honestly believe that if any of this stuff is real if any of this stuff is provable whether it's walking mannequins or bottomless pits
Somebody wants to own and contain those and study them and more importantly use them
Because why not?
The one thing we forget a lot of times
Is that governments and secret societies and secret agencies?
And it's mad scientists are people. They're us. They are us. They just have more
access to the paths of power or money or technology, but they're us
If you found a bottomless pit
You would start throwing junk into it if the illuminati had access to a pit
They're going to start throwing junk into it. It's just human curiosity to want to do these things
But after you got tired after you got bored of throwing your eight television set down there and never hearing it smash
You're going to think
If I can throw stuff down there
Can stuff from down there come up?
But see that's where we differ from these other groups
We can just think about it or lower a sheep down 1500 feet
If you are a governmental agency or a secret society
You have the resources
to find out
100 percent
What's on the other side of that portal?
You have the power to 100 find out what's on the other side of that portal
The question is
What will they bring back up?
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit me up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio
Twitter is @jasonlcarpenter
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast 200th episode guys 200th episode 200th canum is today, right?
This episode is going to run long. It's a 200th episode. I did a lot of talking but
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]