You've all heard of the Loch Ness Monster, but that's a weakling compared to what comes
out of North Korea.
And then we take a look at a bizarre tale of ghost activity from old timey England.
Was a man really pursued all over town by the demon of Sprayton today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having a lot of fun.
Let's go ahead and get started with our episode.
First off we're going to give a shout out to one of our legacy patrons, someone who's
been supporting the show for a long time.
I gotta say thank you to steroids and crack cocaine.
Steroids and crack cocaine.
Thank you so much for supporting the show.
You have kept me up all night, kept me working hard.
You made me sell my car for steroids and crack cocaine.
I wonder, can you get addicted to steroids?
Hey Jamie, look that up.
Pull that up on the view screen.
I want to see if we can get addicted to steroids.
Is that possible?
You might be able to get addicted to the benefits of steroids, but I'm not, you notice I'm not
asking that question about crack cocaine.
Oh you know what, speaking of that, so long time listeners of the show, i.e. if you've
been listening for just past two weeks, have learned that I've become addicted to the subreddit
about drugs.
There's a subreddit for opioids and there's subreddits for heroin.
I found a subreddit for PCP.
It doesn't get updated that often, because I think everyone's on PCP.
Let's go ahead and actually go get started with the episode.
Steroids, I was trying to think, why did I go off on that tangent?
I forgot.
Our Patreon guy, steroids and crack cocaine.
Let's fire up that carbonicopter.
We are headed out to North Korea.
Now we're in stealth mode, obviously.
The Hermit Kingdom does not like visitors, especially ones from the United States, who
aren't named Dennis Rodman.
We're flying out there now.
Tip of the hat to Stealthy Steve.
Stealthy Steve is the one who brought up the whole idea about North Korean cryptids and
got me walking down this path as it is.
So again, thank you so much for helping out with North Korea Week, which is what this
is.
We're headed out.
Bring that helicopter low steroids.
We're flying over a giant lake.
It actually sits on the border of China and North Korea.
And it's a crater lake.
So it used to be like a big old volcano or something, a regular old mountain that got
hollowed out, a bunch of beavers came in, and then crashed in.
Or is a crater lake when an asteroid hits the earth and makes a big crater?
I'm pretty sure it's when a volcano collapses.
Actually, I'm 100% sure in this case because there's something else that involves a volcano,
but crater lakes in general, I think, can be either one, right?
But anyways, it has nothing to do with it.
Bring that helicopter down.
We are flying down to Heaven Lake.
That's what it's called.
Very, very sweet.
Now, there's an old-timey legend.
It's not that old.
It's just a couple decades.
But Kim Jong-il, previous ruler of North Korea, Kim Jong-un's father, legend has it.
Imagine having a legend that's just like 40 years old.
But I guess, you know, that's what they do.
Legend has it that Kim Jong-il was born at Heaven Lake.
And it's interesting because they want to keep tying the current North Korean regime
into old legends of the three kingdoms.
So they can say that North Korea is the best Korea, that this is Korea.
South Korea is some sort of bastardization they need to be reunified because we keep
finding all this proof.
These old kings are related to the North Korean rulers.
So it's no surprise that Kim Jong-il's birthplace is supposedly a place called Heaven's Lake.
And when he died, the lake was frozen over.
Not like he died and the ice went shh, froze.
Because that would just be creepy.
No, no, no.
It was already frozen.
He died.
And then the ice cracked, quote, "So loud it seemed to shake the heavens and the earth."
The globe itself mourned for the death of Kim Jong-il, producer of the Godzilla movie,
Pulgasari.
That was yesterday's episode.
We talked about the monster movie that the director was kidnapped to make.
And it was a Godzilla movie, Godzilla knock-up.
It was a good movie.
Forgot to add this detail.
The special effects are really good.
The movie came out in 1985.
They're so good because Toho Studios actually worked on it.
See what happened was some people at Toho were given a job offer to make a movie in
China.
They said sure, and they hopped on a plane.
The plane landed in North Korea.
And they're like, oh no.
They meet a director who, at this point, a lot of people assumed was kidnapped.
Some people believe he went over there normally.
But Toho's studio employees are like, well, what are we going to do?
We're here.
So they made these special effects.
It's a really good rubber suit.
Actually, there's a shot of the ending of Pulgasari and he looks terrified.
And that's the first time I've ever seen a muppet look that scared.
Very, very good work on Toho's studio's part.
They were allowed to leave after the movie was done.
The director and his wife had to escape.
But if you guys are interested in that, you didn't hear yesterday's episode, check that
out.
If you didn't know, that's fine.
We're not going to talk about it anymore.
The lake.
We are at Heaven's Lake.
Now, Loch Ness Monster, monster in the lake.
Then there's like Bessie and Ghostie and Mucci and all this stuff.
There's always some stupid named monster in some stupid lake.
I don't like lake monsters.
They're lame.
Oh, no, I saw a log.
You want to know what the Loch Ness Monster was when I tell you this.
It's totally going to ruin that famous photo.
It's an elephant taking a bath.
That famous photo from a long time ago, like the 20s or whatever, there's the lump and
then there's the neck.
It's an elephant taking a bath.
100%.
That's what it is.
There was a circus in town at time.
It's an elephant taking a bath.
But anyways, Loch Ness Monster, I used to believe it was real.
I don't believe it's real.
That photo is not a monster.
It's an elephant taking a bath.
So I'm not a huge fan of it.
But this lake, Heaven Lake, we're not talking about one lame neck monster that actually
looks like an elephant trunk.
No, dude.
North Korea brings it for real.
In the 7th, there's footage.
Blurry footage, the only kind of footage of cryptids, but a Chinese cameraman takes
footage of six separate monsters swimming around.
For 20 minutes, he was videotaping this thing.
Six monsters swimming around in the lake.
Six.
Pfft.
Loch Ness.
They're one sighting.
I should say this.
So there's six of those in all, in total, in this lake.
Three different sea monsters, not 20 different sightings.
20 different sea monsters have been seen in this lake.
One of them had a four foot long neck.
Which isn't that impressive, really.
I mean, the neck's not even as big as I am.
But anyways, that's not impressive.
What is impressive, I guess a four foot long neck is impressive on something that's not
a giraffe, but its head looked like a human's head.
That's creepy, right?
Just like you're watching this giant creature from the past giant four inch long neck and
then your neighbor Barry's head on it.
That's spooky.
In 1962, a bunch of people were hanging out at heaven lake.
Hundred people, to be precise, apparently.
Maybe there were 200 people and only 100 people saw this, but 100 people saw this.
Two sea monsters.
Floating around.
And a dude's like, "Wait a second."
He pulls out his telescope.
They're chasing each other.
What?
That's spooky, right?
Again, see, that's the thing like, I know you guys might sound like I'm being super
sarcastic.
Sea monsters just float.
Sea monsters are fine.
Like giant squids, monsters in the ocean, I'm fine with that, because those are probably
real.
But you go to the Loch Ness and you see a monster pop up.
Their chiring economy is based around tricking people into thinking that there's a creature
there.
So of course they're going to believe it.
Just like if there was a town that can make money off the Blair Witch, they're going to
tell you the Blair Witch is real.
But anyways, big old monster, even if there was a monster in Loch Ness.
So?
Like, it doesn't do anything.
It just floats there.
It just floats around.
You're like, "Jesus, it's a dinosaur."
It would prove so much stuff about science and evolution.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So would a book.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like, yeah, there's a big old sea monster floating around in a lake.
That's not impressive to me.
Is it eating?
This is my first question.
Is it violent?
Is it eating people?
First off, first question, is it real?
And if it's real, what does it do?
And they're like, "Well, it only eats Comquat."
Well, then it's stupid.
That's a stupid...
That might be an interesting thing for you, nerd.
But as far as like a sea monster goes, that's like...
It's not even a monster!
Monster implies violence and/or terror.
Right?
Now, rhinos, I would consider a monster.
I mean, they're technically a real-life animal, but I'm not going to go anywhere near rhinos
and stuff like that.
But I would much rather, if someone said, "Do you want to go and see two rhinos fighting?"
Like, you physically be there, but they're in a cage.
It's like a UFC cage match.
Would you rather see two rhinos fighting or a lame waterlogged dinosaur?
You see the tip of his eyeball.
What would you choose?
Right?
You'd choose the two rhinos.
Unless you were lame.
So anyways, these guys are chasing each other.
See, Heaven Lake, it would be cool to go there.
I mean, if I wasn't going to become a political prisoner or be forced to make movies.
But I wouldn't mind going to Heaven Lake because your chances are higher.
There's 20 different monsters.
They're fighting each other.
And this is something Loc Ness never did.
This is something Nessie never did.
In 1903, it was the first sighting.
The creature, one of them, because again, there's 20 different ones, this buffalo.
Buffalo.
Okay?
They already look freakish.
It runs out.
There's three people hanging out on the beach.
Just enjoying their time in 1903.
They're like, "Oh, this is so nice.
There's nothing else to do but just sit here because there's no television, no internet,
nothing."
And then a buffalo-shaped creature jumps out of the lake onto land, roars, which is interesting
and a little suspicious because there would be no reason for a sea creature to roar.
But anyways, it roars whatever.
I guess I can accept the idea that there's monsters in this lake but not that they could
roar.
It jumps out and roars.
It begins charging these people.
Now again, it's 1903.
There may not be anything to do, but everyone's got a gun.
It's a good old days.
And a dude straight up, "Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop," puts six bullets in this creature's
belly and then just turns and swims back into the water.
That is a monster story.
I don't want to hear about Loc Ness.
You want to know what the very first--this has become.
I'm glad that I'm anti-Scotland pro-North Korea on this story.
You want to hear the very first sighting of Nessie?
This will change a lot of people's minds if the elephant thing didn't change your mind.
The very first sighting of Nessie, the very first documented sighting.
A Christian missionary had gone to Scotland to preach to the natives up there and they're
rowing across the lake and the Loch Ness monster appeared.
You're like, "Well, Jason, that's legit.
It doesn't matter if they're native Scottish people or Christian missionaries."
And then he, in the name of Christ, compels the creature to leave them alone and the creature
fearing the word of God swims away.
That's not true, right?
And if it was true, then that's a demonic entity.
It's definitely not a dinosaur.
There was never a time where you'd be--I never saw that part in Jurassic Park where the T-Rex
is coming towards the car and they all start making the sign of the cross and he goes,
"Hah!"
So either Loch Ness monster is a demonic entity, and that story's true, or it's a dinosaur
and it devoured everyone on that boat or just swam away and it was perfect timing.
Look it up.
I'll have it in the show notes.
That's the very first sighting of Loch Ness monster.
People may go, "Oh, the natives."
That was the first recorded sighting of Loch Ness monster.
They prayed it went away.
It's either a demon or it's totally made up.
But you know what's not made up.
You know what?
You know what I believe in is these reports from North Korea that it has more monsters
per capita than any other lake ever.
Again, how do you believe in that story if that's the first sighting of the creature?
So anyways, let's go ahead and move on.
That was a weird segment.
It was oddly hostile too.
Let's go ahead.
I do not like lake monsters, but Heaven's Lake is pretty dope.
Let's leave it.
There's just utter silence in the carbonicopter.
Even the blades don't want to make a sound as we're taking off.
Steroids and crack cocaine is kind of looking over the shoulder.
This is not muttering in the corner.
"Oh, Loch Ness, I hate you so much.
I'm going to wrap my hands around your giant demonic neck and strangle you."
Steroids is like, "Uh, you okay back there, Jason?"
I was like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
Just don't fly over any lakes.
You might end up in one."
He's like, "Uh, we're flying."
Now I'm just sitting in the darkened corner.
We're flying off in the carbonicopter.
We're staying away from lakes.
We're headed to-- for all I know, Spritan is full of lakes, but we're headed to a little
village in England known as Spritan.
Spritan.
And this story is called the Demon of Spritan.
But I better pick a pronunciation and stick with it.
The Demon of Spritan.
It's November 1682, so let's land that carbonicopter.
Let's put on our old, timey clothes.
We've got some powdered wigs to walk around in.
Got canes, little jackets with coat tails.
But anyways, they were going to meet a man.
His name's Francis Fay, 20 years old.
And he works for Philip first, which is a great name.
He's a landowner.
So we got Francis and Philip hanging out, doing old timey stuff.
Now Francis is walking around the property, and then one day he sees Philip's dad, Papa
Furs.
What we'll call him?
Papa Furs walking around the property.
Now Francis kind of stops in his tracks.
What?
Because he knows that Papa Furs has been dead for a couple years now.
But that's him.
That's Papa.
Dressed the same, carrying the mole stick.
He had this giant stick that he used to smash the heads open of moles.
Now the one's on your back, but you know, the one's that digs through your yard.
And he turns around and he sees Francis, and he goes, "Ah boy.
So glad to see you here.
Yes.
But I'm going to stop doing this voice because it gets annoying.
I have a mission for you, Francis.
You see, I have some unfinished business.
There's two dudes in town that I each owe ten shillings to.
And then my sister I owe 20 shillings to.
I need you to repay them.
Which, to be fair, is the perfect way to settle your debts, right?
Die.
Because a ghost and make someone else pay them off.
But Papa goes, "Francis, listen.
You got to do this otherwise I'm going to haunt you.
You got to pay this money, otherwise I'm going to be super spooky.
I got this giant stick.
Now I may look like a ghost.
I may look kind of see-through.
But trust me, this stick can do some damage."
Francis goes, "Well, you're going to give me the money?"
"No!
No, I'm not going to give you money.
It's ghost money.
I gave it to you.
It just disappeared.
Turned an ectoplasm in your pocket.
You got to pay him back and then I won't haunt you anymore."
Now Francis is probably thinking a couple things.
One, I don't have 40 shillings right now or for a while.
Two, I didn't ask for this.
I was just walking through the house, right?
I just happened to know this guy and I turned the corner and he's sitting there with a giant
stick dead.
Now he's speaking to me, "Pay 40 shillings to people."
And then Papa first goes, "Oh, and just a word of warning.
Like I might be a spooky ghost because I got this giant stick and I just threatened you.
But my ex-wife is way spookier."
Now Francis goes, "That doesn't make sense.
He knew Papa first when he was alive and he knew his wife and he goes, "What?
Your wife's super nice, dude.
She might have been nice, but she's not nice now.
She's horrible."
Yeah, whatever.
So Francis goes, "That's probably just, you know, divorce isn't even good in the afterlife.
He's probably just bitter.
But I'll stay away from her grave.
Like what's he going to do, right?
Try not to attract the attention of a crazy..."
Actually, and he was like, "Nah, she was a pleasant woman.
I think he's just kind of running his mouth."
But he is able to get the shillings.
He goes to the first guy in town and goes, "Hey, Papa first wants you to have these 10
shillings."
Dude's like, "Oh, that's sweet."
Goes to the second guy, "Papa first wants you to have these 10 shillings."
"Ah, that's awesome."
He goes to Papa's sister and says, "Papa first's ghost visited me and wants you to know that
he feels bad that he didn't pay you back.
Here's 20 shillings."
Now the sister goes, "I'm not taking that money.
That's something that the devil would do.
I'm not taking that money at all."
Francis is like, "Dude, I'm going to be haunted for eternity if you don't take these stupid
20 coins."
And now I'm not doing it.
It's just a dorn.
He goes back to Papa first and says, "Hey, man, she's not taking this money.
Can I keep it?"
And Papa's like, "No, you can't keep it.
Use it.
Buy her a ring.
And then if she accepts that, I won't hunt you anymore."
And he's like, "Ah, that's probably a good idea."
So he goes.
He buys her a ring worth 20 shillings.
He goes back to her, gives her the ring.
She accepts it.
Moral of the story, women love jewelry.
So he does accept it.
So his mission is done.
He is now totally fine with Papa first.
He's no longer going to be haunted.
He's leaving the sister's house.
He's riding back to Sprighton.
And as he gets into town, multiple witnesses saw this, as he gets into town, the ghost
of Papa first jumps onto the back of the horse, scaring both Francis and the horse.
Papa first then wraps his arms around Francis, jumps off of the horse, still holding Francis.
They fly into the air, crashing onto the ground.
Off a moving horse, I must remind you, which is incredibly dangerous.
Incredibly dangerous.
Now people in town are like, "What in the world?"
They just see him basically go from riding a horse to watching a spectral figure of
the damned jump on the horse, grab him, and they both go flying off.
He crashes into the ground.
Then the ghost jumps back on the horse.
The horse takes a jump, jumps 20 feet.
Not straight up.
Don't get ridiculous.
20 feet horizontally.
That is not the demon of Sprighton.
Papa first is not the demon referred to in this story.
After Francis is like, "What in the world just happened?"
I did what he said.
I paid everyone off.
He said he wasn't going to haunt me anymore.
He almost murders me.
Almost murders my horse.
What's going on?
But Papa first is never seen again.
Now all of this is cataloged in old town records.
There was a letter written back when this was a contemporary event in the village of
Sprighton.
I know it's pronounced differently each time.
I'm sorry.
But this was contemporary records.
This was written back then about these crazy events that was going on.
But that's not even the beginning.
That's not what they're referring to when they talk about the demon of Sprighton.
That's his ex-wife.
Because after this is all done, she shows up.
He's a shapeshifter.
So most of the time she'll just appear as a woman.
But she would sometimes appear as a dog that would breathe fire.
This is a weird thing.
It kind of shows the weird physics difference between our reality and ghosts.
This story's weird in that aspect.
Francis and a bunch of other people are hanging out in the house and the ghost of the ex-wife
shows up and shapeshifts into a horse.
Which is not something that Francis wants to see anytime soon.
So now there's a horse in the house.
The horse then jumps out of a window.
Now obviously the window, it's interesting because it's big enough for a horse to jump
through but it's made up of individual window panes.
So when the horse jumps through the window, only a single pane breaks.
Interesting then it just ran away.
She was known to tear off Francis' clothes.
He'd just be walking doing his job.
"Oh it's so fun being a servant.
So I don't have to go into the horse table."
"Ah!
Ah!
My clothes!"
"It would rip his wig off his head."
"Ah!
Give me that!
I need that!"
"I'm going to be a judge in a couple hours now!"
It would also rip off other people's clothes but all of the torment seemed to be focused
on Francis.
To this point, so other people would come to the house and get their wigs start flying
around.
Maybe their sleeve would get ripped.
Francis one day was walking through the house.
The woman, the demon, grabbed his head.
Tell me if this isn't a nightmare.
This is something that I hope never happens to me or really anyone ever.
Graps him by the head, pulls him to the ground, is dragging him across the floor.
So he's kicking and screaming.
His hands are trying to grab at a force that isn't really even there.
He just feels pressure on his head.
He's slowly being dragged across the floor as he's screaming for help.
And he's kind of able to look a little bit.
He's being dragged towards the bed.
Now there's a gap.
It's not a very wide gap between where the bed is and the wall.
And that's exactly where his head is going.
And he feels these hands, these cold icy hands, powerful strength pulling him towards that
gap and then begins to squeeze his head in between the wall and the bed.
This isn't your futon.
This is an old timey bed where the lightest materials were iron and oak.
The bed was not budging.
And neither was the wall.
His head is getting wedged into this gap.
And he's screaming for help.
Eventually, I'm sure other people in the house, they're like, "Oh, what's, is this
wig?"
Is he screaming about his stupid wig getting pulled off again?
They give him a couple minutes.
They're like, "Hey, he's still screaming.
Maybe his clothes got ripped off."
I don't know.
He's been screaming a long time.
They run upstairs.
They see his head stuck.
It takes several of them to get his head unstuck.
Again, they're not moving the bed.
The bed probably weighs more than all of them put together.
This is a very nice estate.
This guy has a bunch of servants.
These are all servants working here.
So again, it's not just like some three little bears' bed.
We just...
Not like their beds are garbage either.
They were actually probably pretty well made.
I wonder what the Papa Bear did for work.
But anyway, obviously, you can afford a house.
But anyways, that's another topic.
I'll do some research on that, how much fairy tale characters are made.
They finally get his head pulled out.
Now, because of his fright and the multiple injuries to his head, they call for a doctor.
Doctor gets there and he's all like, "Ugh, messed up."
So the doctor does what doctors do best back then, bloodletting.
So they go, "Okay, we're going to cut your head.
We're going to relieve some pressure."
Because the dude was jacked up.
It wasn't like this guy.
They're like, "Oh, what a hypochondriac.
He just loves having his blood pulled out of his body."
No, he got his head put in a wedge, basically.
It's that scene from Casino, except instead of a vice, it was a bed from the 1600s and
a giant wall.
They give him some bloodletting and you know, you cut, you let some blood out, you cut,
you let some blood out, stuff like that.
Now, they're cutting his arm, which is weird.
You think you would have relieved the pressure where it's coming from, but they cut his arm.
I'm not a bloodletting specialist.
And it didn't work.
So I guess it doesn't matter where you do it.
But anyways, they were cutting his arm, letting blood out and stuff like that, like air out
of a tire.
And then they bandage his arm up and the doctor goes, "Well, I think you'll feel better now."
The bandage is then unfurl from his arm.
Wrap around his neck and start strangling him.
As the doctor is still there, he just put the bandages on this dude.
"Oh, better.
Here's your bill."
And then of course the servants and the doctor have to help him not get suffocated by possessed
bloody bandages.
Now talk about a quick de-escalation before this thing really gets bad, before it gets
worse.
Before this thing really gets bad, his shoelaces come to life and start moving around the floor
like an eel, which in that case, I'd be like, "Oh, thank God, that's all that's happening,
right?"
Like if all of a sudden your shoelaces popped off and they started doing the...
Dance, you'd be shocked.
I'd be shocked, it'd be terrifying.
After having my head pulled into a tiny little compartment and then strangled with my own
bandages, I'd be like, "Oh, that's so cute.
That's so cute."
Also a barrel of salt walked away that happened to just...
Just wobbled and moved into another room.
And that's convenient haunting because maybe they wanted the salt in that room, right?
Maybe somebody put the salt in the wrong place.
Maybe everyone argued who brought the salt and set it down there in the first place.
So now it's in the other room, that's perfect.
But of course, things don't end that way.
Francis is walking outside one day.
Now this ghost is quite powerful.
This is almost like something you'd see in a loony tune, which cartoon?
An invisible force.
He's walking through the field and a hand grabs the back of his coat, lifts him off the
ground, and he flies away.
Now he's flying through the air like if someone grabbed you by your belt or by your waist
and is just holding you up one handed.
So his arms and his legs are dangling.
He's screaming for help.
Not a single servant hears him.
Or maybe they did and they were just really, really tired of dealing with this stuff.
But after about a half hour, they go, "Hey, wait a second.
Where's Francis?"
And the guy who heard it's like, "Uh, I have a feeling he may have been kidnapped
by a ghost."
They start looking for him.
They find him at night, waist deep in a bog.
And he's dazed.
[Singing]
Just singing a song in the dark forest, waist deep in a freezing cold swamp.
Oh, great.
Francis, dang it.
I got dinner cooking.
I got to come out here and get you.
What's going to attack us?
Is that who you're going to attack us?
You got some bandages on we don't know about?
They don't take him to, because he's definitely like, something's wrong with it.
The lower half of his body is frozen.
Not like a big block of ice like Encino Man, but it's just cold to the touch.
You don't have to be Encino Man to have a medical emergency.
That's a little tip from Jason Carpenter.
They take him to a major town.
They take him to the closest town.
So they're going to be seen by a doctor right now.
And the doctor puts him in a little hospital room and goes, "Oh, yep, I've seen this before.
We got to take out blood.
That's how we're going to do this.
We're going to take out some blood.
Slice."
They're doing some bloodletting.
Now the next day, some of his friends, the remaining friends that he has.
Sure, a lot of friends have left him during this.
Remaining friends that he has show up.
He's sitting there.
His legs are feeling better.
He has bandages on his arm instead of around his neck, the way it's supposed to be.
But he has a cut on his forehead.
He has a gash.
They go, "What?
That wasn't there last night.
Like, you were in a bog.
You're waist deep.
You're singing some crazy song.
How'd you get that gash?"
And Francis looks at him just dead-eyed.
Francis is just so done with it at this point.
He looks at him and goes, "Dude, I'm sitting here in the hospital room, right?
I've got these bandages.
I keep looking at my bandages every 20 seconds."
Did it move?
And then a bird.
A bird flew into my hospital room with a rock in its mouth and then threw it at me.
Threw the rock at me.
Not just dropped it.
Straight up like cranked its neck back to get some momentum and threw it at me and threw
it at me so hard.
Put a gash in my forehead.
And the friends are like, "That is ridiculous."
And Francis is like, "You'll find the rock in here."
What's weird is the friends looked all over the hospital room.
I don't know if that's the proper term back then.
I think it was just a room that a doctor had been in.
But anyways, they look all over the room.
They find no rock.
What they find is a piece of bronze.
So this bird didn't come from the bird.
It didn't, even if it was an accident.
It's not like the bird was like, "Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp."
Sees a rock, picks it up, it's flying, and then goes, "No, I don't want this," and throws
it.
It was a piece of bronze.
It was a super heavy metal that a bird was flying around with and threw at this dude
and cut his head.
This letter, this article in the town records that talks about this whole thing, the letter
ends like this, quote, "This is a faithful account of the contents of a letter from a
person of quality in Devin, dated 2nd of May 1683.
The young man will be 21 if he lives to August next."
So even the person writing this record is like, "This dude is not going to be 21 years
old, dude.
This dude is toast.
Something is going to kill this guy."
And the thing is, we don't know how this story ended.
We don't know if he made it to be 21.
We don't know if the demon would continue to be sighted.
It's definitely seemed to be focused on him.
It wasn't like a town demon that these legends would still continue, but apparently this
stuff happened.
Now, again, there's obvious that this could, let's look at some rational explanations.
This is an internet hoax.
I've found this letter in a couple different places and things like that, but it's always
possible that it's a hoax.
We've got to address that.
But it's also possible that it is a true account of a young man who just happened to be walking
through the house one day, ended up owing a bunch of people money, and even after taking
care of his obligations got attacked by not one, but two ghosts.
One, a demonic entity that's pulling people into gas.
Unless you've seen horror movies, or, again, crime movies, or read about in newspapers,
having your head wedged into a space that's too tight.
So the next time you are walking through your house, be careful what hallway you look down.
You may see a former employer standing there, and you may also be requested to go through
these events.
However, if you thought what he went through was bad, imagine having to go to people's
houses and owing them money during a worldwide quarantine, or even worse, being attacked
by a ghost in your own house when everyone is isolated.
If your head got wedged into an impossibly tight space, would anyone ever hear your cries?
Or when the quarantine is lifted and things return to normal?
Would people wonder what happened to you?
Would someone eventually do a welfare check and find your body squeezed into a tiny spot?
It would leave a lot of questions.
Some would never be answered.
But we would know that maybe you were also visited by a demonic ex-wife.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also head us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbitRadio is your daily paranormal conspiracy and truth crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Be safe, be kind, I love you guys, and I will see you later.
Bye.
(upbeat music)