Did a witch
Enactor vengeance against a small town in Mississippi?
And then we take a look at
One of the newest theories to come out on the internet was 9/11 really a time travel experiment and and hold on hold
I'm not done yet and
I have found an audio clip that'll blow your mind today on Dead Rabbit Radio
I'm a rock big gal
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys really are having a great day
hope everyone is safe and
Yeah, I just hope everything's working out
So
Let's go ahead and jump into our first story
We're just gonna go right into this so let's hop on board the carpenter copter
We are going to a small little town
Somewhere in Mississippi. I don't know exactly where it's at
But I do know it's along the Yazoo River because and the town is called Yazoo
So pretty easy to find you're just gonna fly around till we see a river and then land and ask if this is the Yazoo River
And when the people are like no, we just keep flying around. It can't be that many rivers in Mississippi, right?
So as we're flying around we also have to go back in time. So
We're sure I don't know what sound effects I've done before but anyways all of them all the sound effects play at once we are in the year
1884 there's a witch living on the edge of town and
Fishermen because she lived on the edge of town towns by a river ergo. She lives by the river, right?
Fishermen go out to fish and
What they found out was?
Fishermen weren't coming back from fishing and the town sheriff is sitting there in that wooden chair that rocks a rocking chair
Rocking to rocking chair in his police station because he's super casual boots up on the desk twirling his gun and
People are like hey Jimmy Jimmy Joey Fisherman hasn't come back from fishing and I
Forgot the cops name I made up. We'll just call him Jerry. Maybe that's the same name
I don't remember and and Officer Jerry Sheriff Jerry goes
No, wait. Well, I'm rocking in my chair right now
I'll get it off work it out later and people leave and then the next day someone else comes back and they go
Samuel the fishermen the old dude who fishes all the time. He's gone
Sheriff Jerry is like that's a little suspicious and this goes on
He's not very good cop if you're not picking up on this. He's not very good cop, but eventually
After this half the fishermen are gone. He's like I should go find out what's going on down there
So the sheriff finally gets out of his rocking chair and gets all suited up and goes out to the witch district to find out
Actually, he doesn't go to the witch district. He doesn't know the which has anything to do with shit
He goes to the river to look for the fishermen and can't find any fishermen
He's like that's interesting and so then the witches district is right next to it
He's like, oh, I got to go pick up that I have new right I want to cut through the witches district by some I knew
He's walking through the witches district witches are like curses curses. They got carts full of like goblins in them
He's like, I don't need any of those but as he's looking through the witches district
He starts finding chopped up people and he's like, ah, I need to find out who's chopping up these bodies
And not only were these bodies being chopped up
There were signs of torture and these were the fishermen if it wasn't obvious the fishermen were showing up to fish on the lake
and then the witch would get them and torture them and
Then chop them up. Well, I don't even know if she chopped them up
Okay, the point is is she tortured them and murdered them. I don't know where the the dismemberment came from
Anyways, which runs which takes off because she realizes she's done for she's been caught by officer Sheriff Jerry
She's been caught by Sheriff Jerry. So there's a pursuit. There's a musical montage. She's like running through the jungle
They're playing some 80s song 1884 song
So it's like a musical montage with a banjo and as they're moving through the jungle
forest
Forest I got caught up in my own story as I run into the forest the witch is like looking behind her and she sees Sheriff Jerry
Getting closer and closer and like song highway to the danger zone
Going on she's like where's that music coming from she's running and she jumps into quicksand
And she's about way steep in quicksand right and the sheriff gets there and his deputies have magically appeared and they show up and
She turns around she turns around as she's in the quicksand and she raises her fist of them and she says in 20 years
I will return and burn this town to the ground
Drowns in the quicksand okay the sheriff's like oh
Well in that case I don't have to do any more investigation
My only witness who I never questioned drowned in quicksand that she must have been responsible for all of these murders, right?
We jump ahead
spoiler alert 20 years May 25th 1904 a
massive fire rips through the town of Yazoo huge fire
324 buildings burned and
Nobody to this day knew how the fire started the
The people said that there was a young couple getting married and somehow they think that the fire may have started there
But it moved through the town the people said it looked like it was super naturally
Controlled as it jumped from building to building and going inside and then knocking on a door and opening it walking
Little flame walking inside and people waking people up and they're like on the jump out the window
And then the flames like laughs and then jumps to the other building gets on a bus drives around town
Do people had no idea how this fire spread and here's a quote you go Jason. It's just the wind
Wind makes fire do stuff and two idiots wind seems supernatural. Ah, huh?
Stop who's you can't debunk this story the story's iron glad quote here's an quote
I found on an article quote area weather reports
From May 25th 1904 make no mentions of high winds in the area
Case closed obviously because if I can't trust the weather report written in 1904
What can you trust and especially if I can't fight me if I can't trust a website making such a bold claim then
Then who can I trust?
Anyways, that's the claim day after the fire
Everyone goes to the town cemetery as you do because your first inclination is to check on the witch
224 buildings burned remember, but the first thing you want to do is go to the graveyard
Check on the grave of the witch and when they got to the grave of the witch
They noticed that the chains that were wrapped around the grave site
So there's like four posts and there's chains around them were broken. It's like the witch
Broke the chains and escaped see the chains were put there to keep you in place, right?
Because what else could keep a ghost in place coming out of a grave?
Than four chains not like she could shimmy under them
Not like she could just float under them not like she could just pop out of someone else's grave because she's a ghost, right?
She just go through the ground pop out of someone else's grave. They saw that the chains were broke and
Here's our final statement on this story
Current local lore says that when all of the chains are gone from her grave
The witch will return again to exact her revenge on Yazoo City to this day our cemetery
Sextons sexy are similar not the cemetery part not the cemetery think about it sex tons
You know ton of sex. I have no idea what a sex then is to this day our cemetery sex
Then it might be something super gross actually
Maybe like 80 year old men like who inject stuff into bodies on with a quote to this day
Our cemetery sex and are very careful to keep the chains repaired and in place though
They are often broken again very soon after being repaired
That's the story of the witch of Yazoo now there are a lot of people who believe this story and
I wanted to highlight this story for two reasons one because I love the idea of people falling in a quicksand
I think that's hilarious. That's not the only reason I didn't talk about this for 10 minutes
Just because I wanted to tell a story about quicksand the story is
Stupid and and the thing and listen here's the thing
I might as well talk about this right now because I think you can obviously tell there's a bit of a different tone to the episode today
It was a rough weekend
We had a lot of bad news this weekend and it was funny because when I wanted to do this episode
I said let me try to find some stuff that's kind of funny
And then I realized that I would probably be better suited if I found stories that made me mad
Because I'm a little just it's just sucks like it's just been such a bad news day
That I was like yeah, so I was yeah
Anyways, let's look into this legend again a lot of people believe in this story, but let's take a look at and there's urban legends
I've talked about like the wandering busts of Philadelphia, which I said this is urban legend and it's fake
But it says something to us. I've talked about the bunny man's story a couple episodes back
Same thing but that story had some basis and truth
Let's look at this story here from the point of view of a human being with brain cells
There's a witch murdering fisherman. She's able to get away with him a long time
She tortured and killed him. How do they know?
How do they know she tortured him? How do they know she killed him?
None of the details are ever revealed in any of these things
Sheriff goes out to the witch's hut goes to arrest her. She takes off. That's a rational
That's a rational part of the story
That is what would happen in real life if you were if you were murdering people cops showed up
You're gonna run or if you were into any nefarious activities or just a witch in 1884 and when just cops show up outside your house
You're gonna run that part makes sense. She runs and she falls in quicksand and then she turns around and says in 20 years
I'm gonna burn your town to the ground or something like that drowns and the sheriff is just watching the whole thing
Here's my question. Why would the sheriff tell anyone that story? Why would he he goes back in a town?
They're like, hey Jerry, did you get the way? She's like no, but she didn't tell us. We're all doomed to die in 20 years
Like why would you tell that part of the story?
You're not gonna spread that version around town because people are already petrified that this witch has murdered a bunch of people also
No record of anyone being tortured or murdered in this city back then so then they
The fire starts is burnt. There was actually a fire and I think that shows I think that tells you why this story was created
But there was actually a fire bunch of buildings war burned
Not a ton of casualties actually any casualties that I could have could see but I could be wrong on that there could have been
Three or four or whatever. It's tragic. I'm not saying that's an okay number, but
The the town burns down that that's true and then the next day they go to the graveyard and they go to her grave with the chain
Stuff like that. How do they get the body out of the quicksand?
Why would they get the body out of the quicksand if they dug up a witch out of the quicksand if they decided to go through all that
Effort to get an old dead woman out of sandy water
Why would you then take her to your graveyard in town and bury her and put chains around it?
And don't tell me it's protect us from her magic because it would have been easier just to a lever in the quicksand
If you actually thought she was magical you could have cremated her because she didn't have any family friends
No one was gonna care or you put her in unmarked grave
The truth of the matter is nobody knows who's buried in that grave that has the chains around it and then the idea of
Any town official who says we have to prepare these chains or the witch will destroy us all should
Automatically lose their seat any town official who says we need to keep these these
Chains repaired otherwise will be destroyed is would not be a town official for long and again. Let's put logic to the story
Do you have chains wrapped around a grave that keep breaking right?
And really I mean I dispute the first off I dispute the fact that any part of the story is real except for the fire
I definitely dispute the fact that to these days these chains keep breaking if I'm wrong and these chains keep breaking
Buy chains from somebody else because if any other if you bought if you had a car that kept breaking down
You're not gonna be like well if I let it break down all the way witches are gonna destroy me
I gotta keep repairing this car. No, you would sell the car or return it
You wouldn't just keep repairing that car over and over again on the off chance that the one day you decide to take it
So the auto lot a bunch of witches come out of it that is probably one of the most stone
Here's the thing. There's two different audiences for urban legends twelve-year-old kids and idiots
I do enjoy reading urban legends because it speaks to me as a I have the thought process of a 12-year-old kid
When I initially am reading it, I'm thinking oh, that's you know, which which in the quicksand
Oh, it's kind of cool which quicksand which but then the second I finish it or actually this story while I was reading
I was like that doesn't make sense like why did they get her body out of their way to me and idiots people who go
Oh, no, that's totally true. I believe it my cousin saw the witches ghost
He was also trapped in quicksand. He turned to the side and there was a witch standing, you know
I mean like there's a certain point where the entertainment factor of a story just flat out becomes insulting some
urban legends are
Transformers 3 which means it's very well crafted and tells a good story. You know, it's not real, but it's entertaining
Some urban legends, however, are Transformers 5 which really insult your intelligence and you end the end you feel bad that you
Spent any amount of time listening to this one was a Transformers 5 that'll be our new ranking system for urban legends
Just I'm disappointed in you town of Yazoo. So yeah, that is the story to which he has who was that it was that
Appeal to you was it were you not entertained? I
Have to say I have to say at this point that that was pretty cathartic
To do to basically take some some towns urban legend a town that no one's ever heard of and
Just written some pieces that did make me feel a little bit better
But let's go ahead and move on to our next story now our next story
Hopefully will be less irritating to me
We're going to talk about the tried the true the you can't kill it with fire conspiracy keeps coming back to life
9/11 now 9/11 we I we've talked about on the show a hundred times
It's basically the granddaddy of conspiracy theories used to be JFK, but that's not that's not really relevant anymore
That's what your that's your grandpa's conspiracy theory, but 9/11 was 18 years ago
So people keep coming out with conspiracy theories about 9/11 and they get dumber
They get dumber and dumber and dumber and dumber as time goes on and you think Jason
I think you're just still a little wound up that which cast a spell on you. No, that's not the case. She might have but
There's a video out there right now called 9/11 planes traveled in time
No, oh by the way, no slash between the 9/11 so technically he's saying
9/11 planes traveled in time, but that's nitpicking and this video is so ridiculous
We don't even have to really nitpick it we can dive right into this video. This is the claim
This is the claim that's being made first off before I get into the claim
Let's talk about the evidence because that's really important, right?
You've got to find out the evidence the first piece of evidence this guy presents to us is a
commercial for a car and guess what the model of the cars
The Porsche 9/11 Porsche 9/11 car so and it travels in time in the commercial, right?
They see if the guy gets in an old version of a Porsche and drives and he goes through a time portal
Then it's the brand new Porsche and the commercial says time travel might always remain a dream, but we're working on it
Porsche 9/11
Time travel ergo
9/11 represented time travel forget the Porsche forget the Porsche part
I'm surprised it didn't try like adding up the each number of each letter and adds up and then you divide it by six and then
Add 16 and it would keep doing stuff until it reaches 9/11
But anyways forget the Porsche part you got to forget that part and just focus on the number 9/11
And then that tagline and here's this other piece of evidence when the plane hits the building it disappears
Right we all saw that the I mean obviously logically it did disappear it disappeared into the building
It's like when a plane hits a it's not a cartoon Bugs Bunny wasn't flying it
It didn't hit the building crumple up and then fall to the ground like yes
Yes, you're right in a sense the plane disappeared from view because it
smashed into a building going full speed
But to him it just simply ceased to exist ceased to exist right so do you have any proof of that?
Well before he gets into that before he gets into where the plane went or if it did really disappear
You start talking about back to the future so we did an episode
I don't know maybe a month or two back about did back to the future predict 9/11 and
It was a fun episode. I enjoyed it
But the answer is no
Did it but this guy starts citing that video and starts saying did you know did you know that?
Back to future predicted 9/11 and but see he goes in a different route with it luckily because I didn't want to just do a
Repeat of that he goes in different things
He says the car in back to the future has to go 88 miles an hour
so remember that number 88 miles an hour has to go 88 miles an hour and
Doc not Doc Martin talk brown at the end of the first one when everyone piles in the car
He goes where we're going we don't need any roads
Car takes off like an airplane and in the first movie when the car crashes into a barn when he first goes when Marnie McFly first
Goes back in time crashes into a barn farmer comes down goes it looks like some sort of airplane and
The YouTube dude the guy's making this video goes no it doesn't and
Then he moves on to the next point
But he's trying to say that the car is an airplane and people think it looks like an airplane
But it's not an airplane but in the end it actually flies like an airplane and the only vehicle that doesn't need roads is an airplane
I mean forget boats or hydrofoils or any other like blimps the only thing that needs doesn't need a road is an airplane and
88 88 miles an hour 88 is the key to his conspiracy theory
For some reason he gets stuck on the number 88 and the rest of his video is talking about the number 88 now
We get into the weird stuff because the idea of people of the planes disappearing have we've heard about before
We've heard it dude and trust me it's going to get really bizarre
We've heard we've heard about the planes disappearing before that was an early conspiracy theory that the planes are just holograms
Because they simply just smashed into the building and just seemed to disappear remember again disappeared from view is different than
Disappearing it's baby logic if one of your friends gets up and leaves the room you don't go oh no my friend disappeared
I can't see him anymore, and then they come back and you go
But some people don't understand that so when they see something smash into a wall and it disappears from view it's disappeared
It doesn't exist anymore. So anyways, that's not a new theory the planes just disappeared
9/11 being predicted by back to my head
I'm just leaning against my hand at this point 9/11 being predicted by back to the future is not a new theory either
But this is this is okay. Let's get into this now
I'm gonna have to shred it to pieces before we put it back together
He goes on to connect Donald Trump and this isn't gonna get political so don't reach for the off button now
Donald Trump was connected to the time travel experiment again. He never really says what happened
He just believes the planes went in time. He never even makes a statement if they went in the past or they went into the future
He just says time travel was involved. It's super super vague conspiracy theory. He says
Donald Trump we've covered this as well Donald Trump is all these connections to time travel his uncle
Took all of Tesla's designs and he gave Donald Trump time travel machine and the story of Baron Trump
We covered that on Donald Trump as a time traveler. That was our Thanksgiving episode
You can listen to that one if you'd like to as well
I think that's a good episode as well
But but he had ties Trump into 9/11 time travel in two other ways in this YouTube video
About 9/11 time travel the person who I didn't write down the dude's name
So his name is defeating the Sun
The YouTube video you actually be able to check out it's in the show notes and all that stuff
But defeating the Sun says
This okay says this
If so, I just took away two minutes to go look up his name and it was a breath of fresh air and have to concentrate on this nonsense
So Donald Trump's quote regarding 9/11 he plays this audio clip of Donald Trump and what happened was Donald Trump had called up a
local
New station on the morning 9/11 as the all of the chaos is going on and he's talking
He's doing an interview with these guys and this is what he says
If you know anything and he's there they asked him specifically about how the buildings were built and stuff like that because he's a
Real estate developer so he would know have a basic knowledge of
So this is what he said if you and I gotta read a verbatim here
If you know anything about structure
It was one of the first buildings that was built from the outside
The reason the World Trade Center had such narrow windows is that in between all the windows you have this steel on the outside
So you have this steel on the outside of the building
That's why when I first looked and you had big heavy I beams when I first looked at it
I couldn't believe it because there was a hole in the steel and this is steel
That was you remember the width of the windows of the World Trade Center folks
I think you know if you were ever up there they were quite narrow and in between was this heavy steel
I said how could a plane even a plane even a 767 or 747 or whatever it might have been how could it possibly go through this steel?
so
What defeating the Sun is saying and what Donald Trump is saying is that the reason why the windows were?
Narrow on the World Trade Center was because they're all of the steel of the building was on the outside normally
There's more steel columns in the middle and when they built this World Trade Center buildings
They wanted to be super sturdy
They are trying a new thing where they're putting it all on the outside basically creating an armor system
And he said the reason why the windows were so narrow up there as opposed to other
Complexes in New York or even around the world because they had all that steel
They didn't have a lot of room for the windows and basically what he's saying is that from what he understands
He doesn't understand how a plane could go through that heavy of steel
And that's the end of the quote on defeating the Sun's topic now
I did have to go and research that a little more just to make sure I understood the context
We'll get to that in a second because again
Yes, Donald Trump didn't talk about that on 9/11 and he said I don't understand how a plane could go through these steel reinforced building
But doesn't call him a 9/11 truth. He was not saying that Donald Trump says that 9/11 was an inside job
Doesn't say that Donald Trump says that it was control demolition nothing like that
He's based Donald Trump's basically making the statement. I don't understand how it could have happened and and somehow
That means Donald Trump has something to do with the time travel experiment
So remember that remember that Donald Trump says he doesn't think a plane can fly through a building and somehow that
Implicates him in 9/11 just like everyone who looked up and said oh my god. How how can this destruction be possible?
Are we all implicated in this but that's not where
I'm saving the death blow
Defeating the Sun has the best info for last he puts up this little picture of stuff, right?
He puts up this little infographic and it's all this list of information and he says I'm not gonna read it out to you
But you can pause the video and read it yourself
Which is hilarious to me because it makes me think that even he knows it's nonsense
It's definitely nonsense enough that he didn't want to waste his time reading it
Unfortunately, I had to and this ties it all together with a nice little bow remember 88
Remember you have to go 88 miles an hour to go in time in
Back to the future now the planes weren't going 88 miles an hour. They are going way over that
None of the planes were united 88 there weren't you know
If you added up the ages of everyone and divided by 12 it everyone didn't add up to 88 no he ties 88 into
Donald Trump and nothing to do with time travel
Nothing to do with time travel
So somehow back to the future the car goes 88 because they knew that 88 was Donald Trump's favorite number
So here we go. This is the list of proof that we have Donald Trump's favorite number is 88
Trump spent 88 million dollars on his election. It's not true. He spent 65 million dollars
I had a look all this nonsense up
Trump had 88 events or campaign stops during his campaign not true. He had 323 stops
Flat out lying to us at this point disinfographic
Trump's cousin Thomas P. Trump died one year before Trump's inauguration 88 days before he turned 88 flat out not true
Trump doesn't have a cousin named Thomas P. Trump
It was a meme that went around that somebody let wrote and thought it would be funny didn't exist the guy never existed
He said that 88
appears at every Trump rally on his podium and I
Couldn't verify that but I'll tell you right now. I know for a fact that's not true because 88 is gang code for a hail
Hitler and a lot of people know that and if Trump had 88 on his podium at every single rally he held
That would be huge news
That is not you this guy may think that 88 means back to the future time travel
But to anyone who's ever spent any amount of time on the street knows
88 if you see a guy wearing a jersey that says 88 on it do not assume he's a back to the future fan
So if Donald Trump is walking around with 88 on his podium
That would have been the the biggest controversy of the election
It's not a you can't be like I'm a big back to the future fan. My elections going 88 miles an hour
also
14 I mean like people there's no way he would be able to get away with putting coded messages like that that are even
vaguely close to game symbols at all
Anyways, where was it going? Oh, yes. Yes. Yes. So he wraps it up with this
Actually, no he wrapped it up then then the official video he goes. Oh, yeah, Donald Trump time traveler uncle Tesla all that stuff
Bear and Trump all those stuff. He wraps it up video ends and you're thinking that that's dumb like
It's funny because the conspiracy theory I think I almost feel like I want to give this guy helping hand
I'm not going to I almost feel like I could help him like partner with this dude to give him some tips on how to craft a
Good conspiracy theory and I've covered that multiple times
He's he has a good angle the coming up with the idea of the buildings
The plane's not crashing in the building, but the planes going back in time is an interesting sci-fi
Idea and you could from his video right now if it gets a little bit of traction
He'll probably get one two thousand people to actually believe in it and a lot of people will watch it just to laugh at him
But we can tweak it so we can say that yes the planes did go into the bit the planes did time travel and
The reason why we only have the one camera angle
I'm actually riffing I haven't thought of any of this through in my head yet
But the reason why we have the one camera angle of the first plane attacking is because those guys knew the attack was coming
Which which is actually a conspiracy theory already because those guys were Israeli and that that kind of connects it to the massage
But anyways in this new made-up conspiracy theory off the top of my head those guys were time travelers
Who were on the second plane that traveled into the past the second plane hits the building goes back into the past
They get off of it and they wanted footage of the first plane so they could create some sort of loop of footage because this is some sort of
Illuminati
Mine game they need to show both planes going in but what happened was the first plane goes into the building and
Travels back in time and the second plane goes into the building and goes forward in time
And we find out in the course of this conspiracy theory that everyone on the first plane was also
Everyone on the second plane except for the two people on the ground they decided not to continue their journey
So the first plane goes into the building and a time portal opens up and it goes back in time and
They go and they live their lives like normal
But now they know that they have to go forward in time for the circle to be complete for the Illuminati nonsense
No, let's forget the Illuminati nonsense first plane was a test all these people were basically
Had no future so they were paid like they're like here. We're gonna give a bunch of money to your families and stuff like that
Okay, now that's even getting a little more unwieldy. Let's go back to basics
the first plane actually was hijacked by Al-Qaeda and
Instead of crashing in the building went into the past and and oh dude
Here's and then what happened was in in their timeline
Everyone realized that the World Trade Center had a time portal in it and it became this huge dystopian future because
Countries were fighting over the portal so the plane that went back into the past had to plant bombs in the World Trade Centers
To bring them down and that way it would cover for the fact that there were time portals there
So it was a control demolition. It was totally controlled. I'm actually I don't believe in any of this
But you understand like that is how to create the theory and that was 100% off the top of my head
That's how you do it. You can have time travel airplanes and stuff like that the theory that I just came up with off the top of
Head and you there was those parts where I was kind of stopping and having to discard elements is
100% more cohesive than anything this dude put out like his video is absolute nonsense
It just jumped there's no theme going through it and he again never really states was it a time travel experiment
Was it on purpose? Was it an accident? Where are the planes now?
My made-up theory at least accounts for a lot of questions
Why the planes just there wasn't a lot of wreckage of the planes and the buildings coming down because they went back in time
And then have to hide the existence time portal time portals are still up there, but now they're in the middle of nowhere
So it's it's less likely that some guys are gonna be working in this office and go to the bathroom and then end up in
1884 a witch is chopping them up now just the the portals are there
Oh and those lights where they had that giant light shoot up in the air
That was basically trying to deactivate no no no that was trying to send a message to the time travelers that the mission was successful
Wait a second
This is a horrible theory because that means the people who went back in time
Planted those bombs and killed everyone in the world right I forgot about all the people who died in the World Trade Center
But but but all that being said
That is a more cohesive that conspiracy theory if someone put it out there
I predict if I was an unscrupulous person
I could just make a YouTube channel with nonsense like that and I'd get 10,000 subscribers
Overnight maybe not overnight
But if in a far shorter period than this channel does a lot of people don't like debunking stuff
And I'm glad you guys do stick around and listen to the show. I'm glad you guys enjoy the show
But I mean really like I'm competing with a lot of people who put this nonsense out much bigger channels than mine
And it's just I'm not I'm not bitter or anything. It's just a different lane
I've quoted this statement before some guy says you never get rich writing books saying UFOs don't exist
So I mean, you know, I'm not a skeptical
I'm more skeptical on conspiracy theories than I am on paranormal events like UFOs or aliens and ghosts and stuff like that
But conspiracy theories are just they're almost always built on quicksand. That's your second quicksand reference for the day
But I'm gonna read you to what rest of this Donald Trump quote
I was shocked when I heard this quote now again
I went to find out what the context was of this because I first heard this
Donald Trump quote on this weirdos YouTube video and I thought where's this coming from?
So I had to go find and I did I and it's in the link. It's in the show notes. I found I can't believe this isn't more popular
I found the
Interview he was doing with radio station the morning of
9/11 and he does say the whole quote and then folks
I think you know if you were ever up there, they were quite narrow and in between there was this heavy steel
I said how could a plane even a plane even a 767 or 747 or whatever it might have been how could it possibly go through this steel?
next sentence I
Happen to think that they had not only a plane, but they had bombs that exploded almost simultaneously
Because I just can't imagine anything being able to go through that wall
Was Donald Trump a 9/11 truth there and nobody knew about it
That was a weird quote to accidentally stumble across I
I
Was shocked that he didn't include this part on his YouTube video. I'm actually shocked that nobody as far as I know has ever
found this I
Think this might be a dead rabbit radio exclusive as far as like conspiracy stuff goes I
Don't know about today, but at some point it sounds like Donald Trump was a 9/11 truth or the world is so
weird and
It took an idiot's YouTube video to expose the truth
Hats off to you defeating the Sun
It wasn't the truth you wanted us to hear
But it might have been the one we needed to
Dead rabbit radio a gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/ dead rabbit radio Twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today
Have a great day guys
You
(upbeat music)