Straight from the conspiracy theory iceberg, we take a look at a man who would do anything
to protect his family.
That man's name?
O.J. Simpson.
And then we end the week with a personal theory of mine.
We talk a lot about where ghosts come from, why they haunt particular locations and not
others.
But there is one location that everyone uses that is most likely the most haunted place
on the planet.
And we'll take a look at those today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We're just going to go ahead and get started with this because we kind of got a lot of
stuff to cover.
Now a lot of listeners go, "Hey man, we want more conspiracy iceberg stuff."
And I'm totally down to do more conspiracy iceberg stuff.
It does tend to take more research.
And there's so much of it.
So if you guys have any particular recommendations of what you want to hear about on the conspiracy
iceberg, just shoot me an email, leave a comment in the videos, things like that.
There's just a lot of stuff.
And so I kind of have to pick and choose.
And there's a lot of stuff I come across on the conspiracy theory iceberg that just isn't
super intriguing once you really start looking at it.
And I'm like, I could, this would be like a five minute segment.
But this story is one that people kind of laugh about.
You see it on the conspiracy iceberg.
You think it's one of those made up things.
There's actually quite a lot of evidence.
Well, I don't know if I want to use the word evidence, but alleged evidence to back this
up.
So I'm going to briefly cover this because I think a lot of people are familiar with
it.
But back in, I don't remember the year, unfortunately, I think it was like 94.
I know his trial was a 95, but O.J. Simpson murdered, sorry, shouldn't have said that.
The police said that O.J. Simpson murdered Nicole Brown and Ron Goldman.
So Nicole Brown was his wife.
And they were kind of on the outs.
It might have been his ex-wife at the time.
I'm not too, I lived through that whole time period.
And I remember really not caring much about it back then.
But you watch this guy, you watch this world-famous athlete/star of the naked gun movies, which
the first two hold up really well.
He ends up getting charged with the murder of Nicole Brown and Ron Goldman.
A brutal, brutal slashing murder.
And I remember at the time, it's like he just chopped him both up with a knife.
Assuming, well, the reason why I have to keep backtracking on that was he was acquitted
of it.
He wasn't found not guilty.
He was just acquitted of the charges that he had killed those two people.
And he had a great legal team and a lot of people thought he had something to do with
it and he, as legally, they could never prove anything.
So he walked on those charges.
So everyone thought O.J. Simpson was going to be found guilty and he wasn't.
And he says, "Now I'm off to find the real killers."
And then he just played golf for pretty much the rest of his life until he ended up committing
like strong armed robbery a couple years ago and he's in a Nevada prison.
But so if he was guilty of the murder, he did eventually end up paying for it because
he ended up going to prison for trying to steal back memorabilia that someone had taken from
him.
All that being said, this next thing we're going to talk about on the conspiracy theory
iceberg actually may paint O.J. Simpson in a new light and may actually paint him as
world's best dad.
Maybe.
Let's take a look at this.
So there was a private investigator named Bill Deere.
Bill Deere.
If he said both names together, he sounds like a character from The Hobbit.
But Bill Deere was a private investigator and he started looking into the O.J. case and
he said, "O.J. is innocent and I can prove it."
So much so that he wrote a book called "O.J. is innocent and I can prove it."
And in this book he lays out the facts that O.J. Simpson did not murder Nicole Brown and
Ron Goldman.
His son did.
Now everything I'm about to talk about is completely alleged.
It's from Bill Deere's vault that he got underneath the minds of Moria.
He found this giant ancient text and he got all these details.
So I'm not saying that Jason Simpson did these things, but he does.
He's saying that.
So on the conspiracy theory iceberg it's listed as "O.J.
's son is the real killer."
So this is what Bill Deere just plotted out in his book.
Nonfiction book, by the way.
Well, nonfiction according to him, people have disputed it.
And he says he found evidence that Jason was diagnosed with IED, which if you're gonna
have a mental disease, have one named after a bomb.
That is at least that's pretty badass.
But anyways, he has I- could you imagine going to people and be like, "Yeah, I'm having a
terrible day.
My IED is really flaring up."
And people are like, "Uh."
He's not allowed into home depots anymore.
He's not allowed to buy nails.
His name, it's not his name.
His disease's name allegedly is IED and that's the last time I'm gonna say allegedly.
I think you guys will get it.
He's supposedly, I guess it's the same as allegedly.
Anyways, Bill Deere says that Jason Simpson has IED, which is known as Intermented Explosive
Disorder.
That's still pretty badass.
It sounds like a horrible thing to suffer through, but it still sounds pretty cool.
And it's something where you're, you have extreme outbursts of anger over little things.
So you just freak out all the time.
I'm sure you've known someone with IED.
I definitely have.
But around the time of the, this is all really bizarre.
Now again, we're going to assume for the sake of this that Bill Deere's done his research
and he's not just making stuff up.
But Bill Deere said, "Around the time of the murder," and this actually would be easy
to verify.
No one's really disputed a lot of the details.
They just dispute the motive.
Around the time of the murders, Jason Simpson was on probation.
"Probation for what?" you ask.
He was probation for attacking a former employer with a knife.
Now I guess I should have said this earlier, but Nicole Brown and Ron Goldman were stabbed
to death.
Actually that's kind of a misnomer.
They were cut to ribbons.
Cut to ribbons.
Don't want to go into a lot of the grizzly details.
Like, I mean, they weren't just poked a couple times with a knife and whoever did it ran
away.
They were, they were completely slashed up.
This guy was on probation for attacking a former employer with a knife.
Two months before the murders, he had violently assaulted his girlfriend.
Just beat the crap out of her.
And then on another occasion, he attacked a former girlfriend and cut her hair off using
a knife.
So Bill Deere is saying that Jason has this tendency to fly into a rage at a drop of a
hat.
That he has attacked people with knives in the very, very recent past around the time of
the murders.
I don't know about right now, but around the time of the murders he had attacked people
with knives.
He also found some of Jason, Jason Simpson's diaries.
Now this is where I'm kind of like, how did you get these?
But anyways, he found these diaries supposedly that belonged to Jason Simpson.
And I'm gonna read this excerpts or these excerpts to you.
They're pretty brief.
And I want you to ask yourself, are these the signs of somebody who is suffering from
IED?
They could just blow up at a moment's notice?
Or is this the lead singer of Papa Roach?
This was in his diary.
It's the year of the knife for me.
I cut away my problems with a knife.
That's one thing from it.
Anybody touches my friends, I will kill them.
It's kind of edgy, kind of edgy teenage.
Cut my life into pieces.
This is my last resort.
That was a trick question.
But then he also supposedly wrote, I'm also tired of being Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
I mean, I'm sure you can find a lot of edgy people's diaries or writings and they'll have
stuff in it like that.
Or song lyrics for new metal bands.
But we're seeing a pattern here.
The knife attacks, the mental instability, these very edgy writings in this, I'm assuming
spiral notebook with like the Stussy symbol drawn on the front eight times.
Now let's look at some other brief pieces of evidence.
One, they think if this is true, what set him off was that Nicole was supposed to come
visit Jason's restaurant and at the last minute canceled it, which made him fly into a rage.
People at work were like, oh my God, dude, settle down.
He's like, give me a knife, give me a knife.
They're like, dude, settle down.
He's like, give me my notebook and he starts scribbling out lyrics.
People said to the restaurant, it really upset him.
And apparently his alibi was, well, I couldn't murder them.
I was working at this restaurant.
So I wasn't anywhere near him.
People at the restaurant said we closed early that night and his time card was simply hand
written that night.
It wasn't punched like they normally are in the machine.
But the police never really formally questioned him.
But as Bill Deere keeps going through this evidence, he says, listen, this is what we,
these are the facts we know about the murder.
Ron Goldman had fought for his life.
The police said there was most likely like a 10 to 15 minute struggle between the killer
and Ron Goldman.
Ron Goldman had bruises on his body so deep, so big that they said it looks like someone
punched him to the bone.
When they checked OJ Simpson, he didn't have any like bad bruises.
He didn't look like he had been in a boxing match.
He had some cuts, some small like abrasions, but nothing would suggest that he went, he
fought a man to the death for 10 to 15 minutes.
Nothing would suggest that.
Jason Simpson was a black belt in karate, so he could fight so, okay, actually before
I go on to that, I've lost track of the amount of people who said that they are good at karate
and gotten their butts handed to him.
So I'm not saying just because you're good at karate means that you can definitely win
a fight.
However, for this instance, let's say that the karate black belt actually means that
he could stand up and fight a man for 10 minutes.
But he has a knife.
He's able to just kind of poke him, take blood out of him, weaken him, fight keeps going
on, gets more violent, things like that.
OJ Simpson did not look like he was in a fight for his life.
Nobody ever checked the sun to see how bruised up he was.
He's all busted up.
He looks like Rocky at the end of the movie.
He's like, "Ugh, I was just, uh, I stepped on a rake."
So, but nobody questioned it.
Nobody examined him to see if he had any of those things.
Now the question is, there, and then the other people are saying, "Listen, Jason wasn't
seeing anyone anywhere around the house that night.
People thought they saw OJ Simpson walking in the bushes, like Bigfoot, skulking about.
People said, "If this is, so this is what's interesting is all the pushback on this is,
well, what about all the evidence of OJ Simpson?
Why did he go running for his life?
Why did he ride a suicide note?
The bloody shoe prints match the type of shoes that OJ Simpson wears."
All of these other details that came out in the trial, they're going, no one's saying,
that's not true about, Jason didn't get arrested for attacking someone with a knife.
Jason wasn't having been diagnosed with IED.
They just say, "Well, no, no, look at all the evidence we have for OJ Simpson."
The problem is, is that that evidence failed in court.
So let me ask you this.
How good of a father do you have to be to know that your son killed your ex-girlfriend
and her new lover, and for you to say, "I'll cover it up for you?"
And if they point the finger at me, I'll go to court.
Not only will I do that, but I'll actually make sure they point the finger at me.
I'll go on the run.
I won't show up for questioning.
I'll write a suicide letter.
I'll give them all this stuff because I know 100% I did not kill them.
I know 100% I have no DNA left there after a 15 minute knife fight with two people.
I know I left none of my own blood there.
I will cover it up.
If you found out that your son had done something like that, or your kid or whatever, would you
help cover it up because you would go into court thinking, "I didn't do it.
I'm going to give the best lawyers I can, and at the end of the day, I didn't do it."
There's nothing physically tying me to that scene other than the bloody shoe print and
a glove, which they denied, which his team denied.
That's not even his glove.
If the glove won't fit, you must acquit, was Cochran's famous saying.
The bloody glove that was on the ground.
O.J. Simpson tried to put it on during trial.
Now he did make a weird hand.
It was going to be impossible for it to fit in trial.
He could also just drink a bunch of water or had a bunch of eat a bunch of salt, get
a bunch of sodium and just kind of swell up.
That also make it hard for it to fit.
Or the glove wasn't his.
Would you be able to take the blame for a crime that your son committed?
Would you be willing to risk it all to cover up for his crime?
It's an interesting question.
And I think all of us just being reasonable adults that we are, you know when you go into
trial even if you are 100% innocent, there is a chance you will be convicted.
Which, if this theory is true, makes O.J. Simpson's actions even more selfless.
He could have said, "I had nothing to do with this.
There's no physical evidence connecting me to this whatsoever.
But I've seen enough people throughout my life go to prison for crimes they did not
commit.
And I will take that chance for you, Jason.
I will take that chance."
Would you be willing to do the same thing for one of your kids?
Interesting question.
Interesting topic on the conspiracy theory iceberg.
It's one of the ones that didn't pop out to me at first.
And even when I was researching it and I was like, "Huh?"
The more I thought about it, I thought, "That's an interesting angle.
Not that the fact that someone came up with this theory, but would you be able to do the
same thing that this theoretical O.J. Simpson did?
And is it not just that he's back in prison?
He was actually a good man who America hated, but his son never stopped loving him."
Now let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
Now, our next story, we're taking a little road trip.
Everyone hop in.
Everyone hop into the Jason Jalopy.
Glad it's back in operation because we're going to be driving around.
We are going down America's highways.
In fact, we are going down one highway in particular, Highway 152 in California.
In Pacheco Pass in Central California, it runs Highway 152.
The road was initially set up during the Gold Rush, and now it's become one of the
many roads that gets Californians, California owns, gets people from California to drive
all around.
It's a beautiful state.
California has a lot of problems, but it is very visually stunning in a lot of places.
I used to move up and down the state.
First 35 years of my life was just moving from one end of the state to the other.
And it is quite beautiful there.
And Highway 152 is no exception.
But the road is known for two things.
It isn't a straight shot.
So you'll have straight shots of it, but then the road will get narrower, and then it will
expand back to where it should be.
You'll have this long, open stretch of just straight road, and then it will start curving.
So if you want to play Mario Kart, it's perfect.
But if you're just trying to get around, it's not the most comfortable drive.
So it's no one for that.
But secondly, it is recognized by the CHP, the California Highway Patrol, the CHIPS,
to be one of the most dangerous stretches of highway in the state.
They are constantly getting called out there for fist fights, for road rage incidents,
and for accidents.
And they've never really been able to figure out why.
The accidents they can go, people are just going super fast, super straight, and all
of a sudden the highway will start to turn, start to veer off.
Those throw internal shells at them.
The accidents they can kind of figure out.
But what is it about this road that seems to make people angrier?
Seems to make people have IED.
So they don't know.
The cops just patrol it like it's any other highway.
They just know they're going to spend more time on Highway 152 than any other stretch
of California's highways.
Some people say that it has an overflow of negative psychic energy, that psychics have
gone out there and they've been like, "Oh, I'm feeling extra angry.
There must be some sort of ethereal anger moving through the area."
They say that as they're punching the reporter, they're giving a quote to strangling them
out.
But there's never really been anything to key in on what could have caused this.
I mean, the road is quite old.
1849, 1850s, is when this road would have been established.
Maybe not right at 1849, but this path of roadway has been in operation for over 100
years at this point.
Now there is one expert source who thinks they haven't figured out.
Backpackerverse.
Backpackerverse, my favorite new website, thinks it has this figured out.
In 1800s, there is a local legend that's still told today, but probably only by backpackerverse.
So since the 1800s, there's been a story of a woman in a 16th century dress walking down
the highway covered in blood.
Now I know people don't listen to every episode, but we've talked about backpackerverse before.
They like to make stuff up.
And you're like, "Jason, why are you talking about a story you pretty sure is fiction?"
First off, the first thing I told you about the most dangerous stretch of highway, that
I've heard from multiple sources.
And those links are going to be in the show notes.
All that stuff is more likely to be true than the woman who was seen in the 1800s wearing
a dress from the 1600s covered in blood.
Backpackerverse always likes to exaggerate or just make stuff up out of whole cloth.
But the whole cloth that this...
Ah, cramp.
Ugh.
But anyways, there's this woman walking around since the 1800s.
It's so bizarre to me.
Was there anyone from the 1600s walking around in California?
That's what I don't understand why she's wearing this old dress.
Or was she a woman who died in the 1800s who was like total retro?
Like she was a hipster.
She's like, "I'm not wearing any of your 18th century clothes.
I'm only wearing this 16th century stuff."
Or she was going to a costume party.
But anyways, apparently there's a specter of a woman dressed like she's from the 1600s
who walks around this area, walks alone at night, covered in blood.
It has to be blood.
They always throw blood in all of their story.
So she's covered in blood, which technically I'm going to argue then that it's probably
not a white dress, which is a detail I didn't add earlier.
It's a 16th century white dress.
But if she's covered in blood, how can you tell?
She walks along this, she makes you get in car accidents, seeing her makes you angry,
she raises the psychic energy.
So they've created an origin story for why this road is so freaky.
I think the idea of the road being freaky itself and having some sort of malevolent
energy, and no one knows why, is actually creepier than making it a woman walking down
the street covered in blood.
Apparently, again, according to Backpackerverse, this story sounds great.
Don't think it's true.
There was a woman named Hattie.
Who would name their kid that?
There's a woman named Hattie who said she found her great grandfather's journal.
And it told the story that he lived off of Highway 152, way, way back in the olden days.
And he lived by himself, and he would go out among the trees.
He would be looking around for squirrels to shoot, or rabbits to pet, whatever.
And he would see a woman off in the distance, a woman in a white frilly 16th century dress,
which again, how do people from the 1800s go?
That's not a modern dress.
Like they didn't have photos.
They didn't know what they looked like, but anyways, he sees a woman in a retro dress,
and he would see her off in the distance in the forest.
And then right when he would kind of comprehend that that's out of place, she would disappear,
and then a heartbeat be standing behind him.
She would hiss in his ear, and then he would turn and she was gone.
Now the first time it happened, he thought, oh, that's nothing.
Like I must be hallucinating during a too much moonshine.
Whatever.
But he sees it again a couple days later.
He sees this figure standing off in the woods.
And the second he recognizes what it is, he hears that shhhhhhhh.
Turns around she's gone.
And what happened was first he saw her every few days, then he started seeing her every
day he left his cabin.
And then eventually he saw her multiple times a day, and then he was never seen again.
Creepy story.
Creepy creepy story.
Apparently it took place over the course of four months.
He's writing in his journal the whole time.
And in 1876 they just found his empty cabin and this journal detailing the story of this
woman in the white bloody dress.
Moving about the forest and appearing behind him.
I love that story.
It's a great creepy story, but it's not true.
I can almost guarantee it's not true.
One, for a couple reasons.
We have no proof that had it exist.
We have no proof that the diary exists.
It's definitely something you'd want to take photographs of or sell to the Warrens or sell
to any ghost hunter.
It doesn't exist.
Why is she hissing?
Kind of weird.
Well, over the course of four months if you keep going out in the woods and you see a white
woman covered in blood floating around, and then once you realize that's what she's doing
she appears behind you and hisses in your ear.
What's the best way to prevent that?
Don't go into the woods?
I mean even if I found a gold vein, even if I was like "Oh yeah, I got all this gold.
I'm gonna, I'm a pirate now.
It was first 49er but now I'm a pirate."
After I saw that, once I went, the first couple of times I'd think "Oh, it was just swamp
gas or venus or something like that."
But after I kept seeing it I would think "I better leave."
Because if I'm even a miner it doesn't say what this dude did, but let's say I was a
miner and I have a good gold vein that's keeping me there.
I just get enough gold to leave and then sell the land to somebody else and not tell them
about the crazy woman.
You wouldn't continue to go throughout stuff for four months of this happening.
That's like, imagine having the worst roommate in the world plus this roommate can teleport
and is covered in blood.
How long would you stay with that roommate?
So that's that story and I love it but I don't think it's real.
But you're like, "Jason, why are you spending Friday?
Why are you spending the last episode of the week to talk about backpackerverse?
Because we know how you feel about backpackerverse.
Here's why.
I said in my intro, the most haunted places that everyone uses.
So here's one of my theories.
I want to share one of my theories with you.
I believe, if we believe in the certain ideas of like ghosts are dead people or ghosts are
spirits, trapped spirits and things like that, people who have died violently.
There's other theories on ghosts and this one actually works for that too but if we
take that into account, where do most people die?
In their homes.
Most people tend to die in their homes.
But a good amount of people die on the road.
They die on highways and city streets.
When you have a house, so let's say that you die in your house and your ghost is there and
you're feeling comfortable.
When another family moves in, you can be like a specter and kind of messing about, mucking
about, knocking their candles over.
Don't do that, you'll burn the place down.
But you know like unscrewing light bulbs, turning the water faucet on, things like that.
But over time, you may say, you know, it's time for me to move on.
Like this isn't my home anymore.
They've changed everything.
They put up that Metallica poster.
I like Slayer.
This is too much and your spirit leaves.
And that may be why we don't have a ton of home hauntings.
That may be why we don't always have a ghost in a house where somebody died.
But nobody's home is the road, except for maybe like Johnny Cash.
Nobody's home is the road.
You are driving down the road to go home and you die.
You are by all respects really trapped in limbo.
You're not at your workplace, you're not at home.
You're not at your school, you're not at home.
You're not at your friend's house, you're not at home.
You're trapped in between these places.
And it's the one place your spirit couldn't find rest.
Your car crashes, you have a heart attack while you're driving, you choke on a chicken
bone because you're eating KFC, driving down the road to go 80 miles an hour.
You die.
Ambulance shows up, puts you in the back, drives you away.
But your spirit stays there.
It's trapped in a sense that it doesn't have another place to go.
It is, by all accounts, limbo on earth.
And it's the one place that can't be investigated.
Are you going to have a paranormal crew stop every mile down the road and spend a couple
hours out there or a couple days taking readings and then drive another mile down and do another
thing?
Every stretch of road and every stretch of highway has had numerous deaths.
A house that was built in the 50s may have only had one person dying it.
A house built in the 1800s may have had five people dying it.
But a stretch of road connecting the house from the 50s in the house in the 1800s could
have had 10,000 people die on it over the course of those 150 years.
That actually might be a bit high.
But you know what I'm getting at?
Hundreds if not thousands of people could die on the same stretch of road between those
two places where one person died or five people died.
Yet we always concentrate on haunted houses, haunted churches, haunted asylums.
And think about how many people die on the freeway versus how many people die in an asylum.
Some people say that ghosts are psychic energy.
It doesn't necessarily mean that you have to die there to leave some sort of psychic
residue.
You could have a horrible fight, you could have a horrible heartbreak and you're leaving
a piece of yourself there.
Where do you do most of your thinking?
Shower, yes, sure, but driving.
It's generally when you are alone or when you're with someone and they're nagging you
the whole way or your kids are screaming in the back seat and you're thinking, "I wish
I was 25, I wish I learned how to play the guitar, I wish I had done something."
You're leaving that little bit of psychic energy every time you drive to the job you
hate or driving from the job you love back to the home where you don't feel welcome.
You're leaving a bit of psychic energy on the side of the road.
We travel so fast down the road.
Unless it was a phantom hitchhiker or something, a woman in an old dress covered in blood
standing on the side of the road, you wouldn't notice the specter standing on the side of
the road.
You wouldn't notice the grieving spirit, you wouldn't notice the angry poltergeist, you
wouldn't pick up on any of these things.
You're driving from one location to another.
But that road you travel down may be littered with ghosts, spirits, poltergeists, and the
damned watching you underneath the darkened streetlight, behind the grass, just out of
sight.
And the next time you're driving down that road, take a look in the rearview mirror.
See if you see anything out of the ordinary.
Because if you do, if you see a trapped lonely spirit walking down the road, you may drive
a little safer so you don't share its fate.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.
[Music]