The ghost of a little girl haunts the creepiest location.
And then we take a look at a lake monster that destroyed the town built next to it and brutally
savage the farmlands around it until it finally met its match today on Dead Rava Radio.
Hey everyone and welcome back to another episode of Dead Rava Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We've got a lot to cover today so we're gonna go ahead and jump in here right now.
So I actually got an email recently from a listener named Austin and we talked about
a couple things via email but one of the things that he said was why aren't there any, he
actually had two points, why aren't there any ghost cavemen, why don't we see any ghost
cavemen and why aren't there a lot of haunted office buildings and department stores and
things like that.
Now I'll get into the caveman thing in another episode but there are, you know it's funny
because I said the Walmart and Hood River is haunted.
There's actually a ghost apparently in the hardware department which is funny because
it used to be the fabrics and crafts department and then they did a remodel of the store so
the fabrics and crafts department got shortened, got made smaller and the hardware department
is now where most of the fabrics and crafts were and since they did the remodel, employees
don't like being over there by themselves late at night.
Stuff will get knocked over, they say cans fall off the shelf.
I don't know if there's any video proof of any of this, I've just heard it from the
workers there.
Stuff gets knocked off the shelf, signs will get knocked over, you feel creeped out while
you're standing over there and my theory and I shared this with Austin, my theory is that
there may have been a ghost of an old lady who's favorite thing in the world was fabrics
and crafts.
It's not my thing, I don't like that type of stuff but you know a lot of people do and
so she was really into it and her ghost was like I want to spend eternity looking through
all the fabrics and kind of watching the young girls and their moms pick out scrapbooking
supplies and go man their lives boring but once they remodeled it to the hardware imagine
being the ghost of a little old lady stuck around carburetors and power tool sets and
since then stuff's getting knocked over, that's always been my theory.
Now again it could just be a bunch of workers are paranoid or they just don't want to work
over there and they go no no there's a ghost over there, I don't want to work over there
tonight.
Put me in the video game section but there is another, I found another Walmart ghost.
Now I've stumbled across this website, I've used them a couple times before but they've
really started to lose their credibility recently and we'll cover that in an upcoming
episode but there's a website called Backpackerverse and they do these stories about ghosts and
they're just so so poorly sourced they're hilarious but this one there might be something
to it I don't know.
This one is in Oxnard California.
Apparently there's a Walmart there in Oxnard California and you're walking through the
Walmart.
You're there to buy your video games and your laundry detergent and some new pants and a
picture frame that's the best thing about Walmart you can pretty much buy everything
there.
But for some reason you go to the toy aisle, maybe you're there to pick up the latest,
my little pony toys, is that still even a thing or are there still like bronies and
stuff like that?
It's been so long, it seems like such a f- I don't even know if the show's still on
but anyways, you know the show's still on and you're there to buy the latest Rainbow Dash
toy.
They got a new one, it talks.
So you're walking down the aisle and you see a little girl standing in the little girl
toy aisle and you're thinking that's typical, I don't even know why I registered that, there's
a bunch of little girls here and me buying my little pony toys.
But this little girl, she's just standing there and you're like, "Oh that's weird, girls
are normally seen in themselves or if they do it's like Taylor Swift or something."
And then she turns to you very slowly and dramatically.
Maybe she flickers a bit like the ring.
I don't know if she does that but anyways this little girl turns, they're just trying
to make a groove here.
This little girl turns to you, she looks at you and her eyes.
She stares at you with milky white eyeballs.
Looks right at you.
And that's when you notice she's covered in blood.
She smiles and right when she smiles, right when you register there's this bloody little
girl in front of you with milky white eyes, she vanishes.
Now if that happened to me, the first thing I would do was to make sure that I wasn't
on any sort of drugs.
I'd be like, "Did I take acid today?"
No, no, I didn't take shrooms.
I would run a mental check to see if I took any drugs.
But I would still have to wonder, like maybe someone slipped me something.
And then I would go to security and go, "Hey listen guys, I don't know you and you don't
know me but you can either make fun of me or we can make a million dollars.
Let's watch this video and see if there's a little girl in this aisle."
And if there's nothing, make fun of me but if there is something, we can sell it to whoever
buys this sort of nonsense.
We sell it to the Sci-Fi channel.
So apparently a lot of people have seen this little bloody girl in this toy aisle in Oxnard,
California.
There is a quote in an unsourced quote in this article about a woman who saw this thing.
This is the direct quote, "The first time I saw her, I just about died and went up to
Jesus."
Now, on the one hand, immediately when I read that quote, I go, "Black woman said that."
And you could go, "That's racist."
But I don't think it's racist because I don't think this quote's real.
So I think the person who made up this quote is racist.
Does that make sense?
They might as well just put, "Laudy, laudy, laudy.
When I first saw her, I thought I'd die and went up to Jesus."
That is, come on, if you're going to make up a quote, don't make up a stereotypical quote.
I don't think this person existed.
I don't see why they wouldn't put their name in this thing.
The whole article is poorly sourced.
But I want to believe, not that the writer can make up racist quotes.
I don't want to believe that.
But I want to believe in little ghost girls, or just ghosts in general.
I think it would be interesting if you actually had proof of this.
If you had a place that you could go to where you will see a ghost multiple times.
Now, again, supposedly this girl's always hanging out here, so I don't know why it's
not being swarmed by ghost hunters because it happens so regularly.
This quote here, the first time I saw her, I just about died and went up to heaven.
That means she saw her multiple times, but again, the person's not, there's no proof
or anything like that.
And to top it all off, because it's 2019, sometimes this little girl is spotted in the
boys' toy aisle.
So she's progressive.
You don't tell her where to go.
Sometimes she wants to play with Barbies.
Sometimes she wants to play with GI Joes.
If they still make those, I don't know.
Sometimes she wants to play with Barbies.
Sometimes she wants to play with the Avengers.
But then you see her just handling the Black Widow doll and you're like, "That's what I
figured."
She's not as progressive as you thought.
But that is the story of the bloody ghost girl from, the actual name of the article
was the bloody ghoul of Walmart.
I expected a little bit more than a girl covered in blood.
I don't know, that actually sounded quite grim.
I mean, oh, and the theory is, is that she was a Hispanic girl who was killed before
the Walmart was built.
But again, there's no proof of any of this at all.
Suckerverse comes out with these articles that basically are almost 100% fiction and
they get suckers like me to click on them and then read them and then go, "Well, I want
it to be true, but it probably isn't."
And you guys are racist for, if you're going to make up a quote, don't make up a quote
like that.
Just be like, "Hey, you know the first time I saw him, I was like, "Oh no, a bloody ghost."
Not, "I just about died and went off to Jesus."
Sorry.
Why would you quote?
Why would you make up that quote?
Although maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe the fact is, why would someone make up that quote proves that the quote is real.
I don't know.
If you live in Oxnard, California, go to that Walmart.
Check my, here, there's a history of backpackerverse websites where they'll have this article
and then the comments will be like, "That place isn't haunted."
I've been there 100 times, it's not haunted.
They get facts wrong all the time.
So again, I'm thinking they made up a racist black quote to add some color, no pun intended,
to this made up article about a bloody Hispanic girl who plays with girl and boy toys.
It's very, very diverse, very diverse hoax, backpacker universe.
But let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
We're going to modern day Palmdale, California.
It's near Arizona, but it's in California.
It's a little, it's a little region.
It's a little geographical spot on earth.
And specifically in Palmdale, there is a place known as Elizabeth Lake.
Not Lake Elizabeth, Elizabeth Lake.
And we'll get to that maybe, that's part of the story is dumb.
But anyways, it's called Elizabeth Lake.
But before it was known as Elizabeth Lake, it had a more evocative name.
In the year 1780, there was a Spanish explorer/priest named Junipero, Junipero, Sarah.
Now he's an explorer/priest.
Here's a little tip from a D&D player, old D&D player.
I haven't played in a while, but never split your class because then you can never specialize.
You never get the good stuff.
He should have just been an explorer or a priest.
But if he was a priest, he probably never would have found this place.
But he would be able to fight the undead much more effectively.
He comes across this beautiful, beautiful lake.
And the natives in the area tell him, yeah, it looks really sweet here.
And it would be a nice place to raise cattle.
And the priest is like, yeah, I was thinking that too.
I was thinking about splitting my class again and being a rancher.
And they're like, yeah, don't do that.
Don't do triple classes.
Come on, even we know that.
And we've never even seen a 20-sided die.
But it seems like a beautiful place to raise cows and stuff like that.
But there's a monster in the water.
Priest is like, what?
I don't know.
Okay, you know, back then there were monsters everywhere.
Actually, he probably would say, what?
He probably didn't even write down his notebook.
He's like, yeah, another monster.
There's monsters everywhere.
But it was then named Laguna del Diablo, which basically is the Devil's Lake.
Now you would say, and then he just scurried on and went on to his next adventure.
So he named it Laguna del Diablo.
Now, like most places called the Devil's Lake, people were still like, ah, yeah, it's
probably just a legend.
So they started finding this beautiful lake.
And they're like, this is a perfect place to raise cows, right?
Natives?
And the natives are all gone at this point.
They've all basically been run off the land.
So no one was there to tell them, hey, no, no, no, there's a monster here.
And so settlers, though, now there's just a bunch of settlers moving through the area.
Even though they had no natives there to warn them of the legends, they would start to see
stuff in the water.
Sometimes it was just a glimpse, a head poking out of the water, a noise at night, a spooky
noise at night, not just any noise.
And they would be like, that's kind of creepy.
Let's move on.
Let's leave this place.
That was kind of spooky.
And they're like, really?
So bobbing in the water, you're going to leave?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think it was more than just a log.
And over the years, the description of this creature kept getting added to.
Now, this is one of those things.
We've seen Loch Ness Monster type beasts.
We haven't seen them, but we've heard of Loch Ness Monster type beasts.
They're basically those swimming Brontosaurus creatures.
What are they?
Plastiosaurus or something like that with the paddles instead of the feet?
It seems sucky.
I'd rather have feet.
But anyways, it's always like this.
Not this one.
It's just your time with just a sea monster story.
This creature, check this out.
This is what I was like.
This thing is either the most badass thing that's ever walked the earth or 100% fake.
And we'll get into that in a bit.
A massive creature, 50 feet long.
So right there, you're like, boom, dinosaur sizes.
Massive creature 50 foot long.
Huge wings of a bat.
I bet you didn't expect a flying lake monster, dude.
The neck of a giraffe, that's pretty standard for these type of creatures.
That kind of puts it into that Brontosaurus character.
Head of a bulldog.
Just a flattened little mug head.
What is it?
Not a mug.
A little pug head attached to the neck of a giraffe all swinging around.
Six legs.
That's pretty dope.
Look at that Loch Ness monsters getting jealous right now.
Bat wings.
You got six legs.
And I don't know if this is a benefit or a con, a pro or a con.
Horrible horrible stench when it goes flying.
So you could say, Jason, that's obviously a con.
Who wants to be stinky?
But it's a perfect weapon.
Especially if you're living alone.
If you live by yourself, if you're a monster all by yourself, why not stink as bad as you
can?
Because then you don't ever have to worry about anyone.
I wonder how bad Shrek smelled.
It's always the funny thing when you watch movies.
They can really give us pretty much any sensation but smell.
And touch.
But touch you can kind of like look at something and go, oh that's quite spiky.
Or that looks soft.
That looks super cuddly.
But with just like, I wonder how Shrek had to smell like human waste that was sitting
in the sun.
Every character should have been like, oh god.
He bathed in dirt.
So you wonder, like yeah, in all of these movies, all these cuddly monsters, monster
squad, that must have been the smelliest weekend for those kids ever.
They're fighting decaying flesh and all sorts of horrible things.
Gross werewolves.
You can't really replicate smell.
Zombie movies would smell absolutely terrible.
Like you're like, Jason, that's a bit of an understatement.
But imagine like Dawn of the Dead when they're on the roof of that mall, the remake, which
was my favorite.
Just the smell of armies of the dead, all that rot.
Plus all the flies would be flies and maggots everywhere.
Movies can never really capture smell.
But anyway, so imagine this guy smelling like Dawn of the Dead meets Shrek when he's flying
around.
So people would show up, they would catch glimpses of the monster, they would leave.
And again, there was no one ever really there to tell them, hey, don't go here, there's
a big old monster.
In 1830, there was a guy named Don Pedro Carrillo.
And he goes, oh, this is a perfect place to raise cattle, because it really was a perfect
place to raise cattle.
So he puts up all of his cattle, and he's there for a bit of time.
But then one day, his ranch is completely burned down.
Every building's completely torched, and he leaves.
Now it doesn't really say how often he sighted the monster, but apparently he thought that's
what was going on.
In the 1850s, there was various American settlers coming to the area.
The American settlers eventually set up a town on the banks of the Devil's Lake.
They were probably hoping to call it something a little better, and again, we'll get to that
stupid story.
But anyways, it was called the Devil's Lake.
They set up this town, but what happened was at night they would hear screaming, they'd
hear a lot of screaming in the forest, not like sexy, sexy screaming coming from the
brothel.
That actually sounded really bad.
Screams of fascism is what I meant, not screams of human enslavement.
But like sexy, sexy screaming, they would hear unnatural voices.
So who knows what that could be?
That could be a guy who sounds like he's underwater or could just be some foreigner speaking in
another language, and they're like, "Oh, that guy's not from around here.
Let's move."
And they would also experience terrible visions, terrible psychic visions.
So I think at this point you're realizing this is something more than just a lake monster.
Now I have my theory, but before we get to my theory, the settlers moving away.
And at this point there was a guy who came into town called Don Chico Lopez.
And he's like, "I'm gonna set up a huge ranch.
I see that there's abandoned town here.
I see that there's a bunch of burnt out buildings over there.
I don't know what happened.
I don't care.
I'm gonna set up a big old ranch."
He sets up a big old ranch.
And for a couple months he had no problem at all.
Now one of the issues was is that whenever someone new would come to the area, the previous
occupants were already gone.
By the time the American settlers got there, the ranch that was set up, they got burned
down, that dude was gone.
By the time that guy got there, all the natives were gone.
So people just kind of kept stumbling across ruins of previous settlements and going, "This
is a perfect place to raise our cattle.
We're all alone."
And they weren't wondering why there were abandoned buildings on the edge of this lake.
But when Don Chico Lopez came in, he didn't really care.
He set up this massive ranch and for a couple months, absolutely no problems.
But what happened was he started having cattle disappear at night.
Like not like he comes out and there's like a dead cow.
The cow's gone.
And it's happening so commonly that he starts to put two and two together and thinks, "Something's
stealing my cattle."
So one night him and his ranch hands stay up and they see this creature come up out of
the lake and begin to descend on the cattle.
Basically like a raptor, a bird of prey would fly out of the river, grab cows and take them
back underwater.
They're shooting it.
All him and all of his ranch hands are opening fire with these old-timey rifles.
Bullets are straight bouncing off this dude.
He's like smog, but he has no weak point.
Bullets just...
He's flying down just eating cows.
And he did that all the time.
He just kept coming because he knew they couldn't stop him.
Eventually Don Chico Lopez has to leave.
He's just simply losing too much cattle.
But at this point, we got a new character show up into the story.
Now the people who have heard me in my Christmas episode, I talked about that I'm Bask.
My ethnicity is Bask.
There's only like two million of us left on the planet.
So whenever there is a Bask person shows up in a story, I'm like, "Oh yeah, here we
go baby.
Here we go."
Little bit of that ethnic pride my friends.
Bask farmer, there's this Bask farmer named Miguel Leonis.
Direct descendant of Leonidas and future ancestor of Optimus Prime.
Yes, we are born from heroes.
Anyways, Miguel Leonis comes to town.
Apparently historically he was a total jerk.
He was actually considered like a dictator.
He owned huge swaths of land in California.
And he didn't treat people that well.
And since he owned a bunch of land, squatters would come and live on his land.
And he would send armed guards to go and beat up these settlers.
They're like, "No, we're just sitting, we just sat down underneath the rock."
So not the nicest man in the world, but he was just getting his job done.
He was doing what he needed to do.
So he goes, he's like, "I'm building a ..." It's almost like he knew there was a monster
here because he came prepared.
So he's there, he sets up a huge cattle ranch pretty much the same size as Don Chico Lopez's.
Miguel sets up this massive cattle ranch.
And the same thing starts happening almost immediately.
The giant monster's coming out of the water, begins eating his cows.
And he's like, "I'm not leaving.
Not only am I not leaving, let's set up an ambush."
People are like, "What?
People are working on this farm?
What are you talking about?
It's a 50-foot-tall flying monster with six legs and bat wings.
You want to set up an ambush?"
And he's like, "Did I stutter?
Get your guns.
We're setting up an ambush."
Well, the other people don't want to do this, right?
And so, anyways, one night the creature comes out to just get a little snack.
Now the creature is the good guy basically in this story because of what's about to happen.
This creature is just doing what it does.
It eats cows.
That's what it does.
I don't know what it was eating before people showed up when there were no cows, but anyways,
it's eating these tasty, tasty cows, breaking them open, drinking their delicious milk,
eating some meat.
So one night the creature does come and it's the same effect.
The animals are loading their guns on this creature and the bullets are just bouncing
off of it.
Well, eventually the creature doesn't care.
It lands to go eat a cow.
Miguel, this badass rancher, runs up to the creature and takes his gun and smashes it in
the nose with the butt of his rifle.
"Oh, my nose!
I'm just trying to do what I do."
But Miguel didn't care.
Miguel beats up squatters.
Miguel beats up humans down on their luck.
He doesn't care that this creature is only following instinct.
As the creature is rubbing his nose, he climbs...
We'll get into whether or not this story is true in a second, but this is the legend.
And relatively recently, again, this was like in the 1860s this happened.
As the creature is rubbing its nose, Miguel runs up and punches it in the eyeball.
This bulletproof monster that's been plaguing people for over a hundred years, Miguel punches
it in the eyeball.
And then releases the worst stench possible, like worse than normal, as a defensive measure.
And they watch it fly into Arizona.
Now again, I know that Palmdale's close to Arizona, but I don't know if they could just
be like, "Yep, he's left the state."
Flew away.
Now, there's been a connection between that creature and a couple years later another
creature was killed in Arizona.
And they say that was the Thunderbird, the famed Thunderbird photo of the five guys standing
in front of the dead pterodactyl corpse, which is a fake photo.
A lot of people keep saying that it's real, but it's fake.
The first time it was ever really seen was on that show, "Irie Indiana."
It was like viral marketing for "Irie Indiana."
And it's fake.
But anyways, they're saying that that creature may have been the pterodactyl killed in that
photo, but it doesn't even match.
The pterodactyl is 50 feet long.
The pterodactyl photo didn't have the giant neck or the six legs or anything like that.
But that's the legend of Devil's Lake.
And at this point now it's called Elizabeth Lake.
The reason after that whole amazing backstory, the reason why they changed the name to Elizabeth
Lake?
Because like in the 1920s, some ditzy chick named Elizabeth was walking by the lake.
It was so funny when I was reading this, they were like, "Later on, decades later, there
was a young pioneer named Elizabeth who was walking by the lake with two pails of water."
And I was like, "Oh dude, is this like an epilogue where she mysteriously disappears
like the creature came back?"
And then it's like she was carrying these two pails of water.
And she slipped and fell in the lake in front of a bunch of tourists.
And begin teasing her and calling it Elizabeth's Lake because she slipped in it.
Everyone thought it was funny.
So the name is now, I'm like, "Are you kidding me?"
You go from Devil's Lake, you come from this amazing story with the sea monster, to some
girl slips in it and a bunch of tunies, a bunch of outsiders see it and they start calling
it, "Hey look it, that's Elizabeth's Lake."
That's lame.
Call it Laguna del Diablo, way better name.
But here's the thing.
Is the story true?
There's elements of it that are true.
There is a true part of the story where people would set up ranches there and their cattle
would be eaten.
You could not ra... even though it was perfect grazing land, great water supply, you couldn't
have a ranch there.
Now I found this out on the Wikipedia page and it was mentioned nowhere in any of the
articles about the sea monster.
This area, especially back around the time the 1850s, 1830s, had a massive bear population.
It was infested with grizzly bears.
So they think that... in the Wikipedia article they never mentioned the sea monster, they
just say there was a huge bear population which made ranching almost impossible in the
area in the early, in the mid 1800s.
That is most likely what happened.
That there was just a bunch of bears running around and no one could get anything done and
that's why people would stumble across settlements and be like, "That's weird, why is this town
here and there's nobody here and there's like bears in the poker parlor, there's bears
in the brothel like banging other sexy bears, bears that are all curvy, like ahhh."
That's where the shaman bear met his wife actually was in the brothel.
So that is the most likely scenario and you wonder, well then why were people making up
these stories about a giant sea monster?
There may have been something in the water but it having all of those like wings and
the six legs and stuff like that, that sounds super imaginative.
There may have been something in the water people can understand.
It could have just been a floating log people saw every once in a while.
That plus massive bears coming out of the woods every night and eating everything.
They could have had the legend mixed up plus also the unnatural voices could have been just
bears, the sounds of bears, the visions in your head could have been the vision of you
seeing bears climbing through your window.
A ton of bears, they were everywhere.
You go to the bathroom and bear would pop out of your toilet like the goolies.
So as much as I like to think that a bass guy beat up the Loch Ness monster, I mean maybe
he wrestled a couple bears, I'll give them that, but most likely there wasn't a sea monster.
But I always think it's interesting when we can look at these legends and watch how they
evolve and then find an actual real world component because really the mystery is what's
happening to all these cows?
The logical answer is well it's the bear that recently ran for mayor and won because all
the other bears in town voted for him and you're like oh yeah that makes more sense than the
giant monster.
But I think it's interesting because we get to see the real world, we see these real world
events and then the myths that are created to kind of hype everything up because at the
end of the day people just kept coming to an area and go what happened to this town?
I'm just going to build something here and see if something happens to me.
Makes you wonder about stuff with the Bermuda Triangle as well where there's natural events
but then people have made up this whole mystical thing to it.
Also I do believe this, I've been doing a little bit of research on this.
Bigfoot and I'm not the only one to do this, I'm not going to take sole credit for this,
I've read this in other places as well but Bigfoot's associated with the terribly strong
scent.
These creatures associate with the terrible strong scent.
Demons are associated with the smell of like sulfur, terribly strong scent.
There's a theory going on in kind of the scientific community that kind of borders on the paranormal
community that these visions are caused by natural gas releases and basically you're
smelling the smell of a gas, like a gaseous element, a chemical element and then you're
hallucinating these things.
So that could definitely be it too.
A lot of these creatures are always associated with bad smells.
Bigfoot in particular and the theory is that you're walking upon some sort of gas release,
some sort of natural gas release and you're getting so much into you, you're basically
hallucinating this and you go I smelled a horrible smell.
I turned around, Bigfoot was behind me, you're hallucinating and that would be the same thing
with demons, that would be the same thing with this creature.
There may have been some sort of chemical leak in the area, some sort of gaseous leak
in the area that was giving people visions, was making people associate the smell with
the monster and they weren't really paying attention to the bears that were actually
doing the property damage.
So kind of an interesting link to that too.
But maybe all the theories are wrong.
Maybe there really was this creature.
You know it's interesting because all of this stuff would have happened back when the frontier
was new.
All of these stories that we hear about these monsters come from a time when people from
the west were really first planning their flag in these areas.
The natives said, despite all of my stories about the scent or the bears, the natives
in the area had said yes there is a monster in there.
Besides the fact that it almost seems like a biological impossibility to have a creature
like this.
Could it have been something unexplained, something truly monstrous living in that lake?
Unlike the Loch Ness Monster which supposedly lived for hundreds of years and you could
still go over there and maybe catch a glimpse of it, a true monster would only exist in
one place at one time.
And that's what makes it a monster, that's what makes it so fierce and frightening.
I think this idea of Bigfoot having a tribe and having a family and stuff like that actually
just turns it into a monkey that lives in a place they normally don't live.
When you try to add some sort of biological necessity to it, that makes it biologically
or scientifically possible.
That doesn't make it a monster.
I'm not afraid of Bigfoot because again that's just a gorilla that may be a little bit smarter
and an area gorillas don't normally live.
The six-legged lake monster with bat wings is truly something out of the realm of nightmares.
To us in the modern world it may seem like a quaint story of settlers trying to figure
out why their cows are disappearing, but back then it would have been an insurmountable
obstacle.
We look at it through the lens of modern times and go just to fable, just the next explanation.
If this monster existed the question isn't where did it go?
The question really is where did it come from?
And could another one show up today?
A bulletproof flying creature appearing in modern times would be a marvel and a disaster
because it would prove to us that these things really do exist.
And if they exist, what can't exist?
If another creature like this showed up, even if it was dispatched very very quickly by
another strong Baskman/podcast host, never split your class, but punching it in the eye
during a live stream, it wouldn't matter.
Because once we know that the stuff of nightmares is real, all bets are off.
If the sea monster can exist, so can the monster under your bed.
Thank you guys.
(upbeat music)