We start off Monday with a story that will really kind of piss you off, it still gets under my skin and I've been reading it all week.
And then we take a look at the conspiracy theory that a popular reality show may have been warning us of the coming police state.
It's not cops, that's not the reality show I'm talking about.
Then we travel to China, specifically the Great Wall of China, to investigate a new rumor that is spreading around the internet.
Is it possible that there is an entire civilization living inside the Great Wall of China today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio, I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too, I hope you guys had an awesome weekend.
We have a ton of stuff to cover, so first off, let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, Alexander Helllander.
Alexander Helllander, he's walking into the building doing a little bow.
He should change his last name to Highlander, that would be dope.
Or you know, just have his family legacy, his name Helllander.
Alexander, you're going to be our captain, our pilot of this episode, and if you can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
Just help spread the word about the show, that also really, really helps out a lot.
So I'm going to toss Alexander the keys to the Jason Jalopy, he's kind of spinning them on his finger there for a second.
I wanted to give you guys a little news update.
Real quick news, we are doing a live episode on Thanksgiving Day.
That's at 12pm Pacific Standard Time, we're going to be doing a live episode.
And afterwards, and maybe a little bit before the episode, we'll be taking questions, having talking and stuff.
You know what humans do when they meet each other?
And I announced it during the live stream that I had on Saturday.
Next year, we're coming out with the Dead Rabbit Radio video game.
So I've been working on that, it's a lot of fun.
It's with RPG Maker, which I've used in the past.
I did create a game from start to finish.
It was a two hour campaign.
It was fun to do.
And it thought it was fun as well, so we're going to be doing that game.
It's going to be on itch.io, so it's free.
If you want to kick down a buck or two, you can, but it's going to be out there.
It's for you guys.
It gives me something to do too, so I'm not just playing Minecraft on my time off.
I'm building this game.
You are going to be able to play a Dead Rabbit Radio fan.
You get to play you, searching for me after I have been kidnapped by Mormon Bigfoot.
So it's going to be all of our favorites.
Hans is going to show up.
Hans, the little monkey army is going to show up and we're working on it,
but that's going to be coming out next year.
So Alexander, are you ready to take us to our first story?
He nods.
Do, do, do.
Alarm's going off.
Everyone's looking around.
They're like, what's that?
I go, you didn't know we all have a new job.
We are now officially baby savers.
And you're like, what in the world is a baby saver?
I'm like, what's up with that?
You're all filling out your W9.
I'm like pushing you aside.
We got this new job.
Baby savers.
Alexander's driving the Jason Jalopy has a little siren on it.
We're driving to save little baby person.
Could you get any more noble than that?
We're in Newton, Alabama.
[Makes a noise]
The car is racing through the streets in Newton, Alabama.
It's the year 2017 and we just got a call that a baby needs saving.
So we pull up to this department of human services building.
We're kicking down their door.
They're like, dude, we know you work here, baby savers.
You don't need to kick down our door all the time.
Get out of the way, person who's trying to help us.
Pushing our way into the back.
In the back office, there's a woman named Grace Locke.
And she's holding her little three month old baby.
Now Grace Locke has two kids already, got busted for some sort of drug crime.
We don't care.
We don't care about the specifics.
We're just baby savers, right?
She got busted for a drug crime.
Part of her parole, her probation, she had to do drug tests all the time.
And she'd been doing really good.
That's what she'd been telling people, right?
You can never trust these guys.
Oh, I'm not using the meth anymore.
I'm not doing that no more.
And she decides that she wants her other two kids back.
She wants to have her family because now she has this three month old child
and she wants her other two kids out of the foster system.
They can be a family again.
I'm not on drugs anymore.
She tells everybody.
But when she's at department of human services,
she's holding her three month old baby.
We're standing in the room.
We got our sunglasses on.
Me, Alexander's looking super tough.
He's all in his antelope.
Dude, dude, calm down a bit.
Calm down a bit.
No punching yet.
And it turns out that while she's sitting in the office,
someone comes in, she's like trying to make her case to get her other two kids back.
And they go, yeah, that's all well and good,
but we are getting the results of your most recent drug tests.
You tested positive for meth.
And not only that, so did your baby.
Your three month old baby tested positive for meth.
So her baby is taken from her arms at that meeting.
That's where we come in.
And then, I don't know, we just save them.
We put them in a corral in the middle of a park.
Someone else can handle that side.
We just literally take the babies.
So that unfortunately happens, right?
You have people trying to get their kids back.
You have people who are struggling with drug abuse.
And it's a struggle.
You're going to use, you're going to go a while without using,
you're going to use for a while.
It's this whole thing.
But Grace was sitting there and going, that's impossible.
It's impossible.
I have not used meth in a long time.
She's just sobbing.
Around the same time, there was this woman.
She had already had issues with the law.
She was getting drug tested, popped a drug test.
Her kids get taken away from her.
Because again, this happens.
This is pretty common.
But that girl's mom, the grandmother to the children,
is like, I know for a fact my daughter has not been using drugs.
I know for a fact she hasn't been using drugs.
She gets the lab paperwork and she sees the doctor who signed off on it,
saying that she tested positive for drugs.
She goes to the doctor's office and she says,
I want to talk to you about this.
Like, I'm sure you hear this all the time,
but I can guarantee you my daughter was not using drugs.
And the doctor, that's all he does is process drugs.
Even on his off time, he's like,
Oh, what a long day at work.
He brings home a bunch of urine and blood.
And he's like, I'm not going to do drugs.
And he's testing it.
He goes, I test it all the time.
Yeah, I do hear this all the time,
but let me take a look at that paperwork
and he looks at it and he's looking it over and he goes,
That's not my signature.
I never tested this person.
This story really pisses me off.
This story absolutely pisses me off.
Brandy Murrah,
she was the owner of A&J lab collections.
So what it is is people do the drug testing
and then they, the lab collection people collect them.
People collect it as per their name
and then they send it out to be tested by the doctors.
They're handling stuff for like employment.
They're handling stuff for probation.
They're handling stuff for foster system,
trying to get their kids back to department of health
and human services type of thing.
Brandy Murrah, the owner of A&J lab collections,
she owed money to these doctors.
So she would gather the samples
and then send the samples out to the doctors,
but she wasn't paying her bills.
She was collecting her samples until she caught up on her bills.
But she can't catch up on her bills
unless all these other places are paying her
to send the stuff off.
So what does she do?
She just takes these drug tests.
She takes these vial of blood, urine, a little bit of hair.
She's a foodie witch.
She's doing that on the site.
She's just saying positive for meth,
positive for heroin, positive for meth.
She just starts making up positive drug results
and then forging doctors' names.
People's kids were taken away because of her.
People who...
Listen, I make a lot of jokes
about people using meth and stuff like that.
We pretty much had meth Monday going on for a while.
But come on.
You gotta...
Someone who's a drug addict,
how many times were they lying to people,
saying, "No, no, no, mom, I'm clean.
I'm clean this time."
And then they OD or they...
"No, can I have $20?
I'm gonna go check your cheese.
I know I'm gonna beat the high score."
And then they go out and they cop again.
And that goes on and on and then eventually
you hit rock bottom and then you do try to recover
or you go to prison or something happens
with your kids or something like that.
There's always with drug abuse,
there's always a trust issue.
Now imagine that you are actually clean.
After years and years and years of lying
and stealing, lying to yourself as well,
you're clean.
And you fail a drug test
and somebody takes your three month old baby
out of your arms.
That's quite sinister too,
to make up a baby drug test.
My first drug test by Fisher Price.
Like that's pretty sinister.
She was making this stuff up,
ruining people's lives.
People who were really trying to make it work.
That, oh man, this story pissed me off
so much when I read it dude.
I was like, you're really picking on
people who are trying their hardest
to get their life back.
Together.
She's in prison for 15 years now.
For fraud.
15 years for however much money.
And the police say,
we don't know how many times she did this.
We estimate it's in the thousands.
Thousands of false drug tests.
And I'm wondering too how,
it's not so bad if you're applying for a job
and you have meth in your system
and she says tested negative, right?
You go to the job, you act all,
all, uh, totally freaking out all the time.
Your PBheromins personal assistant,
he's like, oh, I like your moves.
That's fine.
I mean, it could be troublesome if you're the boss
and you hired that guy.
But to struggle so long with addiction
and be clean and people still kind of like
not believing you because you lied so often
and then having science tell you,
oh, you're lying.
The story really made me mad.
Really, really made me mad.
So let's take Grace's baby out of the pin
that we have built in the park
and give Grace her baby.
Could you imagine that?
Listen to this quote that Grace had after it happened.
Quote, it was terrible.
I felt like my heart was being ripped out of my chest
because I knew I was doing right with this one.
I knew I was doing right.
(exhales)
Jacked up, dude.
The story really, really, really makes me mad.
Alexander, let's go ahead and leave behind Brandi Marash.
She has on a little jail suit.
She's looking out between bars.
I don't have to say allegedly
because she's already been sentenced.
Call in that.
Carbinder caboose.
We're hopping on the rails.
We're taking a train trip out to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
(imitates train train)
I know you wanted to pull the whistle.
Alexander, so go ahead.
Everyone wants to pull the whistle.
Everyone gets a chance.
The whole time we're going there, we're all deaf by the time we get there.
We are now in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
We are at Abby Lee Dance Company.
And so there's Abby Lee.
You're like, I still don't know where we're at.
Who's that?
The Dance Moms.
It's the show Dance Moms.
It's that reality show.
It's exactly what it sounds like.
It's a bunch of little girls trying to hone their craft.
And their moms who are, I have a weird attraction to the moms.
I should say right now, I've watched more than a few episodes of this show.
I have a weird attraction to the moms because I like people who are super driven.
And they're all wealthy, which is another thing I'm attracted to.
So you have them and they just sit there and they mock each other constantly.
And then they talk trash about other people's kids.
Not so much.
You're like, what's happening this afternoon with paranormal conspiracy and true crime?
I'll get to that.
You're like, this isn't Dead Ravre Recommendant.
And I was like, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't watch as much as I used to because I don't have a lot of time,
but I do enjoy reality television set.
I enjoy competitive reality television and I enjoy reality television.
It is a subculture that I'm not a part of.
Like I was watching that, my big fat gypsy wedding.
That's not even a show.
It was about a bunch of gypsies running around Britain, getting married.
They were like all living in a trailer park and you had to have subtitles on
because you couldn't understand what anyone was saying.
But anyway, so I watched non-sense like that.
I used to watch it all the time.
So I've seen more than a few episodes of Dance Moms.
Abby Lee is basically yelling at kids.
The whole show is yelling at kids.
It's actually quite terrible.
The kids are crying the whole time.
But again, this is not a Dead Ravre Recommendant.
You want to see kids crying?
Watch Dance Moms 8 p.m. on A&E or TLC or whatever.
The reason why we're talking about this,
I have a legitimate reason why we're talking about this.
We're sitting in Abby Lee's dance studio.
There's a bunch of hot moms sitting next to us.
And there's a bunch of like kids dancing and stuff like that.
And then so we're watching that, but seeing the corner,
we see like this guy, he's like this dude just standing there in the corner.
And he's like, he has a little earpiece in him.
And then he's like, they're doing the dance.
They're doing the dance you like, boss.
They're really cool.
And the technical one where they have to twirl around on their toes.
Yeah, they're doing it really good.
There's a guy with an earpiece and he goes, the dance has commenced.
Sir, we can start with plan one.
This is you.
I'm making it so convoluted.
Here it is.
Let me just tell you what the conspiracy there is.
I don't know why I built up this whole mythology.
This Dance Moms universe.
Here's the conspiracy theory.
There's this person on Reddit named Gator Quake,
who put together this timeline.
This is going to blow your mind, guys.
January 5th, 2016, season six, episode one.
I actually had to watch this because I had to verify she wasn't just making this stuff up.
But season six, episode one, the girls put on a performance.
It's all interpretive dance, which is my least favorite kind of dance.
There's a girl in a bubble and the other dancers are wearing face masks
and they're pushing the bubble around.
And she's like, "Ugh!"
And then the dance, I watched the whole routine because again, I was like,
"That's the least interesting part of the show, honestly."
We'd rather see the Dance Moms.
They're doing the dance and then she's like getting pushed around and stuff like that.
And then she dies in the bubble.
Not in real life.
It was part of the interpretive dance.
I got to watch that show.
No, that doesn't happen.
January 17th, 2017, season seven, episode eight.
One girl is not there.
She doesn't show up to practice and again, it's super competitive dancing.
She's at the ER with chest pains and the dance teacher goes, "Mmm-mm, that's not good.
I heard a virus is going around."
January 24th, 2017, season seven, episode nine.
I tried looking for this clip on YouTube because it sounds hilarious.
And I found it, but it wasn't as funny as I thought it was going to be.
A girl starts throwing up and she throws up into a garbage can.
So, you know, it's not super funny.
You don't actually see like chicken bones coming out of her mouth.
She's throwing up and the other moms are like, "Get her out of here, dude."
Like if she's throwing up, she's going to get all these other kids sick and the girls are like,
"Oh, the show, dude, maybe I should, did Rev recommend it."
Because the show is hilarious.
The kids are like between the ages of like nine and 16, 17.
There's this little 11, 10 year old girl.
She's like, "I don't feel so well, mom."
She's throwing up in this garbage can.
The other moms are like, "Get her out of here.
She's going to get all these other kids sick.
We're in this enclosed environment."
And the girl's mom is like, "Oh, no, no, no, she's okay.
She'll just practice over here."
And then she takes a giant garbage can, sits it down next to her daughter and goes keep dancing.
If you need to throw up, just throw up in the...
[laughs]
I can't imagine a parent being so callous.
Let her go home, dude.
She's vomiting.
Like if someone has a bad tummy ache, yeah, whatever, do a couple spin a right turn.
Don't do that.
But you don't mean like work it out.
They just put a garbage can next to her and go, "Okay, five, six, seven."
[laughs]
It's so awful, such an awful show.
But anyways, the point is, is that Gator Quake on Reddit posted this.
DanceMoms predictive programming.
The show DanceMoms was preparing the world for COVID.
With these three episodes, it was tuning into people's brains.
You see, the first one, her and the bubble and everyone with masks.
The show, the containment, the isolation that the world is coming to.
Second one, Abby Lee goes, "There's a virus going around because no one ever says that, ever."
Unless they're predictive programming for a pandemic.
No one's ever go, "Yeah, I heard the flu's going around."
If you said that, you're part of the problem.
And then Gator Quake goes on to say, "Oh, that scene where the girls are telling her to leave,
the last one with the girls throwing up, by the way, I'd be telling her to leave, too."
"Take your daughter home."
They're saying, "See, that showed the anger people are going to have at people who don't self-isolate."
This is my thing about predictive programming.
There are so many, thousands of hours of content cranked out a day that you are going to have matches.
That's always been one of my big arguments against predictive programming.
Think about all the movies that are churned out, all the television shows, all the songs that are churned out.
So when you have a rap song from two years ago and he's like, "Yo, coronavirus gonna get ya."
People go, "Oh, predictive programming. This underground rapper."
It's a pretty good song. I'll put it in the show notes.
He really did say that.
This underground rapper said this, predictive programming.
How many hundreds and thousands of hours, hundreds of thousands of hours of content come out in the past two years all over the world?
You're going to get some hits.
That's always been my thing about predictive programming.
So yeah, you're going to get some matches.
You pump out, what is that, seven seasons of dance moms.
And you pull out three episodes where people are sick.
Then yes, you're right.
People get sick sometimes on television.
And there's a pandemic going on. You're right.
But how many other hundreds of hours of television didn't have that stuff?
So that's always my thing with predictive programming.
I just found this one super interesting because it involved a bizarre show.
A lot of times they involve things that are more popular like the Simpsons.
I guess dance moms is pretty popular.
Her argument was that this show was specifically to get stay at home moms ready for COVID.
But if they're stay at home moms, they're already staying at home.
So they already stay at home and COVID is about getting people to stay at home.
So basically they'd be like, "Oh no. Normally I sit on the couch for 10 hours a day.
And now I got to sit on the couch for 12 hours a day.
Oh, whoa, it's me. Bring the wine."
So anyways, you can always find predictive programming and a bunch of stuff.
But Alexander, get ready to call in that carpenter copter.
We are leaving behind Abby Lee's dance studio and we are headed out to China.
We're flying out there, got a little tap shoes.
I'm doing a little tap dance the whole way.
You're like, "Oh my God, this is so awful.
I'm trying to impress those dance moms."
Ladies and gentlemen, as you guys take a quick vote whether or not to push me out of the carpenter copter,
luckily you guys vote not to.
We land at the Great Wall of China.
[Demonic Chatter]
This is actually a recommendation via Levi on Facebook.
So thank you, Levi. I really, really appreciate it.
I thought it was an interesting story.
It's a little baby conspiracy.
This one is just starting off.
I wanted to explore it very early with you and we can see where this goes.
Will it sprout like a mighty tree?
Or just not?
Just be a seed in the ground people forget about.
A long, long time ago, I didn't write it in my notes.
But a long time ago, it was old wind brushing over China, which I didn't put in my notes.
I didn't write in my notes where the wall was either.
You can tell this is a very well-prepared episode.
The dudes, the Mongols kept going into China and pushing over stuff.
They're like, "Ah, they run up to the emperor, they keep knocking him over and then leave."
He's like, "That's it, I'm tired of getting toppled over every time the Mongols show up.
Let's build a big old wall."
So they build this giant wall.
They call it the Great Wall of China.
I don't know, did they call it the Great Wall of China?
We don't call it the Statue of Liberty of the United States.
They just say the Great Wall, or do they have a cooler name like the Barrier from Beyond or something like that?
Who knows?
I'm sure I can look it up, but again, poorly said of episode.
There's a Great Wall all over this place in China.
It's like a supermarket and it goes everywhere.
And it kept out the Mongols, kept out a bunch of raiders.
It's actually the largest man-made structure on earth.
I'm actually surprised there's not more ancient alien stuff.
I have a theory of why.
Because China had good written records, so we know how it was built.
All that ancient alien stuff, they go, "Well, there's no written record, so we're just going to make stuff up pretty much."
But for this one, I've never heard that aliens built the Great Wall of China.
Even though it's the largest man-made structure in the world, I'm surprised there's no story.
There might be out there, I've just never really looked into it.
But anyways, so they have the Great Wall of China and it kept the Mongol hordes out.
No one's going to ride all the way around the wall.
You don't even know at what point you're going to like, the wall's going to end.
So you just give up.
You're like, "We'll go the other way. We'll raid the Middle East or something like that."
Because that's much easier than just climbing a wall.
On June 26, 2020, on the export, there is a post that talks about Klandia.
And what it is, is you had a Mongol horde show up to the wall and they're like, "Oh, great.
We heard people talk about this wall. We saw people coming back."
They're like, "Hey, how is it pushing over the Emperor of China?"
They're like, "Couldn't get there. There is a wall."
"What? There is that big of a wall?"
They're like, "Yeah, you don't waste your time. We're headed out to Turkey."
They get there, they get to the wall and they're like, "Oh, this sucks.
I probably should have listened to my fellow countrymen."
But instead of leaving, they say, "You know, the old Mongol saying, 'Home is where the heart is,'
what if we live in the wall?"
[laughs]
What are you talking about?
He goes, "No, no, no. Hear me out. Hear me out."
We can still do raiding parties.
They're still like people we can attack on this side of the wall.
And maybe if, you know, since we're already digging into the wall anyways,
maybe we could just pop out the other side.
But my point is that why would we scale the wall or dig through the wall,
attack a bunch of people and then have to go back through the wall to get home?
And then make our home inside the wall itself.
And everyone's kind of thinking about it and they go, "Let's give it a shot."
So they begin moving bricks around.
Did they have guards on the wall?
Like, what's the point of having a giant wall because other people like could climb up it and stuff like that
or just bring a giant ladder next time?
Like, what's the point of having a wall unless you have guards on it,
but the wall's so big you would need a ton of guards or guys with really good eyesight?
You know, one of the two, either a thousand people or just a hundred who can see well.
I'm sure they had a guard, right?
Maybe.
Probably should have researched that.
Anyways, the point is that apparently a group of Mongols built a hole in the wall
and then created a series of tunnels underneath and inside the Great Wall of China itself.
And at first it was just like they'd pop out every so often with their horses.
They were like, "What are you doing?"
They were like, "I'm just going to get out of here."
And then they were like, "I'm just going to get out of here."
Because you don't know you're supposed to be afraid of them because you don't even know they exist.
It's possible that this person is onto something, that there is a hidden society inside China.
It's a funny visual, but that there's a hidden civilization inside the Great Wall of China.
So it's possible that this poster, whoever he is, is actually onto something.
He's actually trying to let people know about Calandia.
And they may not even know how dire the circumstances actually are.
This may be a local legend they heard while they were teaching over in China.
But it actually may be a clue to who is pulling the strings around the world.
Now I've always said, I don't think there's one monolithic group that is controlling the world.
I think there are hundreds of separate groups trying to control the world.
I think there are hundreds of separate groups that are fighting amongst each other.
Sometimes they make alliances for short-term gain.
But they're constantly pushing and pulling at world politics, at society, at culture, entertainment.
This is constantly going on.
But it's these groups that you don't even know exist that are the most dangerous.
Because if you don't know they exist, you can't prepare to fight them.
And a group that started off as savage raiders, raping and pillaging their way across China.
If they're now in the boardrooms, if they're now in the halls of power, that savagery is still there.
That take-all energy is still there.
You may not be able to find their nation on a map.
You might not ever know how to speak their language.
You may never even know they exist.
But they know you exist.
They can't wait until they take over the world.
The silent masters vying to conquer everything and rule the planet from within side the Great Wall of China.
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
And I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[Music]