The movie Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind features a man who tries to have his memory erased via sci-fi contraption,
but you can actually do it at home, and then we take a look at an urban legend that is spread around all over the world.
But the origins of it are frighteningly real, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too.
Don't have a lot of time to record this episode. I actually have to go do some grocery shopping for one of my jobs.
Have to run out, go do grocery shopping, then run off to another job and then come back to this other job.
It is the plight of someone who works three part-time jobs, but what are you going to do?
And I got to put out a daily podcast, so you just kind of got to bite down.
It didn't help that I spent the last half hour listening to Kimbra songs. I've never really listened to her before.
I've always thought she was pretty cute. She was in that Goatier song, and I was like, "Oh, she actually has some pretty good music."
So I've been getting all that. I walk a lot, so I need as much music as I can.
So I was listening to a bunch of her songs and downloading them and all that.
But anyways, so for the rest of the day, I'll be listening to Kimbra and walking around doing grocery shopping, running errands, and so on and so forth.
But before I do all that, I've got to cover two stories for you guys.
So the first story we're going to look at, I said in the intro,
so there is that movie called Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind starring Jim Carrey and Kate Winslet, and I think Frodo was in it too.
But I didn't like that movie. I wasn't a huge fan of it. I heard a lot of hype about it.
But it was really, I think you can almost like that movie was Frodo hipster movie.
I think it kind of preceded the hipster movement.
But I ended up watching it and I shut it off halfway through. I just wasn't that entertained by it.
And I appreciate Jim Carrey's early stuff.
And he has he done anything? I'll see him in the Sonic movie. I'll watch that.
I mean, he he's a little weird in real life, but his movies are decent, good to decent movies.
He hasn't made anything really terrible. I never saw him number 23.
I actually should watch that because that really is kind of the conspiracy type movie.
And it's kind of what the show is about. But maybe I'll give it a shot.
Anyways, so it had Jim Carrey and Kate Winslet who's super hot and then Frodo Backends was in it.
He was looking for the ring and he didn't find it in that movie, but he found it in another movie.
So the the concept is this, this guy is a horrible breakup of the girl and there's this device that allows your memory.
I think there's a musical number in it. Maybe I maybe I'm getting a confused.
There were some other hot chicken and who's Mary Jane from Spiderman?
She was also a cheerleader and bring it on. My depth of movie knowledge is what the actors have been in before.
So I'm like, oh, it's the movie starring the mask and Rose from Titanic.
They meet Frodo and Mary Jane Watson and they go on this crazy adventure and if your mind's erased,
this machine allows you to erase your mind.
One of the interesting things, the only interesting thing about the movie is that
would you want to have memories erased? Would you want bad memories to be erased?
You know, one of the weird things, I know I'm digressing here, but one of the weird things about like dying and going to heaven,
I've always felt is that you're supposed to go to heaven and you're a total peace and joy,
but part of what's informed me, part of what's created me as a human is my bad memories,
is the sorrow I've gone through and I feel like that is baked into the cake that is Jason Carpenter.
So can you take out the bad memories and still be the same person?
Or would you want to take out the bad memories knowing that you wouldn't even remember the good stuff?
But as much as that is a sci-fi/philosophical argument, you can actually do it at home.
Here's a disclaimer, don't do this, don't do this, but it's possible, but don't do it,
because it's actually quite dangerous.
I came across this article recently and what it is, is this man in China posted on the net.
So right there, it's super vague. We don't have a lot of resources, but other scientists,
other doctors have chimed in on this. A man on the internet in China said his mom was really
constipated for like two weeks, going to go to the bathroom at all. And then one time she went
into the bathroom and she was in there for a long time and she finally had a bowel movement,
and when she came out of the bathroom, she didn't remember the past 10 years of her life.
They couldn't figure out what was going on. She had no idea what happened the past 10 years of
her life. She's like, "Hey, you want to go to the World Trade Center?" They're like, "Mom,
mom, sit down. We have something to tell you." Actually, that would have been farther back
than 10 years, but anyways, the family had to sit her down and tell her like, "What's going on?"
And she's like, "No, no, I got all this money invested in Enron. We're rich. We're millionaires."
And they're like, "Mom, mom, we think we need to go to the doctor." So they took her to the doctor,
and what happened was the doctor diagnosed her with amnesia, but it only lasted for eight hours.
So for eight hours, she couldn't remember the past 10 years of her life.
Now, this was reported in the media and the news article in China, there's two versions of this
article. One is from the China Times, and we'll get to that in a second. And then one is in this
website called The Week of Buzz, which seemed to really click baity. So I had to go to the
China Times to find out if it was actually published or true or anything like that.
And in the China Times, they quoted this neurosurgeon who says, "Yes, it is possible,
because when you're having a big bowel movement, you can actually start to cut off blood flow to
your jugular vein, which will interfere with your brain, which you're not getting enough blood flow
to your brain, so it will begin to wipe out memories if the bowel movement is big enough."
So yes, it is possible, and it does happen. It's not incredibly common, but it does happen. I had
a cousin one day who, one day her husband came home and she was laying on the floor and she thought
she was still in high school. She didn't remember anything. And they never could, and after about
a year or two, she regained her memories, but she ended up going to the doctor. The doctor was
like, "We don't know what it is," but she appears to have lost her memory. Now, there were people in
the family who thought she was faking it. I actually ran into her shortly after this happened,
and I remember looking at her, and she looked different. There was something about her eyes.
I go, "I don't think she's faking it, because just by looking at her eyes, you could tell there
was something different about her." And she might have just suffered mild brain damage. She may have
made the whole thing up, but I think she probably did suffer some mild brain damage, and she actually
did lose her memory. But I don't know if she was super constipated before that. They just found
her on the floor. So let's go to the ch-- So it is a legit thing. It actually can happen to people,
but now this next segment you might think is a little culturally insensitive, but the next story
we're going to cover is quite grim, so I figured let's pack as many as funny moments into this
next couple minutes, because what we're going to get into is pretty dark. So I go to the China Times.
Now I have to run the translate option, obviously, because I don't speak Chinese. Now I actually do
have a lot of Chinese members of my family. A lot of members of my family, my stepmom, and my stepbrother,
and sisters, and stuff like that, are Chinese. Step-grandpa, all that stuff. Are there such a
thing as a step-grandpa, or at a certain point you just go, "Ah, that's my grandpa." But anyways,
I have a lot of family members who are from China, so I don't speak Chinese myself, they probably
could, but the translation errors when I'm running this translate-- and I don't get these a lot when
I'm running translation from English to, like, on Spanish websites, which I have to go to a lot.
There's some great gems here. Again, you might go, "Jason, that's kind of rude, but
we're going to get into some dark stuff." The headline of the China Times article-- so for
comparison, this is the headline of the World Buzz article. "Women loses 10 years of memories
after she pooped with excessive force." I'm like, "Oh, it's very clicky, very clickbaity," and I was
like, "Oh, it's an interesting story for the podcast." Go to China Times, here's the headline.
"Constipation. The toilet came out and lost 10 years of memory."
Now, other than it grammatically being incorrect, the toilet didn't lose memory, and the toilet
didn't come out. Quite an odd phrasing for it. You poop and another toilet comes out, and then you
poop into that toilet, and another smaller toilet comes out. It's a-- I forgot what that name was.
We covered our past episode, but when people keep looking into mirrors, they see multiple versions
of themselves, it's that, but just toilets coming out of your butthole. And then they had these other
great headlines, here. "Paper folding 103 times as big as the universe."
What? What does that even mean? "He hasn't cut his hair for 50 years. He took his head gear like a
giant clam." Oh, man, that guy's such a good dude. He took it like a giant clam. I'm assuming--
now, I clicked on that one, because I was like, "What does that even mean?" And apparently,
he hadn't cut his hair in 50 years, and they just cut it, and apparently looked like a giant clam.
It didn't. It just looked like a giant pile of hair on the ground. But this headline actually had
to click on, because I was like, "What in the world?" I understand the paper folding thing. It's
probably saying you can't fold a piece of paper 103 times. I've heard that before, but you can't
fold a piece of paper in half so many times, sort of. But this next headline I had to click on,
do some research on, "Under the flashlight, the white light is actually suffering from this disease."
Like, what could that even possibly mean? So I guess this article is a girl, a mother,
took a photo of her son, and when the white light flashed, his eyes looked really weird
under the flash. And he actually suffered from some sort of eye cancer, and they caught it very
early and were able to treat it. But, yeah. So that's what that headline means. "Under the flashlight,
the white light is actually suffering from this disease." Again, the white light's not suffering
from anything. The toilet is not losing 10 years of memory, and you're not the toilet come- the
toilet doesn't come out of anything. It's there. It's in place. So thank you, China Times, and thank
you, Google Translate for these great headlines. And again, I don't recommend giving yourself
constipation so you interfere with the blood flow to your brain. I highly don't recommend that,
because you could probably just give yourself a stroke. But it's still just an odd thing how
balanced our bodies are and how easily it is to interfere with them. This is obviously a
temporary thing, even if you did have a bad breakup within the past 10 years. You'll only buy
yourself about eight hours of solace, but then you're like, "Now I just have to make myself
constipated all the time. Yeah, don't do that. Don't do that at all." I actually don't even know how
an eternal sunshine ended. I don't know if he decided to remember her or not. I just gave up
halfway through the movie. I'm pretty sure there's a musical number, though. I'm almost pretty sure
there's a musical number with Kirsten Dunst. That was it. Dude, if you want to watch a great movie,
Melancholy. I know there's a lot of people who aren't big fans of Lars von Trier,
but that movie's great. And I know why people aren't good fans of his, because he made all those
Nazi jokes during a press conference, and he's just cracking these jokes about Hitler. And Kirsten
Dunst, star of Bring It On and the Spider-Man franchise, is sitting next to him and she's like,
"Oh my god." And he's cracking jokes about Hitler and Nazis in front of a bunch of posh
film critics. But Lars von Trier, Melancholia. Melancholia, that was the name of the movie.
The first half of the movie is an examination of a young woman's descent into depression.
Kirsten Dunst has a nude scene in it as well, if you're not into the depression angle.
The second half of the movie is one of the best end-of-the-world sci-fi films ever.
Top 5. I would honestly say ever, because it just shows the futility of mankind in the face of the
entire universe. And I remember reading an article about Melancholia and Lars von Trier, goes,
"That's one of my least favorite movies. It's one of my least favorite movies." One,
because I was going through terrible depression while I was watching it, hence the point of the
movie. And he goes, "2, it's too good." He goes, "I like my movies to have lots of flaws in them. I like
to have, like my movies to have mistakes in them." He goes, "And I used a lot of tripods in this film,
and I just don't like the way it came out." Beautiful movie. Very, very tragic film. And I
would tell, I've told people too, just skip, just skip the first hour. If you're not into the examination
of depression and loss, and I don't even think she loses anything. I think she's just going through
a chemical depression. Yeah, I go, "If you're not into that, the first hour is pretty slow." I would,
I loved it, but I love all of his stuff. Lars, and this is my last thing I'm going to talk about
is, Lars Von Trier is great because he is a very, he's like an art house movie maker who makes,
takes schlocky genres. And he's done that, he's done that with his past, I wouldn't say past
two movies, but Melancholia and Antichrist are both, Antichrist is a Cabin in the Woods Horror
movie made by an artistic genius. A lot of people don't like the way he portrays women either,
and I totally get that. But it is a art house take on a straight to DVD horror movie. It's,
it's brilliant. It's a man and a woman in a cabin in the woods. Absolutely terrifying film,
very, very grotesque. William Defoe was in that one, love that movie. And then Melancholia is
basically Armageddon made by an amazing filmmaker, not whoever made Armageddon. I think it might have
been Michael Bayer, Jerry Bruckheimer, but it was, he does these, he picks these genres
that normally aren't touched by the arty artsy community and makes it makes these crazy films.
I would love to see him do an action film. I would love to see him get Scott Atkins and Jean-Claude
Van Damme and do an artistic take on a action film. Actually, his last movie was the house that Jack
built, which I haven't seen yet, but it is a serial killer film done in an art house. I've
seen clips from it and it's quite ridiculous, but it's that same type of thing. So hats off to
you Lars von Trier and hats off to the my audience, half of my audience that left because they absolutely
hate that person, but I like them. Dogville, great movie. So anyways, let's go ahead and move on.
Dogville is amazing actually, but let's go ahead and move on. I never saw the sequel. Let's go
ahead and move on to our next story. So there is this old urban legend. It's probably one of the
biggest urban legends really. You have Bloody Mary, which is probably the top one, but the second
urban legend is the babysitter in the house. And the story is this, she's at home babysitting the
kid. There's a lot of versions of this, but really the main one that I always heard was there's a
babysitter at home babysitting two kids, a kid, whatever. It doesn't matter how many kids there
are. They're basically cannon fodder for this story. This babysitter is in this house and
she's getting crank calls to her phone and then she calls up the police and she says,
can you track the phone call? And then the cops call her back and say, we tracked the phone call,
the phone calls coming from within the house. And then the version I heard was then she went,
this totally disturbed me as a kid. I think I first heard this one. I was like eight or nine.
The babysitter then goes upstairs and the kids are all chopped up and I remember being specifically
told their faces looked like spaghettios and that really disturbed me because I loved spaghettios
and it really creeped me out because it took something that I enjoyed eating. And for the
longest time when I looked at bowl of spaghettios, I just would see like chopped up people because
spaghettios, not just spaghettios, spaghettios with hot dogs in them is very specific. Now,
of course, you could not ever chop up a human body and make it look like spaghettios with hot dogs
in them, but totally creeped me out. Now, that version of the story where the cops are tracing
the phone call back and it's inside the house, that we've heard all sorts of versions of that,
but basically the idea is the killer is in the house with the babysitter. We don't always get
the traced phone call, but that's a common thing. Now, the story we're going to cover is actually
something I had never heard of until about two or three weeks ago and it's very, very chilling,
very chilling story. So we're going back in time. We're going back to the year 1950. We're in the
city of Columbia, Missouri and it's March 18th. There is a young babysitter. This is a 100%
true story. There's a young babysitter named Janet Christman and she's 13 years old. She turns 14
in three days. So you guys can already kind of know where this is going. You guys want to tune
in tomorrow? It's totally fine. Janet is 13. She turns 14 in three days. She's trying to save up
money to get a new dress for Easter and she generally babysits for two different families.
She babysits for the Romax and she babysits for the Mollars. So this particular night,
the Mollars and the Romax and a couple other families are going to go hang out and play cards
and Janet picks the job to go to the Romax house and the Mollars have to find another babysitter
and she's at the Romax house and they said, "Okay, listen, here's the thing. We have this little
three-year-old boy named Gregory. I want you to take care of him." And she's like, "I know how to do
my job, guys. They're like, "No, we're just adding details. We're adding details for the story." And
she's like, "That's weird. Details for who?" So they say, "Our little son Gregory is three years old.
The house is kind of in the middle of nowhere, but let me show you some stuff." So Ed Romax,
the dad of the Romax, says, "Here's my shotgun. Again, this is 1950s, so you would have no problem
handling a shotgun to a 13-year-old girl. He showed her how to load it, unload it, and said,
'Keep it by the door.' If anyone knocks on the door, anyone at all, you lock the door,
you turn on the porch light. Do not open the door for anybody." Puts the shotgun by the door,
pats her on the head, says goodbye to his son. The Romax leaves. That night, a massive rainstorm
hits the area. Mid-20 degrees. So it's just ice and sleet everywhere. And Janet is just sitting at
home doing her babysitting thing. Now, at 1035, the police station in Columbia gets a phone call.
Phone rings. Columbia Police. This is, and they just hear a young girl go, "Come quick!"
And the phone line goes dead. Cop's sitting there, looking out the window.
Seeing the rain and the ice, the wind whip across the street outside the police station.
And the officer just sits there waiting for another phone call. They can't trace the phone call.
I don't even know if they had the ability to trace phone calls back then, but the phone call was so
short with no information they just had to hope they get another phone call. Now, while the Romax
and the Mollers are out having this big party, Ann Romac, the wife, calls home to see how everything
is going. But it's really early in the morning. It's like around midnight. She calls home, no
answer. So she goes, "Baby sitter must be asleep. Gregory's probably asleep. Probably no big deal."
At 1.35, the Romax pull up to their house. Rain still just pouring down. They see in their
headlights as their cars pulling up. They see that the porch light is on. They don't really think
anything of it. Maybe she turned it on because she was scared, because it was dark and it was stormy.
Maybe not. But when Ed walks up to the house and he goes to unlock the door, the door is unlocked.
And right when they walk into the house, they see the body of Janet on the ground.
The carpet is soaked with her blood. They see, just in the brief time that they're looking before
they start totally freaking out, she's obviously dead. She suffered some major head wounds and she's
been stabbed multiple times. Ann sees that and she freaks out and then immediately runs upstairs to
check on her son. Totally safe. Asleep. Not even aware of what was going on downstairs. Ed then goes
to call the police and the phone is off the hook. Picks the phone up, dials the police.
We need someone out here right away. Massive police presence shows up. They all show up.
You just can't believe that this would happen anywhere, but it's happening in their town.
The police show up. Now, part of the problem is that their house is kind of in the middle of nowhere.
It's almost on the border of two different police jurisdictions. And so, the Columbia police get
involved and the police in the neighboring area get involved and they start vying for control over
who gets to control this crime scene, who's in charge of this murder. You have a bunch of cops
walking around. You have conflicting orders between the police. All sorts of stuff. And that is kind
of indicative of what's going to happen with this. This is what they start to put together.
She seemed to have been stabbed with a mechanical pencil. She was strangled with a power cord from
an iron. That's what eventually did her in. But she was pummeled in the head. She was stabbed
multiple times with what appears to be a mechanical pencil, which weren't super common back then.
They're not even super common now. They actually quite suck. I've never seen the advantage of a
mechanical pencil. But she suffered head wounds. She suffered stab wounds. Unfortunately, she had been
sexually assaulted as well. The police are fighting over control of the crime scene. They're
fighting for control of the case. And they're looking into this and they don't have any immediate
leads. There is a back window that is busted open and there's some mud by like the back kitchen door.
And so some cops are saying someone must have busted their way into the house. Got in, assaulted her,
killed her. Other people are saying the fact that the porch light is on makes us think that someone
came to the front door. And since the door was unlocked, it was probably somebody she knew.
But in the midst of all this, is there trying to work this crime scene, trying to work this case?
Eventually, one of the officers turns to someone else and says,
"Do you think this is related to the Mary Lou Jenkins case?"
Four years earlier, February 5th, 1946, Mary Lou Jenkins, 20 years old. She was staying at home
alone. Her father was out of town and her mother was down the street, taking care of an elderly
couple. This is in the same town. The mom says, "Listen, if you run into any problems, open the
shades, turn the light on, and call me." Later that night, the mom looks out the window, she's in the
house with the elderly people. She looks out the window, she looks down the street and she sees her
house with the blinds open and the light on, but she didn't receive a phone call. So she thinks
everything is fine. That seems like a weird warning system if you only, of all three things,
have to happen. Blinds have to be open, lights on and a phone call. Like you figured just two
of the three would work, but she doesn't think anything's wrong. When she goes home later that
night, she sees that her daughter was raped and strangled with an extension cord. There was a guy
who around the same time murdered his own wife and during a rather brutal police interrogation,
he confessed to the rape and murder of Mary Lou Jenkins. So he was executed for that. He was
executed for the murder of his wife and on the date of his execution, he says, "Listen, I murdered
my wife, but I didn't murder Mary Lou Jenkins and no one believes him because he's a murderer and
he's about to die. So, you know, it's not like he has the best credibility ever." But there were
issues in this town. There were creepers. Now, she was killed in 1946, but there was kind of this
underlying current of odd activity in this town. Now, three years after Mary Lou Jenkins' murder,
there was a spate of peeping Tom activity in the town. Now, that makes me think the fact that the
mom was so paranoid saying, "If anything went wrong, do these things." It makes me think that
people are already a little on edge. Maybe they hadn't bubbled to the surface. Maybe people weren't
aware of it. But in 1949, they had a bunch of peeping Tom activity that actually escalated into
rape. A few days before Halloween in 1949, a 16-year-old girl was raped by a man wearing a white
mask. Almost a month later, on November 29th, there was an attempted rape and then the next day,
a man, when a white mask finds a couple in a car, robs the man, rapes the girl. So then a couple
days later, on November 4th, a man was caught peeping outside of a house. He was subject to a
rather brutal police interrogation and he confesses to the rape and the attempted rape. Doesn't confess
to the rape of the couple, but confesses to the rape and the attempted rape that happened just
a couple months earlier. So, the police in this town were kind of known for using extra judicial
interrogation methods. They weren't doing stuff by the book and that would come to bite them in the
butt in the end. So, they've, at this point, they have solved all these other crimes they believe.
The police believe that they know who's done these other crimes. So in 1950, though, they're
looking at the body of Janet on the autopsy table. It appears she's been stabbed with a mechanical
pencil several times. And so then the police are discussing it and they go, "Do you know anyone
who uses a mechanical pencil?" And the answer is yes. Yes. I do know someone who's using mechanical
pencil. Not only do I know someone who often uses a mechanical pencil, they know Janet. In fact,
Janet is one of their babysitters. Robert Mueller, which is a bizarre name that this hasn't popped
up more often because Robert Mueller is now such a famous name, but Robert Mueller was a tailor in
town, a very, very successful man. He was always known to carry a mechanical pencil. Now, that's
not enough to make you a suspect, but he was also known to have lewd conversations about young girls.
And Romak said that Robert Mueller was the type of guy who used his hands, not his words, when
dealing with women. Very, very gropey type of guy. Ed Romak said, "Not only had he made lewd
comments about young women, he would make comments about wanting to take a young girl's virginity,
and he would make comments about how curvy Janet was becoming. The kind of comments that were
making Ed a little nervous, which makes me think that when Ed was saying, "Don't open the door for
anyone," and here's where the shotgun is, almost makes me think he is saying, "Don't even open it
for Robert Mueller. Just leave the door locked. Even if you know him, just leave it locked during
the porch light on." But they're all out at a card game together. So, Robert Mueller has a perfect
alibi, right? As the cops started looking into him and started questioning, once he became the
focus of this investigation, they interviewed the people at the party. And the people at the party
say, "Yes, Robert Mueller was at the party for us, except for a few hours." And the cops were like,
"What?" And they're like, "Yeah, he was gone for a few hours." He said he had a doctor's appointment
or something, and they're like, "Really? Late at night?" And they're like, "Yeah." During a rainstorm,
he had a doctor's appointment. They're like, "Yeah, we didn't really think anything of it now." But
now that you're mentioning him, it is a little suspicious, isn't it? The cops are like, "Yes,
you could have told us that weeks ago." So they contacted Robert Mueller's doctor, and the doctor
goes, "I never saw him that night. He never stopped by." Now, his alibi starts falling apart.
But not only that, the police are putting together that this guy's fairly creepy, and
at one point he's talking to Ed, and he goes, "You know, I don't know who killed Janet, but I know
how I would have done it. I would have just walked up to the front door and said, 'Hey, Ed sent me
here to pick up some poker chips,' and she would have let me right inside." And Ed's like, "What the
hell are you talking about?" So there actually was an interrogation. But again, not by the book.
They took him out of the city jurisdiction. They take Robert Mueller to this abandoned barn
out of police jurisdiction and interview him for hours. Doesn't break. Doesn't break at all.
He offers to take a polygraph. He takes a polygraph. He passes the polygraph. So at that
point the cops are like, "Well, he didn't do it." Now, we know now that polygraph technology isn't
100%. They're like, "Hey, man, he passed the polygraph and he didn't break during our basic
torture session, so he's most likely innocent." But a judge disagreed and said, "You know what,
I don't agree with that decision, police. I'm going to convene a grand jury. We're going to look at
all the evidence and we're going to see if we can indict this guy." Goes to a grand jury. But when
all the police evidence is presented to the grand jury, they say, "Too much problem with these
different police forces trying to investigate this. We have all this different stuff because one police
force straight up says it was a stranger who broke in the back window." And then you have this other
police force saying, "No, it's someone she knew." So despite all of the weirdness with his alibi
and his statements and his creepy behavior, he's never prosecuted. He ends up leaving, dies at
the age of 83 in Arizona. The Romacs and the Mollers go about their business. Janet had a little
sister who ended up going off into college and just kind of moving on with her life. The parents,
obviously when I say moving on with their life, obviously they mourned the loss of their daughter
and sister. But things just kind of faded away. To this day, no one has ever been successfully
prosecuted in any way for the death of Janet Christman. Just a 13-year-old girl, three-day
shy of her 14th birthday, raped and murdered on a cold, rainy Missouri night.
It doesn't have all of the extra creepy details that the urban legend has.
But the idea of a lone babysitter, a young woman trapped in a house, being confronted with the
ultimate evil, is creepy enough. Whoever did this got away with it. Whoever did this most likely
was responsible for the other crimes. And because of the way the police were interacting with these
suspects in the past, people were confessing most likely to crimes they did not commit. The guy
who was convicted of Mary Lou Jenkins was a murderer. The guy who was peeping outside the
window was a peeping tom. But was he a rapist? Were all of these crimes connected? Nobody knows.
And I don't really know if anyone really cares. You think this story would still be floating
around out there as one of the big unsolved cases. But it's not. It's been swept away into a sea
of unsolved mysteries. What really happened that cold, rainy night? Was she confronted by a man
she knew who had always lusted after her, who had a friendly demeanor and walked through the front
door before committing the ultimate evil? Or was it a stranger skulking about the house who saw a
young girl alone and decided to do something truly despicable? Either way, that person went on
with their lives. Someone truly evil continued to live, function, and walk among the rest of the
world. And that is scarier than any urban legend. DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our
email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio. Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen
to it every day. But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
Bye.