A man returning home is suddenly thrust into a world of true crime and conspiracy.
And then we travel to your bedroom to take a look what's hidden behind that closet door.
Is it really just a bunch of clothes? Is it a ghastly spirit? Or something far, far worse.
Today on Dead Ravorating.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys had
an awesome weekend. First off let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter,
Zach Yoga. Zach everyone give a round of applause to Zach Yoga. Zach you're gonna be our captain
or pilot this episode. You can't support the Patreon that's fine too just help spread the
word about the show really really helps out a lot. Now Zach I gotta warn you. I gotta warn you
I gotta warn you dude it's always luck of the draw when people support the show what episode
they end up on. This episode's a little creepy. It's actually quite quite creepy so I hope you're
really good at yoga. I hope you're really good at de-stressing and if you're not um if if you have
already had a bummy weekend and don't want any more bad news or creepy news I guess I'm building it up.
This episode isn't about you and how crummy your life is. This episode's a little dark though
and it ends with spooky things in your closet. It ends with a thin piece of wood separating you
from eternal evil so you know Zach doesn't have a choice. He has to be in this episode but maybe
it's not the right episode for your Monday but Zach I'm gonna toss you the keys of the Jason
Jalopy. We are headed out to Las Vegas Nevada. Zach Yoga's all flexible he's driving the car
with his feet totally not hygienic but you know he is a Patreon supporter. It's November 6th 2020
so incredibly recent story this just happened. We're driving through Las Vegas in front of us
is a car driven by J. Kwan Singleton. Now J. Kwan was just leaving his grandma's house. His grandma
was taking care of one of his children and he was headed back home to a house he shares with his
girlfriend Amanda Sharp Jefferson 26 years old and their two daughters Rose is one year old little
Lily is two months old. As he's driving back to his house he can't wait to see his kids he can't
wait to see his girlfriend but things haven't been going well at the house recently. Now not your
typical domestic strife fighting over bills and stuff like that she accused him of cheating on her
which that's not abnormal right I mean I'm not saying J. Kwan gets accused of it all the time
it comes up in relationships someone gets suspicious things like that but no matter how much he
denies that he's cheating on her she says you are in the spirit world your alter spirit wife
is who you're cheating on me with you see there's a world right above our own that's where you're
going to cheat on me. J. Kwan walks into his house and Amanda's just sitting on the couch
he's just kind of walking in the house is unusually quiet he notices that Lily's bassinet
is sitting there but as he's walking up dropping his keys trying to get settled back into his house
he notices Lily and Rose are both in the bassinet they're stacked on top of each other so it's not
like they're comfortably laying taken a nap they're completely prone one on top of the other
obviously J. Kwan doesn't his brain's trying to catch up to this situation of what he's seeing
he sees both of his daughters perfectly still in a bassinet just laying on top of each other
he turns to Amanda and goes what's going on shhh Amanda shushes him from the couch
Amanda what happened to my dosh
he reaches down and touches his daughter's bodies they're cold
he goes to call the police Amanda's trying to keep him from calling the police
telling him no no no no no no no no no don't call the police don't call the police
do you know how much their organs are worth she begins to talk about how much the daughter's
organs are worth as he's looking for his phone to call an ambulance call the police to call anybody
she begins talking about how much money they can get for their organs when rescue personnel got to
the house they overheard her talking about selling the organs she got arrested obviously she got
arrested and then the story gets even more bizarre when the cops take her in a custody they ask her
so tell us what happened here and she goes i don't know and they go ma'am we know that you murdered
your two daughters just tell us what happened you'll get that weight off your chest people want to
confess and she looked at them and said i don't have any daughters i don't know who that man was
who walked into my apartment i live alone never seen him before police kind of look at each other
her story is that basically she's from an alternate reality she said that she's been living in her
apartment alone all this time and then one day she walked into her living room and there were two
bodies in a bassinet now that story okay so i'm leaving some stuff out that story in and of itself
because let me just say that story in and of itself is is very disturbing
it's very there's four multiple reasons one i can't imagine what that father is going through
and all the family is going through to think that um somebody that you loved and had kids with killed
those kids that's the worst crime like killing your parents it's pretty bad like if i had to
rate them if i had to rate a family side killing your parents it's like uh you know at a certain
point you know saying all kids are destined to kill their parents but that's actually isn't that
part of the motto myth like first you kill your parents then you kill your teacher then you kill
god that's kind of like the evolution of man i'm not saying literally saying start banging on the
gates of heaven or kill your parents don't start on that first step but like fighting your parents
whatever oh i guess there's even fighting and killing them but don't kill your parents that's
not what i'm saying but if someone told me that they killed their parents i'd be like what did
they do to deserve it and hopefully there was a good answer hopefully it wasn't asking questions
like what did they do to deserve it siblings killing each other it's pretty rough right it's a little
more just a little more understandable again not advocating it i'm saying on the list of killing
like if i had to rank them if i had to rank them killing your kids would be the worst is what i'm
saying that was all leading up killing your kids would be the worst because you're that guardian
you're that person who's taking care of them who created them and then but you know like siblings
killing each other it's still horrible and then you killing your parents it's still horrible
don't get me this is not i'm not starting an advocacy group but there's something just so
despicable about killing your own children and then the things that that father must be going
through is absolutely awful so we have that we just have this the sheer circumstances of it
when we look at it through a paranormal lens we look at it though what if this would explain
let's put on our conspiracy caps here for a second what if this would explain why people
are caught at crime scenes or people 100 believe they're guilty there's a bunch of evidence leading
them to be guilty but they're not guilty like they're actually found not guilty or 20 years later
evidence comes out that shows they're not guilty it's because they actually came from an alternate
universe now hear me out hear me out or not or totally dismiss me but my point is is that
what if like let's say oj simpson for example right immediately like that's a terrible example
let's say oj simpson for example let's say that he the the oj of universe prime that's our universe
because we're the best universe oj simpson of universe prime did murder nicole brown and uh what
was the goldman uh i don't remember his first name but oj simpson of universe prime killed brown
and goldman and then just disappeared then just fell through a wormhole and a you would be indistinguishable
the oj simpson from universe 897 came through that same portal and was like out out of the crime
scene he just stand there he's like uh oh and then uh but he's found not guilty because let's say he
didn't appear at the crime scene let's say like say he appeared at a boutique or something like that
then he was nowhere near there and that way he'd have the alibi but the cops could go we found
all this evidence half of it we manufactured but there's evidence here or there's people that you
know the cops know are absolutely guilty but their dna is different and they get set free like the
cops are like we know that was the guy we have all this evidence maybe not dna evidence because that
can fix a lot of people but they go we found the same type of fiber in his car and the jury's like
nope they're not guilty what if you so what if your dna is different in another universe so if
jason from universe prime this one interacted with jason from universe 1257 would we have the same
i don't know how we're interacting we're playing ping pong and throwing skin flakes everywhere
would our dna be the same it's creepy and again the crime itself is absolutely inhumane i don't
want to minimize that but again with our conspiracy caps on paranormal view of looking at this
she sees this alternate reality and she may have slipped in she's this basically the
amanda in universe prime here she did she wasn't married in this other universe and she's walking
around this apartment and she's like oh my god like there's i don't know who these children are but
they're dead i don't know what's going on that story is creepy now i did leave out some key details
because it totally would have ruined that ending she did she does say that she does 100 say that
she just she does not marry to this guy she doesn't know who these kids are she walked into her house
one day and she found these two lifeless kids in her basket the stuff i left out is after she saw
that she went to take a shower and then went and sat on the couch and the cops are like if your
story is true why did you take a shower so that kind of throws a little i don't want to say water
because then that's a pun but that throws a little bit of you know milk and the honey on that one because
if you walked in your house if you did come from an alternate reality and walked home and there was
a crime scene there you want to be like oh i can't do anything about that time to take a shower
obviously you would call the police also what's totally she could probably argue probably argue
an insanity defense and they could say yeah you know it was just really hard to win on but she
could they could say yeah she thought that she'd come from an alternate reality and that would be
a wouldn't be a great defense you'd lose but she didn't even stick to that story because as the
cops are investigating her and she's saying i don't know who those kids are i don't know who this guy
is i just came home and found these bodies as the cops are investigating her she goes hey you
guys are in law enforcement right they're like yeah yeah we are and she goes do you know how much i
can sell their organs for cops you're like what so even then like even if she did come from an
alternate reality for some reason she wants to sell people's organs she said she saw it in a movie
she said she saw a movie where she found out organs were expensive so
i'm that creepy it's funny the other day i was talking to pom pomeran on twitter
pom posted a survey about who's hotter who didn't want a date or something like that and it was
shigo from kim possible and then it was some girl from danie phantom i actually might cover this
coming up but pom pomeran reminded me of this there was this guy who doesn't like buttholes
he hated buttholes and he was in love with danie phantom not danie phantom himself but the girls
from danie phantom and he would draw pictures of himself in the world of danie phantom and he
hated buttholes so much he shot up a grocery store and then killed himself because he thought once he
died he'd go into a world full of no one would have a butthole and everyone would be from danie phantom
so i might do a whole episode on that i think he has a manifesto if i can find his manifesto i'd
love to dive into that i've always loved doing that on the show i've only done it once but i
read the manifesto again i think he has one if he did i read it years ago i love reading stuff like
that and um yeah but anyways the point is is that it's crazy to think and that's probably a poor choice
of words but it's crazy to think i'm just gonna do it again it's crazy to think that you can have
someone who's already teetering on insanity and then they watch the wrong show and it fully
see ments that insane world view like had the guy who was shooting i'll put it in the show notes
i'll put it in the show notes if you can't wait for my episode on it it'll probably be next week
but if that guy had not seen danie phantom if he had said watch tenage mutinousia turtles would he
have tried to focus his energy into being a superhero i don't know i don't know i mean i guess
anything would be better it'd be better if he just watched dragnet and just decided to be a cop or
just watched nothing decided not to be crazy but it's creepy to think this woman watched a movie
watched some random movie where someone was saying oh you know how much money we can get for these
organs and that was the key that unlocked this horrific horrible plan kyle yogi you ready to
take us out of here he's he's not in his head enthusiastically yeah i know it's a grim story
it's especially a grim story for a monday but tomorrow's episode has something even grosser
it's maybe not as grim but it's way grosser so i feel bad for the patreon the guy who supported
the patreon for tomorrow uh zack gonna have a good laugh at that one zack go ahead and call in that
carbonar copter we are leaving behind las vegas and avada and we are headed out to tulsa oklahoma
rainstorm lightning and thunder kyle is perfectly cut zack i think i called you kyle
i think i called you kyle a second ago so if i add in zack zack we'll edit those up and zack is
flying us expertly through this rainstorm we're headed to tulsa oklahoma to meet a young girl
named melissa helicopter lands uh we're running out on our raincoach you run a raincoat right you're
like i didn't know he's gonna storm this episode we run and we pick the lock and now we're in melissa's
house she didn't invite us she doesn't know the stories going on melissa h was living with her dad
in this house in tulsa oklahoma and she had heard stories that it was haunted she got a feeling that
it was haunted it was just one of those creepy places and she did what i consider one of the most
unforgivable sins i hate doing it i do it if i'm too easy to get up she sleeps with the closet door
open it's not a cat it's not her cat trying to get in her bed that's the door slowly swaying back
and forth she probably should get that checked out doors aren't supposed to do that but anyways
she wakes up one night her room is pitch black in the closet though she sees someone standing there
no someone hanging there who she describes in her closet is a teenage girl wearing a white wedding
dress this figure in the closet her whole body is spazming every muscle every joint every limb
looking like it's the middle of some sort of musculature fit melissa is sitting in bed and she's
too scared to scream she's just looking at this specter twitching in the darkness of her closet
she jumps out of bed and she has to walk by her closet poorly designed poorly designed bedroom
she jumps out of bed and she has to walk by her closet to get out of the room the whole time
she has her eyes on the ghost even as she's reaching back to turn the knob to get out
she can't stop looking at the girl the whole time this teenage girl in the closet her entire body
is convulsing the whole time she's staring straight into melissa's eyes here's another one we
like oh that wasn't too scary here's another one zack let's hop back in that carbonicopter we are
headed out to actually I don't have a location this one we'll just say this one's across the street
it's a really really haunted neighborhood so we get in the carbonicopter we fly we fly 30 feet we
land we're now at the house of another young girl let's call this one rebecca because we don't have
a name this story actually came from mysterious universe they got it from true ghost tales rebecca
is sitting on the couch watching tv with her mom and all of a sudden they hear screaming
they recognize the screaming it's her father so they jump up now the dad is an alcoholic so apparently
he screams all the time so there's that it wasn't like they're like oh no right away but as it continued
on they're like okay we should probably go check on him it's a commercial break on the show let's go
check on him no they don't know where the screaming is coming from so they're kind of walking around
the house probably taking their time honestly they're like dad where are you eventually they
trace the screaming into rebecca's bedroom then they trace the screaming into rebecca's closet
they hear the sound of her father screaming on the other side of this closet door now
even though he's an alcoholic not all alcoholics scream that's a stereotype that i've just invented
but there's a difference running through the house or just sitting there and getting mad at the game
and throwing stuff around it's not great behavior either versus being in a closet screaming it's
definitely more creepy they go to open the closet door rattle rattle rattle rattle rattle rattle the
knob won't turn the door is stuck the mom's using all of her weight she finally opens the door and
they're in the closet is their father which is what they expected they didn't expect the rest of
this paragraph he was floating in midair hanging it seemed by his neck for a few seconds this doesn't
go by it's not like a flash it's not like he jumped up right before they opened the door and he's all
ta-da for a few seconds they're actually looking at this adult man hover in the air like he's being
hung or held up by something finally he falls to the ground he scrambles to his feet but get out
of the way women and he runs out of the bedroom to hide in another corner of the house now the
daughter and the mom go to follow him and they're like what was that that's not what we expected
we were watching charles in charge and we got this since then he said what happened was he was
walking through the house he's thinking what am i going to scream about tonight i'm just the right
amount of drunk i need to start my screaming soon it's almost 7 p.m he's walking through the house
he's walking through the house he walks into rebecca's room and he watches the closet door open
he said he heard something begin to call his name i didn't make up a name for him so the thing is
going dad daddy papa papa come here kind of stunts him for a second because he didn't expect to
hear that he also didn't expect the closet to go daddy he's like dude my name's robert the next thing
he knows a dark figure darted out of the closet and then he blacked out next thing he knows the
closet doors opening up his family is looking at him stunned a few days later rebecca's sitting on
the couch i don't know why they haven't moved at this point right rebecca's sitting on the couch
and she said the whole light was on and it was the way that the house was structured was that
you could look down the hallway which is one of the creepiest things possible ever looking down a
hallway you look down the hallway and see into her bedroom and she said she looked down the hallway
and the whole the hallway light was on the whole place was lit up she says her parents are only
about 10 feet away from her in this story so i don't know if that means they were in a separate
room or if they were in the same room just 10 feet away i don't know how small this house was
she said her parents are only about 10 feet away she sees like in a flash a dark figure
standing in her bedroom doorway it reaches its arm out and begins to beckon her to him
she opens her mouth to scream nothing comes out it's interesting because that happened to melissa
as well she starts to scream she's trying to scream but nothing will come out she turns her head
looking for some sort of help and when she turns back the figure is right next to her it's sitting
on the couch she feels a hand wrap around her neck this demon kisses her forehead kisses her neck
disappears rebecca said her family had not seen the thing since they'd never seen it again
but she does say whenever she's in a dark room she feels like she's not alone
so super spooky story obviously i did leave something out of that story as well though
because i don't i don't know if this adds to the spookiness or if it makes she kind of roll
your eyes but i don't want to ruin the narrative but i did want to include it so the next day in
between those two events right there's a little prequel for you here's a little prequel for you
or uh jason why'd you ruin that story the next day so first time the dad's being hung the third time
it jumps out this is the jump scare real-life jump scare on the couch but in between the two events
the next morning after the dad was hanging in the closet they went into her room and they opened the
closet door and inside and inside and inside and inside was a vampire was a vampire so
i love that part out because it's so dumb it totally ruins the story this is what they next day
they these are my notes next day they checked out the closet they saw a man standing in there
his hands over his chest like Dracula when he sleeps he had long fingernails and he had wings
and he was sleeping because it was daytime it was the next day and then they closed the
closet door like what do you do after that anyways that's that part makes it totally
ruins the story right anyways forget about shut the door on that part of the story as well totally
ruins it the reason why i wanted to cover this is because closets are super super spooky but i
didn't want to end it with just telling you some spooky stories one that involves a movie vampire
i fought to suck your blood that was the part that she cut out because even she knew that was
ridiculous the question isn't are closets scary they are scary i'm sure one or two of you guys
will be like well closets aren't scary i work in a closet repair shop and i've never seen a ghost
and you're actually a ghost you didn't know that you've been a ghost for a hundred years but for
the most part most rational people think closets are scary so i wanted to tell a couple scary
ghost stories involving closets but then i wanted to talk about why are closets spooky actually
looked into the science behind closets being spooky it's interesting i didn't find any science on it
at all but i did find a website called magic for the real world and so it's like the reverse of
science magic is the reverse of science so this counts as scientific there's been a lot of studies
on doors that's actually true i'll see if i can find it for the show notes but there was a study a
long time ago that when you know how when you walk through a door and you forget what you were trying
to do you're like what was i gonna do what was i gonna do oh yeah i was behind in this closet and
be a vampire you walk through a door you go to get your keys you forget what you're in there for
you can't figure it out you're like why am i in this room all that stuff i've actually done studies
on that of why that happens the answer is they don't know the scientists don't know but what's
weird is they can actually do it virtually they said you can set someone up at a computer
and if they press a button and a virtual door opens it actually degrades their memory there is
something about passing through thresholds that makes people forget why they are in there that
doesn't make sense at all did cavemen do it when they were walking in one cave they're like oh me
og me no no why i'm here they're like do we only have three things we have a club we have saber
two tiger meat and we have a this chalk to ride on a cave he's like me still not know at what point
if i'm walking through a forest and there are two trees their branches come over and make an arc
or an arch however you pronounce it and i walk through those while i forget why i'm in the forest
so at what point is a doorway a doorway like does it actually it doesn't actually have to
have a door because in the vr you can do it so at what point like if i crawled through a hole if i
was crawling through a tunnel i keep forgetting why i'm in there like why am i in here why am i in
here why am i in here every foot like at what point is a doorway a doorway so that's weird that's
just a weird scientific thing and a big philosophical question as well if you cut a hole in the wall
and crawl through it is that a doorway technically it's an area of transition but if you took the
forest that example or if you had like a broken down gazebo it's just one side it's just one side
and you walk through the gazeb I don't need to keep making examples you guys get it at what point is
a door not a door because otherwise you shouldn't have any doors at all or any archways and nothing
submarines submarines just have to they're basically boats you can't have little hatches on them
that's the last thing you don't climb in a hatch and they're like what am i doing on here they're
like look out torpedoes are hitting them but my point being is those are that's weird just the
idea of doors is super spooky but uh back to reality magic for the real world website they say
that an area of transition is actually exactly what it sounds like you're moving from one room
to another but anytime you have an area of transition it's not just for us that doorway you built
also allows anything else to transition through that doorway see that that wouldn't make sense
about like haunted woods because you'd have ponds that would basically be a transition spot between
the earth and the water archways and trees groves circles of rocks all of these would be
transitional areas any area of transitions can allow these creatures to come through magic for the
real world had a pretty simple solution for this what you need to do is you need to remove
as many transitional areas as possible which is unless you live in a yurt is impossible because
again even if you removed your door you're still going to walk through it they're not they're not
requiring you to remove your doors but they are saying to limit them as much as possible they said
rearrange furniture to minimize shadows so there's that um or you could just change your light bulbs
or have no light bulbs at all i mean i guess i'm taking it to the was just thinking stream
they're just saying move your couch and i'm like burn down the foundation and move your furniture
around so there's less shadows they also said this and i think this is the worst advice ever
leave your closet light on now i think that's a bad advice for two reasons one must closets
don't have lights but let's say that you went out and got a light bulb for your closet i think it's
creepy you're honestly i hate this is one of the things i hate because i'm laying down to go to bed
if i leave a light on in another room which i'll do for different reasons i have i have my reasons
i leave a light on in the other room i'm going to bed i can see that thin strip of light i'm always
worried i'm gonna look and i'm gonna see feet stand in there you're like you're like chaston
so you're so you're saying there is an off chance that one time you may look over and see feet standing
outside your door because the light there but the alternative is to have monsters giant monsters
floating around in the darkness waiting for you monsters that look like universal pictures vampires
that's your choice is a pair of boots a pair of boots outside your bedroom door or some sort of
hellish monster yeah but i don't see that see the monster plus i think if i was a ghost it'd be a
lot easier to just manifest my feet so if i wanted to scare myself i would just be feet i mean
that'd be terrifying anyways right you're sitting there eating lunch you just see feet sitting on
your table seeing a full body like standing there would be super scary but i'm imagining that it
takes a lot of work takes a lot it takes a lot of spiritual work to get your body in shape so
you could either manifest your entire body after maybe a hundred years or you should just be feet
today be feet today and if you could just easily be feet then you could just appear outside my door
but as you get ready for bed tonight make sure that your closet door is locked possibly barricaded
shut make sure that your feet aren't hanging off the bed and the blanket covers you from
toe to neck and just keep an eye on that old rickety closet door you might think that with it
locked there's no chance of anything getting out to hurt you but is it really possible for two inches
of wood to hold back the might of a dark spirit we tell ourselves that these things will protect us
so we can get a good night's sleep but in the end that door opens and while you have a restless
sleep it stands over you and watches it's just waiting for the right moment to make you disappear
from the world of the living
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true front podcast you don't
have to listen to it every day but i'm glad you listened to it today have a great one guys
you