account is like exists I don't really know what more to say it's just weird
we'll talk about it and then we'll meet a man who got abducted by an alien now
we've covered a lot of men like that why is it always men now that I think about
it usually dudes right but we've met a lot of men who have been abducted by
aliens however this one met his soulmate on a UFO today on Dead Rabbit Radio
hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I'm your
host Jason Carpenter I'm having a great day I hope you guys are having a great
day - I really do I really mean it it's funny that intro was kind of informal
compared to how I normally do them why is it always that men are getting
abducted by aliens I bet you if you looked at the statistics of it and I'm
not going to I got other things to do I got a read stories about ghosts and
goblins flowing around math what I bet you if you looked at the statistics I
bet you it's like a 70/30 split 80/20 maybe and then this is anecdotal this is
just going off of the hundreds and hundreds of UFO stories that I've read
over the course of my life usually the female ones the ones where women are
abducted it's horrifying it's really bad medical experiences they're getting
poked and prodded and have an alien babies put in them or taken out of them
every show often you'll get a woman who's like happy she's given birth to
aliens but interesting I'll see if I can do some research on that I that is kind
of my job is kind of my job I wonder if there really is a division of the sexes
as far as it goes men versus women getting abducted but before we do that
let's go ahead and get started with this episode this episode that I've
prepared let's go ahead and give a shout out to one of our legacy
patreons Dalton Ogden Dalton thank you so much you've been supporting the show
for a really really long time really appreciate that Dalton we're gonna give
you the keys of the carbonar copter but we're not taking it anywhere right now
so just just sit just don't move now for our first story let's travel to reddit
now I know a lot of you guys don't like reddit I'm not a huge fan of reddit
myself but I do find the fact that the information is permanent interesting as
opposed to like 4chan where the information just did it and then it's
gone the thing I like about reddit is that it's permanent things I hate about
reddit take another podcast for me to mention the karma system and all that
stupid stuff but let's take a look at reddit there is a reddit board it's
really interesting one called RVI or reddit bureau of investigation where
people go help help I saw like this weird fox walk by and I'm trying to figure
out what type of fox it is or help help my family's being stalked it's weird it
there's this weird it has a really wide swath of mysteries but it's a place that
you can go to to post weird stuff not even weird stuff but just like sometimes
it is like I'm getting crank calls from this number but I don't know how to
track it down and sometimes it's like I saw this there's a butterfly in my
apartment but my apartment's hermetically sealed how could it get in I'm the boy
in the bubble and I'm especially allergic to butterflies help help please
it's a place where you can post stuff on reddit and reddit will help figure it
out now I found this one today this is from a user named fishatron3000
fishatron tells this story on RVI looking for this advice I'm hanging out
with my girlfriend she gets an ad on her Instagram account this sounds okay to be
fair this starts off sounding like a horror movie from like 2015 when the
technology was brand new and they're like what if the apps downloaded you
remember all those horror movies you had like ring and phone and app and killer
app there's a whole spate of horror movies that was based on your phone other
than scream which did it right then you had like ring and vibrate and what was
the one do not call no that was no no was it do not answer the caller not
available something like that the Japanese horror movie that you would look
at your phone and it would say like you hung up or something like that anyways
let me fishatron3000 hanging out with your girlfriend she gets an ad from a
weird Instagram account called @deepfrycrust the only picture on @deepfrycrust
his account is a close-up of a patch of skin you know maybe it's like a creepy
ARG something like that that's what I think a lot of you guys might think this
is but it is this is kind of creepy so and I'll kind of go into a why it's
creepy but anyways there's a patch of skin there's a close-up photo of a
patch of skin so the boyfriend is like what that's kind of weird and there's a
linked account on deep fry crust that takes you to an account called sour
crust at sour crust so at sour crust has probably about well it's hard to say but
at the time of me recording this I think has about nine images on their
Instagram account quite a few of them are videos so I'm gonna play some audio
clips here for you this first clip is footage it's handheld camcorder footage
walking through a graveyard looking at gravestones
burial site of the Sunter County does so weird right maybe like an ARG maybe a
weird art project and you maybe think it's kind of a lot to throw at you first
time you're like Jason I'm super creepy I'm listening to this at one of the
warning sorry guys but it gets creepier so and also you might want to turn to all
to warn you you need to turn the volume down on the next audio clip because it's
kind of scared me and he's talking about in this video you just heard he's
talking about the Sunter County does Sunter County does now I'll talk about
them in a second but let me play you this second audio clip and be prepared
for listening with headphones you might want to turn it down a bit this next
clip is a video clip of a guy and the reason normally I don't do this because
the video the video component of this I actually don't think is super important
the audio is disturbing right I don't know why I don't know why maybe I'm just
big old baby just agree that it's super disturbing yeah Jason that's super
creepy kept me up all night long your podcast so spooky yay just agree with
me for a second this next is a footage of a again it's handheld camera footage
just like an old-school camera footage of a man narrating first he's walking by
the gravestones of the Sumpter County does now he's walking down a dirt path
this is Locklair Road near Sumpter South Carolina dirt road frontage road is the
murder scene summer 1976 of the Sumpter County does young couple shot to death
just after bodies found by a trucker the next morning it's been an ongoing
baffling mystery not so much who the perpetrator was but the identity of the
young couple now that horrible noise you heard at the end that kind of jumps
scary thing at that point an image flies by and I'll tell you what that is in a
sec tell you what that is in a second I know it's hard to talk about a video on
a podcast but this all it actually all works so the first thing he's walking
through the graveyard he's like these are the graves of the Sumpter County
does second video he's walking along this road and he's like this is where the
Sumpter County does were found and when that weird noise cue hits the floating
head of Jane Doe enters the picture for just a second now the head of Jane Doe
is really going to be an introduction to who are the Sumpter County does who are
the Sumpter County does back in 1976 August 9th 1976 in Sumpter County South
Carolina his dude was just kind of hanging out in the middle of Sumpter
County just kind of walking over along walking along that dirt road that that
guy was subscribing in that video and he sees two bodies dead laying there each
one had three gunshot wounds both of them were dead obviously they just weren't
picnicking and they're like oh these know we're going to the doctor later these
two people were dead and of course the cops come out pick them up start
investigating it obvious murder the way they are both killed they're all had
where shot through the throat through the chest through the head kind of hard
to commit suicide that way so anyways the cops start investigating it as a
murder but one of the first things you really need to you have the victims but
you don't know who they are and a big thing about solving a murder is you
know who they are they knew who they're last seen with where they work who their
enemies they couldn't figure out who these people were this young man and a
young woman anywhere between they think they're in their mid-20s but the corner
goes they could be anywhere between 18th to 30 I'm gonna think they're like 26
27 but based on these facts they can kind of figure out a couple different
things one they did they weren't they were from out of town and they were
visiting the area and a tow truck driver heard the guy call himself as Jacques or
Jacques I like okay they have that and he was found with a ring that had the
initials I believe JRS on it so they go maybe his name was Jacques he had a
ton of dental work done and then the they had to bring in a dentist and he goes
they whoever had this dentist work done spent a lot of money and actually looking
at it it seems foreign it was weird it was weird he was able to say this is the
procedure they use up in Canada so they're like okay his name might have been
Jacques might be from Canada that would kind of make sense looks like he came
from money he had a line on like one of those bulgoli watches bulgova whatever
you call it now the girl they go this is probably a sister they kind of look
alike but we just don't know much about her either they they had took all of her
jewelry off took photos of the jewelry took photos of her shoes and then had
no idea what her name was what they did was they took photos of their dead
faces and begin to circulate them around the area saying do you know who these
people are also all over sour crusts Instagram page there's photos of this
dead woman's face now sometimes it's just her face flying onto screen sometimes
it's her face sitting in a car as hip-hop music is playing that's a video
where it's just like the car is a gif and it's moving up and down there's like
and her head is in the picture kind of move in there he has one this was weird
this shows me that this account is active one he had a post go up 10 minutes
after I started looking at the page and that was a picture of a wanted poster or
a missing persons poster in Asia and then he had a picture of the boy in the
box which is a really tragic true crime story back in like the 1950s five-year-old
kid was found dead in a box and they've never identified him to this day they
don't know who killed him how he died I think they might know how he died but
they don't know who he is he had a picture of the because that the boy in
the box was another photo that they took a photo of his face and they circulated
it all over the country really back then he had a photo of the boy in the box but
the boy in the box mouth was replaced with a photo of Sumter County do Jane
Doe's head while I was investigating the story that photo was removed so this is
an active Instagram account eventually they kept they with the Sumter County
Does they circulated the pictures everywhere people who had missing kids
would come out and they go that's where I wish that was my kid because at least
there'd be some closure but it's not my kid and they ended up when they buried
them they didn't bury them when they put them in coffins they were glass the
coffins had a glass lid it was an airtight coffin and for a year both
these people were available for viewing you could just be like hey I family we're
bored live what do you want to do Jane do John do yeah yeah we'll go see the
Does again yeah you could go see these corpses at your local morgue and then
after a year of that they buried them now they've done DNA testing they're not
brother and sister they're not brother and sister they know that for sure but
they still have no idea who these people are where they came from so and I
guess this should say this they don't know who murdered them whoever murdered
them is still on the loose Henry Lee Lucas kind of alluded to him that he
might have done that he was a prolific serial killer but people have said now
he's making it up because he made a bunch of stuff up he didn't know any
details about it he was just like well I was in the county that day but so there's
no leads on who killed him there's no leads on who these people were his out
found dead in the middle of a field by side of road so what does any of this
have to do with anything I don't know now you could go Jason you this is just a
lark or some creepy pasta that you fell for and that's definitely possible
definitely possible people fall for stuff all the time myself included but
this is also the way this is the way that weirdos communicate nowadays right
like yes it could be an art project and someone's like I'm gonna pick the super
obscure case make much of heads float around and stuff like that this guy
could also be super mentally deranged now people on the reddit Bureau of
Investigation were like maybe it's the killer for this guy to have killed him
back then let's assume most serial killers let's assume they're the youngest
kills are around their mid to late teens so let's say this guy was 18 and 1976 who
murdered these two people that would make him about 60 something now which I
guess isn't too old to use Instagram but it's possible that the person who did
this is now posting this stuff and learned basic photoshoppers getting his
nephew to do it yeah uncle why do you want me to do all this creepy stuff oh I
don't know son brings back memories and if he's like no I'm glad I'm getting
paid enough to get a new computer and then I'm out and the uncle's hiding oh
you'll be out all right you'll be out of sight if he's like dude I can hear you
stand right behind me click I'm all done dude leaves nephew runs out another
victim I don't know why I'm doing creepy uncle now look anyways the point is it's
possible that the killer is announcing this on Instagram it's possible they
never caught him it's possible that it's just an ARG someone which is an all
alternate reality game for people who don't know it's some sort of like puzzle
that the internet supposed to figure out and there's just like a interactive
crime or something like that but it's also possible that there is someone who's
obsessed with this crime and is reaching out about it is putting it out on the
internet is adding random people to this because the guy was like I don't know why
my girlfriend got added to this account it's definitely creepy I'm creeped out so
is this just a someone looking for some weird marketing gimmick what are
they what are they selling they for Halloween be this deceased woman's
face weave his mask could be some weirdo looking for attention could be a serial
killer he's letting the world know that he's never been caught or it could be a
budding serial killer someone who's always been fascinated about the two
people found at the side of the road the killer never caught the identities of the
victim never known could be some crazy kid he's been obsessed with that case
since he heard about it and now he's trolling Instagram looking for his next
victim I don't know it's probably it's probably the ARG but I do think it's
creepy do you think it's creepy let's go ahead and go on to our next story go to
that Instagram though and check it out don't harass sauerkraust I'm not asking
you guys to harass sauerkraust but again it is creepy let's go ahead and move on
our next story now Dalton is what you've been waiting for fire up that
carbonicopter we're flying out to Mormon Mesa Nevada now I haven't used the
dead rabbit dune buggy in a while so let's land the carbonicopter we're gonna
park two three miles away from where we're going it's getting the dead rabbit
dune buggy guys Dalton you got the wheel on this one - be we're going over the
dunes I don't know the place could be a rocky desert we're gonna imagine there's
dunes war pups are chasing us from the distance which is normally on Chase's
work they're normally not right next to you that's not a chase that's the end of
the chase we're going out to Mormon Mesa Nevada it's four in the morning spooky
right super spooky time it's July 27th 1952 and there's a man named Truman
Bethrom Truman Bethrom 55 years old he's a mechanic who works for a road
construction crew and at the same time so imagine working with this guy a
spiritual advisor hey Truman hand me that wrench do you really want the wrench
or does the wrench want you damn it Truman just hand me that wrench oh here
you go boss here you go cars are totally falling apart no you must believe the car
works and the car Truman the car we're broke down in the middle of Mormon Mesa
we're in the middle of desert fix it does the car need to be fixed or do you
need a bit of damage room and think okay okay sorry sir actually that'd be
totally awesome work with this guy maybe not work with them I would just show
up at the work site and be like oh dude this is so funny I imagine everyone
else is wearing like mechanic those onesies what are those called like
unitards the overalls the coveralls whatever unitards they're walking around
I would have loved to see much mechanics and unitards wait no I wouldn't I'd want
to see that at all all these guys walking around and their coveralls he's
walking in big shaman robes they keep getting caught in the gears of machine
Truman anyways Truman road construction mechanics slash spiritual
advisor he has a hobby he loves to collect seashells so where would you want
to collect seashells the most you're right in the middle of Nevada which sounds
stupid right but this whole thing about this guy sounds stupid but he wanted
these seashells because you know it used to be like a ocean because Lena like back
in time on the other's water everywhere and then there's like they went away it
is like there's a bunch of icebergs melted and then it filled up the world
full of water and then the icebergs came back I don't know but the water went
back away so there's hope you like that you like that geology lesson kids who
are at home for learning at home like mom dad please let the schools are open
I don't want to learn science from this guy anymore anyways take it taking kids
that's your science lesson for today you get an A all the water goes away now you
have seashells everywhere because they were there for millions and billions of
years he's hanging out now he's walking around this flashlight he's finding
seashells now my question is when I'm reading this why is he doing this at
night right like wouldn't wouldn't it be easier to look for miniature dead life
forms during the day but whatever maybe it's his only time off so he's looking
for seashells eventually he's like I was born this is stupid hobby I shouldn't
have done this my life it sucks he go he gives up he goes to sleep in his truck
and then he should be alone right it's middle of nowhere no one else is
collecting seashells everyone ever literally everyone else has a better
hobby than that and he hears a mumbling talking outside his car he's like what
now he it's a foreign language doesn't he can't make it can't make it out but
he comically pokes his little eyes and nose up over the door thingy so he can
look out the window you know the the driver's side window and he sees ten
people or are they people now he describes them he goes they look like
normal people but they were short they're all either they were all four to five
feet in height he says they weren't dwarfs they just were short humans and
he sees them kind of gathered around his truck mumbling in this foreign language
and then he kind of shakes his head and then he hears them perfectly talking
English opens up his car door jumps out apparently he's five hundred pounds on
the car shakes when he gets out and when he jumps out and now he sees about 75
yards away now that he has full vision the roof of the cars not blocking his
vision 75 yards away he sees a UFO floating there so he takes he's a go
get it right he's a mechanic / spiritual advisor he doesn't wait for no one he
jumps out of the car and he goes which one of you is the captain the guys look
at each other and they go well huh our captain is on that ship over there that
that's yeah I know what the only UFO within within orbit right now that yeah I
know what ship you're talking about aliens are like yeah that one would you
like to go and meet the captain it's like yeah totally let's go there this is
how to describe the aliens quote Latin types that is with complexion something
like Italians oh so you know those little just little dark-skinned dudes
walking around it's so funny because that's pretty specific it's like you
know they're kind of dark-skinned specifically those from northern Italy
I would say more around the province of Vo like dude like okay fine there's just
dark-skinned humans but or darker skin humans compared to him but anyways then
he goes on quote all were neatly dressed in uniforms we've heard that before
right up not finished all were neatly dressed in uniforms similar to those
worn by greyhound bus drivers now come on like you have interstellar travel right
you have the ability to bend the universe and you're like you're wearing
like a gray suit little clip-on tie little collar and stuff like that these
are elements that would make me think this is a dream at least with like grey
aliens on the holographic suits the armor plating or the robots we've seen
stuff that seems out of this world that makes you think oh maybe it might be
something to it this guy's brain seems to be picking stuff out of his subconscious
however there are arguments that aliens are so bizarre that sometimes you'll
look at them and your brain can only perceive what you could recognize and
things like that so we're gonna assume the story is true though just for the
sake of how bonkers this whole man's life gets anyways he says they're all
beautiful they didn't look old at all they had no creases or wrinkles or
nothing which actually makes me think they kind of look like Odo from Deep
Space Nine which is not an attractive looking alien he passed away then and
not the alien he's still alive in the books but that actor Renee Aubrey
Jonas yeah that sucked it early like that guy he's on Vincent I used to watch
him way back then and Deep Space Nine is one of my favorite shows anyways and I
wonder why my episodes get longer and longer he gets on to the UFO
now he's hanging out with these ten dudes on the ship classic UFO layout
bunch of like blinking lights and control panels and stuff like that but then we
meet someone that we meet very rarely in UFO lore we meet a bombshell
[Bomb Shell]
aura, rain, tight, skirt, dressed in all red, big ol' alien boobies, long black
flowing hair, perfect olive Latin complexion with not a wrinkle or a crease
but she's sexy she doesn't look like Odo she looks like a goddess she liked
that music there so anyways that's aura reigns now you know true man he's a
married man but come on man when you meet the most beautiful woman in the
universe what are you gonna do he immediately falls in love with aura
reigns now he's thinking this chick is super hot this chick and he turns to the
camera is out of this world and the audience is like yeah yeah yeah and he
goes okay so can I meet your captain and she's kind of stares at him dumbfounded
for a second she goes oh no no no I am the captain turns to the camera beauty
and smarts yay audience claps so anyways she's the captain of this spaceship the
hottest chick in the universe is also in charge who doesn't like that so basically
then we get the kind of UFO backstory stuff she says the aliens are from the
planet Clarion that's from the opposite side of the Sun there's another planet
on the other side of the Sun which is actually an old myth because if something
was on the other side of the Sun we would never know it all of our satellites
orbit Earth like we can't technically we can but we've never really like as far
as I know launch the rocket to see the other side of the Sun that people said
that if there was something on the other side of the Sun we would detect the
gravity of it but that's been a myth that there's an other Earth this one's
called Clarion it's an earth where they have listen to how amazing this place is
no wars no strife no juvenile delinquency they said that planet Earth is the
only planet in the galaxy that has strife and the reason why we can never do
interplanetary travel is because of our strife once we learn to be peaceful we
can travel the universe with beauties like ororanes now you're thinking Jason
that sounds brilliant I want to go there right now I'm gonna jump off her I'm
gonna get on space soon I'm gonna jump off Earth and we're gonna stay there so
the planet Clarion floats and I'm gonna land on there that is a good idea and
100% scientifically accurate but let me finish telling you now now that is a
great thing right I shouldn't mind my no wars who are those lame those dude I
love stabbing guys with sticks yeah war is awesome war does is not fun it's
fascinating as it is to read about in history books it's not fun I love a
planet where they was just all in history but before you go that sounds
awesome you got it also remember those the 1950s we're talking about 1950s so
this is their paradise in the 1950s when this story is happening so Truman has
some other tidbits of how amazing this world is with no juvenile delinquency no
war no strife every single person on the planet is Christian there is no liquor
at all on the planet at all and you're like Jason that's fine I'm born again
Christian and I don't drink yeah yeah me too but that might get us to jump off
earth and float around but then we get to these next two ones the only music is
polka and the only type of dance is square dance so for Truman that might
have been a complete paradise people are like honey pack the bags we're going to
Clarion it sounds amazing I don't think I can be on a I absolutely know for if
I'm Christian but I cannot be on a planet where everybody was Christian you
gotta have like some sort of like diversity and stuff like that right but
anyway so that was Truman's that was Truman's most amazing society I wonder
if they had like marijuana he's like no liquor but methamphetamine for everyone
there's just meth needles falling from the sky you're like ah I'm a Christian but
I'm so I am tweaking tweaking for Jesus yeah like why just no liquor like there's
so many other damaging drugs out there that are worse than liquor there's no
liquor but here's some crocodile everyone's limbs are rotting anyways the
point is that it was this paradise so this newspaper so he has dropped back off
on earth right everything's hunky-dory has to tell us a story now that rhyme now
he tells the story he does tell the story to the media there's a newspaper in
the redondo beach called the Daily Breeze in September 25th 1953 they published
this story and it was such a huge hit such a huge hit I wish other newspapers
said this is kind of awesome they had a vote for who what was the best story we
had this year and we'll reprint it and this story won a best story of the year
so on October 3rd just like a month later they reprinted it in whole people
loved this story back in the day now usually when people get abducted by
aliens it kind of affects their life like they get abducted by aliens and they
realize that we're all interconnected and there's a universal brotherhood and I
shouldn't hate people based on things like race or nationally stuff like that
we're all connected sometimes and it leaves them with a deep-seated fear of
the beyond sometimes they remember it sometimes they just have visions of it
terrifies them he just gets super horny he decides that he's totally in love
with aura range that that is his soulmate now he was already a mechanic
spiritual advisor now he's going full bore to be the spiritual advisor and his
1950s wife is up to here Truman I'm up to here with your Babylon and your UFO and
your aura this and your aura that she actually divorces him she specifically
divorces him because he's in love with another woman he's in love with aura
Reigns he cannot let her go now he's just kind of hanging out doesn't have
anyone in his life except his secretary he hires a secretary because now he
started a cult called the sanctuary of thought in Prescott Arizona he has this
compound he hires a secretary to work with him she walks in the interview room
he's looking down at the paper he's like what are your qualifications miss looks
up curvy all of skin woman hires her simply because she looks like aura
Reigns now guys you shouldn't be thanking with the lower half of your body
you're gonna make bad decisions now I would like to say that because he hired
her she was comically inept and she's like you told me to balance the books
boss but I was walking over the Grand Canyon and they fell down
secretary I love you but I don't know maybe she was actually competent at her
job and looked like a hot space alien but he went on to start writing books
because he got a lot of publicity out of this thing a lot of publicity out of
this thing started writing books about Clarion started writing books about
UFOs and spiritual and stuff he ends up passing away like all men do 1969 he
lived to be 70 years old and he never became reunited with the true love of
his life sure he hired a woman who looked an awful lot like her but it's not
the same right however however
we're gonna do it to be continued on this episode because not only do I have a
story that's not very well known of him meeting aura Reigns again but possible
proof possible proof that the aliens not only met him on Mormon Mesa but they
left a calling card we'll discuss that tomorrow on Dead Rabbit Radio
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit
us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio Twitter is @deadrabberadio
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime
podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to
it today be safe be kind I love you guys and I'll see you tomorrow
you
(upbeat music)