We've all heard the saying snitches get stitches, but in the country of Malta, snitches get
a monument built to them.
And then we travel to Ohio to meet a haunted VW bug that has one mission.
Not teenagers from having sex today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
And before we get into that, let's go ahead and introduce our Thanksgiving livestream
show financially I totally understand just helps spread the word about the show
that also really really helps out a lot now Allison's wake is bringing us in
Ally sat down this big giant box of beef jerky and I'm gonna eat it all I
actually just broke fast I took a 48 our fast that I just broke before doing
the podcast I wanted to do 72 hours but the other part of my crazy days I got
prescribed all of these steroids for this tooth issue I'm having so I don't
know a ton about steroids but I do know you can't take them on an empty
stomach so I did break fast at 48 hours and the reason why I'm telling you guys
about this I'm flexing on you guys it's a little bit of a brag but I would like
you guys to try fasting now there's a lot of health benefits to it and stuff
on you know you guys know me I'm not a big health nut that's probably why he
constantly needs steroids for my body to keep functioning and I'm not a big
health nut this is the reason why I fast one I figure it is personal
endurance and I like being able to brag I can go two days without eating but
secondly that's what you brag about you have a hit podcast you have a hit
podcast and that's what you're going around telling people I think about it
this way alien drop ships appear in the sky people are blowing up world leaders
please please kill the populace not me I'm famous all these like alien foot
soldiers are walking through the streets just blasted dudes I will not have to
eat for two days like I can go at least two days I was out walking I did all my
normal stuff I was going to work I'm walking everywhere I walked down to the
Walmart to get my prescription all that stuff if I would be able to go two days
without eating and I think most people wouldn't and when I say most people I
mean most people are like the modern world I know there's a lot of parts of
the planet where they don't eat every day but you need to be prepared you need
to be prepared when President Joe Biden begs for the aliens not to kill him that
may happen so if you're not this is actually like I think Alex Jones is
always trying to sell you supplements I'm trying to sell you nothing literally
don't do anything if your diet allows it obviously I don't want to be get
accused of killing a bunch of people a diabetes people or something if you can't
go two days without fasting medically don't don't don't die please but if you
won't kill you try it I always think it's interesting to see what the human
body can do what your human body can do there's my tummy rumbling so I don't
know if the microphone picked it up the microphone is sensitive if you hear lots
of noises that's probably what it is but let's see if you can do it maybe start
off with just a 24-hour fast but dude because when those aliens start coming
when the zombies invade or maybe it'll just be something lame like a civil war
or something and the tornado boo think about it right now if something bad
happened I wouldn't be immediately looking for food which is a good thing
because I've stated several times on this podcast pretty much from like episode
seven I'm willing to eat other humans if my back is to the wall so now knowing
that I can go at least two days to active days to new in my normal routine
days when no food means if you and I are ever trapped in a scenario I will not
eat you for two days
Allison's is super nervous they're bringing in even more beef jerky I don't know
Allison's you're looking pretty good Ali I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the oars
to the dead rabbit robot we're gonna leave behind dead rabbit command we're
gonna row all the way out to Malta splash splash rowing all the way out
there long-time listeners of dead rabbit radio know that dead rabbit radio is the
number one science podcast in El Salvador from time to time someone else
some real science podcast gets rid of us not just up the top but generally we're
at least on the top five but a lot of times we're the number one science
podcast in El Salvador another bizarre flex but I'll take it well recently the
country of Malta has jumped up and for a while I was the number one science
podcast in Malta so I was like okay I already gave my El Salvador bros some
respect by doing a story about a man who had sex with a donkey making a little
donkey baby what can I give to my Malta minions what can I give them is there
anything going on in Malta that fits the theme of this show we are now in Malta
specifically we're in the town of Saint Julian's and it's about like the mid
1700s so get on your old timey clothes like your pantaloons and like your big
old hat everything super rule and like itchy and stuff and we're walking down
the streets of Saint Julian's and take my shirt off because I'm itching too much
we're walking around and in between San Juan not San Juan San Juan and a place
called Berquerara there's there's a two different neighborhoods there's like
this road going in between those two places and one day there's this dude
just sitting on the street kind of just hanging out reading a newspaper where
newspapers around at 1700 and there's like wood carvings of like people like
herding cows and eating wheat whatever made the news back in the 1700s and this
dude where so this guy reading the newspaper we're gonna call him Tommy so
Tommy's sitting there and he's reading this newspaper and a guy comes running
by oh no oh no oh no oh no and Tommy's like what what in the world was that and
he sees this guy kind of running and he ducks down an alley Tommy goes on it's
kind of weird but let me go back to reading this giant wood carving and then a
couple minutes later this other guy's kind of like jogging jogging down the
road and he sees Tommy reading these wood carvings and he goes hey pardon me sir
pardon me sorry to interrupt your your news reading but did you happen to see
some dude run by and Tommy thinks about it he looks down the street and he goes
yeah yeah yeah there was some guy like just kind of like distraught look like
he was in a lot of trouble and the dude standing up his eyes go from side to
side he's like trouble I don't know what you're talking about you know where he
went you know where this man went Tommy goes yeah yeah he went down the street
a bit and then he turned left going down that alleyway the gentleman goes well
thank you very much for your service sir I will let you get back to reading the
paper the next day Tommy wakes up oh he's milking cows and eating wheat and
then he gets his picture carved into the newspaper the most exciting man in
Malta that day and he's reading the newspaper and he turns and it says
murder he's like ah and it says a man was murdered in between San Juan in
Burkara down this alleyway and he's like oh my god oh my god I can't believe what
happened any pieces it together he realized which you realized he snitched
the dude out this guy was running for his life and he's told this other dude
where he's at and and the dude got stabbed to death in this alleyway and he's
like bleeding out and stuff like that he's like any time now why Tommy didn't
hear the man getting brutally murdered down the street I don't know there's
some questions I have about the story but this story is so famous in Malta
that not only did they build a giant monument you know in America at least
when there's a car accident they'll put like a little cross in the road a little
wooden cross and teddy bears bite and stuff like that it's like that but it's
it's made of stone it's permanent it's about 15 feet tall at the top is a
crucifix is this giant pillar and even today people put like flowers by people
stop and use it as this monument it's called Ratch Mock Ratch you smash Mott
smash now if you are one of my listeners from Malta you can go ahead and
correct me because I can guarantee there's some weird letters in there
there's some X's in there I don't know if the X is silent but what this means in
English is this this pillar is called I saw I didn't see and I heard I didn't
hear so basically keep your mouth shut if you see something say nothing the
month the story is very famous the monuments very famous and at one point
you kind of think maybe this is an urban legend maybe this pillar was here and
someone made up the story behind it no this is very well known in Malta
culture there's actually a pop song about it written by a dude named Tony
Camilleri and the name of the song was I don't see I don't hear and it just
basically is like here let me read you some of the lyrics I live in punishment
I live because I did not control my tongue I didn't see it I didn't hear it
this is the warning written on the wall I didn't see it I didn't hear it see what
you see hear what you hear don't talk to anyone don't talk to anyone I don't
think a rapper could write stronger snitches get stitches there and he
didn't get the stitches the other dude got stitches it's weird because the
moral of the story is keep your mouth shut which generally in societies like
in America and Britain they have that whole if you see something say something
this is the opposite right but it is ingrained into that culture if you see
something maybe just maybe just don't tell anyone really fascinating story and
it's what I was looking up like true crime in Malta this was one of the ones
that popped up a lot the murder of this man and the lesson is keep your keep your
mouth shut for me I grew up in bad neighborhoods right snitches get stitches
wasn't just a phrase it was an actual thing you have to worry about and I
always saw it like this because it was so funny because my friends are like dude
we just can't tell when you can tell what your view is on law enforcement my
view always was there been time ever once this dude took this little girl
hostage and they were doing this hostage situation it was up where was this
it was in art and fair I think out in Sacramento and the cops had surrounded
the apartment complex they were there for two days everyone was watching it on
the news and I go you know what those cops must be awfully thirsty so I went
and got like two or three 24 packs of soda I got two 24 packs of soda and a
24 pack of water and I pulled up to the line of where all the police were and I
went to go give them the sodas and the officer goes oh I appreciate that he I
think he took some waters because I appreciate that but it's we we solved
it everything's good and I was like okay and then as I'm driving home the radio
was like the police what they did was they got a sniper and they were able to
have all the infrared stuff to see through the wall I mean he was holding
like a three-year-old girl hostage for like two days and the sniper shot a
bullet right through the wall and blew his head off right in front of the kid I
mean the kid was gonna be traumatized either way but they shot him through the
wall they could see him through the wall and so yeah they didn't need sodas
they're all going home to their families so on that like nobody's pro holding
three-year-old kids hostage but there's other I had other interactions with the
police that in we're far less friendly overall so my my goal my always goal is
this is that I think it's wrong to snitch if you're part of a criminal
enterprise and you get caught and snitching reduces your sentence you're
gonna get stitches if you're part of a criminal enterprise and you're making
money off of that criminal enterprise but they start blowing you off or they
start sleeping with your girlfriend or something dumb and you snitch on them
snitches get stitches that's on you if you're a civilian if you're outside of
an organization or you have nothing to do with the money making you're driving
home and you see a crime that to me was never snitches get stitches now that
depended on the dependent on the particular gangster who was involved in
that situation for me snitches get stitches is that's where you're working
with them there are other times I've obviously dealt with law enforcement
because I see someone doing this someone doing that the web is a probably a couple
weeks ago some dudes are beating some woman up and some dude some random guy
outside of bar I called the cops I'm 45 years old I'm not gonna go out there and
and tussle with a bunch of 19 year olds a bunch of drunk 19 year olds in the
middle of the street I'm not gonna do that I walk outside these guys are beating
up this dude and this girl the dude and the girl are holding their own honestly
and I just do hello yeah this is me know me the cops know me as Jason hey I got
a fight under my name was getting in their car but I don't know and then I
talked to the girls for a bit and that was that so I don't consider that snitches
get stitches that's something where I think you could easily say you see
something say something like that it's always a tricky thing though I also know
I've never been this has never happened to me but I also know of people who have
snitched and they did not work out well for him I actually know of people I got
to be careful how much they talk about this but I actually know of people whose
family members snitched and they had to like quit their job and move away like
I'm hanging out with this dude and a relative of his snitched and this dude
was like hey dude I'll see you later or never again like I have to leave the
state I was like hey what's going on and he told me this crazy story about how
his buddy or how his relative did this and then went to the police about this
and then him and his family were in danger to the point that they had to
leave people were trying to actively kill them like actively kill them because
something that is really so it's always an interesting I mean when you're on the
outside is interesting I hope that friend of mine is doing fine but yeah that was
years ago that was years ago so yes niches get stitches is a famous famous
phrase and Malta it's the opposite keep your mouth shut it's just an
interesting story it's keep your mouth shut and that's that's not what your
government would want I'm surprised this story is still around it seems counter
intuitive that the government would want to keep this story around but
Allison's I'm gonna give you the keys of the carbonic copter we're leaving
behind Malta we're headed all the way out to Ohio
and as we're headed out there I want to do a really really quick dead rabbit
recommends speaking of alien evasions this is what kind of why I'm singing about
alien evasions I watched the dopest movie the I've watched a lot of great
movies recently this one I just watched like two days ago and it jumped to the
top of my list of movies I wanted to talk about it's a Netflix exclusive it's a
Netflix exclusive movie starring Michael Pina who's been in like everything he's
he's just this great character actor he's been in a ton of movies it's called
extinction and it's I love alien invasion movies when they're done right
same thing I love about zombie movies or pandemic movies because it's about the
end of the world asteroids coming down all this type of stuff and how people
are dealing with the end of the world and it's a great alien invasion movie with
a twist Michael Pina is kind of like a dad on the cusp of a failing marriage
his kids don't like him he works at like some CERN type laboratory as like an
engineer and he begins to have dreams visions of an alien invasion he keeps
seeing people just getting shot in the streets and all these drop ships coming
down in the cities and people just getting gunned down and he's at work and
he has a vision of himself like beating someone to death with his hands he's
having these horrible visions about the future and his wife is just like listen
you're just going crazy please please get this treated me and the kids can't
deal with this anymore so he goes to the psychiatrist's office and while he's in
the office there's another patient sitting next to him there and like in
the waiting room and the other dude turns to Michael Pina and goes you're not
crazy I see the aliens - I've seen the visions and they're coming and you're
like oh dude this movie's really dope because not only is it a really tight
alien invasion movie it goes it's like an hour and a half long but it moves so
quickly not only is it a really good alien invasion movie you have the
mystery is how does he know the future and I'll tell you right now as I was
watching I was like oh I hope it's not that this is also a vision and he's gonna
wake up and he's like oh now I know what's going to happen like invasion from
Mars or something like that no it's not a twist that it's all a dream you have
this really cool alien invasion movie where they are gunning people down on
the streets it is like block by block alien invasion mixed with the mystery
how does he know how did he know this was going to happen really really tight
movie reminded me of a short science fiction story that I would have read
some Saturday afternoon when I was a teenager like I it's such a good sci-fi
adventure it's actually quite grim I don't know if I'd call it an adventure
but Dead Rabbit recommends extinction on Netflix really really recommend that
movie I said recently that the exports been putting out a lot of quality stuff
and they have the guy who's writing the story had an uncle when he was growing up
he had a great uncle who would always tell him about local urban legends and
where we're at is in Buckeye Lake Ohio and he goes Michael tell me stuff like
Crybaby bridge you know that's very typical story we've covered stuff like
that on the show before the grass man of Ohio which is basically like a big foot
a type of creature all these all these local urban legends and there was one
story that this poster had heard that intrigued him for years and he actually
tried finding more information on it he could never get any more info on it he
goes I kind of think that my great uncle might have made it up but I don't know he
goes it's so weird that it I can't find any proof of any of it so maybe my uncle
made it up but he also knew all about all these other urban legends why would he
make this one up if all the other ones can be traced to something back in the
late 1950s in the town of mountain Vernon a bright blue Volkswagen Beetle
comes driving into town and inside this beetle was a father will call him Jake
and his daughter will call her Alyssa and they're driving down the road the
relationship between Jake and Alyssa was so stereotypical is so cliche but it is
realistic he was a devout Christian man who ruled the house right a man's home
is his castle and everyone has to do what he says and he follows the one boss
the big boss in the sky he is a devout Christian she is a rebellious teenager
she wants to dress how she dresses and listen to the music what she wants to
listen to he's like I want to listen to checkberry he's like oh that's so
rebellious and she wants to date who she wants to date now the one person that
united this family is passed away this is like a real life the righteous
gemstones they no longer have this unifying force you just have two people
that are on different paths but the rebellious girl is living with her dad
and my house my rules Jake always said so they would constantly fight
she was gonna follow the rules but she also couldn't afford to get her own
place they're constantly fighting it was a house full of torment and it came to
a head when the father one day found out that Alyssa was dating a 20-something
year-old man he flips out Jake totally flips out because listen you know this
is a recipe for disaster the dude's not gonna stick around at best he's just
gonna break your heart at worst he's gonna knock you up it's gonna be this
huge thing so Jake forbids his daughter from ever seeing this guy again and
Alyssa in the throes of teenage love doesn't care doesn't listen to the dad
she needs to keep being with this dude right which is the dumb decision but
again very very cliche because it happens all the time Jake actually thinks
that it's solved though he think he actually got through to his daughter but
one day when he was rummaging through her room apparently he finds a pair of
men's boxers kind of stuffed away in the back of her closet so Alyssa's at
school and and Jake is enraged he can't believe that this is a crime even in the
1950s I'm pretty sure you weren't allowed to be 25 years old dating a 15-year-old
I'm not for sure but I hope it was against the law he decides to confront
this boyfriend so while Alyssa's at school he jumps in his bright blue beetle
and Jake is driving through town going to this boy's house he's going to
probably kill this guy for sleeping with his teenage daughter but he doesn't get
the opportunity to he doesn't get the sweet sweet satisfaction of strangling
a man who did you wrong on his way to this boyfriend's house he blows through
a stoplight the truck slams into him and he dies at the scene
police show up taking reports ambulance shows up they're like what was
supposed to do he's dead I don't know we're throwing the gurney so they put
him in the gurney and then the tow truck shows up eat eat eat and they take their
wreckage of the blue beetle to like a holding area and then eventually to a
scrapyard where they're like put it in the box thing it's not really good
people who work at the scrapyard they don't know what anything's called the
workers are like what is the box thing they just tumble the car around till
they get to the compactor that's what I meant that makes more sense and the blue
beetle is getting crushed until it's now like a little cube and hoisted up put
the cube put the cube on the box they're like dude quick calling stuff boxes
everything's a box stuff gets turned into boxes here you're fired you can't work
here anymore so the blue beetle is crushed to bits and the story of Alyssa
we never really know what happens to her did she stay with her boyfriend was
she she overcome with emotion at the loss of her father does she decide to
dedicate her life to Christ we don't know any of this stuff because that would
be an involved character development and human interest instead the story goes
like this a couple weeks later these two teenagers are making out in the woods
near Mount Vernon mm-hmm oh Terry you're so sexy oh thank you Bruce I'm they're
kissing and they see some headlights in the distance now like oh maybe that's
the cops coming to break us up and then they go wait a second no because unless
the cops started driving Volkswagen bugs there's not the cops and they were
looking at this blue Volkswagen Beetle sitting on the road and then it starts
going and it starts driving on the road towards them now I used to have a
Volkswagen bug they're very iconic cars so they're very fuel efficient they are
not they are not knowing for their speediness though but these teenagers
claim that they were chased through the forest through the forest no paved road
the car begins to chase them through the forest yeah this Volkswagen bug is like
going like driving over roots and it's a little goalies and stuff like that but
they report to the police we were making out and a car chased us through the
woods and the police are like okay that's weird we'll put that down on our
paperwork but hope that doesn't happen to you again I'm trying to get it a little
bit more than that they're like what attempted kidnapping will all write that
down but hopefully it doesn't happen again stories start to spread around town
of teenagers in their bedroom oh my parents are out of town Johnny you want
to get to third base he's like well that's really aggressive do you know what
third base actually means she's like I do I do and she starts undressing do you
guys you guys know what third base is it's it's up there called third base
for a reason as she begins undressing she begins taking off her bra and then she's
trying to show off her headlights but instead headlights illuminate the room
from outside ah it's blinding and the guy would look out the window and there
would be a bright blue Volkswagen bug sitting in the street it's headlights
shining on the teenagers ah cut it out man cut it out I'm trying to have sex
with this chick it starts happening all over town teenagers start saying whenever
I start taking my clothes off before I'm about to make some whoopee headlights
appear through the window and I look outside and there's this bright blue
Volkswagen bug teenagers start reporting the blue bug following them around
town whether they're driving with their snuggle bunny or just walking down the
street holding hands
bright blue Volkswagen bug behind them and then there are some that say that this
car is not a simple voyeur it's not just tracking down these people or slowly
pursuing them through the forest as fast as a Volkswagen bug can drive through a
forest people start to realize that teens are going missing in the town of
mountain Vernon now some of them you could chalk up to runaway some of them
you could chalk up to them just going on getting tired of their home joining the
military whatever but there are some who say that the blue beetle itself was
kidnapping and killing young teenage lovers the story is known as the sex
hating Volkswagen of Mount Vernon Ohio it's interesting because the way that
the story was presented to us again was I don't know if this story is true but
all these other stories my great uncle told me I was able to find verification
of it would be one thing if he was like and that was the time I stopped the
leprechaun from ending World War two if he was making stuff up you think you'd
have more made-up stuff so the legend may be true in the sense that the great
uncle didn't make it up but they that he had simply heard it as an urban legend
himself but even going one step further in the world of the paranormal this
makes sense this is something that could happen in the world of the paranormal
because it's really fascinating because what we have is a vengeful spirit the
father who was trying really what he was trying to do yeah he was probably a
little overbearing but at the end of the day he was trying to save his daughter
she was in a relationship with a much much older man who was taking advantage
of her right so despite that he might have come down a little little heavy
and he wasn't gonna murder the guy we have a man who feels like he has to do
this to take care of his family and he dies in that rage he dies in that moment
so a vengeful spirit a wraith totally fits with ghost lore as we know it and
if the car itself the mechanical structure of the car was possessed by a
ghost we see that as well not necessarily with cars but we see dolls possessed by
ghost and paintings possessed by ghost I have a friend who says that her lamp is
possessed by a ghost it's not really her lamp she bought it from a thrift store
but the point is is that the idea of a ghost possessing an inanimate object is
very very accepted within the paranormal lore but remember this car was
destroyed this is a really interesting story because we have a vengeful spirit
taking the form of the car it was almost like he had infused the physical
being of this vehicle with his rage so when he returned to earth as the spirit
it wasn't him just walking around town which to be honest wouldn't be super
intimidating I mean okay if I was trying to have sex in the woods with some hot
chick and some dude starts walking towards me I'm gonna run I'm gonna get
her take her take her and I run away but it'd be far more scary right to be
chased by a car remember that old movie Wraith was kind of about that was
about the guy who died in the car accident and then drove around running
people over it's really a movie who was in it like Richard Greco or Robert Downey
Jr. or somebody anyways you did have recommends Wraith I saw it when I was
12 maybe it's the holds up the idea of a ghost taking the form of a car chasing
people down this all fits with the lore so while the story may have been made up
it's possible that it was real and when we go back to the 1950s if this was
something that teenagers were reporting obviously it sounds really really dumb
so no parent is going to take this seriously and actually now they think
about it they wouldn't be reporting this right like the couple in the woods
would have told the authorities because they were almost killed but no one's
gonna be like mom mom you won't believe what happened when me and Johnny were
trying to have sex last night she's like wait wait what you wouldn't you would
this would be spreading from teenager to teenager that's how the story would be
being told so it's possible that this poster is great uncle was a teenager at
this time and was hearing these stories it wouldn't be something you would
announce to the world because all of these kids are doing something that they
shouldn't be doing right trying to have sex I mean I'm not saying sex is bad
but obviously teenagers the longer you can postpone having sex the better off
you're going to be especially if there's a killer car on the loose so the point is
is that you could have this phantom in this form of this car stalking the city
of Mount Vernon trying to stop teenagers from having sex and if we accept the
story as true and it does fit into Ghost Lore it's possible the VW bug is still
out there Roman these streets if this is a super obscure story it would be one of
those things it's kind of the plot of it's kind of the plot of Nightmare on Elm
Street right they erased all knowledge of Freddy Kruger and that was fine for
about 30 years but then the kids started having dreams about this guy and asking
who's Freddy Kruger the parents are like oh so it's possible that this legend did
happen and people just forgot about it it was whispered among teens and then they
grew up and then they go oh maybe that wasn't real I always do wonder what
happened to Tiffany she went missing that one day but I don't know go about me
that's the cop investigating the crime I don't know someone else will figure it
out everyone moves on with their life but this Volkswagen bug is still out there
looking for teenagers about to have sex trying to scare them off but when that
fails trying to chase them off and when that fails killing them so next time
you're driving down the road on the way to your special loved ones house you got
a box of condoms you're very very optimistic you have a box of condoms in
your glove compartment you're driving over to your special ladies house make
sure to check in that rear view mirror see if you're being followed look in
that rear view mirror because there might be a set of headlights behind you but
it's just the mailman for some reason he's delivering mail see real late a
night you know he passes you and go whoo and then you get to her house and you
bring in a shopping bag full of condoms and you set him down on the table honey
I'm home and she's like ooh and then you see some headlights outside your window
and you're like ah you look out and it's it's old farmer John on his tractor just
going by you're like what that's weird tractor noises and then you go to the
bedroom with your lovely lady and you're like hey you know what third basis I
heard on her podcast and run entirely for sure and she goes take me and she
throws herself down on the bed and right when you get on top of your lovely
lady to make sweet sweet passionate love to her you hear the closet door creak
open you turn and the cat walks out of the closet you're like stop listening to
this paranormal podcast before I have sex with my girlfriend obviously I'm very
very paranoid and you were able to make sweet love with your girlfriend and
everything's great and you go through the bag and then you go to the store to buy
some more condoms and then you run out of those and then eventually it's Dawn
is three weeks later and you've been late for work you've been fired and you're
walking out to your car and you're driving home with a big smile on your
face and you see another set of headlights behind you and you're like oh
that's probably just the mailman or the tractor or the cat but instead it's a
bright blue Volkswagen bug you might not be a teenager you might not be having
illicit sex with someone you shouldn't be with but to a vengeful spirit from
beyond the grave those are just trivialities you have now run afoul of
the sex-hating Volkswagen bug there's nowhere to run there's nowhere to hide
it will get you it will take you away to the bad place soon you find yourself
freezing cold in a junkyard made out of desiccated human remains you're like
wow this escalated fast and as the compactor starts to press in on you
no no I want to live longer let me get laid at least 10 more times and as the
very last thing that pops is your eyeball you have one eyeball and right
before it pops you see a Volkswagen bug it's like Lightning McQueen it's
operating the gears of the compactor with its wheel hands it's like gotta go
fast and then the eyeball gets squished and you're totally dead you became the
latest victim of the sex-hating Volkswagen bug if it existed it still
exists if it was a vengeful ghost trying to prevent people from having sex
it's still continuing that mission to this day the only question is will you
become its next victim or will you or will you have stayed from sex forever
the choice the choice is yours and then radio a gmail.com is going to be our
email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
tiktok is @DeadRabbitRadio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but
I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys
(upbeat music)
[Music]