Are the highways of Mexico becoming a real-life example of Mad Max's apocalyptic road warfare?
And then we take a look at a battle that everybody knows but nobody remembers.
And then we take a look back to the conspiracy iceberg for the theory known as French Viper Releases.
Were farmers really telling the truth that poisonous snakes were being dumped all over their countryside?
Or was it just another case of mass hysteria?
We'll get to the truth today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. It's Friday and it's funny, I don't know why I said it like that.
It's funny because I was saying that this week's recommendation week, but just to clarify, we're going to be doing a lot of recommendations.
I'm really going to just kind of in season four be going through more of those because I got a lot of them backed up.
But first off, I want to start off with the story that I saw in the news recently.
Headline was very evocative. It's a very short story, but I think it's definitely one that's really interesting to cover.
The headline was Mexican truckers fight highway robbery with armored semis.
Now obviously, I immediately pictured a like, Fury Road where the semis have like bus-saw weapons.
[Ring ring]
Shopping up cars running next to them, but they're having a real problem in Mexico with highway robbery.
They get 30 a day. The semi-truck... It's not like... Yeah, why do they call them semi-trucks?
Is it only because it's only half a truck and then you attach the other part on the back?
Or is a semi a different type of engine? Like a Hemi, but with an S?
I think it's actually a semi because it's only half a truck, right? And then you attach the trailer in the back.
Semis, the semi-truck company, they spend in Mexico for security. 6% of their revenue was spent on security on their trucks.
The global average is 0.5%. That's how bad it is down there with highway robberies.
That's an astronomical... It's not technically astronomical. You can do the math, but it's a very, very high upgrade of money being spent for security in Mexico.
So at this point, the insurance company says, "We're not going to ensure your transportation company unless you get armored semis."
Most bulletproof, quote unquote bulletproof glass is only bulletproof versus handguns.
It takes another type of stronger material to be resistant to like rifle fire.
And the insurance companies are like, "No, no, no, no, you don't need the handgun glass. You need to make your cars impervious to AK-47 fire."
And the transportation companies are saying, "Well, we need the insurance where there's 30 robberies a day."
30 robberies a day since 2015, by the way. This isn't a recent thing. It's not just happening this month.
So they've had to start heavily armoring their semis. And they tell the driver, "Trust the truck. You stay in the truck, you're not going to get killed."
When you get in, the little stairs disappear into the truck.
And no one can get in the truck. As long as you don't get out of the truck, if they block you off, just stay in the truck.
We have transponders and stuff like that. We'll get cops out of there or anything like that.
I think it will come to the point where they're going to have to go straight up Mad Max and put spikes on the trucks down there.
And little bus stalls and like have warped pups on the back throw and Molotovs at people.
Because eventually you can say, "Okay, I'll just trust the truck."
And whoever is robbing the trucks are going to have to one-up it. And they're like, "Well, if we can't get in the truck, if we can't get in the semi-part, the cab, with our AK-47s, then we're just going to have to start blowing up the cab."
So there's going to be this weird arms escalation race down there. And they're shipping television sets. They're shipping high-end electronics.
This isn't like they're shipping these aren't armored cars. These are just semi-truck drivers now having to basically get encased in armored car plating.
Not themselves like Robocop, but the cab has to get that hardened so people can buy a flat-screen television set for $99 at Walmart down there.
It's absolutely insane, but I think it's only going to get worse. I think they're just going to start seeing this escalation.
And who knows, in two years from now you could have warped pups international.
They are the number one transportation company in Mexico driving their little dune buggies with all the spikes and stuff like that.
Okay, so let's go ahead and move on to our next story. The next story was one that I found very interesting to me.
It's actually quite fascinating to me. It was so fascinating. I was out with a girl and as she's sitting there smoking a cigarette, I go...
Have you ever heard this story about the battle between the parliamentarians and the royalists?
As she's smoking her cigarette, she's like, "No." That's how excited I was about the story. It wasn't a random girl.
It was a friend of mine, but I was telling people it in real life.
Now you're going to be like, "Jayson, thanks for hyping it up." But anyways.
So, the year... I don't know the exact year. The century? 17th century.
It is the height of the English Civil War.
The war was between the parliamentarians and the royalists who were royal to the king.
And quite fans of Lord Scyth's Royals.
Sorry, that was dumb.
The parliamentarians, their nicknames were called the roundheads, which I think is hilarious because that's how you generally describe every human head.
I'm assuming they had some sort of stupid looking helmet that made their head look rounder.
But if someone's like, "Hey, roundhead!" I'd be like, "Oh, are you talking to me? That is quite apt for the shape of my head."
So anyways, the royalists and the roundheads are going to war. There's this city.
I really hope I wrote it down. I didn't here. Hold on.
Oh, yeah, I did. Here it is.
Clochester. Now at this point people are like, "I know where this story's going, but not everyone does. Don't spoil it. Don't spoil it."
And when in fact everyone's like, "I have no idea where this story's going."
We're the city of Clochester. It is controlled by the royalists.
The roundheads are going to advance on the city.
Now, Clochester has two advantages going for them. It's a hardened target. It's a city that has a ton of weaponry.
So they're not really worried about being invaded. They know that they can repel an invading force.
But they really put their faith in a giant cannon that's posted on this wall, like on this tower of this church.
And it's operator, one-eyed Jack Thompson. One-eyed Jack Thompson.
So you have this church tower, so you had a wide field of view.
This massive cannon, the biggest cannon in the city, probably one of the biggest cannons in the region.
And one-eyed Jack Thompson. Now, one-eyed Jack Thompson had only one eye. That's why he got his nickname.
But he was a crack shot. He knew how to use the cannon. He was a veteran.
There was no way that the roundheads were going to take this city.
They try it, though. The royalists hold them off.
The roundheads keep trying over and over again. And again, a key to their defense was one-eyed Jack Thompson and his massive cannon.
Just launching these cannonballs.
Green grass goes everywhere. Little weeds, leprechauns are getting blown to bits.
And so are much of roundheads as these giant cannonballs are rolling through the ranks, breaking everyone's legs, bouncing off the ground, hitting them in the head, just smacking...
I mean, this cannon was having a devastating effect on the roundheads.
And the roundheads are like, "You know what? We're just going to lay siege."
At this point, we're going to pull back to a certain area. There's lay siege. No one gets in, no one gets out.
Now, it was a range war at a certain point because they wanted to lay siege, but the giant cannon could shoot farther.
So the roundheads are like, "Listen, we can lay siege to this thing, but that thing's going to keep chopping us up."
But what else? We can't take the city right now. We're just going to have to hope we don't get crushed by these giant cannonballs flying at us constantly.
And we can't get our cannons close enough to knock it down.
Seed goes on, and they're like, "Just keep shooting cannonballs at the city. We can't get to this one. We can't destroy this giant one just yet.
Keep laying cannonballs into the city."
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo
And the roundhead general says, "You know what? We've got to take this cannon out."
They don't know how bad it is in the city. They can kind of guess because it's been so long, but they know how bad it is out there when all of their troops are mangled by this giant cannon.
So let's push our cannon forward. They're going to be in the range of 1A Jack Thompson and the giant cannon.
Let's push them forward. We're getting there, and I want every cannon concentrating fire on that tower.
So how many of our guys gets taken out? Because if we don't take this out, if we don't take that tower out, we cannot take the city.
So they moved in their troops, they got their cannons, and just [whistling]
1A Jack Thompson is lobbing these massive cannonballs and just [explosion] blowing up.
But they get enough cannons close enough, and they aim them just right.
[whistling]
When I Jack Thompson looks up, sees a bunch of cannonballs coming at him, turns to the camera and goes, "Today is a good day to die."
[explosion]
The cannonballs miss Jack Thompson and the cannon, but hit the wall underneath, and the church tower collapses.
Now the people in the city are very, very panicked at this point, because that was their death star weapon.
That was the only thing keeping the roundheads from coming in any earlier.
The royalists show up, dust everything off, one of them picks up the crumpled body of 1A Jack Thompson and goes, "Noooo!"
And they're like, "Dude, put them down and help us move this stupid cannon!" Because they got to get that cannon in position.
It's pretty busted up, but at the end of the day it's just a giant cast-iron thing that holds gunpowder and balls.
But like the hinges, the wheels and all that stuff are jacked up.
And they're like, "We gotta move it somewhere. We gotta get it on another wall, and we have to do it now."
So all of the troops are trying to move this cannon. Roundheads are approaching and they're like, "Crap, this is not gonna go well."
They start lashing it to their horses. They start trying to drag it through the street to anywhere else where they can elevate it, but it's too heavy.
They can't move it. The roundheads, they take the better positions.
The town leaders say, "Should we hold out? Should we hold out? What do we do? We lost our super weapon."
We have these other cannons. We're kind of able to hold them at bay, but not for any amount of time.
And they start getting word that other cities that are loyal to the king have started to surrender, so they surrender too.
So the roundheads invade the city. And the general of the roundhead says, "I want to see that cannon. I want to take a look at that cannon."
So they ride their horses over to the cannon, and it's just laying there on the ground.
The general is like, "So many men, so many lives destroyed by that hunk of metal."
He sees a little street urchin walking by. He sees a little street urchin walking by.
He goes, "Hey son, what was the name of this cannon?" The street urchin looks up at him and goes, "Dumpty. Humpty Dumpty."
So that story, I just... First off, that story I just told you.
Imagine me telling that story to a young woman smoking a cigarette outside of a restaurant.
Almost word for word and about as long. She sat there, smoked the cigarette.
She didn't know me as well as she did. I would assume she would have walked away, or thought I was some sort of psychopath.
But that is the true story of the story of Humpty Dumpty.
Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall. Humpty Dumpty had a great fall.
All the king's horses and all the king's men could have put Humpty back together again.
There are people who say that no, no, no, the Humpty Dumpty thing references the fall or the power of the pope.
There's a little bit of dispute to that. But back in those olden times, Humpty Dumpty was the term for a fat person.
Just like how when we invented the nuclear atom bomb, I guess I should say, fat man and little boy.
It was the same thing. They invented this giant cannon and it probably had some official name,
but because it was huge, people just called it Humpty Dumpty like it was some fat dude.
And that was the slang term for the cannon was Humpty Dumpty.
And that again, some nerd will be like, "No, actually Humpty Dumpty is referenced to King Edward VIII."
Humpty Dumpty's story of about a badass cannon that fell off a wall and in the last stitch effort to get it moved into another position.
Oh, and I should say the entire story I told you was true, except for the general showing up at the end and asking the urchin.
That's all historical. So whether or not the nursery rhyme is related to that, that cannon was no one as a Humpty Dumpty a big cannon.
I don't know, I really like the story. I'm sure I mean, there's a human smoking a cigarette.
And she goes, "Yeah, I think I heard that before." I was like, "Oh, that's all the only response I got from my animated story."
She doesn't listen to the podcast so I can say whatever I want about her.
That's the power of the podcast apparently. I've made that comment a couple of times.
She doesn't listen to the podcast. I can say whatever I want.
So the last story we're going to cover this night is an interesting one.
It was one on the conspiracy iceberg, but there's so much on the iceberg I never really noticed it before.
And it was a request. Someone sent it to me. It was a young man, I'm assuming.
It was an email from Astoria, not the country. Is there a country called Astoria?
The entire country emailed me at once. But there was this urban legend.
This is really fascinating because it's one of those things that you start peeling back layers.
Now, my research consisted of reading an article that was so well written that that was it.
And because most of the sourcing, most of the articles about this are in French and it's an older story,
it was really the only one covering it, but it was a very... I wasn't even really an article.
It was more like a research paper.
There is this research paper known as Viper Release Stories, a contemporary French legend.
And it's an onion man. It's a weird onion story. So this is the conspiracy theory in the nutshell.
It started off in the 1980s in rural France. You'd have farmers, you'd have, you know, people walking through the countryside.
And they'd see a Viper and they'd be like, "What the...?" Well, that's weird. There's normally not snakes in this far.
I mean, I know there's snakes in France, but that's weird. Snake scurries on by.
They walk a little bit further and they see another snake and they're like, "Okay, now that's really weird."
Because there's definitely... I've never seen two snakes on the same day. Keep walking a bit.
And then they see another snake and they're not just like, "Well, that's super weird." It's a different snake.
It's not the same species. So now they're like, "Okay, now I've seen three snakes and one of them was completely...
Like, this is really weird." They'd go home, they'd sit in their little thatch-tut.
I guess they probably still live like that in the 1980s in France. They have a little thatch-tut.
They're smoking their hobbit weed and they go, "You know, Antoinette, today I saw the most curious thing."
And the Antoinette goes, "That's weird. You sound like an old British guy." "Wee-wee, yes."
"Today I saw the most curious thing."
Now he sounds like the Count from... It's just me sure, apparently.
He's like, "You know, today I see all the most..."
"Well, okay, now he's Italian. Forget it. No accents." He goes, "Today I saw the most curious thing."
"I saw a bunch of snakes." That is weird, right? And she's like, "Yeah, that is weird."
And it's even weirder because I saw a bunch of snakes. The other day, I just figured it was worth talking about.
And the legend grows. People in rural France start saying somebody is dumping snakes in the countryside.
And as bizarre as that sounded, the proof was there. They said, "Look at all of these snakes."
"There's normally not this type of snake in this region. There's definitely not this many snakes in this region."
There's a ton of them. And the legend starts to grow until it becomes... Until they start to create these conspiracy theories.
One, snakes are being dropped off in unusually large numbers. So it's not just like two or three snakes,
but you'd see a lot of different snakes. And generally, as you were walking through the countryside,
not only would you start to stumble across snakes, like literally, you're like tripping into them like Indiana Jones,
but you would see proof they were dropped, like a box or a bag nearby. That was one part of the legend.
Second part, when you would stumble across the bunch of snakes, there would be an aircraft, most likely a helicopter,
leaving the area. Three, you would find boxes, bags, and parachutes in the middle of nowhere.
So there would be no snakes around, but you'd find a box in the middle of a field.
That sounds a bit of a stretch to me. And four, the new variety of vipers.
So you would see different types of snakes that were never in that region.
It exploded in popularity in rural France. Rural France.
And what happened was two magazines ended up covering the story.
Now, they were called, one of the magazine was called Rumors, and the other one was called Liberation.
I don't know what those are, I don't know what type of newspapers those are.
I don't know if they're like weird newspapers or just like regular newspapers.
But anyways, it was covered in two newspapers. But by then, people were already talking about it in rural France,
and they're starting to complain about stuff. They're starting to contact their government officials and say,
"Why the hell are there a bunch of snakes in my area?"
Now, the French government, because this is the 1980s, they're starting to get all like, protect every animal, you know, type of thing.
They said, "You can't hurt snakes." That was the French set up this law saying, "You can't hurt snakes."
Very specific law. And so the people in rural France thought they're part of the cover-up.
Like, why would they have a particular law protecting snakes, and then a bunch of snakes show up in our backyard?
Another interesting thing was the conspiracy theory started in the 1980s. In 1979, the government made the sale and exploitation of snakes illegal.
So France does have a snake population. When I think of France, the first thing I don't think of is like, oh, snakes.
Actually, if I had to think of what animal lives in France, I can't even think a cow maybe?
A council of everywhere? Like, are there any animals indigenous to France?
Whenever I think of snakes, I think more like Middle East or Africa or something like that.
But they have enough snakes in France that they had to pass a law saying, "You can't sell them and you can't exploit them."
And then a couple years later, there's a bunch of snakes everywhere, and the government's like, "You can't hurt them at all."
"You can't hurt them at all." So people started thinking about the cover-up.
But, so the people in rural France are having to deal with all this stuff.
They're reporting these snakes, and people are originally saying, "It's just an urban legend."
"There's no helicopters dropping off snakes. It's a mass hysteria."
"Maybe this person saw one snake, this person saw one snake, and it becomes this over-exaggerated story."
"You guys are just country bumpkins. You don't know what you're talking about."
And all the reports were firsthand. They weren't like, "Well, my cousin saw a bunch of snakes."
"I saw a bunch of snakes in middle of nowhere. They shouldn't be there."
So you have these two groups of people, one of them saying, "I know what I saw. I saw snakes."
And the government's saying, "There are no snakes there."
"No one's dumping them in the middle of nowhere. You don't have to worry about it."
And it's funny because it's close parallel to, "You could replace snakes with UFOs."
"You could replace snakes with UFOs, and it's the same story."
"I saw UFOs. There's no such thing as UFOs." That's what was going on here, okay?
But, the next part of this story, so it turns out after these rumor, these Viper Snake release stories,
went on for like a decade. It kind of petered out.
But, in the 1980s, it really started.
So, in rural France, there was the, okay, so, and let me say this too, the bad guys in this story.
So it wasn't just, "There's a bunch of snakes magically appearing here."
The farmers were thinking that it was, people were dropping off snakes for one of three reasons.
One, ecologists trying to help endangered species.
So they were like, "Oh, we want to make more snakes appear?"
So they were dropping them off in the middle of nowhere where they could breed un-molested.
And then the second theory was, it's ecologists still, but they're providing food for birds of prey to help their population.
Now, I think you can kind of guess that the farmer people weren't a big fan of ecologists,
and that seems to kind of be a trend across the world.
Because I need to put the right, like, nitrates into my soil and do the right stuff for my farm,
and you got some scientists going, "Uh-uh, you got to use sunflower oil for that stuff."
And they're like, "Well, that doesn't work. I have to use this nitrogen."
They're like, "Nope, it's not natural."
So you have a lot of that happening here too, in America, where you have ecologists saying,
"You have to save this. You can't do anything there because the, you know, like, metaphysical tadpole,
this is only breeding ground, and you're like, "That's where my cows drink."
And so you kind of always have the headbunny.
So the farmers, the rural people were saying it was either ecologists trying to help endangered snakes
have a safe place to breed, ecologists were trying to provide food for birds of prey,
or that scientists from pharmaceutical laboratories were taking them out in the middle of nowhere,
letting them breed so they could extract the venom from them and then make anti-venom and cell and stuff like that.
Those sound oddly specific, but that was kind of in the town, because they didn't have any proof,
in the town they're thinking, "Maybe it's this local ecology college doing it, or maybe it's this guy."
And then, you know, as the helicopters start getting brought into the story, they start thinking,
"Oh, maybe it's a pharmaceutical lab. They're dropping the snakes off." Whatever.
So let's go back to when I said that the government said, "You can't sail or exploit snakes."
There was a specific clause in that. There was a specific clause in that law.
So they said, "You can't sail them. You can't harass snakes at all. Leave them alone."
"You can't do crank calls in the middle of the night. You can't pull their pants down."
Pharmaceutical companies go, "This is true. We talk about all the rumors."
But pharmaceutical companies say, "We need to be able to take anti-venom from snakes,
so we can produce anti-venom and sell it and also use it to save people's lives."
And the government says, "That's true. We will allow you."
This is in the law. "We will allow you to take snakes and extract venom as long as you release them."
After you're done. So pharmacists are like, "Oh, that's okay. That sounds like a thing."
Now you would think it's not like they would take one snake, take his venom,
and then let him go out the door and take another snake and take his venom, let him go out the door.
They're in the industry, so they're going to milk a thousand snakes of their venom,
put a thousand snakes in a box, and take them somewhere.
They would release them. There's no law saying where they had to release them.
So the fact that all of a sudden mass amounts of snakes were showing up in the middle of nowhere.
Now when the conspiracy theory was starting, people were just seeing the snakes everywhere,
and from what I gathered, they came to the conclusion that it could be the pharmacists
releasing them due to the venom because of this law.
But the pharmacist, the pharmacologist I guess is a better term, or yeah, the pharmacologist,
were saying, "Oh no, that's not us. That's not us."
And the government was denying it was a problem at all.
And then, and then, between 1980 and 1982, there was an ecologist who was releasing snakes into a swamp.
So it was bizarre. Both conspiracy theories actually turned out to be true.
That guy got caught. He was releasing snakes into the swamp because he wanted to help them breed.
Whether or not those people were seen doing that, or they were caught afterwards,
or the urban legends started first that these are the people who are doing it and they just happened to do it,
it could be a mixture of all three.
Because they didn't like the ecologists anyways, so they were going to place blame on them,
and then when it turns out one of them was actually dumping snakes in rural areas of France,
it just kind of fit perfectly.
I think the people in France who were walking around and stumbling across snakes had seen the law about snakes
saying that it was okay for pharmaceutical companies to milk them as long as they dropped them off,
and they just assumed they're just flying helicopters and throwing them out of boxes on parachutes and stuff like that.
But the whole time, even though it said in the law that pharmaceutical companies could release snakes wherever they wanted,
whatever amount, the government completely denied the fact that there was as much snakes running around out there.
It was considered an urban legend among stupid, uneducated country folk in France.
The same way that if you say you saw a UFO, someone could be like, "Yeah, you're hitting that moonshine, right?"
You know, like, it was the same disregard for people basically saying, "You're stupid for believing that."
That's not true.
Even though everything linked up.
Now, to be fair to the upper crust, witty or bane people who are sneering at these country people,
we know that ecologists dump the snakes.
We know that the pharmaceutical company could milk snakes and release them.
It's possible that the country people were exaggerating the amount of snakes in their area.
But I think it's interesting because we have, the two groups they suspected, actually have been caught releasing snakes.
The only disagreement is could they have released as many as the people in rural France say that are out there?
But the disregard for their real experiences is what's so bizarre about it.
You have these people who live in that area reporting an ecological disturbance, i.e. a mass amount of snakes.
And the government's simply shrugging and going, "There's no snakes out there."
Not anymore than would normally be there.
So why don't you go back to your farm and let us handle things?
And then the farmer goes back there and is like, "Whatever."
And then three weeks later, he reads a report about a guy dumping snakes in his hump.
It's a bizarre story.
And even today it's considered an urban legend.
Even today it's considered that's just something people believed back then.
Even though all those pieces fit together.
Is it just like a bunch of conspiracy theories, a lot of weird coincidences that happened so close together that a little bit of mass hysteria kicked in?
And one snake became 20?
Or were multiple groups actually dumping snakes in the middle of nowhere, hoping no one would ever find them?
The government knowing these groups are doing that.
And when people complain about it, the government simply shrugs and says, "There's nothing to see here."
It's just your imagination.
The parallels between Viper Release stories and UFO sightings is obvious.
Or any sort of paranormal activity, but specifically UFO because you have the government kind of poo-pooing the whole thing.
Government doesn't really come out and say ghosts don't exist. They really don't care.
But you have the people saying, "We're seeing this phenomenon in our area that's not natural."
And then you have the government and the scientific community saying, "That's not true. That's not true."
When in fact the government and the scientific community were actually taking part in their own ways of creating the snake outbreak.
But I also like it because it's a fairly harmless conspiracy theory.
No one died. There's no tragedy to it. It's just a farmer getting mad.
He goes to Melchus Cow and a bunch of snakes come out.
It's just that level of a conspiracy theory.
A conspiracy theory nonetheless.
And again, I think it's important to look at these ones that are much more grounded in reality.
Because it gives us clues on how to find these mysteries.
It's easy to sex everything up and make everything super dark and super violent and throw some aliens in there.
Make aliens drop the snakes. Yeah, yeah, let's do that. It's really easy to do that stuff.
It's just a harmless, fun, conspiracy theory. And it's a great way to end the week.
I like these stories. I like these positive conspiracy theories. It's still a little wacky.
Still a little mysterious.
But not everything has to be doom and gloom. Not everything has to be so dark.
I think the key to paranormal stories and ghost stories and UFO stuff is entertainment.
We want to shed light on these mysteries and we want to find out more.
But not everything has to be so grim.
Sometimes it's just a farmer.
A bunch of snakes.
An empty box.
And a mystery.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
Twitter is @jasonlcarpenter.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great week, guys.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]