On February 24th, 2022, Russia invaded the Ukraine.
And did they accidentally set off the long-prophesized dimensional merge?
And then we take a look at conspiracies involving nuclear missiles.
We know that UFOs and aliens have long been curious about the world's nuclear missiles.
Are they also currently being monitored by the forces of hell today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too. I'm just gonna say this right now.
I'm recording this episode on Sunday, February 27th. I don't know how things are in the future.
What things are going on Wednesday when this episode actually gets released?
Hopefully the world is still in one piece. I don't think there's gonna be any widespread nuclear bombs.
I don't know how I really specified that. Nuclear landmines maybe. Local nuclear bombs maybe.
I'm hoping not, right? But as of the time I'm recording this in my haunted closet,
nothing horrible like nuclear has happened. So that's good, right?
Sure, listen to this podcast in the future from your MP3 player as the battery's slowly dying
and the fallout is coming towards you. Like Jason, why'd you pick this stuff to talk about?
And you recorded it so far in the future. Someone who always joins me when I'm hanging out in the
future coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our Thanksgiving live stream supporters.
Give it up for the entire export. Woo! Come on in, come on in from the radio after fallout. Hurry up,
hurry up, shut the door. Dead Rabbit Command is protected from all sorts of attacks. Again,
these jokes are all completely insensitive if a nuclear strike has actually happened.
But I don't think it's gonna. The entire export, you're gonna be our captain or probably this
episode. If you guys can't afford the show financially, I totally get it. Just help spread
the word about the show that really, really helps out a lot. It really helps the show grow,
which is also very exceptional. The entire export, let's go ahead and give you the keys to the
Dead Rabbit Durgible. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're gonna float all the way out
to the Ukraine. Export, go ahead and fly this Durgible over the Ukraine. We're definitely not
gonna walk around. We're just gonna be up in this Durgible the entire time. February 24th, 2022
was the day that Russia invaded the Ukraine. And that is also, I'm just gonna get to the chase right
here, February 24th, 2022 is the birthday of Kris Chan, aka Christine Chandler. That name means
nothing to you. You are a well-adjusted adult and shut off the podcast to never listen to me again
and go on with your day. Don't know about the matters I'm about to talk about. We did an entire
episode on Kris Chan a while ago. Kris Chan believes that eventually the fictional world will merge
with the real world. So Gotham is gonna appear somewhere like where Chicago is and New York is
gonna be replaced by Metropolis and regular New York's from all these other fictional universes,
all fictional universes. Collide with Earth, you'll finally be able to challenge Sonic to a race,
arm wrestle Popeye, and go hang gliding with Powerpuff Girls or whatever the world they do.
The point is, is that it's all gonna collide, but it's also gonna be like super violent and
destructive. So his birthday is the same day that Russia invades the Ukraine. He's 40 years old,
I didn't know he was that old. He's 40 years old, this invasion starts. But what's even weirder
is, what's even weirder than the fictional world colliding with our own, is for the first time
we are able to see behind the curtain, visa v propaganda war. This is really really interesting.
I got an email from Kris K, another longtime supporter of the show, actual founder of the
Golden Rabbit Brigade, he's the guy who made me set up the Patreon in the first place.
And he sent me this stuff, and I haven't been following the news, but he sent me this stuff
about the ghost of Kiev and what this is. It's an unknown fighter pilot flying an older plane,
a MiG-29 fulcrum, and on the very first day of the invasion shot down five Russian jets,
plus a helicopter, that's kind of being a bully, right? What's a helicopter going to do to a jet?
So anyway, shoots down five jets, worthy opponents, the helicopter was just a bonus target.
I blew it up, and I remember seeing this on Twitter and it said this is the first combat
ace in the past 52 years, no one's racked up this many jet kills in a day, and I was like,
oh that's interesting, that's fascinating, footage started coming out of this jet.
I was researching this story as it was going on by February 26th, so two days after the invasion,
he'd already racked up another six jet kills, so he's sending out 11 kills right now,
and you might be worried right now if you're a Russian pilot and you're like,
oh no I didn't know about this guy, they don't let us look at the Twitter, he's fake, he doesn't exist.
This is so fascinating to me, this is so interesting.
We are seeing for the first time, I'm going to keep it brief because I know no one really
wants to hear about this, right? You guys are like, you want to get to the nuclear weapon
stuff, just the same reason I didn't talk a lot about coronavirus, right, when that was happening,
because we hear about it all the time, but the Ghost of Kiev is something different.
It was video game footage from the game War Thunder coupled with some unsourced tweets
and people needing hope that created the Ghost of Kiev. Even the former president of the Ukraine
tweeted, oh no no no, because people started going, oh it's fake, it's from this video game,
we totally know it because the clouds, the clouds had a little turtle with a fishing
pole in it, it's obviously a video game. The former president of the Ukraine goes, oh no no no,
yeah I know that was, I know that was fake, but he's real, and here's a photo of him, here's a photo
of the Ghost of Kiev sitting in his jet and that photo was from 2019. That was an old photo from
some Chinese website, it's so weird and they're creating these fictional, I don't know who's doing
this, the Ghost of Kiev was a joke, but it spun out of control and people started believing it,
and then Newsweek had to start running articles being like, we don't know if the Ghost of Kiev is
real or not, but we know that this video footage is fake, but maybe there is a Ghost of Kiev out
there, then they, I started seeing stuff about this guy called the Ukrainian maniac, no I'm sorry
the Ukrainian Reaper, the maniac's copyright, that's another guy, the Ukrainian Reaper, I saw an
article on him, 20 confirmed kills of Russians on the first day, right, and so he, that guy's
going around, it's like move out of the way, move out of the way, fake propaganda thing that no one
believes in anymore, this time it's the Ukrainian Reaper, and by now there was one, some guy started
the Odessa Aspandant, and that was this guy had had a confirmed 20 butt rapes of Russian soldiers,
and that's obviously fake, right, but the point is, now all the jokes are coming out about it,
we don't know what's real, that guy's not real, don't worry about your butt, if you're Russian,
don't worry about the Odessa Aspandant, but we don't know what's real, and this started so quickly
that when I'm sitting here at home and I'm reading reports, reading news articles and
we're talking about this amount of troops have been killed and this is going on and they have
this but they, I don't know, I don't know what's real, fascinating, fascinating, I don't know what to
believe, Putin's troops have been stopped at this city, Orange Glow, seen over Kiev was a new
detonated, talks are gonna happen on this border, I don't know, I don't know if any of that's real,
at all, fascinating and really alarming, isn't it, I have a conspiracy theory, America
has never gone to war with an English speaking enemy since the civil war, and I think there's
a reason for that, I think if you could sit there and watch the world leaders and you could understand
what they're saying, you could be like, I don't know, Saddam Hussein's making pretty good points,
maybe he should be torturing all those people, I don't know, I thought torture was bad, but he's
a really good speaker, America does not fight people who speak English and I think there's a
reason for that, I think it's because they don't want us to know what they're fighting and it's not,
it's not a racial thing either, because they walked all over the world, they walked all over
Europe, stepping on people, right, fought the Germans, fought the Italians, fought the Spanish,
and had nothing to do with race, they don't fight people who speak English as a first language
since the civil war, and I think it's a propaganda reason, I do think that's a conspiracy theory
I have, I think that they don't pick that fight, because if we went to war with England and we
could listen to what they were saying, I have to depend on the government's telling me these guys
are the bad guys, I mean yeah, when you fly a couple planes into the World Trade Center,
that you're a bad guy, but I remember there was that speed, I remember there was, there's like,
we found video footage of Osama bin Laden bragging about the 9/11 attacks, it was all over the news,
and then it later came out like a month later, like that's not what he was saying,
these independent translators are like, that's not what he said, but I don't know, do I believe the
independent translators, do I believe the guy, very rarely believe the government, but do I believe
the independent translators, do I believe these translators, do I believe these troop movements
in the Ukraine, do I believe these troop movements in the Ukraine, I don't know what's going on,
and I'm reading a bunch of stuff, and I've come to the conclusion that I think everything that you
know, this is including me, if you took the total sum of your knowledge, 10% of it is factually
incorrect, I'm not talking about political opinions, I'm not talking about religious opinions,
I'm talking about 10% of what a normal person actually believes to be true is probably false,
and now we have this war that's going on, that we don't know what's going on, I can watch camera
footage, I can watch like streaming camera footage of Kiev and these other cities in the Ukraine,
you must be really bored if you're sitting watching this camera footage, beautiful cities,
right, I'm just seeing cars drive down the road and stuff like that, I don't know what I was
expecting, like call of duty cutscenes with a bunch of helicopters and mortars,
well again, I'm recording this episode on Sunday, that stuff may have happened by the time you
hear it on Wednesday, and I obviously know there's a war going on over there, I'm not saying that
it's not real, but I don't know what's true, I'm hearing all this stuff that Russia's getting
stymied here and stymied here and he can't move the troops and da da da da, and for all I know,
two days from now the entire country could be taken over by Russia, and everyone's like,
wait, I thought you said that the Odessa Aspen did was protecting the country, I thought you said
that he had been stopped on all these things, and then the people who told us those propaganda
stories are like, they don't even, people don't even apologize anymore for telling you the wrong
thing, fascinating, like I've never seen, I lived through the first Iraq war and the second Iraq
war and all this stuff, and I remember hearing about Iraqi soldiers going in and taking babies
right out of the incubators when the Iraqis invaded Kuwait, the first before they secured any
strategic targets, they went to local hospital and pulled babies out of the incubators, I remember
hearing that, there is an Iraqi woman testifying before Congress saying this happened, never happened,
never happened, that story about soldiers taking babies out of incubators is an old story,
it's been, it's happened in a couple different wars, so what's real, fascinating story, the ghost
of Kiev, people are saying the footage isn't real, but he's real and now I think people have kind of
moved on because he's not, and people are making up brand new characters, they're like the juggernaut
of Kiev, he gets plus two defense if he fights more than five Russians at a time, and that stuff's
obviously favorite, those are jokes, but at the same time real propaganda is being put at, and I'm
watching history unfold in real time and I don't know what's true, and you can go Jason, well you
gotta go to Lewis, this website, this website has all the true information, are you sure?
Are you sure? Like you don't know, I mean you could be sitting in the Ukraine right now, you're
like yeah I know, here's a photo of what's going on, but fascinating, it's fascinating to see this
propaganda war play out in real time, and Christian's birthday, does this have enough, is this part
of this dimensional merge, because what we're having is we're having fictional event, you didn't
think I was gonna get back to that, you thought that was clickbait, we're having a real event
with fictional characters in the real event, and people are believing the fictional characters,
does it become a tolpa at a certain point? Could we see a ghost of Kiev, a person flying this older
jet? Chris Kaye had the suggestion, maybe it's a ghost, maybe it's a literal ghost, that's why it's
in such an old jet, and connected it to my episode about George Washington fighting his ghost, fighting
during the Battle of Gettysburg, I'll put that episode in the show notes, but yeah, it feels like
the real world and the fake world are colliding, and I know there's always been, see here's the
difference, you go Jason there's always been propaganda during war, there's always been these
type of characters, we don't see them, because they don't exist, but with the footage you can
actually show footage that in a tweet in the little low res tweet box, looks like a jet flying
overhead, right? I was fooled, I was fooled, so before you would have, and also these stories
would be local to the combat, you'd be like oh and you won't believe it, this guy he took on 10
soldiers at once, he had an AK-47 in each hand and perfect aim and just every bullet landed a
headshot, it was amazing and that would inspire people locally to walk around with two AK-47s,
if he can do what I can do it, it was local stuff in the battlefield and now you can have footage of it.
Fascinating, absolutely fascinating, we are taking the real and making it fake, we are taking
the fake and making it real, and in front of all of it is the looming shadow of chris-chan,
leaves their big old stamp on it, weird story, the real is fake, the fake is real, I don't know
what to believe, anything could happen and even after the dust is settled, will we know the truth?
Who knows, who knows? The entire export, let's go ahead and touch the keys of the carboner
copter, we're leaving behind Kiev, we are headed all the way out to Johnson County, Missouri,
DADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADADAD
his team, his job was to provide security for the nukes there, so I mean that would be so boring
if you think about it, you just be sitting there all day long, who's going to break in and steal a
nuke, bring up a flatbed truck, I guess you could just put up some camera, you're like,
they're not worried about someone stealing an entire nuclear missile, it's so people don't go
in and sabotage it or copy it, some guy comes in with a piece of paper and traces it and then takes
it back to russian, this is what their missiles look like, give me a million dollars, I got you
some intel, it just sounds boring, at least if you were like, if I was a security guard, if you
said you can guard this nuclear missile or you can guard this, you can guard this jewel that the
penguin is trying to steal, I'd much rather do that, I guess then I'd probably get gassed in the face
or kicked in the nuts by a penguin, but still it'd be more exciting, anyways he's walking around,
he's working for the military, the military is 99% just boring, he's sitting there and he's doing
his job one night and this night they're actually getting ready to move some warheads around,
they're shuffling them up, they're like only one of these warheads are real, can you guess which one
and they're putting them on different missiles, he goes, I remember I'm sitting there, we're moving
these warheads around and I see up in the night sky a glowing ball high up there and he's like,
hmm it's really high, there might be a satellite right, I heard those things are pretty high up,
but it's look, it's hovering there for a long time and once the transport team shows up to
officially move the warhead, he said it just kind of bounced a bit and then shot up directly into
the sky, disappeared, never saw a satellite do that before, however to be fair it'll sit outside
and watch satellites all day long, here's the thing, it's pretty common to have UFOs over nuclear
power plants, we have a lot of stories about that stuff and I think most of those are terrestrial
spy planes, so when you were moving the warheads around, so of course the Russians or the Chinese
or France or Egypt or Israel or Australia or any of these other countries that wants to know what's
going on, they want to know what we're doing, they're trying to guess which warhead's the real
warhead, but we have a lot of stories about UFOs flown overhead, what makes this more interesting
is we're in the year of 2006 and it's summertime, this dude Adrian's at his workspace and he's in
a restricted area, I mean technically the entire military base is restricted, I'm not allowed to
go there with an ice cream cone and start taking pictures, but he's in an extra restricted area,
so he's alone in this area, the rest of his team is working on a trainer bomb, it's like a
fisher price bomb, all the pieces are huge and plastic, he's sitting there in this restricted
area and he hears the sound of footsteps walking down the hall and he immediately realized something
was off because one, he knew he was the only person there, but two, everyone in the military wears
boots, but these were not boot footsteps, these were the footsteps, this dude totally has a
foot fetish, I never would have been able to pick this out, only someone who's heard feet,
like watches YouTube videos of nothing but feet walking, ASMR, he goes these were not allegedly,
don't sue me if you don't really have a foot fetish Adrian, but he goes I did not hear the
sound of boots walking down the hallways, I heard the sound of bare feet walking down the hallways,
short tiny, short tiny delicate feet with a little wisp of a long afternoon playing tennis,
I added that was not his description, he hears the sound of bare feet in the hallways and he looks
up and he doesn't see anything and the sound goes away, so he just goes back to work which is probably
playing with his phone, a couple minutes later the sound comes back, he's on YouTube looking up
feet noises and he's like what where is that sound coming from, oh well I also put my headphones back
in and keep watching feet, a couple minutes later he hears more feet walking around behind him and
this time he can tell the sound is moving away from the area that he's at, so he gets up and he
gets up in turns just in time to see a blurry figure walk around the corner, he said this figure
was about six feet tall and it was blurry, it was completely indistinct figure, he says it reminded
him of if you took a black mass, a black swirling mass and compressed it into the shape of a human
walking through the hallway, now remember this is a restricted area, he's supposed to be the only one
in this area plus he also wants to see this dude's feet, so he gets up, I don't know I feel so bad for
this guy, all of a sudden he's defining trade, he loves feet, he gets up and he begins running down
the hallway and he wants to catch this guy, he wants to know what it is right, so he goes down
the hallway and he turns and he looks down this long hallway, nothing, he begins searching all
over the area, he goes into the offices, he goes into the break room, he gets on all fours and he's
sniffing, sniffing around, now I know the sense of feet but where is this one gone,
nothing, he can't find it anywhere, he goes this is a secure base, this is a military base, how did
anyone get in here, all the doors are secured, no alarms went off and so he just goes back to his
workstation, he walks back, takes his shoes off, takes his shoes off and walks through the hallway,
his bare feet touching the cold linoleum floor, you'll expect his workstation all depressed,
tears himself up, I take in a quick whiff of his own socks and goes, you know what, I'm not going
to report this because I'll just be considered a lunatic, I'll be considered a foot-smelling lunatic,
you know he goes, I don't know why I've made it, this is his defining trait but it's all part of
the propaganda, it's all part of the propaganda machine, he goes I'm not going to report this
because people will think I'm crazy, and that's true, if you went to your boss at work, because I
do this at every workplace, every workplace I've ever worked has been haunted, I don't think Wells
Fargo was haunted, that was like this call center, they're not around anymore but all my other jobs,
I've been like this place haunted, there's a ghost here, that's why I wasn't able to come
to work sir, because a ghost was in my desk and it was super spooky so I stayed home for three days,
I've worked at a lot of haunted places, I worked at a haunted pizza parlor, technically I brought
the ghost to the pizza parlor, the pizza parlor wasn't haunted, I did an episode on that, and then
I just worked a lot of haunted places, but I dare you to do this, where you work, go to your boss
and say hey you know I like working here and all, but every so often there's a swirling black mass
in the shape of a human that walks around and doesn't wear any shoes, tell your boss that
and watch how quickly your hours get reduced, they will think you're a lunatic, they'll be like
wait a second, unless you work in Shadowman or us and he's like well I'm glad you saw that,
I'm glad you reported that to me, because that means we have more inventory, usually people,
and they may not actually reduce your hours or fire you or anything like that, but like what?
But what's in, so we have this report right now, this is a Shadowman, and Shadowman kind of fallen
to the realm of the paranormal, not necessarily alien, and this report is not alone, outside of
Las Vegas, Nevada, we all know about area 51, but what a lot of people forget is that's area 51,
there's 50 more of these areas scattered around the United States, area two is outside of Las
Vegas, Nevada, and we have a report from Chris Cabera, former Air Force Security Officer, he
said he was on this base and he sees this black mass, very similar to what Adrian saw, walking
around the facility, but he said this one didn't have a head, this one just had like its shoulders
and its arms and it was walking around, and there are other reports of shadow people on this base
as well. So we have the UFO encounters, we have a ton of those, couldn't even tell you all of them,
there's so many encounters of aliens, or UFOs at least, over nuclear bases, but here we have
shadow people, which tend to be more in the realm of ghosts and demons than aliens, so why are the
shadow people here, what I think is interesting is first off, let's put on our skeptic hat,
which is nothing because we don't believe in hats, skeptics don't believe in anything,
technically my go-to, let's say these stories are true, right, you're like Jason is skeptic,
wouldn't even give me that much, but let's say that these stories are true, my first go-to is,
these aren't shadow people, this is camouflage technology, these are actual humans walking
around, and this is good as it gets, they're like "hey can I have a suit that makes me invisible?"
and the scientist goes "well I can make a suit that makes you less visible, how would you like
to be a swirling black mass?" and they're like "what, that actually makes me more visible,
I'm trying not to cause any commotion at all." They're like "listen," the scientist goes "I can't
make you invisible, what do you think this is Harry Potter?" but what I can do is make it so if
somebody looked and saw you, you would look like a ghost, scientist comes out with a white sheet
with holes in it, he's like "here you go, that'll be $50 million please, I can make you look like a
shadow person." But there's two limits to the technology, one you can't wear suits with it,
for whatever reason, we can turn everything into a shadow but your shoes, your Nike Air Force
ones have to remain at base, but they'll be able to see you, but if they look at you, no one's going
to tell anyone that there's a shadow person walking around and you go "Jason that's actually quite
fascinating, that's the reason why I listen to your podcast." However, what about the dude with no
head? They send in a spy with no head, I got an answer for that too, no, they send in a spy with
the head because that's kind of integral to being a spy, but he was probably like looking down,
like eating an ice cream cone, I actually don't have a reason for why he wouldn't have it, I figure
maybe if he was looking down, but even if I looked down, was eating an ice cream cone, first off,
first rule of being a spy, 20 ice cream cones on your mission, but maybe he was like trying to
fix a zipper or something like that, or maybe he was looking down at his beautiful feet, I don't know,
but anyways if you looked down enough, you would just see shoulders and you wouldn't see the top
of your head or that you had a head, and he could be doing that, he could have been a double-jointed
freak who also had a camouflage technology, that would be my first guess, right? Because I believe
a lot of the UFOs we see over nuclear plants are terrestrial in nature, and this could be,
same thing, this could be a spy from another country who has this camouflage technology
and is walking around, and then I started thinking, "Wow, I wonder how many shadow people actually
are spies?" But then I remember most of the shadow people that I've personally seen were in my grandma's
backyard, and I don't think the CIA was going to my grandma's backyard because she was growing weed
or whatever, she was growing weed, but I don't think the CIA was there for that, I think, I think,
I've seen shadow people and they definitely weren't agents of the federal government, I've
stuck my hand inside of them, I'll put that episode in the show notes, it was a really good
episode, but it would be an easy way to be less noticeable, right, to basically be unbelievable
you'd be unbelievable in that moment. Then there's the option these are actual shadow people,
and the thing with shadow people is we don't know what this phenomenon is, they're not demons,
they're not ghosts, this is something that really the best way to describe them is alien.
I think one of the best explanations I heard, it's definitely most evocative, is that the
shadow people were the original inhabitants of hell, when the big giant war happened in heaven
and God threw down one third of the angels into hell, there's much shadow people there already
and they're like, ah, and because they seem so aloof when I've encountered shadow people, it's,
I, it makes you feel like an ant, it makes you feel like a pet, it's super weird, like when you see
these things, they, the same way you don't really care if there's a potato bug in your bushes outside
your house is the way it feels when you encounter a shadow person, you're not terrified of them,
they don't care that you exist, you can do nothing to them, you're less than an ant, because even an
ant you're like, oh dude get out of here, I love ants, so I feed ants, but most people would be
like dude get out of here, go away ant, they don't even care, they're so, they know we exist,
but they just don't care, there's nothing we can do for them, so it's such an aloofness that makes
it weird, like a ghost may try to deliver you a message, a demon may try to scare you or trick
you, the shadow person wants to do neither, they just, it's not even that they want to be left
alone or they want to exist, it's, they're so aloof, you can't even put a, like an intention
on them, it's very, very weird, I've interacted with ghosts and I've interacted with demons and I've
interacted with shadow people and out of the three, the shadow people are the most, I won't say the
most upsetting because that's the demons, but there's just, you feel insignificant to them,
like you're not even part of their daily structure, demons want to cause a downfall of man,
ghosts are just floating around and stuff, but it's so, I can't even, there's nothing I can
compare it to, because at least like a pet we take care of, I can't, but anyway so it's super weird
to be around these things that have no feeling for you up or down, they know you exist, they don't
really care, fascinating, why are they at these nuclear facilities, if these shadow people, these
are legitimate shadow people sightings, what are they doing at these facilities? We don't know,
that's the thing, they are so aloof, I can't even come up with a theory. Now I have a follow-up
story, I didn't have time to talk about today because I do have an encounter, it's not necessarily
nuclear, but it's along the same lines, of a monster being sighted at a NASA facility,
I ran out of time, I ran out of time, I spent so much time telling feet jokes,
there was another story I want to cover, I'm gonna have to save it for another episode, but
we talked about shadow people at these facilities, what if I told you that there's another story,
it's about a monster at a NASA facility, there's multiple sightings of this giant monster,
it doesn't say whether or not it wears shoes at a NASA facility, but we will save that,
that's a little teaser for a future episode, I do think that demons would have, just like aliens,
an interest in our technology, but the interesting thing is aliens, I believe, would want to stop us
from nuking ourselves, the forces of darkness would love to do nothing but encourage it,
so if the original inhabitants of hell are walking around our nuclear bases,
maybe they are just passing through, right, or maybe they're not as uninterested as they seem,
maybe they're just uninterested in me, because they make me feel insignificant,
maybe this is the first scouting mission for their infernal neighbors,
because if you think a madman with a nuclear arsenal is dangerous, imagine a demon without much power,
imagine a dark prince of hell with the ability to press a single button, and start nuclear armageddon,
truly a frightening thought, as nukes rain down on the planet, and vaporize human life,
it sends countless souls into the clutches of satan, while also turning god's greatest creation
into a charred landscape, choked with fire and smoke, spinning forever alone through a silent cosmos.
[Music]
DeadRabberRadio at gmail.com is going to be our email address, you can also
address it at facebook.com/deadrabberradio, TikTok is @deadrabberradio,
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast,
you don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today, have a great one guys.
[Music]