A family in Italy breaks out the Ouija board.
It's all fun and games until the cops kick down your door.
Then we travel to Russia to take a look at a bizarre story of a man who claims he was
abducted by aliens and not taken aboard a spaceship, but taken to a swamp full of zombies
today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had a great, great weekend.
We got a lot of stuff to cover today, so we're going to go ahead and get started here.
First off, I want to give a shout out to a supporter of the show behind the scenes.
This guy has helped me out a lot recently, really, really appreciate it.
He took care of a task that I myself couldn't have done.
I can't really say who he is or what he does.
I can't tell you what his job is.
It's very sensitive.
But there was a particular issue that I needed help with and this gentleman helped me out.
So Joe from Portland, Joe from Portland.
Let's salute him actually.
We're saluting this guy.
This guy is an American hero.
I'm not saying that facetiously.
He's a really good dude and I can't tell you guys fully what's going on behind the scenes,
but he helped out a lot.
So we're done.
Joe's all embarrassed.
He's like, "Guys, quit saluting me."
We're still saluting him.
Wipe away a single tear.
Where's his parade?
Damn it.
Where's Joe's parade?
No, he's really, really a good guy.
Thank you for helping.
Helped me out, helped the show out, so he helped you guys out as well.
Joe, let's hop aboard the Carpentercopter.
We're going for a flight.
Now, this is a request from Fabio via email.
So Fabio, really, really appreciate that.
Let's bring that Carpentercopter nice and low.
We're coming over the Italian countryside.
We're specifically headed to a place called Monza.
Monza, Monza.
Everyone's just eating the whole time.
It's the town of Gluttons.
That's Monza, isn't it?
Same thing.
In two ways, I'm sure the words mean the exact same thing.
They sound like we're flying over this town.
It's July 8th, 2013.
So Joe, let's land that Carpentercopter.
We hop out of the Carpentercopter and we see a bunch of Italian police officers run
past the Carpentercopter.
And now we're in Italian police uniforms as well because we're going to blend in.
We're walking with the cops and stuff like that.
The cops walk up to this house and they're like, "Italian police, open up!"
You just hear ruckus upstairs.
Sounds like some people are just making weird noises.
The Italian police are looking at each other and they're like, "You ready to go in?"
And we're like, "Monza."
And the cops are like, "Okay, he's hungry, but that's the only word he knows in Italian,
so that's works too."
And we're getting ready to breach.
See, I know law enforcement terms.
Now we're going to rewind to get to why the police are here.
So you like a little cliffhanger that I gave away in the opening when I told you why the
cops are here?
It doesn't matter.
The police are sitting in their office and the phone rings.
Ring, ring, ring, ring.
Italian 911, what's your emergency?
And these people are like, "Dude, this totally sucks.
There's this family.
I'm living next to this family."
Right?
Totally normal people.
Father, he's a bank employee.
He's 53 years old.
He has a wife who's 43.
He's his housewife.
And they have a 13-year-old daughter.
And these dudes are like throwing a big old ruckus up in their attic.
And then 911 goes, "That's not how you pronounce it.
It's attic."
But it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
The point is, don't correct my grammar.
The point is, is that they're making a much noise and I'm afraid something's going on.
So Italian police hang up the Italian phone and they go, "Let's go."
Ring, ring, ring, ring.
They drive out and now we're back to where we are.
So we're standing with all these Italian police.
We're getting ready to breach this building and kick the door in.
And then we're running up the stairs because we know the noise is coming from the attic.
We're standing outside the attic door at this point.
And you hear people inside the attic.
Damn it.
We hear people inside the room in the roof.
And they're going, "I am the goddess of love, Hitler.
I am the goddess of love, Hitler."
That's not a sample from a weird Kendrick Lamar song.
These are people saying this, people saying this weird stuff in this room.
And the cops are all looking at each other and they're like, "Oh, do we really want
to go in here?"
But it is the Italian police job.
So they open the door and what they see, the first thing they go on, it's super hot in
there.
It's basically my apartment right now while I'm recording this episode.
It's super, super hot in there.
All the windows have been taped shut.
So it's like stifling hot.
There's cans of solvent.
Now Fabio is from Italy and he sent me this stuff and I basically was run through a translator.
So when it said cans of solvent, what I think it was was like aerosol canister.
They were basically huffing is what the police figured out.
Cans of solvent.
So I don't know if it's like WD-40.
I don't know if it was like model airplane glue.
Whatever it was, it was everywhere.
And the implication in the article that this family was sky high.
I mean, they were blitzed out of their minds, allegedly.
Anonymous family in Italy don't sue me.
Anyways, the cops were looking around.
This is the quote.
They're making these references to Hitler.
They just keep going, "Hitler, Hitler."
And then every so often one of them would go, "I am the goddess of love."
And they're just saying incomprehensible things, right?
And they're all in their underwear too.
Skip that detail.
The whole family, father, wife, and daughter are in their underwear.
In the middle of the room is a Ouija board.
And in between saying Hitler and "I'm the goddess of love" and other ramblings that
the police sent it right down, the family members turn, stop talking.
They turn, look at the police officers and go, "We are the children of Odin!"
And run.
And they begin fighting in this hot, sticky attic.
At tick, they're fighting a family in their underwear.
The police are now straight-handed in combat.
I mean, think about it, dude.
You could probably take on the dad, but that little 13-year-old girl, she's like a spider
monkey.
She's jumping off rafters and stuff, grabbing on in your neck.
"Joe, look out!"
She's in a headlock.
Got Joe in a headlock.
He's like, "Ugh, what did I have to be the pilot for this story?"
I'm punching.
I'm just punching the dad.
I'm like, "I'll save you soon.
First, let me take care of this guy."
The cops are going toe-to-toe in this super hot attic.
The family's biting them, scratching them, saying, "We will exterminate you."
Probably saying Hitler a few more times just for good measure.
Finally, the police get it under control.
Drag the family downstairs.
They get out of that hot, hot attic.
Police win the melee.
The daughter gets taken away to like child services, Italian child protective services.
The father and the mother were forced to go to like a psychological evaluation.
They were charged with police assault, but they were acquitted.
They weren't found guilty for any of that stuff.
They ended up being hospitalized, but there's no record.
This story took place back in 2013, and there's no follow-up.
So we don't even know these people's names.
Most likely, they just were in the hospital for a bit.
Here's the...
This story's creepy for a couple different reasons.
One, I had to come to grips with the fact that I can't pronounce the word "attic."
So that was "always leave a lasting scar on me."
Two, I have a thing with the paranormal.
Treat the paranormal like a gun.
Assume it's always loaded.
Oh, a Ouija is just a board game.
It's nothing.
Always treat every ghost investigation, every Charlie Charlie game, white noise generator,
Ouija board like it's a loaded gun, that it is extremely dangerous and can go off at any
time and hurt yourself or anyone around you.
It's not something to be goofing off with.
That's the second thing.
One, I can't pronounce the roof above the house.
I can't pronounce that.
Two, treat the paranormal like a loaded gun.
If you're going to a haunted location, assume someone's going to get possessed.
Just assume that.
So you can be prepared to throw holy water on everybody.
Always treat it like you're going into a dangerous situation.
Three, this family dodged a bullet.
I think we can all agree it's a creepy story.
Thank you for the recommendation, Father Go.
It's a creepy story.
Because this family dodged a bullet because not only were they messing with the Ouija board,
they were getting high while doing it.
Getting high and playing with the Ouija board, you could have had demonic possession.
You could have had one of them murder.
The other, you could have had some sort of gross family thing, which I think you guys
get the implication with that.
You could have had all sorts of horrible things happen.
Treat the paranormal.
First off, and this is rule four, I think we're on, do not mix substance abuse with
paranormal stuff.
That's another thing.
A lot of people, "Hey dude, let's drink some brews and go to the haunted house."
Friends from the 1980s?
Don't, don't mess.
If you're frat from Revenge of the Nerds, who were they?
Not the lamb the lamb the lamb does the other guy.
Tri-Pi, it doesn't matter.
If your frat buddies want to get drunk and go to the graveyard, smoke a doobie, say,
"Nah, ah, ah, I only hunt for ghosts when I'm stone sober."
So yes, we've learned a lot of lessons from this.
This family really dodged the bullet.
It could have gotten really bad, and hopefully they learned their lesson, but since we don't
know who these people are, but who knows what happened to this family?
They're probably still out there.
They're probably looking for another attic to hang out in.
Tonight when you're reading a book, late at night you hear Italian footsteps above
your head.
Huh?
Do you hear them like footsteps from around here?
Those totally sound, those aren't, those aren't, they sound like Italian leather shoes
on my, in my attic.
Don't go up and check.
Call the police.
Because I know how this story ends.
Ends with people in their underwear biting me.
Call the Italian police.
Let's go ahead, Joe.
Let's hop back in that carbonercopter.
It's so hot in here right now.
I'm in my underwear.
That's not a meme.
I have not joined this cult.
It's so hot and sticky in here.
So Joe's like, Joe's like sitting in the helicopter.
I'm getting in my underwear.
I got my undershirt on.
He's like, oh, come on.
Seriously, this is the episode.
You have us getting bit by a family in their underwear.
Now you're wearing underwear.
Take us up, Joe.
Up, up and away.
We're leaving behind Italy.
We're headed out to Russia.
We're leaving behind the country that looks like a boot and we're headed to the country
that looks like a big old slab of steak.
The good old Soviet Union.
I found this story on ThinkAboutItDocs.com, which is one of my favorite...
Competiums, Competiums, collections of UFO stories.
I found this on here.
Let's take a look at it.
It's really interesting.
I was recently looking through the entire year of 1990.
We saw a massive amount of alien encounters in Russia in the year 1990.
Now we had seen them in previous years, 88, 89, but in 1990 was when we had a ton of cases
of aliens making contact with humans.
And a lot of times they would say, would you like to come on our ship?
And the person would come on the ship and they'd kind of look around and they'd tell
the story and the aliens would be like, stop using nukes or clean the environment, aka
boring stuff.
I would be so disappointed if I met an alien and they sit down and they start talking about
the environment.
I'd be like, lame.
Can you at least...
Rather you try to shoot me with a laser beam than bore me to death.
And then they're like, okay, here's our boring machine.
No, that's not what I meant.
That terrible joke aside, we're headed to Russia to take a look at a very interesting story
that I think we can use as a springboard for an interesting discussion.
So there was a man...
We're flying to the year 1990.
We're in the served-loss region in the Urals of Russia.
There's a night watchman named Sanon.
He's 60 years old.
And in the day, he's a carpenter.
He's one of mine.
He's one of my brief.
But at night, he was a night watchman.
Now I'm going to give you a detail about him and you may think that would probably make
him a bad night watchman.
But in the end, it might have made him the best night watchman ever.
He's deaf.
He can't hear nothing.
So you would figure, you know, at night, your senses are already compromised.
You have to use a light.
You've got a flashlight.
You know, you guys understand how darkness works.
You can't see in the dark.
You think losing another sense would actually make it more difficult to do the jump.
People are sneaking up behind you and stuff.
Throwing burlap sacks over your head.
Gophers are running away with your carrots.
All sorts of stuff.
But he was the night watchman.
So he was taking care of that.
It was like a farm collective.
It was his job to keep everything secure.
Well, one night, he's sitting there.
He's just doing his job.
He's keeping an eye on those gophers.
And a bright light comes down from the sky.
And he's like, "This sucks."
Like he immediately knows that this is out of the ordinary.
He's not curious about UFOs, none of this stuff.
He immediately knows it's about to get real.
And what steps out of this glow is three aliens.
You know, a couple of grays.
You could take a meat.
Joe could probably take two of them.
He holds them.
I punch him in the stomach.
But the third one shoots both of us with a laser beam.
Oh man, I forgot to stop that one, Joe.
But these aliens are eight and a half to nine feet tall.
Yeah, you're not going to tangle with these things.
These aliens start coming out.
And the Tsanen's like, "Dude, listen, I'm just a night watchman.
Like I watched stuff at night."
They never said anything in the job description about actually stopping anything, let alone
giants.
So he hides.
But then he's like hiding in a big piece of machinery in the door.
Swings open and he feels this unknown, compelling force pulling him towards the light.
"No, I'm not going.
I'm not going."
He's holding onto the steering wheel.
His grip starts to loosen.
He's getting pulled across the ground.
He's like, "No, no, I'm not going to do it."
Finally, though, against all odds, he crawls away.
The aliens look at each other.
He's crawling.
He gets away from this beam.
He runs into the nearby forest.
Oh my God, that was close.
He's laying against the tree.
Oh my God, super nervous, dude.
That was close.
Okay, I'm safe.
There's only one way to cure my nervousness now.
I gotta have a cigarette.
So he puts a cigarette in his mouth in the darkness of night, being pursued by aliens.
He's like, "There's only one way to cure these blues."
A little bit of that flame, flame, click, click, lights is lighter.
The aliens immediately realize where he's at.
He goes unconscious.
Not the smartest decision, Sanon, but when you got a smoke, you got a smoke.
Actually, that's not true.
If you have to smoke and you're being pursued by the supernatural, don't smoke, then.
What happens next?
He's missing for five days.
The people in the collective, they wake up the next morning and they find his food there.
They find his equipment, but he's gone.
They're like, "That's out of character for him.
He's normally eating food and owning things.
This is weird."
So they begin a search party for him.
Five days later, though, in another part of Russia, this truck's driving through the forest
and this dude comes running out of the woods all sweating and stuff.
He's like, "Stop, stop, stop."
Truck stops, he gets in.
"Dudes, do you have a cigarette?"
"I'm super nervous."
And I have a story to tell you.
Now, he goes back to town and he tells this insane story of what happened.
Now, a lot of times people get abducted by aliens.
They're sitting on a spaceship.
Maybe they remember it.
Maybe they don't.
But sometimes they're given the whole environmental spiel.
Sometimes they're medically experimented on.
This guy had a close encounter of the "interned" kind.
You like that?
Does that make up for the boring joke?
It does, doesn't it?
So what happened?
You're like, "No, it doesn't.
I don't know the context."
Okay, I'm going to tell you the context and then you'll laugh.
He was taken to a slave labor camp in the middle of Russia.
So what happened was the aliens pulled him into the beam of light and the next thing
he knows is it's daytime and he's sitting in a swamp.
And it's super gross everywhere, right?
And the first thing he's like, "Oh man, this is super stinks."
He said there was a film covering the whole area, right?
And he's all grody.
I mean, also he's a captive of aliens.
I think he was more worried about, "Oh no, my freedom."
Not like, "Pewwee!
I thought you were going to take me to a nice smelling prison."
He's on earth.
He's in a swamp.
And he sees it full of humans.
There's actually a ton of humans.
There's still some giant aliens walking around, but it's full of humans and they're walking
around like zombies.
Now their arms stuck out, but like robots.
And what he's singing, he sees these humans walking in the woods, gathering berries, twigs,
and stuff like that, putting them in sacks and dropping them off in front of the aliens
and then walking away.
And he's like, "Dude, dude, what's going on, man?
Like, what's going on?"
And the people are ignoring him.
They're just like zombies.
So it doesn't take him long to deduce that they're under the aliens' control.
And he starts over the quote, he's there for five days and he comes up with some interesting
analyses.
One, everyone's a slave.
I mean, that's the most interesting part, right?
These aliens are controlling a bunch of people.
One, you have a bunch of slaves walking around too.
You had men and women slaves, but the women had their faces covered with handkerchiefs.
So you couldn't see their faces.
And more importantly, they couldn't see anything either, but they're still able to expertly
navigate the bog.
So you have this bog and then around it is a burned out forest.
I don't know how many, I don't know how berries grow in burned out forests.
Maybe the berries are planted after the fire?
I don't know, I don't know nothing about nature.
But apparently that's what happened.
I guess that's actually a quibbling detail.
There are alien slave labor camps.
I'm worried about where berries come from.
The women had handkerchiefs wrapped tightly around their faces.
You couldn't see their face.
They shouldn't be able to see how, but they could expertly navigate the bog.
Now, they would be just walking across the swampy ground, not slipping, not falling,
anything like that, as if someone is controlling them like a puppet.
Now there were metal planks, there were like metal plating laid across the ground as well
that kind of made a gangplank, but they weren't always walking on that.
Sometimes you would just be carrying bags of berries, dropping them off at these alien's
feet.
There was also another subset of aliens.
They were shorter.
They were wearing these cows and like little hoods, like they're little superheroes.
And they seem to be controlling some sort of silvery net thing, which makes me, it isn't
going a lot of detail of that, but I'm almost wondering if that is some sort of, I mean,
I can make up anything at this point.
We don't know, but you said there was some silvery net they operated.
I wonder if that was only us like, you know, when military is doing stuff in areas, they'll
throw up that camouflage netting.
So if planes are just going overhead, it looks like a bunch of bushes are down there.
I'm wondering if there was some sort of cloaking, because it was a big area.
It's not like they were sending up helicopters looking for this dude.
He was just like a missing dude from the area.
He said that the smaller aliens were operating some sort of silvery net thing.
He said that you had these people that were acting like slaves.
They were completely under control of something else.
And then he noticed two piles.
Now generally piles of anything are not good unless you're Scrooge McDuck and you're going
to your own house.
When everything's are described as piles, they're normally not good.
They're either referring to the piles in your stomach because you can't defecate or piles
of horrible, that's horrible too, but or piles of stuff you don't want.
He sees these two piles.
One of the piles is freshly dead humans right off the assembly line dead.
And it was dead men.
There were no dead women.
It was dead men.
And then oddly enough, red-headed children.
What?
That's a weird detail.
And it's details like that that either makes me think that this guy is completely insane
or telling the truth.
That would be a weird detail to lie about.
He sees a pile of dead men, adult men, and in that same pile, much of dead red-head kids.
No women.
He doesn't see any dead women in this pile.
And I have a theory about that, a very grim theory, but we'll get into that in a second.
You're like, Jason, I have no idea what you could, the madness that you can pull out of
this pile.
I have no idea what's coming.
The second pile was people that he thought had been dug up from graves, people much more
decomposed in a separate pile.
So it's not like this was the Monday dead and then they just slowly got rotten.
He said that he saw a pile of bodies that was a combination of men, women, and children.
I'm so sorry to present Joe's like shaking his head.
He's like, really, this is the episode I'm on.
Sorry, sir.
He sees another pile.
It's dead men, women, and children.
And he says they looked like they'd been dug up from the grave.
So maybe they're wearing like old Victorian clothing or something like that.
He could tell they were super old.
He goes in that pile, the aliens seem to be experimenting on the bodies.
So I have a theory here.
I have an interesting theory here.
What if you have the human men walking around and then you have the women walking around
with the handkerchiefs on their face.
My original theory was that we always have stories about aliens banging human women.
They go far back to the Bible times.
You get stories of the Nephilim coming down.
And when I was reading the story originally, I thought maybe the women had to cover their
face because they're so hot that if they didn't have their faces covered, the dudes would want
to keep banging them.
So instead of that happening, the overseer is like, dude, you can't, you got to stop
banging these women.
Look at all these illegitimate, superpowered babies that are running around.
You got to stop doing that.
They had to cover up the women's faces so the dudes weren't getting all like spacehorning
and stuff like that.
But then I thought, that's ridiculous.
That's ridiculous.
Then I thought, what if the reason why there's no dead, freshly dead women, sorry, this is
a super disturbing.
The reason why there's no freshly dead women is because the aliens were taking the corpses
of women and turning them into robots.
And the reason why they wear handkerchiefs isn't because they're super hot.
It's because they're super gross and there's like worms and stuff coming out of their face.
Now I have no evidence to back that up.
I don't want evidence to back that up.
I just think it's interesting that we don't have any women in the freshly dead pile.
I can't believe I'm saying these phrases out loud.
And that their faces are covered up.
I'm wondering if the aliens were digging up the, because they weren't experimenting on
the freshly dead corpses.
They were experimenting on the gravedug corpses.
What are they bringing women, like old dead women and stuff and then, oh my God, turning
them into robot zombies.
Okay, what if the aliens were digging up Queen Elizabeth, old, like old ancient person,
like 1500s Queen Elizabeth.
And then turned her into a robot.
Catherine the Great's walking around picking berries.
Anyways, to be fair, Sannin doesn't say any of that stuff.
He would turn around and be like, what nonsense are you talking?
He's just saying he's seeing these humans walk around acting like robots.
Now this is the interesting thing about this story, other than the pile of bodies, the slave
labor camp and the aliens.
The aliens begin to command him to go pick berries.
And he will go off into the forest and he starts harvesting berries.
And then he's walking back and he starts slipping in the swamp.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Falls on his butt.
Berries go everywhere and aliens are like, what?
He knows the aliens are giving him commands, but they're not working.
He really quickly realizes he doesn't have to go into the forest.
He starts going, no, I'm not going to do that.
He's over attending.
He's alighting in the pile of bodies.
They're like, Sannin, we know.
Come on, dude, we can see you breathing.
You're reading a magazine.
We know you're not dead.
And he's like, I'm not working for you guys, dude.
And the aliens start getting-- these aliens have perfect mental control over this whole
group of people, but not him.
To the point that he can't navigate the swamp.
He can't do things the way that these people, they can be blindfolded while perfectly through,
because whoever controlling them can see where they're going.
The aliens start threatening him and they're like, dude, just pick up Barry.
Just one Barry, bro.
One Barry and don't slip on your way back.
And he's like, no, you pick your own berries.
The aliens eventually just stop even paying attention to him.
He basically is such a pain in the butt that interstellar travelers are just like whatever.
After five days, a massive rainstorm hits the area and he thinks, I think it's my chance
to get out of here and he runs away.
He gets back and then he's seen on the road.
To be honest, I don't think the aliens look too hard for him.
They're like, no, stop, please.
Come back where your cab-- okay, he's gone.
Thank God that guy was annoying.
We want to do what we said.
It's an interesting thing because it's possible in this article I was reading, it's possible
that the fact he was deaf made it so the aliens' commands didn't work on him.
The fact that he couldn't hear them.
Even though the voice-- we have so many times where the voices are in the head.
You hear it in your head.
Even though he was getting telepathed to commands, the fact that he was deaf is possibly why
the commands didn't work on him.
What's interesting is we saw in 1990, in summer and fall, in Russia, there's four other stories
of people being abducted of acting like robots of meeting small aliens with little cows on
their head.
A group of girls was being kidnapped from a campsite.
They were walking like robots through the river until the boys woke them up.
There was a mother and her three young daughters who got teleported away and ended up in a
field with a bunch of other people.
They were acting like robots.
She said that she knew she was in trouble.
She couldn't control her body as she's walking across this field and she saw her young daughter
and another group of people being led away with this other group and she's panicking
but her body was moving.
She couldn't control her body, which is more terrifying, obviously.
Being a slave is awful.
Being possessed, having someone else control your body is awful.
And then having your own soul being like, "I don't want to do this.
Why am I doing this?
Please no, daughter.
Come back.
Come back."
And not even be able to shed a tear because your body is being manipulated by somebody
else like a marionette puppet.
That's all terrifying stuff.
So we saw, I saw four other cases in Russia in the same time period that had similar incidents.
But only Sanin.
All of these people, all the other people got away but Sanin was actually able to resist
them for five days.
It's interesting.
And I'm wondering if the fact that he got away from them in the first place, that pulling
force that was pulling him towards the light.
We've talked before, I did an episode a long time ago, if our gray aliens actually evolved
dolphins.
And it was the fact that when aliens paralyze you, they're using a sonic attack.
Like a dolphin can stun its prey with a sonic attack.
These aliens can give you this sonic attack.
If you can't hear, that probably won't work.
Even though the voice is in your head, if there's still a biological sonic component
to them having power over you, he's just like, "No, I'm not going to do it.
This is lame.
I want to go home."
And he just waits till it starts raining and the aliens probably would have let him go
home earlier if he had just wandered off.
It's an interesting idea because I've come across several stories where people get abducted
by aliens, the aliens run a couple tests and go, "Now, we can't do nothing with you and
they'll drop them back off at Earth."
The aliens may, for their technology to work, they may need to have somebody be "healthy"
of typical health.
Which I mean, fine.
They're abducted by aliens and it turns out that you have some disease and they drop you
off.
That's one thing.
You might feel a little disappointed.
But this guy broke out of a slave labor camp because of his hearing issue.
I mean, there's a whole other host of issues going on here.
One, alien slave labor camps operating on the planet.
He said that the aliens were actually living underground and they would come up and they
would take all the supplies back underground.
And the woman who was kidnapped with her daughters said she was going up and down a ladder.
There was a civil...
And they all take a place in Russia, all over Russia.
But again, if they're getting teleported around, then it doesn't matter if you get kidnapped
in Moscow or get kidnapped in the Urals.
It doesn't matter.
But because they're just going to where the aliens were.
But even she described there was an...
These are all coming from different sources.
I found them all on ThinkAbout@Docs.com, but they got them from different books, different
articles.
So even the articles of the time weren't putting these stories together.
It's an interesting question because it makes you think, are the aliens that easy to beat?
I mean, it may not be as simple as throwing in some earplugs, but it might be.
You know, I'm not saying if I'm at your alien's corner you pull out an ice pick and start
going at your eardrums.
Don't.
Don't do that.
But all of this advanced technology, the ability to teleport people away, to bring starcraft
across the cosmos to get into your head.
If all of that can be beaten with a pair of $2 earplugs from Rite Aid, bring it on aliens.
It's an interesting story because despite the fact that him being deaf might have made
him a bad night watchman, it might have given humanity a hint on how to defeat aliens if
the time ever comes.
I'll tell you this.
I want to keep a pair of earplugs on me because if I ever get abducted by aliens and they
pull out that PowerPoint presentation on peak oil, the greenhouse effect, while they're
backsturned, I'm going to put my little earplugs in.
The whole time I'm just going to be nodding.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, that's a tragedy, man.
Sure glad you came across the cosmos.
Tell me about recycling, bro.
Good job, aliens, and I'll just be nodding.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)