Today we talk about a bunch of stuff on the first and last Hangover New Year's Day special
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
I need to drink more water.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day over here, having a great day too.
I am hungover.
Now when I say the first and the last, it's not the first and last New Year's Eve or
New Year's Day episode because we'll have many more of those.
But it will be the last episode I do hungover.
Yesterday wasn't just supposed to be the bonus episode.
I started to record this episode.
I was going to really sit on New Year's Eve.
I had one beer.
It wasn't even a beer.
It was one of those straw burritos.
It's just a margarita and a can.
I proceeded to talk about Bird Box for 20 minutes straight and I was like, "I can't
do this."
I went and I edited up the bonus episode.
I have a really low tolerance to alcohol.
Then I went out.
So quick note, my buddy Aaron, he's a listener of the show.
Hey Aaron, he invited me to his show.
He's in a rock band called Sundiver, great band.
I wish I could have paid more attention to the lyrics because he says there's a lot of
cool concepts in the lyrics.
But in live shows it's kind of hard plus by that time I had three more ciders.
It's not just regular, a lapel cider.
And I was pretty blitzed.
Then I came home and just kind of stumbled around my house for a while, went to bed,
woke up today, ate my body weight in Taco Bell and now I'm recording this episode.
Once Sundiver starts to get some music recorded, we'll definitely see about playing some of
it on the show.
It's a really good band though.
I think a lot of it, when we're talking to Aaron, a lot of it crosses over to the same
topics we talk about here.
So I'm not going to talk about Bird Box for 20 minutes like I did on yesterday's Scrapped
episode.
I wanted to highlight two scenes.
Now, first off, let me back up.
Bird Box is the biggest hit movie that Netflix has announced.
They said they had 45 million views of that show within a week.
And it's a horror, sci-fi horror movie about a world where it's the normal world, but one
day these invisible ghosts or demons show up.
And if you look at them, you either get so sad you kill yourself, you get so afraid you
kill yourself, or you fall in love with them and you keep running around and going, "Open
your eyes!" and you try to take people's blindfolds off or hold their eyes open.
It's completely ridiculous, completely ridiculous.
Premise and the movie doesn't work on multiple levels, but I'm going to break down my 20-minute
review into basically two scenes because this really, early on, this happened and it set
up everything.
The star is, who's that chick?
Sandra Bullock.
But Sandra Bullock and her sister are driving away from a hospital where they just saw a
bunch of people kill themselves.
Because this infestation or whatever has just come to the United States.
And the sister is driving the car and she said, "We need to get to my ranch.
I have supplies there.
It's off the grid.
No one can find it because they don't know what's going on."
And after watching multiple people kill themselves and on the news it was showing this was happening
worldwide.
Someone makes that offer to you.
There's a mysterious disease causing people to kill themselves and someone says, "I have
a place completely remote that's stocked up on supplies."
The normal person would be like, "Just fine, whatever."
Sandra Bullock goes, "What?
What will I wear?
I owe my clothes or at my apartment.
We have to go to my apartment first."
And then, which is completely stupid, and then the very next scene, they're still in
the car, a huge explosion blows up behind the car, like maybe two or three blocks away,
but a massive explosion.
And Sandra Bullock goes to the driver, her sister goes, "Go, go, go, go, go!"
And the driver goes, "What?
I can't run a red light."
The whole, and they just sat there for a while and then they started driving, the whole movie
is that.
It's people's personalities changing scene for scene.
Sometimes Sandra Bullock is very caring and we're like, "We can't let this guy go back
out there.
That's suicide.
We have to take this guy in."
And then she also has her kid and her friend's kid.
They both gave birth at the same time as one of the Colt members who was running through
the house trying to open their eyes up.
And she has both those kids for five years.
She gives birth to one and the other little babies there and the mom jumps out of the window.
So Sandra Bullock with two babies, five years later we go into the future and she named
the kids boy and girl.
So it's like she's sentimental towards total stranger.
It was supposed to be like she wasn't ready for motherhood or whatever, nonsense like
that, but in some scenes she was totally close to strangers and other scenes she can't even
like name these kids for five years.
It's called bird box because she has a box full of birds.
Birds make noises when the monsters are around.
And the whole climax of the movie is her rowing a boat down a river blindfolded.
I've seen some stupid, implausible stuff in movies.
But rowing a boat blindfolded down a river, it takes the cake.
I've never seen anything that dumb ever.
Early in the movie they drive a car blindfolded and they kinda are like "well this car is
GPS and it has like these sensor warnings, but you would be in a, if you did a boat blindfolded
for more than two minutes, you're totally gone."
It's like a six mile journey.
It's completely ridiculous.
So yeah, that's it, bird box.
Don't watch it.
Sorry guys.
Better luck next time, Netflix.
It was better than Cloverfield Paradox.
Kinda.
Okay.
So, as my dehydrated body, my husk sits here.
Still soaked with four ciders.
Trying to rehydrate.
Let's take a look at some New Year's traditions stuff.
I thought it was interesting.
Because I was trying to, I was like "are there any New Year's ghosts?"
There's always a ghost walking on a hall somewhere, but that's not interesting to me.
So with all that being said, let's talk about Pizza Gate.
It's only barely connected to it, but it all started off with a Pizza Gate thread on Twitter,
which eventually brought in the daughter of Hillary and Bill Clinton.
So Chrissy Teigen.
Chrissy Teigen is a model and she's been around forever.
I'm not calling you old Chrissy, but you've been around for a while.
She posted on Twitter, she posted pictures of a little girl, and her little girl was
dressed up as a hot dog, as a pineapple, and as Alice from Alice on Wonderland.
Not all of the same time.
As awesome as that costume would be.
A hot dog dressed up as Alice with a pineapple on it said.
It was three different costumes.
And then another tweet, she tweeted the emoticon of a slice of pizza.
So the Twitter people jumped all over this and said "oh my god, Chrissy Teigen is part
of Pizza Gate."
Look at these photos.
And other people were like "oh my god dude, how can you deny that these photos are pictures
of Pizza Gate?"
Here's why.
Alice from Alice on Wonderland is supposedly used by MK Ultra agents to brainwash young
girls.
You know Alice falls in the looking glass, the mirror.
Anytime you see Alice in Wonderland imagery, it's because the Illuminati wants you to see
that.
They're showing you that that's how they brainwash young girls.
And hot dogs.
You're like "well hot dogs are all American."
How can that be associated with a French revolutionary group of masons from the 1700s?
What does a hot dog have to do with them?
Well a hot dog is a code word.
You should know this audience.
Oh what a...
I can't believe I have to even explain this concept to you.
It's so obvious.
A hot dog is a code word for a young boy.
I should dump you for the Pizza Gate audience.
How can you not give that reference?
Now obviously your question would be "why is the little girl dressed up like a hot dog
then?"
Hold on!
Don't think too much about it.
Just post a bunch of comments and like this video on YouTube.
And if it's so funny on the tweets they're like "yeah I don't know what pineapple means
that the pineapple has no code in this Pizza Gate mythology.
It's just pineapple."
So they couldn't fit that in.
Anyways, a couple of the tweets and I've actually discovered this too.
We talked about Hans and he believed that men are women and women are men and there's
this big thing to...
That's actually way bigger than I thought it was.
I thought it was just a Hans thing.
There's tons of people who believe that most women are really men and most men are really
women.
So we'll have to explore that again.
But in these tweets they bring that up and they're like "Yeah Chrissy Teigen's a man
anyways" and other people are like "What?"
And there's one person who said "Hey, whoa whoa whoa, I believe in Pizza Gate but you
know you gotta knock off with this trans hatred."
So it was this weird...
Cause the dude just threw it out and was like "Yeah, you know it's a man.
What do you expect?"
Anyways, Chrissy Teigen responded to this and said "I normally don't respond to this
type of stuff but you're assaulting my kids."
One of the people on Twitter said "Look at the kids...
Look at the look in that kids eyes."
It's very common.
That's what sexual assault or that's what abuse victims look like.
That's pretty low dude.
That's someone's kid.
That they're like wearing a costume and you're saying "Yeah, but that kid gets abused."
That's pretty jacked up.
So Chrissy Teigen responds to this and she's like "Hey man, you guys are making fun of
my kids."
Like kind of crossing the line.
And Chelsea Clinton responded to that tweet saying "Hey, you know, happens to me.
I don't mind when they make fun of me but when they start making fun of my daughter and
threatening my daughter, I report all of those."
Now the beautiful thing about Twitter is you can have somebody who is super duper duper
famous, super powerful and whatever and anyone can contact them in public.
There was a thread recently where Mila Jovovich was just randomly talking about movies like
resident evil movies and someone tweeted back "You suck!"
And she was like "I suck, you suck, you'll never be on the set of a movie."
And then total, I mean it's probably a fake account.
Someone created, yelled at a huge movie star and flipped her out.
So Chelsea Clinton, daughter of Hillary and Bill Clinton, reaches out to a Twitter friend.
They don't really know each other in real life but a fellow mom and says "Hey, I go through
it too."
And then someone with the account called Rogue Hooters staff, like a rogue member of the
restaurant Hooters, just says "Eat shit Chelsea!"
And it just tagged right to her.
That's the greatest thing about Twitter.
So that started a big thing where people were then contacting Hooters and saying someone
is using an account that makes it seem like they work for you to insult an ex-president's
daughter so then Hooters had to get involved and say "Hey, we don't have anything to do
with this account."
Once Hooters gets involved, Chrissy Teigen is like "What is happening?"
Like "Hi Hooters, that's her exact tweet.
Because you have these two powerful famous women and a restaurant that is known for busty
women and potwings has to get involved."
Chelsea Clinton responds in 2017 "At Church of Satan and I were put on a few threads together
in 2018.
It's Hooters.
What a time to be alive Chrissy."
The Church of Satan, because she tagged them in this, the Church of Satan responds "The
never-ending excitement here is never-ending."
And then Chelsea Clinton responds "It's been so long, happy new year."
And in that she tagged Church of Satan, Chrissy Teigen, and four other people, most likely
Hooters and whoever else was in the thread.
Now that happened earlier obviously in like January of 2018.
So people took that seriously.
It's funny because it's on Snopes.
Did Chelsea Clinton tweet "Happy New Year" to the Church of Satan?
And it's true.
Because she did.
So you have to take it in the context of all everything that happened before that.
It was kind of this thing like, what a wacky world we live in.
First I'm connected to "At Church of Satan" and now I'm connected to "At Hooters" and
I'm this person and it's just, I'm a mom and it's just such a weird thing.
But that actually made things worse for her.
And Pete's a gate and everything like that.
Even Sarah Palin, Vice Presidential Candidate Sarah Palin, chimed in and then a bunch of
other just normal people chimed in saying, you know, this just goes to show what we're
up against.
This is Peter Wood, this is the Satanic Elite, so on and so forth and blah blah blah.
Yes, she did wish "Happy New Year" to the Church of Satan.
But it's so bizarre that all the context is gone from that.
A lot of this stuff has to be about the context.
However, of course, this just threw fuel on the fire because now Chelsea Clinton is talking
to someone who's accused of being, dressing her kid up as a hot dog and now the Church
of Satan's involved.
You know, is Hooters part of the Illuminati?
I don't know, it's hard to keep track of all this stuff.
But yes, she did.
It is true.
She did wish them a Happy New Year.
But again, yeah, it's all about the context.
So New Year's traditions.
We've talked about Chelsea Clinton ringing in the New Year by talking to the Church of
Satan.
Did you know?
No, Franz is not showing up.
Even though that is his character, that is his official phrase.
I should get a shirt made that just says "Did you know?" as a picture of a guy named Franz.
But did you know?
Did you know?
No, no, Franz, I just did Franz on Bam McGarr's afterlife.
He can't come back that quickly.
But did you know that there is actually a movement, it's probably like three people,
now they actually believe it, that New Year's Day is Satanic and so are New Year's resolutions.
So the New Year Day, the New Year Day being Satanic, that's a fairly, that's not a very
controversial belief.
The idea is, and it's true in the sense that when Christianity began to take over Europe,
they went the path of least resistance.
People had traditional holidays, pagan holidays, and the Church says, "Yeah, that's Jesus'
birthday."
Because they really don't care.
They're like, "This is when everyone gets together and hangs out, we'll just rename
it."
They did that with churches and holy sites and holidays across the board.
Apparently in the Bible, there's a part in Exodus where God says to Moses and Aaron,
I think Aaron's his son or something like that.
Maybe it's just some other dude who's just like, he was like a time traveler who just
hung out with Moses and he pops up occasionally in the Bible.
I wonder if there is a time traveler in the Bible, like Bible times, like just chilling
in the background.
Okay, so Moses and Aaron are hanging out and God goes, "This month shall be unto you the
beginning of months.
It shall be the first month of the year to you."
Fades away.
So, what he's talking about is back in Hebrew times, there was, they used a different calendar
obviously because they had no idea what Julius Caesar was.
They, they're basically, when God was saying that, it was the month that is between our
modern March and April, which is supposed to be the new year.
And we have it on January 1st, therefore New Year's Eve and New Year's Day are satanic.
Those aren't the days that God wanted us to worship or wanted us to celebrate as the
new calendar.
I don't think he cares, dude.
And actually the website I was reading, it was from a book that was published in 1964,
hasn't gained a ton of traction.
It's a belief because again, I don't, that's such a minimal thing.
It's not a holy holiday when you celebrate the New Year's, it's simply just a day to
say, "Hey, it's new beginnings."
I don't, we're not a farming culture.
The reason why the logic saying that God assigned that time is their new beginning is because
it was harvest based.
You gotta pick your battles sometimes.
Like if you're trying to save the souls of humanity from eternal torment, if that's what
you truly believe, I don't think getting them to put down their poppers on December 31st
is a good tactic.
You gotta choose your battles.
And I think that's what Rome was doing.
Just the church in general, they're like, "Whatever, dude.
Yeah, Jesus was born right now.
Your old holiday is gone.
This is the new one."
They're just choosing their battles.
So on its own, I didn't find that one super compelling.
However, there's a trick that I've learned.
You can type in blank conspiracy.
Someone believes a conspiracy about that.
And I talked about that on episode four or five, a long time ago.
But the problem is, a lot of times it just pulls up criminal conspiracies.
However, you can, into Google, not just, I shouldn't be specific, not just type it into
a text file, you have to type it into a search engine, you can type anything blank satanic.
Someone will believe it's satanic, oddly enough.
No matter what you choose, if you put in laundry detergent satanic, I'm sure something
will pop up.
So when I typed in New Year's satanic, I found this old article.
But then, oh man, I think I hit the jackpot here.
Did you know, did you know that not only is New Year's Day satanic, but New Year's
Resolutions is one of Satan's greatest weapons against humanity.
So I'm gonna read from this article here.
It starts off with a bombshell.
It starts off with something that I always personally believed, but my mind was blown
when I read this sentence.
Here's the first sentence of this part.
A society is not a chimney.
Oh, what?
I, oh man, I always compare society to a chimney.
I, I was, I thought I was the only person who ever even saw the two connected in any
sort of way.
But this guy, this guy knows, man.
Society is not a chimney.
You know what?
According to this guy, a chimney is built of bricks.
Okay.
You stack up bricks one on top of the other, and at some point you have a chimney.
I think you have to have a little more planning than that.
I don't think you can just stack bricks up and you have a chimney.
I think you have to design it and it has to be like a shape with a hollow tube through
it.
But it's analogy, whatever.
A society is not a chimney because a chimney is built of bricks.
You stack one on another in any sort of random order with no design, whatever, and eventually
becomes a chimney.
But actually, no, I'm adding the but.
He doesn't add the but.
This is his quote.
A society, in a way, is built up of spiritual bricks, i.e. resolutions.
But doesn't that make it like a chimney if now it's built of bricks?
He has this weird, it's almost like he's going by the most strict definition.
Of the word resolution as possible.
When people say, "Away, what's your resolution for the new year?"
It's a goal.
It's a decision you're making.
We tend that they're good resolutions, but something to be like, "Oh, I'm just going
to drink as much alcohol as I can tonight."
That's my resolution.
It's a goal.
It's you're making a determination to do something.
I'm resolved to do this.
He goes into this whole thing.
Think about the police forces, for example.
A policeman has a uniform, a badge, often a firearm if he's lucky, or he could be in
Britain.
But what distinguishes a true policeman from a uniformed bandit?
What happens when policemen abandon their resolution to serve and to protect?
You gotta have both of those in there.
They just can't serve.
The material objects remain the same, the uniform, badge, pistol, but the spiritual
brick shatters, crumbles, and disappears.
What does any of this have to do with a new year's resolution?
The title of this article that I'm reading from?
New Year's Resolutions, A Satanic Plot?
And I cut out where he spent the first third of the article.
He came up with this weird mathematical formula to show what a resolution was.
But anyways, so yes.
But that's not when people say, "Oh, what's your resolution?
Oh, my resolution is uphold the law, because I'm a police officer and that's my job."
That's not what we think of when we think of a New Year's resolution.
He then goes on to say stuff, "Think about banks.
Do you think that the money in your bank is really inside a big vault with your name on
a stack of dollar bills?
If the bank decides to abandon their resolution to give you your money when you ask for it,
you're broke."
But that's not what people mean.
Now, he goes on and on with all of these examples of it, but I gotta get to the meat of it.
This is the section entitled, "How Does Satan Attack Resolutions?"
There's no "I couldn't make this up."
Satan doesn't have huge biceps or money or an army except for the millions of demons
at his control.
And I think Satan would be pretty fit.
I don't think he'd be super lanky or incredibly fat.
I think he'd probably have huge biceps, maybe not 33 inch pythons or anything, but I don't
think he would be someone who you'd be like, "Man, you need to hit the gym, Lord of Hell."
I think he would be pretty ripped.
Satan doesn't have huge biceps, and he has all the money in the world if he's tied in
with these Illuminati guys, but anyways, Satan doesn't have huge biceps or money or an army,
but he's the owner of a kind of big marketing consulting firm.
Satan is a liar, and the father of lies.
I wonder who the mother is.
I wonder if that's just a turn of phrase, or if it's supposed like, "He gave birth to
lies."
I guess the snake lied for the fruit.
I don't know.
Since Satan wants to destroy everything that is good in our society, he must attack the
very substance of the spiritual bricks that make it up.
Therefore Satan does everything he can to give bad publicity to good resolutions.
One of Satan's favorite tricks is to throw dirt, throw a handful of dirt, on the reputation
of resolutions using his famous New Year's Resolutions ad campaign.
So I imagine Satan sitting down in hell, and he's like, "Oh man, humanity's been doing
so good for the past 10,000 years.
There haven't been any sort of wars.
People aren't just murdering each other in the streets.
There's no terrible diseases.
If only I had some way to stir the pot up on Earth."
He's like, "Nah, it's not good enough.
What I need to do.
We need to straight up madmen this.
We need to get an ad campaign going."
They're like, "Whoa, devil.
Devil."
He's like, "My name's Satan, dude.
Don't call me devil."
Okay, Satan.
Satan.
What?
What do you think we should do?
What do you release more Ebola?
He's like, "Nah, it's child's play."
You know what?
I hear, have you guys ever heard of the term "spiritual bricks"?
And they're like, "What now?"
And Satan's like, "Me neither."
But we should tear apart these things we've never heard of by starting a thing called
New Year's Resolutions.
The other demons are like, "Ooh, yeah.
We could have these start during March between March and April."
And Satan's like, "No, we have to do it the Satanic New Year, January 1st.
What do you guys think?"
And the demons are like, "Oh yeah, sorry."
So Satan has set up the idea of New Year's Resolutions.
And here's why.
Back to this article, or leaving hell to back to this article.
The poor, gullible suckers who bite this diabolical fish hook always bitterly repent afterwards.
The New Year arrives and they are filled with good intentions, so they leap.
Quick!
I must run a marathon right away since I'm fat.
That's me, no fat person ever says they have to run a marathon right away.
And at the same time, I'll do my income tax return since I'm always late.
And while I'm running with my computer and my bundles of invoices under one arm, I'll
hold a paintbrush in my mouth and a canvas under the other, since I've been wanting to
learn oil painting for years.
What are the probabilities of success for such an endeavor?
About zero.
I would say that's beyond zero.
You're fat, you're running a marathon, you're doing your taxes and you're trying to paint
at the same time.
But back to the article.
But this is exactly what Satan wants.
He wants people to take as few resolutions as possible and to take them as incorrectly
as possible in conditions which practically guarantee their failure and especially that
they create as many bad memories as possible.
He didn't laugh in the article, that was me.
Also apparently Satan, father of lies.
And lord of the flies, it kind of rhymes.
And has this huge demonic army and according to this guy isn't fit, but I'm sure he has
at least a barbell set in hell.
He has all this power, magic basically.
He can be invisible, he can tempt people, but his main plan is having like whispering
in people's ears, "You should lose weight."
He'll never lose weight.
But the problem with that is that what if the dude loses weight?
And he's like, he goes about it the right way and says, "I'm fat, I should run a marathon.
Next marathon's in eight months, I'm gonna do it."
And Satan's like, "Dag, nab it!
I should never whisper it in his ear to lose weight.
Now I'll have to wait 60 years to capture his soul."
But you know, again, it's one of those things, like this dude was reaching, he had to come
up with such a strict definition of the word, I think he was working backwards.
I think he was probably sitting there smoking the Christian equivalent of marijuana and
thought, "Dude, what if New Year's resolutions are Satanic?"
And then worked backwards to prove his point.
That if I have such a strict version of the word resolution, then it's, New Year's resolutions
are something you say you're gonna do and you're right, not a lot of people do it, but
it doesn't create bad memories.
You just go, "Oh yeah, I totally forgot I was supposed to learn how to play guitar this
year."
You don't sit around and cry about it.
And to be fair, if it is part of Satan's plans, most people's New Year's resolutions
are pretty self-serving.
So you think that would work against Satan, because New Year's resolutions are stuff like,
"I want to buy a house.
I want more money.
I want to lose weight so I can be more attractive to attract the opposite sex."
That's all very, really kind of selfish.
Not a lot of people do New Year's resolutions when they say, "I want to give more money
to charity."
Normally, it's something material and say it should be like, "Yeah, yeah, do it.
Lose weight and buy that house.
That's all that's important.
Don't worry about your spiritual growth."
Do it.
You think it would be the opposite, but again, clever little trick.
You want to find anything bizarre, just type in "blank Satan" or "blank Satanic" and you'll
get stuff like this.
The idea of Satan running a marketing firm, though, I just imagine him with one of those
tripod things and you have the sheet of paper on it and you flip it over.
He says of all night on these huge sheets of paper, writing down his marketing plans,
and then he takes those into the office with all the other demons.
He sets up the tripod, puts the big sheet of paper on it, and instantly he rubs it
in flames and he's like, "Oh yeah, forgot I'm in hell."
How would you have a marketing team in hell?
What are their desks made of?
I mean, everything would have to be stone.
You can't have a computer down there.
It's all on fire.
Everything, I mean, all of your legal documents would be on like five miles of rock.
Go walk three miles over that way, that's where the fine print is.
I'd like to give this diet gotten a benefit of the doubt and not think that he actually
meant that Satan ran an actual marketing firm, but or marketing campaign, whatever the term
was.
No, it says he's the owner of a kind of big marketing consulting firm, so maybe he
has a bit of an outlook because he said kind of, but it's still, I just imagine it's a
place called like Satan and Sons and you go in there and you go in there and you're like,
this is my product tower we're going to sell in.
Satan's like, "Discarded baby flesh."
There's a market for that somewhere.
He sells it to Avon.
I just love the idea that God's eternal, apparently God's like spent the past 10,000
years preparing for the final war between good and evil and Lucifer's down there making
ad campaigns for IBM.
I love that idea.
I'm just imagining at some point in the future, Satan's going to be sitting there going over
a pie chart that's made out of pebbles and seashells and then all of a sudden he's going
to look up at his clock and go, "Oh wait, I forgot Armageddon's coming."
And then just a bunch of angels show up and just lay waste to his entire empire.
And Satan and Sons, that's just where I'm going to start getting all my marketing done
from.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @JasonLCarvinder.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Sorry for the vibrating mic there.
Have a great day guys.
Bye.
[Music]