Is there a magical elixir that can elevate us to a new consciousness?
And you know that famous Bigfoot video, the famous Bigfoot video of the Bigfoot walking away,
turns to the camera and looks? Is it possible that that Bigfoot was walking away from the scene
of a Bigfoot massacre today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. We have a lot of stuff to
cover today. I'm just gonna jump right into this. Our next story, what we're gonna do, is we are
going to talk about Ormus. Now Ormus is something that you've never heard of, most likely. It can't
be tested scientifically. It's all around us. And some people call it mana from heaven. Some people
call it Cleopatra's milk, I think. I think someone called to that. It is this elixir that you take
into your body and it enlightens you spiritually. It aligns, I don't, if it doesn't align your chakras,
it aligns a hell of a lot more than that. It can actually like bring you to a point.
It can bring you to a point where you can astrally project while you sleep, not just dream,
but project, float around. All you need to do is make it yourself. Or you can conveniently buy it
at retailers all over the internet, the most trusted source to buy things, to put into your body.
Yes, a website, most likely created by Squarespace, that is selling you something that you ingest
into your body that they claim science has no idea what it is. Yes, we are climbing down the
Ormus hole. So what actually is Ormus? The explanation is, not even they really know. The people who
sell Ormus seem to be very, very unclear on what this stuff is. The scientific claim that they make
is it is monoatomic. So it's any element, most like it's usually gold, but it's any element
broken down to a single atom. Okay, so it makes it so small that it's invisible to science. And I
thought atoms were visible to science, but apparently not. And then you break an element down to one
atom. And then step two, I don't know. And then step three, you eat it and you gain spiritual
enlightenment. It helps align both sides of your brain, because brains aren't built to do that anyways.
It gives you energy, gives you a calm and focused mind, stuff that wouldn't occur any other way
unless you took this element apparently. So you go, Jason, I don't have gold and I don't have the
way to break it down to a single element. And like I said, hey man, just buy it online. That's
what a lot of people are doing. But there's another way you can do it. You can make this Ormus,
this miracle mineral yourself. You can make it yourself. I can't believe this. Let's listen
to this quick clip from this YouTube video explaining to us how to make what they know as
the philosopher's stone, this pure magic, this pure height of alchemy. Okay, listen. First off,
I can barely hear what the YouTube video is saying and that's, I get that. That's fine. It's on YouTube.
The quality is not always perfect. But you're giving me a recipe that involves lie, drinking
lie and it is one of the most vague recipes possible. Get some salt, boil some water,
put some lye in it, maybe some vinegar. Let's sit around for a while and then drink it. No.
Don't do that guys. Don't ever, first off, don't get a recipe off of YouTube that involves a lie.
That's step one. Step two, don't drink this stuff. And you go, okay Jason, I don't want to use this
YouTube recipe. There has to be another way for me to get Ormus. There is. You can make it out of
your own urine. See what happens is we piss out all of these minerals that are so useful to us.
And using proper chemicals, lie included, you can get the minerals, those precious minerals you
just peed out and drink it again. And this website has photos, photos of a man holding various stages
of his urine as it's becoming more and more cloudy and white. He's like, I'm not going to buy your
store bought Ormus. Ormus coming from my bladder is far more potent and you should get it from
your bladder too. Here, here's a couple photos of watching my urine get old.
Listen, I get it. I take multivitamins. I take my little rose droplets to give me energy.
I get it. We want to have that quick fix that little, you know, maybe for some people to caffeine,
some people it is vitamin C or emergency or whatever. I take my vitamins every single day.
I feel like it keeps me healthy and gives me energy. Guys, if what you are, if you are buying
something to put in your body and they are telling you that science does not know what it is,
don't do it. If people are telling you you can make your own with lie, don't do it. And please,
don't drink your urine. I looked up Ormus. I found out about Ormus because someone said,
you know, you can get healthy from drinking your own urine. Like it's actually beneficial to drink
your own urine because you're pissing out all of these minerals. And I was like, what? And then
that let me down the rabbit hole that yes, there are a lot of people, a lot of people to, enough
that there are competing competitors selling all these Ormus products. It's not just one thing.
There's even, even if you believed in this stuff, that if you can break something down to a single
atom and then step, step, step, you drink it, I think there's, it's so vague. Generally, it's like,
you can break something down with single atom here, we sell these pills. What? How did you get
the pills from the single atom? Because then it's just a bunch of atoms again. You're, I'm swallowing
a piece of gold. They say you can get it from salt. And it's like phosphate and stuff like that.
But you have to use the lie. And you can drink your own urine. Even if you believed all that stuff,
even if you believed you were able to break down something to a, you can, but if you,
somehow, okay, yeah, I'm not going to quibble. Let's say that even you believed that and it was
some sort of magical property. There is a website that is selling a digital version of this, a digital
mono atomic Ormus thing. So you can buy this stuff. What they do, these are their steps. It's,
scams drive me nuts. And you can go Jason, you're getting scammed because you're buying calcium
pills. No, I'm buying calcium pills because my diet is garbage. I eat hot dogs and hamburgers
all the time. That's all I eat and pickles. So I need to take calcium supplements and magnesium
supplements and biotin and I take my daily vitamin. I take all this stuff because, and I feel great
because I don't get that stuff when I eat. I eat hot dogs and hamburgers when I, because I'm on
keto diet and I know people like there's more to keto than that, but I'm just a picky eater.
So I have to take my vitamins. There is no digital vitamin A. I can't instead pull out my iPod
and put in my headphones and get digital vitamin A. This stuff is so made up. You can do that with
Ormus. Let's see how they make a digital Ormus. One, we use a first they extract, we use a proprietary
computer software and innovative energetic encoding techniques to capture the energy,
i.e. informational data field of these various substances in digital format. That makes no
sense. Step two, we amplify it. We then amplify that extracted digital signals many times in a
balanced way. You're just making it up. Three, encode. The final step is to encode the amplified
signature and you know I'm done reading their nonsense. Ormus has no health benefits whatsoever.
It is a made up substance that people are selling you to put into your body and it is 100% the
placebo effect and I know this for a fact because the websites that sell Ormus can't even agree
what Ormus is. They some are saying it is these five elements. Some people are saying it comes from
salt. Some people are saying it comes from plants you grow in the soil. What plants don't grow in the
soil? I'm just gonna eat corn then and not drink lye. It's invisible to science you can't test it
so therefore it works. Scams drive me nuts. They drive me nuts. I gotta wrap this up real quick
but we have someone who posted onto a Ormus forum. This isn't all results but this is quite telling.
Okay I've been on the stuff for about three months even taking a three day Ormus retreat
whatever that is but then we'll go on. I have a variety of strange symptoms. Anyone else got
anything to add? Currently I'm having Cundi pains whatever that is. Cundi is some sort of like
it's like the spiritual energy. I don't know why it would be hurting but anyways sometimes very
painful but also very temporary. Sharp pains all over my body at random times so if it's some sort
of like spiritual pain whatever it's all in your head anyways the Ormus is fake so it's not really
affecting you. Then it says mouthful of blisters and canker sores that's not in your head. I mean
literally it's in your head but you're something's wrong. Heart palpitations in the morning actually
waking me up from taking Ormus for three months but then they go on to add that Ormus is causing
them to have awesome dreams and meditation so you know I guess the heart palpitations balances out
with the awesome dreams and the mouthful of blisters and canker sores. I can tell you what's
causing the blisters and canker sores. You're eating lie. I hate scams. Let's go ahead and move
on to the next story. Now this story is something that intrigued me when I saw it on the iceberg
a couple months ago. Didn't think I would ever find anything on it and I looked I couldn't find
anything despite all of my amazing research efforts. I mean guys we have to admit at this point I am
a top notch researcher. I nothing gets past me and I looked probably every two weeks I tried
looking for this topic again and despite my track record tracking down these great stories I could
not find this one and then I realized I was spelling it completely wrong. So yeah it's
the Patterson Gimlin tape and I was calling it the Patterson Gimling or possibly Patterson Gimling
from Lord of the Rings. So I that honestly happened multiple times and I go damn there's no
I can't find this story that I want to cover and then I was on another thing reading about
Bigfoot and I was like that's how you spell his name and I spelled it incorrectly and a ton of
resources popped up so today we are going to talk about the Patterson Gimlin Massacre. So quick
overview here Patterson Gimlin Bigfoot tape is the tape we've all seen. It's the 20 seconds of
film footage of Bigfoot like strolling through the woods with that unique walk and it turns and it
looks at the camera and then keeps walking and all of really like the Bigfoot stickers it's such an
iconic pose where it has its arms stretched out as it's walking that you'll see that pose on stuff
everywhere. Hood River we have a ton of Bigfoot paraphernalia and it's funny because I don't think
Bigfoot's been seen here but it's very popular. You'll see him like carrying a pizza you'll see
him like dribbling a basketball and I'm saying he it's actually supposedly a woman named Patty
a Patty the Bigfoot named Patty but anyway so the Patterson Gimlin tape has always been
considered the most authentic Bigfoot video out there but so the Patterson Gimlin that's his name
right I keep wanting to say Gimli Patterson Gimlin tape is that famous 30 40 second clip now
we all see that and we go oh look at Bigfoot's actually possible like there is a person that's
walking not like a person and looking like a big old monkey but maybe there's more to the story
maybe there is more to the story so that Patterson Gimlin tape it's called Patterson Gimlin because
Roger Patterson and Robert Gimlin are the ones who made the tape it was shot in Bluff Creek,
California on October 20th 1967 in 2008 there was a Bigfoot enthusiast named MK Davis and what MK
Davis he made his name in the Bigfoot community because he took the original footage of the Patterson
Gimlin tape and stabilized it and got at like a better picture so it wasn't so shaky and so they
were like oh this guy like has really helped make the footage easier to view and brought up the
quality and things like that in 2008 he starts looking at the footage and he goes that's a blood
puddle like right off camera and there's like a flash also off camera like the flash is on camera
but there's like a flash to the left side of the screen as Patty's walking away and then he has this
additional footage that he says shows it wasn't Patterson and Gimlin at Bluff Creek shooting
us there were 10 people there total and there was a Bigfoot massacre a bunch of big feet a big thigh
if you listen to the parapod a bunch of big five were there three of them actually and what we're
seeing is Patty running away from the slaughter of her two friends and apparently there is a close-up
of Patty they did an enhance like CSI you can see a single teardrop coming from Patty's face
now you can look at these they have photos of the additional footage you see some guys
standing there and some red puddles and you see like a dog and these guys kind of look like other
Bigfoot researchers they've said look at this guy this guy is skinny and here's this Bigfoot
known Bigfoot researcher who's also quite skinny they're both white they might be the same I haven't
seen the actual footage I've seen stills of the so-called off-screen footage apparently there
were multiple cameras there but I've seen the stills and you do see them stand on there and
there's some like red puddles and then MK Davis goes look at there were similar red puddles in the
Patterson Gimlin tape it appears that there was a massacre Bigfoot enthusiasts are like what are you
talking about there's so much controversy over this because this tape has been a mainstay I mean
it just people were outraged by that they're like no you you adjusted the color this was just a dark
patch of water and you made it red and so on and so forth and and there was all of this pushback
on it Dave David Pallades the guy from missing 411 he got involved in it and he was like oh no
not publicly but apparently in private circles with the Bigfoot community he's like oh no there
was a massacre there so you're like where I think since we haven't seen the original footage
and MK Davis who's to this day contends that there was a massacre there the two other Bigfoot were
shot what what other where did the story come from did MK Davis just sit there one day and like
discover this extra reel of footage was he just editing it and then he slowed like hit a button
in the camera slowly moved to the left and he saw this going on people were putting their
reputations on the line David Pallades if I'm not saying that right but him most of all a lot of
people see him as like this big researcher into the paranormal and now he's making this claim
that a bunch of Bigfoot were killed without footage all we have on the Patterson Gimlin tape
that shows anything like that is a Bigfoot supposedly running away in a red puddle so where
did this story come from why would people put their careers quote unquote careers on the line
to expose this story with so little proof it must have been a great source right the original story
of the Patterson Gimlin massacre was came from a creepypasta the here was the basic gist of the
creepypasta a couple guys start a band they make it big in Hollywood they meet with a producer
in Hollywood and the producer is like yeah guys what's up yeah let's rock this party yeah yeah
by the way I have a secret footage of two Bigfoot being murdered and the band's like what
and so they see the video and then they tell their friends back home and they're like dude we saw
like two big feet getting shot we saw two big fire getting shot and apparently what the other
addition is you see three Bigfoot Bigfi sitting at a fire or a fire pit and there's just a
hail of bullets reload I don't know if Bigfoot go oh but this one did and then Patty gets up and
runs away and then they just happen to have another camera 10 feet away and they just recorded Patty
running away the hunters were like immediately like oh no we killed two big fi what are we gonna do
we could take this as evidence that the world's most mysterious creature exists but what if we're
found guilty for murder we better skin them right here and take out all their meat and take their
bones and destroy everything so no one suspects us of murdering a creature that no one knew existed
for sure until we shot two of them so that's why they just like the bodies disappeared
and then they didn't say anything they're like oh my god if anyone finds this footage of us killing
these two animals so let's destroy all the evidence that these creatures even existed even
though we're out here specifically to prove they existed and that's the creepypasta it's literally
something you would see like on reddit or creepypasta.com or whatever it is just a story about a guy
telling a story that his buddy went through oh i got a call from my friend he's in a band and he
told me this crazy story if that happened if a bunch of people descended upon a camp of bigfoot
yeah you would have people that are were upset but you would have even more people be like oh that
sucks as you shot him but finally we have proof that these things exist because you know and they're
like oh yeah no they just dispose of all the evidence but they believe totally in bigfoot
they're there purposely to find bigfoot it doesn't wash it doesn't wash and it's weird to me that
mk davis and david polides i can't david polatus whatever that they would be willing to
put this theory forth based on creepypasta and a couple of photos of just random people standing
around a campsite with a red puddle which again can easily be photoshopped in it could be blood it
would be a lot of blood and it's just like all in like where a creek would be so it would be very
easy to just change the color saturation on that photo but Patterson Gimlin massacre i think
it didn't happen i think that it's 100 of creepypasta that got out of hand and once they once these
people i think david polades has kind of backed away from it but again he never really dressed it
publicly like to us in the bigfoot circles from what i could see he was talking about it but mk
davis continues to put this story forth and he's wedded to it now he can't say oh no i was wrong
you're right it was creepypasta i was looking at the footage wrong oh and that gunshot blast that
apparently comes from the Patterson Gimlin tape which is like the official tape people said that
wasn't in the original version that was added i can almost imagine this little cartoon like bang
coming off the side insane stuff and again creepypasta i i think somebody read this who had never
read any creepypasta and thought that it was a true story and then began to prove it existed
i would hate to see what would happen if this guy ever read like jeff the killer i mean he would
go on he would go to the town he would go to every town where a new kid just moved in and ran into
some bullies and try to figure out the truth behind jeff the killer it's fake stuff and you've
ruined your reputation over it mk there was no massacre there there's a big question over whether
bigfoot was actually there but there definitely was no massacre there but again once i learned how to
correctly spell gimlin it was an interesting little mystery to explore so that's it that's our episode
we kind of buzzed through that i i don't know if i can keep up that pace but i actually kind of like
that i had a little timer this time that went off every nine minutes so i was able to kind of keep
i was kind of able to punch in three good stories and uh we'll see how that works out we'll see how
that works out dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast you
don't have to listen to it every day but i'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys