was half a billion dollars recently spent by the US government to train the army to fight
reptilian super soldiers?
Huh?
Probably not, but let's take a look at it anyway so who knows, it could be wrong.
And then we travel to Colorado to take a look at a haunting deep within Dead Man's Canyon.
Is there really a chopped up bloody ghost hiding in the bushes?
And when he leaps out of the bushes, hands wrapped around our throat were forced to ask
the question, is he trying to murder us or does he really just want to hug?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm Coach Jason Carpenter, I'm having a good day, I hope you guys are having a good day
too, I hope you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend.
I'm gonna go see Smile, that'll take up about two hours of my weekend and the rest of the
time I'm just gonna walk around in a circle, hoping for the best.
But someone who always gets the best walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one
of our Christmas livestream contributors from way back in 2022's Christmas special.
Come on in, come on in, he's dressed up in his little uniform, he has on the military
uniform, he's dressed up as the Nutcracker, that's your military uniform, a 19th century
Cossack walking in.
St. James, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode, if you guys can't support
the Patreon or the livestream or whatever he did to get on the show, that's fine too,
this helps spread the word about the show that really really really helps out a lot.
Now St. James when he donated to the Christmas livestream, he put in a request and that's
why it's taken so long to get to you, he specifically requested he wanted to be part of a military
episode so St. James I hope you got that musket loaded, I'm gonna toss you the keys to the
Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy, we're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command, take us deep into
these tunnels leading underground.
I have a theory, I think most people enjoy war as a concept, I don't think they love
it personally, I think like if you could have all of the cool stuff about war, people getting
blown up, buildings collapsing up, people running from it and stuff like that, you could have
all of that cool stuff, people would be like more pro war, you'd have to be protest being
like more war, more war, I think, maybe I'm wrong on that, Jason yeah you're completely
wrong on that, I find war fascinating, I find the idea of two groups of people smashing
into each other and then fighting over contested territory and things like that and I also
find the politics behind war very very interesting, but when you look at the human cost, that's
what I'm saying, you got all that stuff that is a little more boring and a little more
tugging at your heart strings, you got refugees and then you got people buried in the rubble
and their hands sticking out and papa papa let me get you out of the rubble and they're
like no you can't do that, there's like three tons of rubble on your dead, that hand hasn't
been moving for a while bro, I don't think your dad's still here, nobody likes that
part of war, nobody likes that part of war but in theory, I think that's why we can
watch war movies and play war video games and buy war toys, but when a real war breaks
out you're like come on guys, can't you resolve your differences in another way, does that
make sense, I think people enjoy war in theory and I'm one of those guys, I'm one of those
guys Jason yesterday, the only guy on earth who you could possibly think that you can
separate the two, I can watch war movies all the time, I can't tell anyone apart cause
I have facial blindness the whole movie, I'm like which one's Ryan, they all look the same,
but I can watch them, I just you know someone has to go that one, the guy who's clearly
Matt Damon was even in the movie, that guy right there, that's the guy, I can't tell
anyone apart if they're wearing a helmet or they all have a bus cut, I really can't, I
like those movies, I can play video games or I'm running around blowing people's brains
out, but if someone gave me a rifle in real life and said see that guy over there, he
did something wrong to your ancestors you gotta go blow his brains out, I'd be like
I don't know this isn't so fun anymore, does he have a gun too, they're like yeah and it's
like okay now it's definitely not fun, cause there's a chance my brains get blown up, in
theory war is pretty cool, so I do read articles about like the military and stuff like that,
I find the whole theory of it fascinating, well recently this article came out, not
only is it a cool look at the future of warfare, it actually, I'm surprised the conspiracy
theory community isn't eating this up, before I started recording this episode I went to
darkoutpost.com that weirdo conspiracy website I go to, that guy's in love, David Dobrik actually
that's not his name, what's his name, Dave something or another, he has this show called
darkoutpost, Dave Zublik and he's like in love with this woman, he keeps, I almost wanna
do a story on it, he keeps Photoshop in this picture of this woman, into all of his videos,
she gets interviewed, but like he Photoshop, like he, there's a photo of her just standing
here like with her arms crossed, and at first he would just have that in his thumbnail,
and then like a photo of him, and now he's actually like copying her pose, so it makes
it look like it's, they're in the same photograph, it's super weird, I mean this guy's talking
about all sorts of stuff, but he's not talking about the story we're about to discuss, right
now he's doing a thing about who's causing the reoccurring date of the Mexican earthquakes,
he says that monkeypox is caused by the COVID vaccine, which is a whole other ball of wax,
right, he has that, no one else is talking about this story and it's insane because we're
underneath the earth, St. James is on point, he's walking rifle ready because we're about
to engage with the reptilian empire, not really, okay, that might have been a bit of an exaggeration,
let's get to the story, but this is fascinating, I'm surprised no one else is covering this,
I read this really cool article written by Matthew Cox for military.com, and just recently
it has been revealed that the army, the US army has spent a half a billion dollars to
train the majority of its battalions, I think it's like 28 out of 32 or 28 out of 34 battalions
have been trained or are training right now in underground warfare, and the idea is this,
the US military says the next wars are going to be fought in the mega cities, we're all
going to go to judge dreads reality after the dimensional merge, these military basically
they're saying listen the next war is going to take place in the mega cities, you're going
to have just block by block warfare, now a lot of it's going to be leveled by tanks,
a lot of it's going to be leveled by airstrikes or drone strikes, things like that, every
war ends with the infantry moving into an area to be able to security, you have to be
able to walk through the city and look in the pantries and be like nope no one there,
probably you should check the closets in the basement first before you're looking for some
crustables to eat because there's obviously not a gunman hiding in the cupboard, you're
just really really hungry, they said this is really where the next war is going to be
fought, but the other thing is they go we also have to be able to fight underneath those
cities, we have to go underground into these massive structures and they said some of these
structures are underground, they're talking about sewers and subways, they're also specifically
talking about Russia which has a massive underground complex that was built up during
the cold war so they could pretty much hide most of their population or at least the
ones they deemed worthy, underneath the ground, you have whole cities down there that you
can move stuff around, they go we're going to have to put troops into places like that
and for the longest time we've trained our special forces to fight underground because
we're going after groups like Al Qaeda, we're going after groups like ISIS, things like
that, but they go once we start fighting what the term is called peer warfare right, you're
fighting people who have the same level of technology or maybe better, the same level
of troop training or maybe better, you can't count on having these small groups in there,
this is fascinating, they were talking about one of the countries they were really looking
at was North Korea and they said North Korea has, this is crazy, they have 4,800 underground
facilities in the country of North Korea, this is a new manual that came out according
to the army's subterranean manual, I mean that just sounds dope right, they said quote
North Korea could accommodate the transfer of 30,000 heavily armed troops per hour and
they said that these complexes just crisscrossed throughout the country, so you could move
30,000 troops and no air photos are going to pick it up, thermal scanners aren't going
to pick it up, nothing and they would just pop out of these areas, they would be determined
that these are like the 5 main exit points, but even if you put a couple of people together
to watch, there's 30,000 people per hour jumping out of there, just be like this huge swarm
and they also reference they go North Korea, they have an air base inside a mountain, that's
like over commander level stuff, that's the things we see on 80's cartoons, I don't know
if they have a really cool thick metal door that goes up and like jets fly out, as Kim
Jong Il stands here with his hands on his hips, they'll never stop me now, he should,
I don't see why not, he already has an airport built inside of a mountain, they said we got
to train, not just our special forces, we got to train everybody to fight underground,
this is so crazy and they showed in this article by Matthew Cox, they showed like a diagram,
they showed like a drawing from the military manual and they were showing a bunch of troops,
like they showed like all this, it was like inside of a tunnel and they showed like a
bunch of troops standing around and then they kind of like outlined the other things you
would need to worry about in a tunnel as opposed to really anywhere else and it was obviously
there'd be no lights, there'd be zero visibility, everyone would have to have a flashlight,
which is basically a shoot me here sign to someone standing at the other end of the tunnel,
right, you see a bunch of flashlights, you see a bunch of headlights, you see a bunch
of head lamps and you're just like, you stand in the darkness, you know, they're coming
in and you just shoot at anything that's lit up, you just have this big bull down, oxygen
monitors, you could totally wipe out a whole battalion of people by just shutting off the
airflow, like how would you even be able to measure that without an oxygen monitor obviously,
like you don't think about that, you're never outdoors running around shooting people out
of trees and you're like, Joey, Joey, stop, can you breathe, can you breathe there, they're
like, of course I can breathe there, I'm in the jungle, there's oxygen everywhere, underground,
I mean you could have gone underground and walked a mile in with a bunch of troops and
then everyone just drops dead, when you have like a soldier run has to carry a canary,
so they have to have oxygen monitors with them and I can't even imagine the chaos of
a firefight, I mean there's whole first person shooter levels where you're in like a subway,
what's that thing called, I think it's just called the subway but you know like a terminal,
subway terminal, you have whole maps based on that, you're beneath the terminal though
sometimes, you may be in access tunnels underneath that, crawling doing the little crouch crawl,
in real life you don't get to just hold down the C button, you're like, oh my legs hurt
and you're like crawling down, how insane is that, how insane is that, but just as a
interesting thing I wanted to tell you about but also like this plays 100% into the conspiracy
theory that reptilians have massive facilities underneath the earth, I am shocked no one
else in the conspiracy theory community is really talking about this, what's, this is
my conspiracy theory, earlier this week there was a big article in the conspiracy theory
community or a big story about that badge, about that group, I think it was the national
intelligence, let me pull up the exact name of it, yeah they recently had a patch that
was really or a seal for the NIM aviation group and on it you saw a picture of like
a plane, a newer plane, a supersonic plane, a drone and then there was a little UFO in
the corner and that's been all over the blogosphere, they're like, oh dude look at this, they're
finally revealing that they have a UFO, they have access to the UFO clipart, out of the
military you get this, that's been going around, it's kind of a fun story for some people,
I guess it was a mock up, because people have really gone into the designs of those other
planes and they said those are actually foreign planes, most of those planes are enemy aircraft,
so it looks like someone was just taking clipart and putting it on, it was like a mock up
and then someone goes hey you know what would be fun if they tried to UFO in it and then
it got posted to an official website, it's a fun story, it's a fun story but my conspiracy
theory is that popped up to kind of cover up this other story coming out, that yeah we
spent half a billion dollars to train our troops underground because they didn't want
to know about the reptilians, it's still a UFO related right, misdirection right maybe,
are they actually getting ready to fight these alien overlords underground, would they be
under lords at that point, who knows, probably not, they're probably actually training to
fight other humans, which the reason why I like stories like humans fighting aliens
and underground stuff, because again I like fighting, I like war, but I don't want to kill
other people, I remember when I walked out of Starship Troopers, I'm old enough to have
seen it in the theater in 1997, I walked out of the movie and I said I would totally join
the military if I didn't have to kill other people, like even if it risked, even if it
felt like my limbs might get blown off and I might have sex, I might end up having sex
with Dizzy, I would totally do it, I would take that risk because I'd be fighting bugs,
I'd be fighting stuff that actually now the thing about the whole point of the movie was
that bugs are people too, they also have feelings and things like that, they get scared, but
yeah I'd go I'd do it, I would totally throw grenades at stuff if they weren't other humans.
So I would love the idea that week would be fighting underground, they put all the guys,
actually here's a crazy conspiracy theory for you that I just came up with, what if you
had, what if you dosed your soldiers so the enemy looked like aliens, they looked like
cheap, cheap Halloween outfits from Spirit Halloween store, that's all I ask for, all
I ask for is for an intergalactic war so I can blow things up and not be other humans,
I'll be like hey brother, we're both on the same side now right and he's like yep and
we're just like shooting some people from another planet, they're totally innocent,
they came to bring us all the gears and we're like you're not one of us bro, we're blowing
them up, ships taking over other planets and we're like yeah, yeah this is what I've
waited my entire life for to conquer another world, St. James, let's go ahead and toss you
the keys of the carbon or copper, we're leaving behind the battle-scarred planet known as
Elysium I, not very peaceful anymore is it aliens, take us all the way back to Earth,
we're headed to Colorado Springs, Colorado, Colorado Springs Colorado, Colorado Springs
Colorado, we were actually in Colorado earlier this week, we took a look at a haunting, took
a look at a haunting within the city of Denver, we're gonna go farther out from there, don't
ask me which direction I didn't look at a map, but in Colorado Springs, Colorado, there's
a place known as Dead Man's Canyon, or is there?
I didn't look at a map, I can easily verify it if it's still called that.
Back in 1863, there's this little place called Little Fountain Creek, doesn't that sound
inviting right?
Little Fountain Creek and there's this cabin there and there's a man named William Henry
Harkins and he wakes up in the morning, he's like oh what a lovely day, the sun's rising,
beautiful fresh mountain air, I don't have a machete embedded in my head, this is just
a lovely day, what could possibly go wrong?
Well maybe he shouldn't have been bragging about having the brains inside of his skull
because a short while away there was a group called the Espinoza's Brothers, the Espinoza's
Brothers, it's kind of a mouthful, there was five of them and these guys were religious
fanatics, doesn't say what religion, but I'm gonna guess Catholic right?
I don't think they were like Sufi or anything like that.
The Espinoza Brothers, they were these religious fanatics that were running around the area,
they're also really angry with America and Americans because Spain lost the Spanish American
War.
I start from side to side, it's like I probably shouldn't have done research on that as well.
I'm pretty sure they won because most of America is still America, all of America is still
America and Spain's a tiny little country.
I'm looking at that, I didn't know America and Spain fought, I know we had wars in Mexico,
there was the Mexican American War, America went to war with Spain, I was like really
I don't remember this, I don't remember ever learning about this, we learned about the
Mexican American War and the French Indian War, but what?
I mean that kind of sounds like a corp stop honestly like Spain so far away and they
got like their giant galleons, they're floating in America just like shooting camera, like
how did they even, did they deploy troops there?
I don't know, I don't know I probably should have looked at some of this information up,
anyways you know me, I'm all about the ghosts, I'm all about the ghosts.
The Espinoza Brothers were ready to get revenge and they began moving throughout the area
and they were killing minors, they were the job and not the child, they were killing minors
and they were killing ranchers, people would be out there being like run little doggies
run and they're riding their horses and they're rustling up cattle and stuff like that through
own lassoes and then all of a sudden the Espinoza Brothers would jump out of the bushes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
you'd be sitting there with a pickaxe being like I finally found me gold, Leprechaun got
a job as a 49er, he's like I got it and the Espinoza Brothers would block off the tunnel
and you'd just see these silhouettes of five people and you're like no, no, not the Espinoza
Brothers, no, and what's interesting about these guys is that the way they killed people
seems inefficient.
I mean I guess they are serial murderers who are destroying people just because they belong
in the wrong country according to them but they would, I had to double check my notes
so I was like really did I type this in wrong or something?
They would chop you up and then shoot you.
It sounds like inefficient right because everyone had guns back then so like as these five dudes
are coming towards you you're like and I imagine you'd be shooting at them and they'd like
they were just chopping you up and it's like shouldn't it be the other way around?
You figure you'd shoot them in the gut first and then you'd like fall to the ground and
then they would chop you up, not they'd be like coming at you with machetes and stuff
like that hatches.
I don't know maybe it was a torture thing, I don't know maybe it was a religious thing,
they were religious extremists, who knows?
They would chop you up and then shoot you.
Well one night William Harkins is at his little cabin here in Little Fountain Creek
and who shows up?
The Espinoza Brothers and they embed a cleaver right into his head, stack and as this
as they do like you're like oh okay guys oh you guys got me, you guys got me real good,
I got this cleaver in my head, I guess we're even now, you know I didn't do anything wrong,
okay you guys can leave.
Then they shot him, they shot him and then they robbed him which at that point I mean
whatever they're gonna do whatever right, you got a cleaver embedded in your head, you
shot a couple times, you're not like oh no my precious moment figurines as they're putting
them in a bag, you're already going to die, you're not dead already.
Well, law enforcement was obviously on these guys tail for a while, they were trying to
put an end to these brutal murderers and after the murder of William Henry Harkins they corner
the Espinoza Brothers, they do it right, this is how things are normally done in America,
they shoot them first, they did this one by one, they're whittling down the Espinoza
Brothers numbers, they would shoot them first and then decapitate them.
After all five brothers were killed, the posse showed up at this party, I guess it was a different
time, they showed up at a party and threw the Espinoza Brothers heads into the middle
of the party, that sounds like the best Van Wilder movie, they should do a Van Wilder
1863, basically the entire movie, a bunch of people get horribly murdered and then
Ryan Reynolds shows up and starts throwing heads around the party and then someone eats
a donut full of dog semen, that's still the most bizarre thing I've ever seen in a movie
at movie theaters watching that, Ryan Reynolds tricks a man into eating a donut full of dog
semen, I was like what?
What world am I living in?
People fun died during the Spanish American War, so I gotta watch this movie, what is
going on?
Anyways, fast forward, let's fast forward a bit in time, but not too far, these ghost
sightings we don't have a date on them, but they do seem to be around the time period,
people started seeing the ghosts of William Henry Hawkins in the area and when he appeared,
he would jump out of the bushes and he would have a cleaver stuck in his own head and he
would jump out of the bushes and he would pursue you down the canyon, that's his home
turf, he knows every crook and crevice, he knows where the stream is a little more streamy,
you gotta make that jump, he knows all that stuff, you're just walking through, maybe
you're on like a wagon train, you're like riding your horse and then some dude jumps
out with a cleaver and he's like this is the last thing you expected, right?
I mean this guy is chasing you and people would shoot at him constantly and bullets
would go right through him obviously because he was a ghost and then they would go oh,
maybe I shouldn't have wasted my bullets because I'm out in the middle of nowhere and I can
get a bunch more bullets, maybe I shouldn't be shooting at this phantom, but you know
the first couple of bullets obviously, you would think that it was a man with a cleaver
in his head and he was going to put the cleaver in your head, what's interesting about this
is that the fact that the dead have come back to life, we have proof of the immortal soul,
that type of stuff, is that we have this story from 1884, so yeah all of those stories would
have really taken place between his murder in 1884, so we're talking about what a 19
year period, there was a woman named Grandma Wyatt and she was riding through the area
with her grandson, she was taking him home and all of a sudden out of the bushes jumps
William Henry Harkins cleaver deep inside of his brain and he grabs her skirt, so right
there we have the idea of whatever this phantom is, it can manipulate physical matter, it's
super rare, despite what you see in horror movies, it's actually really rare that a phantom
can grab onto you, this thing grabs onto her skirt, now this guy William Henry Harkins
looked so lifelike, everyone assumed he was real, including Grandma Wyatt, when this burly
man with bloody face and cracked open skull jumps out of the bushes and grabs her skirt,
she beats him up, she starts punching this guy and she says we have a quote from this
woman, she goes quote you old buzzard how dare you scare a baby like that, she's referring
to her grandson obviously, and then she says this is weird, maybe she's turned on by men
who have after brains missing, she says you old buzzard how dare you scare a baby like
that, I'll be back here later though, she actually does say that, I'll be back here
though later, and if you bother me I'll give you a what for again, now get from here, like
why would you be telling a guy who jumps out of the bushes instead of an ambush being like
you know you scared that baby but don't worry I'll be back I'll be alone, maybe she was
looking for some lovin, we don't know but anyways as she's punching this dude, he disappears,
and that's when she realizes he's a ghost, so obviously if this story from 1884 about
a punching grandma is true, her punches were landing, they were actually hitting some sort
of physical object, it was able to grab her clothes and interact with her, super rare
in the world of paranormal, super super rare, fascinating, jump to future times there's
a group called a paranormal group called enam paranormal, and they decide to go and do
on the ground investigation of this area, they go out, and listen I've done a lot of
on the ground ghost hunting type of things, you do have to bring protection with you,
whether that's pepper spray, I mean obviously you know like your religious icons, spirit
box whatever device you're using but you also have to have like real world protection, pepper
spray, knives, crowbars, bats, nunchucks whatever you have available, they, and I get it right
you're out in this canyon, worried about bobcats maybe, or a ghost jumping out of the bushes,
they bring a machete with them, they're walking through the darkness of dead man's canyon,
and they have this machete with them, and apparently they start to feel that the ghost
is angry, they can actually say that they can feel the essence of William Henry Harkin,
so they go maybe it's not a good idea to bring an, bring an edged weapon around a man who
was killed by an edged weapon, so they actually get a blunt weapon instead, like I don't know
both staff maybe, and they go back walking through this area and they said they're able
to register a temperature drop in the area, they get EVPs, and they said that after they
replaced their edged weapon with a blunt weapon, the ghost seemed friendly, actually seemed
welcoming to this group called a NAM paranormal, which leads us into a bigger topic, really
two bigger topics, first off is, I had this story prepped to go a long time ago, I had
it ready to go, but just for whatever reason it never fit into a particular episode, so
when I was pulling it back up, I was checking my links again, a NAM paranormal is gone,
it was a ghost research group, their website's completely gone, the link I'll put in the
show notes but it's dead, there's no archive that I could find either, that's so disappointing
and sad, because we have these groups doing these on the ground investigations, paranormal
investigation it's a labor of love, and there's a lot of money attached to it, and I think
a lot of people get into it, hoping they can make enough money to even just pay web hosting
fees, but over time, maybe they can't, maybe they can't afford to keep the website up,
maybe all the members are ghosts themselves, maybe they're all dead and there was no one
left to pay the bills, and so the website's down, which means all of their investigations
are gone, all of their notes, everything is gone, their EVPs, and that sucks, it really
is when you look at the world of the paranormal, the world of the paranormal investigators
to be specific, UFO investigators, big foot investigators, they just disappear, I've
been going through a thing where I'm trying to archive these big sites, I've downloaded
the entire site of thinkaboutadocs.com, I mean the process of downloading the entire
website of the shadowlands.net, not to repost, but if those websites ever do go down for
good, we do have a record of all the research they've done, because it does suck when this
stuff completely disappears, but also I wanted to take a look at it, because I think when
you look at the phenomenon as a whole, we can take, this is definitely an anomaly, it's
a ghost that can interact with living people, it can grab them, it can be hit by them, it
appears lifelike enough that people are completely shocked when they shoot at it and it doesn't
stop it when they're punching it, they don't realize it's not human until it disappears,
so it's not a wisp, it's not just some vapor, it's not someone with Casper legs floating
through the bushes, it looks like a real person who suffered a severe injury, that's interesting
in and of itself, it can interact with the real world, super interesting, but I'm thinking
about this and I go, you have a ghost that is attacking people, and then when we have
this group of NAMM paranormal that shows up later on, it does seem to be helpful, or not
necessarily helpful but friendly, what happens to ghosts when they stop being visited?
Now we know some ghosts just dissipate over time, that seems to be kind of the accepted
wisdom in the paranormal community, that's why we don't have caveman ghosts, that's
why we don't have ghosts of Centurions from Rome, that's why when you go to Turkey you
don't run into some dude from 600 AD, you don't run into these ghosts that are super
old, most of the ghosts we see in the modern world are around 1800s and forward, you don't
get a lot of ghosts from even the 1100s, definitely nothing from biblical time, where's St. Peter's
ghost floating around, there goes all of my Catholic listeners, they're like, he's not
a ghost, he's not a ghost, he wouldn't be floating around, he wouldn't be haunting, Bethlehem
or something dude, he's in heaven, anyways to my remaining non-Catholic listeners, that
was just an example, where are these ghosts?
And I started to think, okay so he's in that timeline, 1800s, these ghosts are still around,
or do they ever get bored? Do ghosts ever get lonely? Because this haunting isn't attached
to a particular domicile, it's not like he was in a house and the house was burned down
like we covered in the Denver episode earlier this week, and so the ghosts as far as we
know have left, this is a man who was killed in the outdoors and he's hanging out in the
bushes and there was a time where a lot of people were moving through this area, but
now in our modern age, how many people are really walking through Dead Man's Canyon?
And does he stay in the bushes? Is he standing out there and he's kind of like looking for
someone? Like I think about how lonely it can be sometimes to be human, and yet we're
still surrounded by people that if we ever feel like we can, we can reach out to other
people, even if it's just talking to other people online, people in your social circle
meeting new friends or hanging out with old friends or whatever, you have these different
options. But if you're a ghost, you're sitting in the bushes and there's a time period where
you're jumping out and scaring people all the time, but then there's less and less people,
you probably stop jumping out of the bushes and scaring them, but eventually you're just
in the bushes and then 10 years pass and you maybe see five people in that time period,
and then another 30 years pass and you see one or two people. And then 50 years pass,
there's nobody, you know, and you're just kind of sitting in the bushes watching them.
Like that's your whole reality, you can't be like, well, I've waited six in the morning,
I've haunted this area all night, it's time to go hit up that sushi restaurant downtown
Denver, like that's your existence, you're trapped in this valley. If you can't even
say you've watched the world go by, you haven't seen cities rise and all this technology being
invented, you're in a canyon, you're just this ghost hiding in the bushes of a canyon.
Like do you feel that loneliness? Do you feel that isolation has the dead still walking the
earth? How sad is it? Like I wonder if William Henry Harkins is like, man, sure did suck
me and murdered, but I could have at least been murdered in a hotel where there'd be
a bunch of people to hang out with. Or maybe like I got killed in a horrible fire at a
clothing factory. He's all looking at all these disasters, he's like, oh man, I kind
of have gotten killed in that. Who know? Like I wonder how lonely it is to be a ghost. And
you know, I've told this story before in the podcast, we'll wrap it up like this. When
I first moved into this apartment, I sensed the ghost of an old man, an old emaciated
man in my closet, which is where I record my podcast. And it didn't feel like I felt
like it, I wouldn't necessarily say menacing, but it just wasn't a entity I didn't want
to have around. And I remember buying, I bought sage at one point to sage my house and I kept
putting it off, put it off for a long period of time. And then I finally, and I had done
this before, I was like, I should sage the house this week, and I should sage the house.
Then I remember finally one day I was resolute, I was like, I'm going to sage the apartment,
I'm going to definitely do it this week. And then that night when I was sleeping on the
couch, it was like a half dream state type of thing. So you know, skeptics totally, I
totally accept skeptics being like a, I remember seeing him standing in my kitchen. And he
said, Hey, sorry, man, I didn't make you mean to make you feel uncomfortable. I didn't,
you know, that wasn't my intent, but please don't sage the place. I never did. And I wonder
if he was like, he wasn't trying to be menacing, he was just kind of lonely. And I wonder how
many people he appeared to and they couldn't sense him, or maybe they just sense something
was off. Who knows, like I imagine it could, I don't imagine all ghosts are lonely, but
I imagine some of them are. So how lonely would it be to be trapped in that canyon? Just standing
behind the bushes. There was a time period where a bunch of people were walking by. You
jumped out with a big, big, giant cleaver in your brain. It was great. Less and less people
started coming through. Until finally, you know, 100 years later or so, a paranormal
group comes through and you're just happy to be noticed. You're just happy to be visited.
This is a super obscure ghost story. An am paranormal is one of the few places you could
find it. I got it from my favorite book, The National Directory of Haunted Places, which
again is, I think it's out of print at this point. I think most copies are used. I have
three copies just in case you can't find another one, but yeah, it's an obscure ghost
story that should be more well known. It exhibits a lot of things that most ghosts can't do.
Even this absolutely fascinating, even this super rare ghost story is quickly being forgotten.
The ghost of William Henry Harkins is being forgotten as well. Is he still waiting in
those bushes, eager to see another human? It's a sad story of a murder victim turned into
a lonely spirit who still hides in those bushes, hoping that another person will walk by. Not
to chase him through the dark, twisted turns of the cabin, but maybe just to say hello.
I don't know, he does have a big record of chasing people around and grabbing their clothes,
so I don't know, maybe pay him a visit, maybe go down to this possibly treacherous area.
I don't know exactly what it's like, but if you're in the area, maybe go say hello to
this ghost. You may think he's chasing you and that he's going to kill you when he catches
up, but maybe, just maybe, if you turned around as you're running in terror, running through
this unfamiliar territory, if you turned around, you would see the face of Henry Harkin with
the biggest smile he's ever had, because once again, he has a friend. Again, he also does
have a cleaver in his head and he might kill you. We're a little unsure on that, so be
careful.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be our email address. You can also do this up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true
crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listened to
it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
[Music]
(upbeat music)