The heart wants what it wants. The old saying goes, "But is it really our heart
that holds our love or is it the cat poop in our lungs?" You didn't know you
currently had cat poop in your lungs? And then we travel to Los Angeles, California
to take a look at the story of a young mother who's alone with her infant
daughter. When she put her baby to bed for the night and crawled into bed
herself, she thought she was just gonna have another restful sleep. Instead, she
found herself going toe-to-toe against an alien kidnapper today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great
day too. Hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing. Let's go
ahead and get the episode started. Walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our
Christmas livestream contributors. His name means Lion and he's probably as furry
as one. Give it up for Leo. Woo yeah! Come on in. You gotta walk on all fours and do
lion noises as you walk. And Leo, Leo, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this
episode if you guys can't support the Patreon if you're not a furry. I just
outed this guy. That's okay too. Just help spread the word about the show. That
really, really helps out a lot. Now Leo, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the
Jason Jalopy. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. Let's drive all the
way out to a research facility. Driving on out there. And I'm telling you, like,
this is where we're supposed to go to this research facility. Now you're
expecting to see like a white building, probably like two or three stories with
a sign in the front that says something like Cyberdyne or Biosyn or something
like that. But we passed those two places. You're like, "Oh, shouldn't we stop the
future from being all terminators?" Nah! Let's someone else deal with that. We're
driving down and we pass all these research facilities and then we see
this old house. The paint's all chipping off and it doesn't look like the porch
has been repaired in 20, 30 years and the grass is heavily growing over. And I go,
"Here, here's where we're going. Here's the research laboratory." And we're walking
inside. Actually, I didn't even plan this. Leo, you're the perfect person to be part
of this episode. We're gonna visit your buddies. This house is full of cats. And
then we're about to meet the head research scientist. This lady comes out.
Her hair's all disheveled. She's wearing a shirt that has a picture of a cat on it.
And the picture of a cat is wearing a shirt that has a picture of another cat on it.
And it just goes on and on. And this is Matilda Buford. Matilda Buford, the local
crazy cat lady. And you're allergic to cats. You're super confident and itchy. Well,
this is just the first part of the show. You won't be itchy the second part. We're
in this cat house. We're in this crazy cat lady's house. And these cats are rubbing
up against us and putting their scent everywhere. And we're just breathing in the stale air
of urine and cat feces. I really hope none of you guys listen to this while you're eating.
Every so often someone emails me and says, "Dude, seriously? That's not my fault. That's
not my fault." No, you know what you're getting into at this point. The smell of uncleaned cat
litter. Breathing them cat feces. Recently, I was talking to Cabot Cove Balloon Friends,
longtime supporter of the show. We were talking about parasites. We were talking about parasites
rescinding each other photos of our bowels. What are you infected with right now, Cabot?
We were talking about parasites. We were talking about some of the conspiracy theories involving
parasites and the way they affect people. And I did an episode not too long ago about
parasitic castration. And there's parasites that actually make it so you don't want to
have sex or you don't engage in sex. And I said, "Are humans getting infected with that?"
Because we're seeing people just disengaging from the dating world and not having sex and
just playing video games all the time and things like that. Which, you know, whatever.
I don't have a problem with it. I don't have a problem with people playing video games all
the time because I wish I could do it, right? I'm listfully looking at them as their gonads
are being devoured by a parasite. I was like, "Oh, why not me? Why do I have to do all
this work? I don't get to play Minecraft all day long." So I did that episode recently
about parasitic castration. I'll put it in the show notes, but I'm sure you don't want
to listen to it. And then I found this article, though. I found this article really around
the time we were talking about, we were sending photos of our own parasitic infestations. In
Finland, the country that famously doesn't exist, there is the University of Turku. And
a new study has come out of the University of Turku into toxoplasma gondii. This is
the parasite that has taken over the world. And I don't think that I'm being an alarmist
by saying that. Toxoplasma gondii has taken over the planet. What's weird is it can only
sexually reproduce in the stomach of a cat. That's the only place where it can actually
reproduce or the intestines of a cat. I don't think it's like, "Okay, we're in the bowels.
We can't see each other anymore." But it can only reproduce in a cat. But what happens
is when the cat poops, the parasites come out of the poop and they're like, "Oh, no,
I want to have more babies." So when you breathe in cat poop, the toxoplasma gondii goes inside
of you. Now right out of a horror movie, this is so insane. They found out that it can only
reproduce in a cat. Toxoplasma gondii can only reproduce in a cat. But cats poop everywhere
and this parasite is highly contagious. Now it has to get back into the cat to reproduce,
but it's already come out of the cat's butthole. What's it going to do? Well, if a mouse comes
in contact with this, you know, an uncleaned cat lady's house, right? This poop's lying
around, it's dusting off, these little parasites are sailing through the air and a mouse inhales
it. The mouse loses it. They've tested this over and over and over again. The mouse loses
its fear of cats and will actually get into situations that will get it eaten by a cat.
And then the toxoplasma gondii is back in the cat's stomach and it's just having a little
horge in there. It's like, "We made it boys! We're back!" That's straight, that is invasion
of the body snatchers. It actually shuts off the mouse's fear. They've tested it, they've
put mice in rooms that are infected with this and they'll spray cat urine around and the
mouse just walks around it. But a non-infected mouse will smell cat urine and be like, "Oh
dude, I saw a bunch of documentaries called Tom and Jerry back in the day. This dude wants
to eat me and he's gone." Now the reason why that would be fine, right? Who cares what
happens to mice? They're kind of cute, right? They're little cool guys. But they wouldn't
say it's taken over the world if it's just infected mice. The thing is, is that this
also infects humans and we know this and this is the reason why you have the idea of the
crazy cat lady stereotype because in some people, toxoplasma gondi can cause schizophrenia
or trigger existing schizophrenia. There'd probably be another way to put that. Because
studies estimate right now, this was really taken over the world, studies estimate that
between 30 to 50% of all humans on the planet right now have either been exposed to it or
are chronically infected with it. Because when it goes in humans, it's eventually going
to die out. If you're walking by and a cat farts in your face, you're not going to have
to run to the mental hospital. You're like, "Oh no, I'm afraid I'm schizophrenic." But
if you're constantly around it and you're constantly breathing it in, you constantly
have this parasite inside of you. It can't replicate in you. But it's going to do crazy
things while it's inside of you. When it is in a man, when a man gets this toxoplasma
gondi, it's been linked to being a worst driver. This has effects on how people think, the
decisions they make. This little guy sliding around in your tummy makes you, for men, it
makes you a worst driver, makes you more rebellious. You're always talking back to authority.
But in a weird thing, it makes women more warm-hearted, more open to relationships and things like
that. We do those things other than the schizophrenic cat ladies. It also increases a woman's chance
of suicide after the age of 60. These are some weird side effects. It would be one thing
if everyone got more rebellious or everyone got more warm-hearted, but we see a distinction
between the two groups. It's actually more dangerous for, I mean, obviously being a rebellious
man can lead to dangerous situations. Being a worst driver can lead to dangerous situations,
but a higher likelihood of killing yourself over the age of 60, we see that. The very
first time this was detected in a human was in 1938. A baby was born with it. It was actually
in its brains. When the baby died, they didn't know what killed it. They did an autopsy. It
was starting to have seizures, right? And then it died. And then when they did the autopsy,
the brain was infested with this, and so were the eyeballs. And that was the first time science
goes, "Well, this can actually infect a human." The very first time we discovered it in a
human, it killed the baby. So, I mean, it obviously had been in people before. Like, sometimes
these are connected to like crazy rulers throughout time. I remember reading an article, there
was some queen who was super nuts, and they go, "It could have been all of the inbreeding,
but it could have also been she was known to constantly be around cats." So we know
all that. That's all established science. But this new study comes out, and it shows
that this is having an effect on who we find attractive. Like, I've always loved bad drivers.
They've done this study in Finland recently. The disease can spread from human to human
in various ways. But one of them is sexual. It's technically a sexually transmitted disease.
You usually basically, it's really disgusting to think that it comes from a cat's anus into
you, and then you're having sex and you're spreading it to somebody else. But when a
man or a woman is infected with tozmoplasma gondi, they are rated more attractive. Even
healthier looking. They did the study and they took people who tested for it, right?
And then they took people who didn't have it, and they're doing these photos. Apparently
when you have this in you, it makes your face more symmetrical, which is one of the things
across cultures that people look for as a measure of attractiveness. They would show
pictures of people and they'd go, "Who do you think's hotter?" One of them is a cat.
One of them is a cat with its tail up and some guys like, "Woo!" Can I see that one?
They're like, "No, that actually got into that. That should have been in the file."
That's in my personal collection. The scientist puts it in his pocket. With women, if they
have this parasite in them, it actually makes them thinner. It actually could be a weight
loss drug. It could be a weight loss drug. People start popping poop. Popping poop pills. It
can make them thinner. And they've seen, this is again because it can be spread sexually.
It can't reproduce in humans, but the parasite can continue to thrive and it can be spread
sexually. Women who are infested with this parasite have more sexual partners. Now they
may have more sexual partners because people find them more attractive, but people are
finding them more attractive because this parasite is reshaping their body to be more
attractive so more people are sleeping with this woman and it is spreading.
Now I think eventually it wants to get back into the cat. So I'm wondering if we could
trace people who are infested with this with people who one day they're sitting at home
and they're like, "I really want to buy a cat. I want to go and adopt a cat." Because
that I wonder if it can change who you are attracted to. If it can physically reshape
a human body. So other people find it attractive. Change the jawline, change the cheeks. I'm
not talking it's not reforming your bones so much, but it can kind of give you a good
look. I don't see why it can't also be like, "Buy a cat." You're like, "Okay, Jason, now
you've turned this real life science into science fiction. It's not like the parasites
in there were the little megaphone. It's not that... What was that? Osmosis Jones. It's
not like a whole thriving city or is there?" Like this is fascinating because at what point
are our decisions our decisions and at what point is it a parasite saying, "You know what?
I don't think I'm going to eat today." I feel like getting more physical fitness. I wonder
if you went to a yoga studio and started taking to the life of swabs from people. How many
of them would be infected with this? Fascinating story. I do think that a big part of our...
I think our soul is our soul and our soul is removed from all of this stuff, but we're
also base animals, right? How much of our day to day decisions is based on gut biome
and bacteria and parasites and all that stuff. I find it absolutely fascinating to hear.
We have one of the most infectious parasites that we know of, right? Who knows what else
is going on out there? Leo, our cat man. Let's go ahead and tashie the keys to the
carbonicopter. Catch them in your big old paws. We're leaving behind this crazy cat
lady's house. We're headed all the way out to Los Angeles, California. And of course,
I brought a box of kittens with me. They're so cute. We're flying around in the carbonicopter.
It's December 1984, and we're in Los Angeles, California. It's nighttime. It's time to
go to bed. We don't have a name for this mother and this daughter duo, so we're going to name
the mother Sally, and she has an infant daughter, little Betty, little baby Betty. Sally walks
up and puts Betty down in the bedroom. They share a bedroom, puts her in a little crib,
and then Sally's walking through the house, kind of finalizing everything before she finally
goes to sleep herself. Now, as she's walking around the house, she's not laying in bed
at this point. It is late. She is tired, but she is awake. However, she starts to feel
like she's in a dream-like state. The event is already beginning. She has no idea what
she's about to face. She sees out of her window a strange figure standing at her front door.
She describes it as an alien that we would describe nowadays as a gray alien. Large head,
short and stature, big black eyes, kind of a frail looking frame. And this gray alien
is wearing a gold outfit, like a gold tight-fitting suit. And this creature is trying to get into
the apartment. She's actually seeing it turn the doorknob. Instantly panicked, right? You
would be scared enough if you saw a stranger trying to get into your house, but this creature
from beyond reality is outside trying to get into her house. So, Sally does what I think
any parent would do. Her first concern is for her child. She runs into the baby's room
and the baby is still sleeping. The baby is fast asleep in its little crib. And at that
point, Sally turns around and there in the doorway of the bedroom stands the gray alien.
The gray walks over to the crib and scoops up baby Betty and spanks her super hard. Whack!
Sally lunges for the child and now her and this gray alien are fighting over this baby
who I'm assuming is awake at this point. She is fighting with this gray alien over her baby.
And gray aliens are physically very weak creatures. They do seem to have some sort of sonic.
Or telepathic blast which can freeze people. But you could grab a football, you could grab
a baby, you could grab anything from a gray alien if you get close enough. And that mom
has that mama bear energy and she closes that distance and she grabs that baby and her and
the alien are tugging the baby back and forth until of course the mother overpowers him and
safely grabs the baby away. Now she's holding her infant daughter on the roof of the apartment
complex. She is looking around. She has no idea what just happened. She was just standing
in her bedroom and now she's on the roof of the apartment complex. The endless night sky
above her head. The cold December wind wrapping around her body. And as she's standing on
the roof of this apartment complex, she looks and sees that the gray alien is there as well
as two other humans. And she starts asking what is going on? Come on guy, what's going
on? I need some help. And the two humans just stare straight ahead. Like they're in some
sort of trance. They don't speak. They don't move. They're just standing there. Her attention
turns back to the gray alien who pulls out a wand. Like a magician's wand. Small metal
silo. And dips it into gold liquid. Which I guess is also up there like a little pot
of gold liquid. Sticks it in the gold liquid and begins to swirl the wand. You're about
to taste this. This is clearly a dream. Hold on. Hold on. The gray alien dips it into the
gold liquid and begins to swirl the wand around and it starts to make a "woooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
blue light. Shoots out of this UFO at an angle and a blue staircase materializes leading
up into the UFO. Sally has no memories of what happened next. I got this story from Think
About It Docs.com. They got it from Duane Bettel who wrote about this in Heartland UFO
Journal #3 which was published back in December 1994. What I love about this story is that
one, it shows... Listen, I'm totally anti-alien, right? I mean I love the stories but I'm pro-earth.
Earth first baby. Like I will go toe to toe with a gray or a reptilian or a pleiadian
any day. I'm a human superiority advocate. But I also understand, I mean I love humans
more than I love whales but I also know that a whale could kill a human if it wanted to
or a shark could kill a human or anything like that. So I also respect the amount of
power that these aliens have and this is completely reality warping power. Hearing in the house,
teleporting multiple people at once, materializing the UFO out of nothingness was at some sort
of cloak, was at entering our dimension. She could physically overpower this gray alien
and she did but it did not matter. The raw power of aliens is always very very interesting
to me. Because I listen man, I'd love to do an Independence Day scenario or a V scenario
or a battle Los Angeles scenario where humans are overpowering our alien oppressors. But
that's all dogfights with UFOs. That's not what it would be like. That's how we can
think it would be like because that's how we battle each other. But imagine trying to
shoot a heat seeking missile at a vehicle that can just dematerialize and then rematerialize
behind you and then all of a sudden you're sitting in a library. You were in an F-22
fighter jet and now you're sitting in an undending library with rows and rows and rows of people
just frozen in time. What library is this? Where am I? Do I have an overdue book? Like
that's the raw power of these aliens. How do you fight something like that? How do you
fight something that can just warp reality? And what I also find super intriguing about
the story is this is the stuff as crazy as it is. This is the stuff she remembers. This
is the stuff that her brain allowed her to process. Because when we talk about aliens
missing time, people not remembering events, you can say the aliens have some sort of technology
or some sort of ability to wipe your memories. But remember a lot of times when these people
undergo hypnosis they can re-remember them. So whatever this technology is or disability
is it's not foolproof. That's one possibility that the aliens are a wipe in our mind. As
a paranormal investigator myself, I deal far more in ghosts and demons than I do in UFOs
and Bigfoot. On the ground research on that stuff. I used to be an on the ground ghost
hunter. I know for a fact I've seen it happen to myself and I've seen it happen to friends
of mine on these ghost hunts. Your brain can only process so much crazy. Your brain will
actually it has fail safes in it. It's like nope I didn't see that. That's impossible.
It's happened to me and I believe in all sorts of stuff. Like I said on Monday's episode
I believe people can get turned into trees. And there have been times where I've encountered
things my brain goes no. Like leave, get out of here, run. And then weeks, months later
I'll just be sitting there hanging out and all of a sudden this vision will come over
me and I was like oh that's what I saw. Did I ever tell you guys that story when I was
in my apartment and it was full of all this negative energy. It's a long story. I had
like this insane roommate. He was like just nuts. And this was back when I was really
really like playing around with you know like magic. Not magic the gathering which is a
fun game but like trying to do like rituals and stuff like that. I was in my apartment
I was there with my buddy Liz. I actually wasn't staying there at this point. I just was like
full of stuff that I needed to move out but I was still paying rent on the place and I
was living somewhere else and you know I have two apartments at one point. And we went back
to this place, went back to my place and I walked in and I immediately felt uneasy. I
hadn't been there for a while. My roommate was nuts. I kicked him out. I changed the
locks. He crawled in through the window. And I remember I went in there and I felt uneasy.
I go I don't feel good here. Liz is like oh whatever. She's never like she's easily
spooked but she didn't believe in ghosts as much as I did. And so we went into the apartment
and I was getting some stuff to take to my other apartment. And I remember I was like
I have to go to the bathroom. Now that's always a try. This episode might run a little long.
I didn't plan on telling the story. That's always a trigger though. A lot of times when
you're in an area of paranormal activity when you're ghost hunting. And I never tell people
this. I don't tell people this. I shouldn't warn them because one of the things when you're
doing a ghost hunt is you don't want to feed them information. If you say we're going to
go to this place where a witch was brutally murdered 200 years ago. Sometimes they say
when you look into the Bubbling Creek underneath Dead Witch Bridge you'll see her face. Obviously
when you feed someone a scary story they'll be looking for that. And you can actually
implant that in your head. My technique was if I saw something I would turn to someone
else and go "Do you see that?" And they'll go "Yeah dude it looks like a shadow. Looks
like an 8 foot tall shadow standing over there. What is it?" "Is there someone over there?"
That's exactly what I saw too. See I know what I see. I have someone else describe it to
me. Now I know it's a real phenomenon. I know that it's not a trick of the like as we're
standing at different angles. I know that I'm not going insane. So one of the things that
I've learned is that when you're with a group of people if one or more people suddenly have
to urinate it's weird. I know people are like Jason you've said a lot of crazy stuff on
this show. I think I might have mentioned this before. If you or multiple people have
to urinate it can be either you just drink a bunch of water or that there's a paranormal
event of hearing manifesting. I don't know what the mechanism is behind it. I always thought
it could be why people say they piss their pants when they're so scared but then also
people get so scared they actually piss their pants. It's a weird thing. Now I remember
being over here and all of a sudden I have to urinate. It's not every time just to be
clear. It's not every time I have to go to the bathroom. I'm like oh there's a ghost.
It's a certain set of circumstances but over here all of a sudden I had to go to the bathroom.
It's like I went to the bathroom and I came out and I was just overwhelmed with fear.
I came out of the bathroom and I was completely overwhelmed with fear and I was like go go
go go. We're out of here. Liz was like ah she was still picking stuff up to take. Go go
go go. We left. I remember it was probably like a couple weeks later if not like a month
or two later I was hanging out. I was sitting on the couch at my other apartment. I wasn't
in that old apartment anymore and all of a sudden I remembered opening the bathroom
door of my old apartment. I had a memory now of what scared me so badly. I remember opening
the bathroom door after I went to the bathroom and standing in the hallway was maybe, I'm
really bad with ages, but maybe like a 10 year old boy with no face. Not like no features.
Not like it was just a smooth face. He was skinned. I could see the muscle tissue. I
could see where the teeth went into the gums. It was like someone had flayed him. Someone
had completely removed his face. I remember opening the bathroom door and looking down
and seeing this boy. Maybe a little older than 10. I didn't ask him his age. I left,
but I didn't remember why I was so scared for a long period of time because my brain
was like no dude that's it. Like we're not going to let you see this. And the thing is
is when I was sitting on the couch when I remembered that I wasn't even thinking about
it. I wasn't thinking oh I wonder what I saw. I had completely, because I've been in areas
before and said oh this is creepy and then I leave. And this was just a fear that crawled
into me. This terror that would just seem to radiate from right in front of me and I
was like we're out. Wasn't thinking about it. Just chalked it up to. It was a weird apartment.
But weeks or months later again I don't remember. It wasn't like years later, but I remember
sitting there and I was completely relaxed just hanging out and then all of a sudden
I remembered myself opening the bathroom door and looking down and seeing this. You know
what's funny now that I say when I'm looking down I didn't, because it was a 10 year old
boy but I remember almost looking at it face to face. I mean I guess if you're a phantasm
from beyond the grave. Maybe he was floating? I don't know. I remember opening. I don't
remember opening the door and looking down. I remember opening the door and seeing him.
Whatever, whether he was floating or whatever caused that. We're looking face to face and
he had no face. He'd been skinned. He had hair which must have been super uncomfortable.
You have this giant open wound and you have bangs and it's constantly getting in there.
I can laugh about it now. I ran out of there. Go go go go go. My brain finally goes oh we'll
let you remember that. Like again I wasn't thinking about it. I just chalked it up to
creepy apartment. That was fun. That was the same apartment. I talked about this on the
show a long time ago where that one day I came home and I opened the door and I was sitting
on the couch. And I remember opening the door and seeing myself sitting on the couch and
me on the couch gets up and we start both walking towards each other and then I don't
remember what happened next. And what's funny is I remember that happening and I still have
a fear of that happening again. Like I won't say it happens every time I come home but
it's not super rare when I'm coming home and I open the door and I'm thinking what if I'm
sitting on the couch again. Like it pops into my head at a pretty regular event. What if
I come home and I'm sitting there like working on my computer and I turn and look. It's super
weird. It's a weird apartment. It was on Sunrise Avenue. It was on Sunrise Avenue over where
Tom Thumb used to be Sunrise and what is that? Anelope Road? Anyways if you guys want to
go get an apartment out there be careful because one of them might be haunted. But so sorry
that ran a little bit longer but this is what she remembered. Like as insane as this is
this is what she remembered. So what happened on the ship? What was so insane, so mind bending,
so soul crushing that her brain said nope. You can remember the staircase. You can remember
the alien. You can remember the wand. You can remember the two humans but you cannot remember
what happened on the ship. You can't. It will break you. What insane things did she see aboard
that ship? What did they do to her and her daughter? We'll never know because she doesn't
know. And she doesn't know because if she knew it may drive her insane. The raw power of the
aliens that seem to visit Earth on a fairly regular basis should never be underestimated.
We can make all the movies we want of aerial combat dogfights with UFOs and some of the
aliens deciding to fight against their own to join the humans. We can make whole series
about the giant Zentradi alien invaders being defeated by the power of love and the technology
of Robotech. But the reality of it is that these aliens are so powerful. It's possible
the war will be won without either side ever firing a shot. There may come a day where
you just wake up trapped in a pitch black room. You scream out for help and your screams
are answered by the echoes of thousands of other screams, hundreds of thousands of other
screams. You are now a prisoner of the alien invaders when you didn't even have a chance
to fight back. They just warped reality so much that they took us over in a heartbeat.
The only thing you can hope for now is that when the aliens come to your cargo container
to pull you out for whatever insidious experiment they have planned for you, the only thing
you can hope for, whatever they do to you, you pray that you don't remember it.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio. Tiktok is at DeadRabberRadio. DeadRabberRadio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)