What happens when you're recording a paranormal podcast and the world of the paranormal wants a sneak peek at your latest episode?
Then we travel to a lonely road in Georgia where an overnight attendant is besieged by a smelly vagrant.
It's paranormal. It's not just some weirdo, it's not just some smelly oboe walking around. It's paranormal.
And then we uncover a brand new conspiracy theory that's currently making the rounds. Well, one guy's talking about it, so we're gonna talk about it on the show.
Is it possible that elderly people are actually grey aliens in disguise today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason Carpenter, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing.
Also, I hope you're not over the age of 65 because you might be a grey alien and then you might want to kill me for the second story.
But before we get to that, before we get to your elderly enraged vengeance streak against me, let's go ahead and introduce our Patreon supporter.
I don't know how old this guy is. This guy might be 88.
Coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now, everyone give a round of applause to LecannionLifter.
Woo! Come on in, Lecannion. Yeah, give you a big round of applause. Checking your ID, seeing how old you are.
Lecannion actually used to be a Patreon and then something happened and they stopped. They're like, "Your show started to suck, bro."
Now, something happened and they stopped, but they're joined back on. So thank you so much, Lecannion.
You're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode. You can scan to where the Patreon. I totally get it. Trust me, I do.
Just help spread the word about the show that really, really helps out a lot.
Lecannion, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jet.
Actually, no, we're not going anywhere right now. Give me those keys back, bro.
I want to tell you guys this. If you guys listened to yesterday's episode, it might have ended a little bit abrupt.
I haven't finished the final edit of yesterday's episode, but actually our first story takes place here in Dead Rabbit Command, here in the recording studio.
What happened yesterday was I was finishing up the story about the ghost car. It was really cool.
I really liked the story of the guy walking around taking the trail through Georgia. Got some good Georgia stories this week.
Let me play you the audio. I edited this out because I thought it was too distracting. It's definitely too distracting, right?
So here, let me set this up for you. When I'm recording, I do record in a closet.
I call it the haunted closet because I have sensed the ghost in this closet before, but it's really been a long time since I've seen anything in my house or really anything even in the closet.
Now, as a studio, it does what it does. It has pretty good audio, but it also gets really, really hot.
These were my first episodes coming back from a long break. I was super nervous. I was just sweating the whole time.
So what I did was at a certain point, I cracked open the door. I know that's not good for studio recording.
They normally don't snoop dog. Normally it doesn't go, "Hey, I'm about to bust the track."
Open the windows. Let's get all that outside noise. But I open the door.
Okay. The door's open maybe, I don't know, a little less than a foot.
I'm getting some sunlight in here. I'm getting some fresh air.
And if you've never, I do a live show every Sunday morning for the Patreon supporters.
They'll often see this. Sometimes I add video to it. They definitely hear it.
None of this show is really scripted. It's all just notes. And then I just kind of go off the top of my head.
That's why I'm always laughing at the jokes, because it's the first time I've heard those jokes too, right?
But a lot of times I come to the end of an episode and I'll just kind of go riff for like 10 minutes trying to find the right combination of words to wrap up an episode.
And that's what was happening yesterday. And I'm sitting there in my closet.
I'm trying to figure out a good way to wrap up the story about a guy who saw a ghost car.
And I just can't find it. And you know, it's like 8 o'clock at night. I'm super tired and I'm super sweaty.
And I look out the little, I look out my door, right?
I'm just kind of gazing around trying to think of a way to finish this episode. And when I look out the door, I see an apparition.
I straight up see a ghost.
Well, okay, so what I see, it's so weird. I turn and I look.
And I see standing right outside my door like this thing was watching me record the podcast.
It was as if you took a ribbon. Now it was a black ribbon that was bold black on the edges.
And in the middle was like a translucent almost see through almost smoky material.
I turned and I look and I saw hovering there for a good few seconds, hovering there a ribbon.
And it looked like if you had an invisible woman, invisible man standing outside your closet, like you're like, "Oh, I know exactly what that looks like, Jason."
If you had an invisible person and you placed a ribbon on them, you could see, I could see the outline of the top of their head.
And then it came down and then was the outline of their left shoulder.
The ribbon was probably about maybe two feet long.
And I'm turning, I'm going to play the clip for you without any audio processing or anything.
I'll play that for you in a second so you can kind of hear what was going on while I was experiencing this.
But I turn and I look because I'm just trying to think of a way to end this episode.
I've been just recording for like two hours at this point. I did two episodes back to back yesterday.
So I look and I see this ribbony, this smoky ribbony thing outside of my closet in full bedroom light, you know, full lamp.
Jason's not saying to the term, you know, full light bulb light.
And I see it and it hangs there for a second and then it disappears.
And it doesn't go, "Bip!" It doesn't disappear like a flash. It just slowly fades from view.
And you can hear the audio of me experiencing this. I just stopped talking and I'll play that for you right now.
I think the answer to that is pretty clear. We have a lot of stories of people mysteriously vanishing in the woods or down dark alleys or inside houses.
We have a lot of stories of people mysteriously vanishing in the woods and very, very few of them ever return.
Would you be one of them? Would you be one of those that make it back to the world of our reality?
Dude, no joke.
[door opens]
There was something standing outside my closet watching me record that.
That was insane.
Yeah. I turned. I don't know why I turned to look. You guys might have even heard me turn while I was talking.
This is not scripted and nothing like that. I don't mess around with this type of stuff.
Like, I don't joke about this stuff. No, he profools or nothing.
I turned and I looked.
And it was like a black ribbon.
It would have been about maybe six feet tall, but it was a black ribbon.
But it looked. Damn it.
I'm like, oh no, apparently there's a phenomenon in my house.
I do have to live here. I do have to sit in this closet.
It's probably, it would be like if you put a ribbon on somebody's head and like laid across the top of their head.
But there's no ribbon. I don't know how often you guys watch videos of my house.
I'm not a big ribbon aficionado. That was weird.
I got that was creepy.
There was straight up something watching me do that.
I don't know how much of the clip I'm actually going to play for you, but what if I don't play at all?
What I do is then I get up and I walk around my bedroom.
I'm kind of processing what I saw and I'm still talking into the microphone. I'm saying how tall.
So here's the thing. This is the weird thing about ghosts.
There's a weird thing about ghosts.
There's dead people or demons or whatever they are.
But one thing that I've had in my experience, because I've seen a lot of ghosts in my life, is ghosts don't,
if it's a real ghost in a place that I'm at, I'm not scared of it.
I'm a little bit, be a little bit at ease, like uneasy.
If it's real, I'm not scared. If it's fake, I'm scared.
So I saw this black ribbon materialized outside my closet, like it was peeking in, not scared.
When about my business, I actually went into the living room and while I was kind of editing episodes and stuff like that,
I see something out of the corner of my eye in the living room.
And then my black mouse, you know, my computer mouse is black and it's shiny.
I actually see something move over the mouse, like the reflection changed.
So we also had that stuff going on as well.
So I wasn't scared, right?
Came in, shut my light off to go to bed, pulled down my phone, goofing off, going to stupid websites, stuff like that.
Went to bed.
Even though I saw a ghost that don't know what it is, don't know what its intent is, I see it in here.
Yesterday morning, I was walking to work. I just watched the movie The Bye Bye Man.
I'd watched the movie The Bye Bye Man and I was walking to work and I was thinking of the Bye Bye Man
and a squirrel jumped out of a bush and I almost peed my pants.
It's so weird. It's so weird like something that's fake will scare me.
The Bye Bye Man, I'm like, "Ugh!"
But when there's a ghost in my actual apartment, it doesn't scare me.
I know I'm a paranormal researcher, I know I'm a ghost hunter, you don't want it in your house.
Really. I mean, now it's attacking me.
No, I'm not saying you gotta leave, but it's more troublesome.
I don't really think this, whatever this is, has any ill will towards me, so that's interesting.
But, like, if the goblins are supposed to be at your house and then I go to your house and investigate goblin activity.
I don't think even a hunter, like, if you were a hunter, I don't think you want a bunch of rabbits jumping around in your house, right?
I mean, you're like, "I love shooting rabbits in the brain with this shotgun,"
but I like to go, I like to do it on my off time, not at home, so we'll see what happens.
Like, this could have been a one-off thing.
I didn't feel any ill will towards it.
If it does the sight of stick around, you know, I'll deal with it.
I'm not gonna sage the place or anything like that if it has good intent, right?
But that was really weird.
It was really weird to see something like that.
It's been years since I've seen a ghost on that level.
But there's one here now, apparently.
Maybe it's just passing through.
Maybe it's waiting for the ghost bus.
Maybe it's on the way to your house.
And if so, then I think it's pretty chill, actually.
I wouldn't worry about it.
But, yeah, it's just weird.
Just weird to be recorded.
And you know what's so funny?
I think it was in that episode or the episode before it.
I was like, "Oh, that ghost can come to my house."
I kept talking about someone who's trying to get a ghost to come to their house.
I think it was the Monday episode.
And maybe a ghost.
Maybe a ghost didn't understand.
I was speaking in the third person.
Who knows?
But a weird story, nonetheless.
You know, that took a lot longer.
And I know with all the processing and everything like that,
that segment's probably gonna be like 20 minutes.
Let's go ahead and set aside the hobo vagrant story.
We're gonna save that for tomorrow.
Let's move into a snowier region than my house.
So let's go ahead and toss the canning and lifter the keys to the carpenter copter.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're flying all the way out to a snowy mountain town.
This story's short.
We might have time for the Georgia story,
but I want to make sure I can give this story its full do.
And I've got to give a shout out to Ampus Allen.
Ampus Allen, longtime supporter of the show,
sent us a lot of really good stuff for Dead Rabbit.
I really, really appreciate it.
This story is just as good as the other ones.
Like, sending me nothing but gold.
Ampus Allen apparently posted this video the other day of a 70-year-old woman.
Let me get this straight, actually.
So he videotaped, no, no, no.
He posted a video.
He's skiing and his mother-in-law is filming him.
His 70-year-old mother-in-law is filming him.
Chirin' him on, "Go, Ampus Allen, go!"
And he's like, he can't even hear her.
He's going down the hill so fast.
And it was like, "Hey, look at this."
It was from a subreddit called Praise the Cameraman.
Because the cameraman's doing-- or Camerawoman.
Don't be sexist, subreddit.
So anyways, this actually was a woman.
They're going down the hill.
So he posted this video.
It's like, "Hey, look at my mother-in-law's filming me as I'm flying down the slopes."
This dude actually is like a world-renowned athlete, Ampus Allen.
So he posted this video and because the internet is a super, super weird place,
he gets a comment from a guy known as "Ohoyle."
And Ohoyle tells this story.
Ohoyle says, "You know what?
I used to live in a mountain town."
And that's where we're walking around right now.
We're walking around this unnamed mountain town.
We got big mittens on in like the parkas and we're walking around.
Ohoyle's story is this.
He used to live in a mountain town up in a snowy region.
And he worked at the local pizza shop.
The local pizzeria where you'd go in and you'd get some delicious food,
maybe throw back a brusky or two and watch the snow fall outside.
And he says, "You know what?"
He's referring to Ampus Allen's 70-year-old mother-in-law videotaping this.
He goes, "You know what?
You'd actually be surprised how many old people can ski in snowboard
and do it fairly well."
And he goes, "I have a theory.
And to be honest, I'm kind of joking, but I'm kind of not.
I believe that aliens hide out in mountain towns all over the world."
So think about it.
Old people look like gray aliens, right?
Hold your questions until the end.
Old people kind of do look like gray aliens, right?
They're balding.
Gray aliens are bald.
They got skinny little limbs.
Gray aliens have skinny little limbs.
That's kind of weird.
They're not gray.
Most old people aren't gray.
However, they do start to get a little ashy looking, right?
Why do they do that?
Why do old people-- YouTube's going to shut this down for ageism.
But when you get old, you kind of lose a little bit of color in your skin.
So why?
Is it because they're old and they are having less nutrients
or they're out in the sun less?
Is it because they're not human anymore?
Gray aliens?
But he says it's weird because old people do kind of look like gray aliens.
But that's not the only thing.
That's not the only part of this conspiracy theory.
He goes, "Sometimes when I'm working at a pizzeria,
I'd get these elderly people showing up to the pizza shop
and they would be paying me in cash."
But the cash was always old money.
Like the bills, the bills, the dates when the bills were printed were like the 1960s.
But they looked brand new.
So I was getting this money that was brand new that had old dates on it from like the '60s
and I thought, "Hmm, maybe they're gray aliens."
Right?
These people up in mountain regions pay me in weird money.
Now I would assume there's some sort of counterfeit ring going on.
That would be my first assumption.
Did I ever talk to you?
Did I ever mention that before?
My grandpa knew a guy who counterfeited money?
Like my grandpa's dead.
You can't come after him, FBI.
But my grandpa knew a dude who would counterfeit money
and he lived on a boat in Sacramento
and he would just have a water cooler of $5 bills, fake $5 bills
and he would just hand them out to people.
I don't know who the guy was before the feds come and asked me.
I don't know who the guy was.
It's been 20 years since I heard that story.
But so you do have old people who counterfeit
and they just counterfeit very, very low bills.
But anyways, anyways, now that it's a counterfeit ring,
he thinks they might be gray aliens.
But here's the interesting part, right?
Ampestallan sent this to me.
We both had a good chuckle.
But there was something that could be fact checked
with this conspiracy theory.
And those are always the best conspiracy theories,
the ones that we can actually take a really close look at.
He said snow, this is what Ahoyle said,
snow is actually kind of a rare phenomenon
as far as the galaxy goes.
Now I can't fact check that old people love to use new bills
other than the fact that my grandpa knew a counterfeiter
and elderly counterfeiter.
And yeah, sure, old people do kind of look like gray aliens
if you forget the fact that they have giant eyeballs
and they're three feet tall and they have these massive heads.
Sure, they share some of the qualities of a gray alien,
i.e. they have arms and legs and they're bold.
But snow is a rare phenomenon galactically.
So me and Ampestallan were kind of joking about this
and then I looked it up.
Snow is extremely rare.
H2, I know a bunch of scientists, I know a bunch of people
who are into science who listen to this podcast
are typing comments and emails right now, hold on.
Snow as we know it, H2O snow that sticks and packs
and forms snow shelves and snowy mountains and stuff like that.
We're the only place in the solar system that we know that this happens.
There's other planets, there's moons that we think it snows,
but it's like volcanic ash coming down from the sky.
It's carbon snow.
It's like Mars, it snows like there's ice,
but snow, they said it doesn't stick, like it snows in the poles,
but by the time it hits the ground it's gone.
We think it might snow on Pluto.
As much as we know that Pluto is like super frozen,
we don't know for sure.
And even then it's Pluto.
Even then it's a dirt ball of a planet that's super far away.
And this is super interesting because snow is,
snow is so rare in our solar system
that you would have to extrapolate that out.
And it's probably very rare galactically.
Something that for the most part we take for granted.
I always thought it was interesting that the number one,
as far as we know, the number one rarest thing in the universe,
liquid water, we pour all over our bodies,
we splash it in our face.
I mean we do drink it, right?
But we build holes in the ground and fill it full of the most precious resource in the universe.
As far as we know liquid water is one of the rarest things ever.
It rains diamonds on like Jupiter or Saturn or something like that,
or one of the moons.
But there's no liquid water anywhere else that we know of.
And we put it in balloons and throw it at people, right?
We spray our dogs with a hose and they go,
and they get it all wiggly all over you and it's fun.
And then Charles Crudin yells at you, "Bate-O-Van!"
That's weird.
That is the detail that makes me go,
"Maybe there is something to this."
So again, YouTube and anyone else who thinks I'm being agist,
I'm not saying that all old people are grey aliens,
but what I am saying is that if you could travel the galaxy
and you'd seen stars explode and you watch your buddies get sucked into a black hole,
you're like, "Oh, that prank went bad."
As you watch their entire starship get stuck on the event horizon,
you've seen all of these great things, but snow,
standing outside watching frozen water softly come down,
sticking out your little tongue, getting some on it.
That's be so rare.
You could experience so many other amazing things throughout the galaxy,
but if you wanted to see snow, you'd have to come here.
You wanted to ski, snowball fight, igloos, whatever.
You'd have to do it here.
That's so interesting.
Think about this.
When you have old people here, or rich people, whatever, and they want to vacation,
sure, they could go to a tropical location anywhere on the planet.
They could go to some deserted island.
They're rich and powerful.
They can go anywhere.
They can afford anything.
But they still go to the same resort towns that everyone else goes to,
because the infrastructure is there to support them.
If Bill Gates wanted to go to a tropical island,
but there's no landing pad there, and let's say that he goes,
"Build the landing pad, then he gets there."
There's no hotels.
There's no houses.
It's just a deserted island.
He's like, "Ah, this totally sucks."
And you'd have to build the infrastructure.
All that infrastructure is here.
So sure, even if there was another planet where it did snow, H2O,
there's no resorts, there's no pizzerias, there's no infrastructure for that.
This, it's interesting, because we always talk about Earth being a prison planet.
We talk about Earth being a zoo.
The aliens a long time ago put us here, and they crossbred themselves with the monkey people,
and then that's where the Homo sapiens came from,
and we went to dig up gold for the Anunnaki, and da-da-da-da.
It's always so dismal and dark and evil, right?
It's always, we were slaves, or we are prisoners,
or the Archons are drinking our luch when we die and we get stuck in a reincarnation.
Why is it always so dismal with conspiracy theories?
Why is it always so negative?
Maybe Earth is the happiest place in the galaxy.
I mean, okay, outside of all the wars, outside of all the wars,
and the pestilence and stuff like that and all the horrible crimes.
Galactically speaking, we don't have volcanoes that rip the atmosphere in two.
We are not sitting on the edge of a star system that's about to go supernova.
It's pretty chill, right?
The environment is stable.
It snows, it rains, there's beautiful sunsets.
You can sit on a beach, and a day later, be scaling a mountain,
looking down at the valley below.
It's really a beautiful place.
So maybe we aren't a prison planet, maybe we aren't some sort of zoo
where the monkeys have taken over.
Maybe we're club med as far as the galaxy goes,
and that's why so many aliens are coming here.
That's why we're always hearing about these reptilians and Pleiadians
and the greys and all these other guys, right?
Because you imagine, I don't think the Pleiadians have a bunch of reptilians walking around.
And I imagine on the grey alien homeworld, if that even exists,
a lot of people think it's their bio-robots created by the reptilians.
But we're going to re-intuit into the weeds here.
We're the only planet that all these other different species can come to, right?
Maybe we are a resort planet, maybe we are the cancun of the galaxy.
And so it would make sense that you would have grey aliens coming down
to many aliens, right?
I think a lot of alien, with an alien lore,
especially with reptilians, they're shapeshifters.
It would make sense for them to come down to a place that's peaceful,
that doesn't have all of their wars, it has our wars.
But it doesn't have these galaxy-spanning conflicts.
We may actually be the Casablanca of the galaxy,
a neutral planet that people can come and relax.
Very, very fascinating conspiracy theory, I think.
And we need more positive conspiracy theories.
I really do.
If you want to talk about the Archons drinking our lush,
the way you could generate the mo-
We did a whole episode on that.
You're like, "What in the world's lush?"
I'll put that episode on the show notes.
But the idea is that there's this matrix built around the planet,
and when you die, when it says go into the light,
that's actually a trick to get your soul to reincarnate on Earth.
And these demons, Archons, whatever you want to call them,
these alien overlords are drinking all of your negative energy.
What produces more negative energy than telling somebody
that they're trapped in a matrix full of negative energy?
We need more positive conspiracy theories.
And I think the fact that if you start looking at elderly people
thinking they're actually gray aliens on vacation,
that's pretty dope.
Again, not all of them.
Don't go to a retirement home and have a conga line
and be like, "Come on, Gray's, get on up."
Actually, that sounds pretty good.
You should volunteer at your local retirement home.
It really helps out.
But do not retire just because you think they're gray aliens.
You're like, "Now I'll do the probing."
Don't do that.
There's actually a lot of crimes that happen in retirement homes.
My point is, this is a good conspiracy theory.
I like this.
We need more of this stuff.
We need more stories that don't inspire negativity in us,
but inspire hope.
So, ohoyle, I hope you are correct.
I hope there is a portion of the elderly community
that are gray aliens.
Because then it would mean that this world isn't a dismal place
on the brink of annihilation every single day.
It's actually stable enough for aliens of all races
to come here and hang out for a bit.
That's a great conspiracy theory.
I really do like that.
Or, I have to be very careful here because again,
I'm sure there's one guy right now probably grabbing his crowbar
and being like, "I got to take care of those gray aliens."
They're walking to their retirement home.
They're saying that all elderly people are gray aliens,
just so we are clear.
But, I love this conspiracy theory.
Are some of them?
Are some elderly people gray aliens visiting in disguise?
Are really any aliens, right?
Although, if I was a reptilian, I think I would take the form of like,
Shaquille O'Neal and not a 80-pound old man.
But, I like this.
I like this.
I like positive conspiracy theories.
And what a way to think of the world as a beautiful place
that other people want to come to visit.
Not a dismal place of hate and vengeance and blood and ash,
but a place that is okay to be fair.
It is those things.
But, maybe it is better than those things combined.
I think maybe the love and the joy and the passion that humanity
truly has for each other reaches out and attracts aliens
of all stripes to this world.
We're that dope.
We're that awesome.
We're the only place in the known galaxy where it snows.
They may have the starships.
They may have the technology.
They may have the cure for all the diseases that plague us.
But, from the highest peak to the lowest valley,
Earth is the place to be.
They're jealous of us.
They have all that technology, but they're jealous of us.
This is the only place in the known galaxy where you can walk outside
and watch it snow from the heavens.
Powdery white bliss,
raining down on the beautiful planet known as our home.
[music]
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also use it up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
TikTok is @deadrabberadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[music]
[BLANK_AUDIO]