A man who lived in a UFO shaped house goes missing.
Did aliens take him?
And then we take a look at the story of Charles Morgan, a man seemingly normal by all outward
appearances.
But when he runs into his own home wearing broken handcuffs, telling his family that
he has been kidnapped and tortured, it's only the beginning of a bizarre story today
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
It's 547 AM.
Just woke up a little bit ago, but my shuttle to take me to the airport leaves at 730.
So I want to see how many of these episodes I can bang out and that way I can have a little
bit more of a restful stay while I'm hanging out with my family and friends in Sacramento.
So we're going to bust out a couple of these.
I think we'll be good.
Now, the first story we're going to talk about is the story of a man named Granger Taylor.
Now I first came across this story because it was considered an alien abduction story.
Here's two of the headlines of the articles we're going to be talking about.
An abduction?
An unsolved case of a man who disappeared after building UFO reopened.
I'm pretty evocative.
Another headline.
The man who went to space and disappeared.
So this story's been going on for a while.
This was kind of, it wasn't a super well known common UFO abduction story, but I had
heard of it a while back.
Quite a while back.
Not necessarily when it happened, but I heard about it in the 90s.
So it's not completely obscure people were wondering about this, but let's go ahead
and get into the story here.
Okay, so there was a man named Granger Taylor.
We're in the year 1980.
We haven't busted this out for a while.
Let's take the carbon or copter.
So I got to check the oil.
Let's get out.
And there it goes.
Get back in.
Numatic field.
And this might take a while.
So while we're going to have to hire a maintenance crew to come out and fix the carbon or copter,
but even though we're on the deadline and I kind of get a bunch of episodes done, we
do get the carbon or copter finally flying.
And we're flying from Hood River, Oregon to Vancouver, Vancouver Island, British Columbia.
Sometimes the city of Vancouver gets flooded in a circle and Vancouver becomes Vancouver
Island.
Little known fact, but you didn't know that.
Vancouver Island, British Columbia.
We're flying overhead and we can look down from the helicopter and we see a UFO on the
ground.
We're like, awesome, dude.
UFOs.
They act technically it's not a UFO if it's landed, right?
That's just a ULO.
An unidentified landed object.
But anyway, so we land next to it.
We find out it's not a UFO.
It is a tree fort that an adult built, but no tree.
It's just a fort then.
It's a fort that an adult built in someone's backyard.
I believe it was his parents backyard, but it is shaped like a UFO.
He built it himself.
Now Granger Taylor was considered a fairly gifted child when it came to things like engineering
and design and things like that.
He was kind of a do-it-yourselfer and he built this big UFO shaped house in the backyard.
Again, he's an adult, but you know, every adult has kind of odd hobbies.
It's not not a big deal.
I do think it's weird that he was living in it, but he just really, really, really liked
UFOs.
So he would tell people that he would tell people about alien abduction experiences, but
he wanted to be abducted by aliens.
He really liked the thought of being abducted by aliens.
So that's the thing.
Most people are scared of alien abductions.
It would be the, and people may go, well, you know, he just wants to be abducted.
He wants to meet some little great people.
Little great people.
That's the thing.
Really, we say abduction.
It's kidnapping.
Now, if you knew someone who was like, you know what, I really want to be abducted by
like the Russian mob.
He'd be like, what the hell are you talking about, dude?
You would think they either had a death wish or they had a fetish.
But when people talk about they want to be abducted by aliens, people are like, oh yeah,
you know, mysticism, you know, maybe you'll learn some stuff from the aliens.
It's the same thing.
You're basically being kidnapped and you probably won't come back.
So he would talk about being abducted by aliens all the time.
He really wanted it to happen.
And then one day he disappears.
So I know I'm being a little flippant towards this story and you might think it's disrespectful
at the end, but there's a reason why.
So Granger Taylor disappears and nobody knows what happens to him.
And the way it was always reported in UFO media was maybe he was abducted by aliens.
Maybe the aliens were communicating with him and wanting him and they knew he wanted to
be abducted and he disappeared.
Hence the titles of the two articles that I chose and most of the articles have headlines
like that.
Now, he said a friend of Granger said that aliens talk to him telepathically and you're
like, okay, you know, aliens are talking to him telepathically.
He has this bond with them.
Again, if I'm getting phone calls from the Rush Mob every day and I'm telling my friends,
oh my God, you won't believe you called me yesterday.
It was Vladimir.
He's going to kidnap me this week.
You'd be really, really concerned.
But the friend was like, yeah, he said he was talking to aliens telepathically.
So at that point you can say, well, you know, he's talking to aliens telepathically.
I believe in UFOs.
Maybe that's true.
And then you could say, well, you know, he got abducted.
He lived in UFO shaped house.
He wanted to be abducted.
He was talking to aliens telepathically.
That could be true.
This is where we start to get into the actual reality of things.
Those things aliens may or may not be true, but this is where the rubber hits the road.
And this is where at any point people were going, maybe he was abducted by aliens.
I'm glad Yogi Bear is a guest star on this episode.
Hey, boo boo.
He wanted to get abducted by some aliens, I guess.
This is where every article should have been like he probably didn't get abducted by aliens.
One, his sister said, oh yeah, yeah, no, he talked about talking to aliens.
He really wanted to get abducted.
He also took acid every single day and not just every single day, a few times a day.
So he's dropping huge amounts of acid.
That's when you go, oh, okay, now the story's getting a little bizarre.
He also, when he magically disappeared and got abducted by the aliens, he left a goodbye
note and two wills.
So now when I read the first article, I was like, it sounds more like a suicide.
And you know, you could be like, oh, that's insensitive.
Maybe he really did get abducted by aliens and he wanted to leave these notes.
This was his note.
It's kind of heartbreaking.
Note, dear mother and father, I've gone away to walk aboard an alien spaceship as reoccurring
dreams assured a 42 month interstellar voyage to explore the vast universe.
Then return.
I'm leaving behind all my possessions to you as I will no longer require the use of
any.
Please use the instructions in my will as a guide to help.
Love, Granger.
So again, if you're getting a note like that and he's dropping acid all the time a few
times a day, you're going to be a little concerned.
But people for years were like, he just floated away.
He just floated away.
Now, like I said, I had heard the story, I think in the nineties and they left out a
key detail.
They left out a key detail because a lot of times that'll happen.
You take the evidence you want.
You're like, oh, I believe in aliens or I mean, I believe in aliens and I'm going to.
Okay, I'm not going to do that voice anymore.
I believe in aliens and this guy said he was talking to aliens and he disappeared.
Case closed.
There is another key development in the story in 1986.
They find his truck and a bunch of bones, but the truck was blown up and his bones were
all over the forest.
He borrowed some dynamite from his parents and blew himself up.
Now there are people who say maybe the explosion was an accident because he actually knew how
to handle dynamite, but that actually makes it less of an accident.
So what it seems and we'll cover this is this plays in another story we're going to cover
very famous UFO encounter kind of has the same feeling.
It kind of seems like he really wanted to be abducted by aliens.
I think the the I think the good version of the story is he wanted to be abducted by aliens.
He was driving on his way to the alien abduction point and dynamite accidentally went off blowing
up his car and himself.
The bad version of this story is he was dropping so much acid and so delusional that the aliens
may have said you need to blow yourself up to join us.
You need to straight heaven gates yourself.
You need to to ascend to the alien spaceship.
You need to leave your body.
So drive to middle of nowhere and blow yourself up and your spirit will go into our spaceship
or whatever nonsense and he did it on purpose.
But it's it's weird because that's that's the complete story.
Like you can't leave off the dynamite part.
And even in articles where they mention it, it's kind of like, oh, well, they did find
some bones in his car and a dynamite blast.
But but no, I mean, that's the end.
It sounds like he got kind of in over his head with some delusional behavior.
His friends didn't intercede.
Weren't like, well, maybe you're not, you know, maybe if you think aliens are going to take
you, maybe you shouldn't leave the dynamite at home.
Because that's really where we see stuff like Heaven's Gate where the Colt were like, oh,
there's UFO coming.
But to join it, you got to drink this poison sad story.
And I know that's the thing like it started off really flippant.
But it's more, I think it's I'm being more flippant towards the way the story was handled
and is still handled today.
The headline should not be the man who went to space and disappeared or unsolved case of
man who disappeared after building UFO reopened.
He blew up.
That's the answer.
And it was just kind of it was kind of dealt with like, oh, maybe maybe he did get abducted
by aliens.
No, he blew up the end.
So we have to, we have to, you have to admit stories like even if they fit your narrative,
you sometimes have to take them and discard them and go, well, that guy didn't get abducted
by aliens.
He got abducted by the combined force of dynamite and gravity.
Sorry, Granger.
And again, that might sound flippant, but we have to be realistic with this stuff because
the subject is already so unrealistic.
Anyway, and this is going to pop up a few more times of people who quote unquote mysteriously
vanished and then we find out afterwards that it was most likely they didn't get abducted
by aliens.
And one of them is a very famous alien abduction story, by the way.
We'll get to that though in a future episode.
So let's go ahead and now I feel bad.
I feel bad for making fun of that.
Oh, you know what?
Let's let's cleanse the palette real quick here.
I'm going to do a very quick dead rabbit recommends.
It's a, is this episode, this episode is coming out on Tuesday, but so this one's early.
I normally do them on Wednesdays, but this is going to be real quick.
Most of you guys know the franchise.
I'd argue that all of you guys know the franchise, but not everyone knows about this part of
the franchise.
The Matrix trilogy.
I'm not going to recommend any movies from the Matrix trilogy.
The first one was great.
The second two were, eh, but that world was really rich in the beginning.
I think they kind of ruin it with the last two movies, but there is a two part and it's
on YouTube, solely available on YouTube.
However, the quality is not that great.
I would recommend trying to track this down if you can a higher res version of it.
Even getting a copy of it.
It is something I watch quite often.
I wouldn't say I watch it like every day or every month, but every show often I'll get
a hankering to watch it.
It's called the second renaissance and it's a two, it's about 20 minutes altogether.
It's two 10 minute cartoons about the rise of the machines and it is one of the most
visually compelling stories of a sci-fi apocalypse.
It's one of the most visually compelling stories about the rise of AI and the fall of
man.
It's absolutely beautiful.
It's calling the cartoons probably a disservice.
It's more of an anime.
It tells the story of how the robots went from simply being manual laborers to one of them
being put on trial for murder to a robot uprising and how the humans deal with that.
And the first part is the rise of the machines and the second part is the war between machines
and man.
It is amazing.
It's amazing.
I definitely recommend watching "Taking 20 Minutes Out of Your Day" even if you watched
the low-rise version, but "Taking 20 Minutes Out of Your Day" to watch the second renaissance.
It's just a great piece of sci-fi and some of the imagery is so stark and depressing.
It sticks with you.
There are certain images from the cartoon that you're like, "Oh man, you think about
it from time to time."
I remember I had a friend over, Jonas, he came over one day, me, Jonas and Jacob were
hanging out and Jonas had never seen the second renaissance.
I was like, "Hey, you got 20 minutes?"
He's like, "Yeah, sure."
And we watched it and me and Jacob had seen it before and we're like, "Oh yeah, it's
totally awesome.
Dude, he's a badass.
Dude, watch this scene because it's really, really good."
And Jonas was sitting there and then after it was over, he just kind of goes, "His response
to watching it for the first time was, I go, 'What'd you think?'
And he goes, 'I got to think about this, man.'
Like, whoa, like, that's a lot to digest."
And it was funny because we were like just hanging out as buddies and they show him this
really depressing, in the end, really depressing anime.
He goes, "I don't even know."
It was like I was showing him snuff videos on LiveLeak.
It really affected him.
And then you think about it, you're like, "Yeah, it was a really cool sci-fi, but it's very,
very grim, very, very good.
Dead Rabbit recommends the second renaissance.
I'll have the YouTube links if you can find a high-res version.
It's amazing."
Okay, let's go ahead and move on to the next story.
The next story is another story that's a mystery.
This one is, doesn't involve UFOs, but involves something far more devious.
So the year is 1977 and now we're in Tucson, Arizona.
Charles Morgan, it's a beautiful morning day, which we're not usual mornings are.
Charles Morgan runs into his house.
His family's sitting there, they're eating Cheerios.
Life kids are all eating Cheerios together, wife's reading newspaper, piping her mouth.
Charles Morgan runs into the house, handcuffs on his wrists and ankles.
Broken obviously, he's not like scooting into the house.
Making these noises, but he can't talk and his wife's like, "What's going on?
What's going on Charles?"
He then gets a pen and paper and he writes down, "I can't talk because a hallucinogenic
drug was put in my mouth."
Now I'm going to make an assumption here, he probably didn't spell hallucinogenic,
right?
They don't have spell check in 1977 and they don't have spell check when you use a pen
and paper, but anyways, he starts writing vague because his wife's like, "Well, who
took you?
Who took you?"
And he would just write things like they, them.
He was very vague about who he was kidnapped by and he said that he got away.
He also hinted that he was a government agent and the wife is like, "Oh."
And he's like, "I can't talk, right?"
Totally freaks out.
Now what's funny is that nowhere in the re-- it's funny, just a dude got kidnapped,
but what's funny is nowhere in the rest of the article do they really state he regains
the ability to talk.
So I assume he did because then he goes about his daily life later on, but you think like
once he was able to talk he would be able to explain it better, but the articles always
leave that part out which is when did he learn the ability to talk again.
But anyways, after the event we'll assume that he can talk at some point.
He's like at work.
"They're like great, great idea Charles."
He's writing everything down.
"And you spilled hallucinogenic right, you get a raise."
He won't let his girls go anywhere alone.
He's super super paranoid, but life continues.
Life continues.
They go to a baseball game as little girls are playing baseball.
He's like "Ugh, ugh, ugh."
Two months later he disappears again.
He disappears again.
And you think at that point his wife's like "Charles, oh that wacky Charles, he's gonna
go get drunk again."
That would be my first thing.
If someone came in wearing handcuffs and were like "I can't talk but this is what happened."
I would assume they had something to hide because I don't know if any drugs would just
make you not be able to talk.
I'd be like "He probably just doesn't want to talk."
So it sounded like a setup.
It sounds like a setup.
Like a guy coming in and he's like "Oh my god, I just got attacked by a bunch of whores
at a whorehouse but luckily I got away.
I wasn't there to have sex with them."
It sounds like that type of setup.
But two months later he disappears again.
In June 1977, so let's see, March, April, May he disappears again.
I should figure all this out before I start the episode.
In June 1977 he's found dead.
So obviously he wasn't larping the first time.
He actually did get kidnapped by someone, got away or they let him go.
And then two months later he goes missing again and then he's found dead.
He has a bullet in the back of his head embedded into his mouth.
So the bullet came through the back of the head, knocked it tooth out and it's sticking
out of his mouth.
He was found with a bulletproof vest and a knife.
His gun was used, he had a gun with him too.
He had an empty holster.
His gun was used apparently to commit the crime.
So you go suicide.
Now people always go "How do you shoot yourself twice in the back of the head?"
It can happen.
Depending on the type of gun.
Sometimes that's always things like "That guy didn't kill himself."
But you can shoot yourself in the back of the head and sometimes through muscle reflex
you can shoot yourself twice.
Pop pop.
You get one bullet in the back of the head and the other bullets farther back up in the
skull coming out of the top or through the back of the skull headed down because your
hands move in one way or another due to the force.
But it can happen.
You can shoot yourself multiple times in the back of the head.
But he was shot in the back of the head.
Bullet lodged in his teeth.
He was killed with his own gun.
So suicide.
He went into his house.
He wove this tale of he's possibly a government agent.
He then runs out of the house later.
Or maybe run out of the house but two months later he goes missing again.
He's found with a bullet in the back of the brain coming out of the back.
His gun was used.
So on and so forth.
So you think maybe it's just a suicide.
Maybe it was a set up for a suicide so his family could get life insurance.
Let's dig into the details here a little more.
One of his tooth that got knocked out by the bullet was wrapped in tissue and placed in
his car that was there.
I guess I should have said that.
His body was found by his car out in the middle of nowhere or you know out in the boonies.
He gets shot in the back of the head.
Tooth comes out.
Somebody wrapped his tooth in a piece of tissue.
Put it in his car.
There was a pair of sunglasses in the car that weren't his.
Now that stuff could easily be a mistake and the wife could be like he doesn't own
those but he may have bought them without her.
But I don't think someone's going to shoot themselves in the back of the head and then
be like oh a tooth put this for the tooth fairy put it in their own car and then collapse
and die.
So the working idea is someone else was there.
But some other there's more this story is really weird.
It's not like the last story the Granger Taylor story.
It's pretty cut and dry.
You think okay then this guy didn't kill himself.
Somebody else did.
That's cut and dry right well it still gets weird here.
He had a $2 bill attached to his underwear and probably that way in case somebody took
his wallet the note would still be there.
He had a $2 bill attached to his underwear that he was wearing not like in a suitcase.
It had a list of Spanish names on it and a Bible verse.
It had Ecclesiastes 12 1 through 8 and then there was a code next to it.
He also had a map pinned to his underwear.
Now I'm imagining like a huge random McNally map going from your waist to your knee but
it was probably just a little piece of paper and the map was showing where he was at.
Where he was going to.
So it was most likely a map for him to get there but actually that doesn't make sense
either because then did he keep taking his pants off to see he's like okay take a left
pull his pants back up.
So anyways before his body was found so he goes missing two months later and there was
a month between when he went missing again and when he was found his wife gets a phone
call from a woman who identified herself as green eyes.
She said Chuck is alright and everything will be alright.
Ecclesiastes 12 1 through 8 hangs up.
So now it's really really weird.
The wife tells the police about what happened and again they don't know that he's dead
at this point.
They just have that phone call.
The wife says this woman called me she said this the woman then goes to the police and
the police have never revealed who green eyes is but they know her they met her they talked
to her and police are like okay yeah the story checks out and the wife's like well who was
that and they're like we're not going to tell you who green eyes is.
So that means she's either a spook or an informant.
She's either like a CIA/FBI operative or she's a criminal informant.
But anyways so she just by saying Chuck is alright people get crank calls all the time
when these crimes happen.
Little kid goes missing the parents will get calls and saying all sorts of whacked stuff
I'm a psychic or I killed her whatever they get tons of crank calls but the fact that
she mentioned the bible verse that would later be found on his body shows that she knew something
about it.
He had a briefcase Morgan had a briefcase full of money he took it with him.
Here's one of the theories that so Charles Morgan in his job he worked in escrow in Arizona
they have what's known as a blind trust so you could have properties owned and nobody
knew who owned them but of course that only goes up to a certain level in the government.
So I want to be able to find out who owned this house but the government needs to know
who owns that house for tax purposes and part of his job was knowing being able to access
who owned what.
The idea was this he found he uncovered some sort of big scam or criminal scheme he found
information on people who were like buying houses and selling them or doing criminal
activities in them or money laundering or whatever he then began communicating with the FBI or
local authorities.
To the point and this is all stuff that's kind of in piece together this is kind of
the working theory to the point that a contract a hitman contract was put out on him.
The theory is that he drove out to this location he ended up getting a briefcase full of money
and I don't believe the money was found at his body I think that was gone as well but
people knew that he had a briefcase full of money I may be wrong on that detail they may
have actually found the money but I'm not for sure and again I have to leave like in
an hour.
The theory is this what was going on there was a hitman contract out for him it was gaining
like $5,000 a day the contract was only getting bigger he drove out to meet the hitman to
pay him off to end the contract and instead he got killed.
Afterwards his car was broken and his car was impounded it was broken into his office
was ransacked and two men showed up at his now what just wife's house claiming to be
FBI agents and they ransacked the house and she goes I don't know if they're FBI agents
they just kind of flashed their badges they came in moved everything around and that was
it so all of that being said we have green eyes we have the story of the hitman we have
him running into his house with the handcuffs the bullet in the back of the head the tooth
placed in his car the sunglasses that worn his a briefcase that may or may not have gone
missing the police after all of that caused a death suicide.
Car gets impounded and broken into no he killed himself no one outside killed this guy that
was their official ruling he committed suicide.
Now it's not impossible for you to shoot yourself in the back of the head find your
tooth fell out put it in a piece of tissue put in your car it's not impossible it's unlikely
but that's what the cops ruled it doesn't sound like a suicide to me at all sounds like
one of those stories that just kind of the cops are like ah bizarre case though and
as far as the police are concerned it's been solved it's been solved you know his behavior
was weird before generally if you commit suicide you don't get life insurance for your family
I know some states are different with that but if you're able to make it look like a
murder or an accident you can get life insurance.
But we're gonna end it like this let's take a real quick look at Ecclesiastes thought
it was an interesting verse because it kind of speaks to the mind of somebody who may
be at the end of their rope or maybe know that they're gonna die very shortly this is
the this is the verse that was written on his two dollar bill the whole verse wasn't
written there but remember your creator in the days of your youth before the days of
trouble come and the years approach when you will say I find no pleasure in them before
the sun and the light and the moon and the stars grow dark and the clouds return after
the rain when the keepers of the house tremble and the strong men stoop when the grinder
cease because they are few and those looking through the windows grow dim when the doors
to the street are closed and the sound of grinding fades when people rise up at the sound of
birds but all their songs grow faint when people are afraid of heights and of dangers
in the streets when the almond tree blossoms and the grasshopper drags itself along and
desire is no longer stirred then people go to their eternal home and mourners go about
the streets remember him before the silver cord is severed and the golden bowl is broken
before the pitcher is shattered at the spring and the wheel broken at the well and the dust
returns to the ground it came from and the spirit returns to God who gave it meaningless
meaningless says the teacher everything is meaningless dead rabbit radio gmail.com is
going to be our email address you can also hit us up on facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
twitter is @jasonocarpenter dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime
podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today have
a great one guys.
(upbeat music)