A miracle drug is revolutionizing the way that parents take care of their kids.
And then we journey back into Jason's Vault, a big old repository of personal creepy weird
stories that have happened to me.
But instead of just looking at a single event, we're going to look at a single place, the
city of Hood River. Nice little tourist town, but when the sun sets, it becomes darker than
you could ever imagine. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Also, great
news. You know, I make fun of a lot of nerds on this show. I'm always like, oh, science
is for nerds, geologists, but Jolamos with rocks. That's true. I'm not taking any of
that back. However, found out a couple days ago that the Russo brothers are now going to
make a Magic the Gathering and Media Television series for Netflix. And I was like, yeah,
all right, some MTG getting in there, getting that pop culture. I played Magic the Gathering
when it first came out when like 93, played it for a couple years, took two or three decades
off and got back into it when I think it was right after, I think it was right before Innistrad.
I was running an infect deck, so I became super popular at the hobby shop. I just moved
up to Hood River here. Hey, this actually works, because we'll talk about Hood River
at the end of the episode. But when I moved to Hood River, I had no friends at all. So
I was just looking for places to like meet like-minded people. Instead of going to a
bar like a normal adult, I'm like, I'm going to go to the hobby shop. Let's see what type
of fun people are down there. And there actually were a lot of cool people down there. But
went down there, built an infect deck and became super unpopular. Because if you don't
know, infect deck is the cheapest, most maniacal- Oh dude, my infect deck is on point too. It's
like a round three win, maybe round two if I get the right card. But anyway, so I'm looking
forward to that cartoon. Not a big fan of cartoons, but I'm a big fan of Magic the
Gathering. And I don't play as much now because I really don't have time to do anything else.
But yeah, no. And then I eventually got into the theater. That's where I made a lot of
my friends too. So, happy ending to that story. Jason has friends now, but let's go ahead
and get started here with our first story. I wonder what the theme song is going to be
like for Magic the Gathering animated show. I wonder if it's going to be like a magic
gathers every night. If it's going to be like a hard rock one, or if it's going to be like
a dubstep, as they're showing Jace spinning around, like stealing your cards. I don't
know. I don't know. I'm very interested in this cartoon. It'll probably suck. The Rooster
Brothers are doing it, so I have a little kind of high hopes for it. I'm sure they're
just executive producers. Let's move on to the topic here. So, I found this story recently.
It was one of those things that I read and it kind of like got under my skin. And I was
like, "Uhhh." And then I was like, "Uhhh, maybe I'll cover it. Maybe I won't." And then
I went and I reread the article a couple of days later and I said, "This is really just...
these people are insane. So, I'm going to cover it. This is totally nuts." So, there
is this article written for The Guardian, which is a British newspaper. And I'll just
read the headline to you, because it's really just the best way to jump into this. "It makes
me enjoy playing with the kids. Is microdosing mushrooms going mainstream?" So, what this
article does is it interviews a bunch of women, a bunch of housewives and working women, and
they take mushrooms. So, they microdose mushrooms. So, what it is is they're taking 0.1 gram of
shroom and eating it and then being like, "Oh my God, life is so awesome. My kids aren't
like totally annoying me anymore. I see the beauty of life." And this article is like,
"Listen, it just profiles women... No men get profiled in this article." And I think
there's a reason why, and we'll get to that in a second, but the profiles this woman after
woman after woman and really the undercurrent of the article is, "Shouldn't shrooms be legal?"
Because look at how much it's helped these women. A lot of the stories of the women go,
"Yeah, I actually do a lot better at work now and I enjoy being around my kids. They're
usually like showed a little douchebags, but now I can like hold them and not want to drown
them in a bathtub." And I love them. I love them so much. "Hey, you don't have any more
shrooms than you do, you name reporters." Like, "No, I don't." And they're like, "Ah, you
sure? You sure?" They're like digging through the carpet. No, so they take, apparently they
take 0.1 gram of shroom every two or three days. This is what's known as microdosing.
You can't take it too much because then you get a tolerance for it, but it allows you
to kind of experience things, kind of trippy. And then other people are like, "Yeah, I do
the shrooms. I also do a little acid, a microdose acid, and the reporter just totally glosses
over the fact that the drug has changed." Yeah, yeah, I do acid. Now, the article basically
as it goes through, these women are saying, "You know what? My life is so much better
now that I'm taking drugs and interacting with my children and doing my job." But I
face up to seven years in prison if the British police catch me with this mushroom kit. And
is it really such a crime for me to ingest drugs and then interact with children? I don't
think it is, world. I don't think it is. So there's a lot of stuff to unpack here. It's
kind of an interesting article, but the first thing is the people that they picked for it,
I think is an interesting look at it, is that they picked all women. They picked all women
like so you have, when you're reading this article, you envision like this harried housewife
or this single mom. They're all single, by the way. The one woman was actually married
and then the mushrooms made her divorce her husband. Like she's like, "It gave me a clarity
of thought that things just weren't working out." So I think if you turn this article
around and it was like, "Single dads, take shrooms every couple days." It would come
across totally differently. Single dads trying to have fun with their kids or drop an acid.
It shouldn't be legal. People would be like, "No, absolutely not. Single dads should not
be doing any drugs around their kids." But when you craft a narrative around like this
single mother trying to like have a corporate life and then raise three kids, it comes across
as more sympathetic, which is weird when you really kind of dig into the media. It's not
a matter of being like, "Oh, fake news, fake news." Like sometimes when you just look into
how a story is crafted, it's always kind of interesting to see the different emotional
pull. Secondly, it's the same thing. What if this article was like, you know, single
moms like to drink and drinking, drinking like, shooting back glasses of wine makes their
kids so much more adorable. People would be like, "That's horrible. That woman obviously
has a drinking problem. She shouldn't be drinking around her kids." But when you frame it in
this way of like, "These women are kind of rebellious," and this unknown substance, which
has been heavily studied, but this unknown substance that you take and makes everything
feel groovy and cool, again, it sets it differently in the minds of the readers. I'm one of those
guys who, I know they're talking about legalizing mushrooms in Colorado. I'm surprised they're
not legal in Oregon. I've never done a psychedelic. I have no interest in doing psychedelics.
If you guys lived in my brain or listened to every episode of my podcast, I think you
would go, "That's one guy who probably shouldn't do psychedelics," because his grasp on reality
is already so slim. At any point, you can just slip through my fingers. The last thing
I want to do is push that to the edge. So, if other people want to do psychedelics,
that's cool. I just don't necessarily think it's something that we should make openly
legal, recreationally legal. I don't know. It could be part of some sort of religious
ceremony or something like that. Because I just think it's one of those things that
if you don't have a strong sense of self, if you don't really know who you are, introducing
alien substances into you, and that's a conspiracy theory we'll get to, but introducing these
substances into you can fracture that identity even more. But whatever. If it is recreational,
if it isn't made legal, I'm not going to go protesting in the streets about it. I don't
think that, first off, I don't have kids, but from my experience around kids and knowing
lots of people with kids, being a parent isn't supposed to be super duper fun. It's supposed
to suck. It's supposed to be a little bit of fun, but it's also supposed to suck. If
you have to do drugs so you can tolerate your kids, your kids are probably pieces of shit.
If you can't, if your kids irritate you all the time, then imagine what they're doing
to everyone else in the world. Now I understand kids are going to get on your nerves some
of the time, but if you're like, "Oh, I have to do drugs to tolerate, to have fun with
my kids," then your kids are not good kids, and you have to do something about that. Because
we all can't get on shrooms too. It's just so bizarre. It's such a bizarre thing, and
it's being tabled, like, "Hey, let's make this stuff legal so these women can keep
getting high." Not the dudes, we're not going to profile any dudes, and we're not going to
talk about any other drugs except mushrooms and kind of acid. They just throw the acid
in there halfway through the article, because nobody wants that stuff. I did watch a Joe
Rogan podcast the other day when I was doing research for this, and he said he knows a
fighter, an MMA fighter who microdoses shrooms, and when he fights, he's too high. Like, he's
on shrooms when he fights, and Joe Rogan says he feels like he can see the punches coming
before they come. He goes, "He feels like it actually gives him an advantage." That's
cool. I'm totally down for that. But again, that's different. You're not doing MMA matches
against kids, and actually, if you do too much shrooms, you might. You might think the
kids are like ninjas coming into your house, and you got to take them down one by one.
So I don't know. I just think it's such a ridiculous trend. And I don't know how much
it's trending, but the article definitely made it sound to be this good thing that mothers
are getting high to be able to go about life. And also, they've done studies on this, and
the studies go, "It seems like a placebo. It seems like there's actually not enough
shrooms to have any effect whatsoever. They think it's just placebo because they think
it's a magical, groovy thing, dude. I'm like taking my shrooms." Did you imagine this article?
They're like, "People microdose meth. People microdose cocaine. You're not going to see
articles being like, "Dude, I got so much stuff done today because I microdose some
methamphetamines because I took crystal meth, but I only took 0.1 gram every 10 seconds.
You're not going to see those articles." So I just thought it was an interesting article
about culture and the way journalism is crafted. And just, I don't know, man. I would have
a hard time. I would feel bad if I turned out that after I grew up, I was like, "Hey, mom,
Memruan used to read me all those books." So she's like, "Oh, dude, I was so ripped."
I'm like, "What?" She's like, "Oh, yeah, dude, I was tripping balls when I was reading
you those books. I wasn't even reading those books. I forgot you existed. I was just reading
The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe, and I turned around, and then there was this little
kid here, and I was like, "Oh, yeah, you're right. I'm a mom." And I'm like, "What?"
That would kind of hurt my feelings if my mom had to get high to hang out with me. But
anyways, let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
Now, our next story is a request in a roundabout way because the other day on YouTube, we
had Charles Tucker, and he goes, "Hey, you got any more personal creepy stories?" And
I was like, "Well, of course. Of course." The question always is when to tell him because
I always envision the show going on for years and years and years. And I think we've covered
a lot of the big conspiracy iceberg stuff really, really early on in the show. When
I only thought the show was going to last 50 episodes, I was doing as much stuff as possible.
And now I'm thinking, "Well, there's not a lot of really good conspiracy iceberg stuff."
"McCamey Manor" is a snuff film. That was the last episode. That's actually on the
conspiracy theory iceberg, but it's the same thing with the personal stories. I don't want
to blow through all of them in the first 250 episodes. And then when we're on episode 1,050,
be like, "Ugh, I don't have any more cool stories to tell." Because what's happened
is they kind of have slowed down. Now, there's a lot of creepy stories that I have, though.
I wouldn't say a lot. There's probably like 8 or 9 or something like that. If I sat down
and really thought about it, I would probably come up with more. But "The Blue Boy" is
a very popular story that I've told my friends, the story of "The Blue Boy." The man with
the knives is actually a story I haven't told many people about. There was one time, actually
there was witnesses for this one. There was a time I fought a witch. And it's funny because
I totally forgot about fighting this witch. I told somebody about the story and we thought
it was funny. And then maybe two or years later, I was talking to that friend and they
were like, "Yeah, remember that time you fought a witch?" And I go, "What? What are you talking
about?" She goes, "Remember you fought that witch?" And I was like, "I have no idea what
you're talking about." And then she told me the story and then I started laughing so hard.
I was like, "Oh my God, I totally forgot about that. I fought a witch." Because my life is
so weird that sometimes the stuff like that, I just totally forgot. Because I was like,
"Oh yeah, there's this other craziness." One time I fought a witch. The portal. The portal
in the hotel. That's always an interesting story. It's fairly short. Giant Jesus. Giant
Jesus I think I've talked about in passing on the show. But I'll do a segment on Giant
Jesus coming up. But those are all stories for another time. Those are all stories for
another episode. What I want to talk about right now is the city of Hood River. That's
where I live. Hood River, Oregon. Now I moved here. I moved up and down California my entire
life. My dad was a minister. We traveled all the time. We grew up on college campuses while
my dad was going to school. Ended up in Sacramento as an adult and was there until I was about
34, 35, somewhere around there. Moved up to Hood River. There's a street in Hood River
called Wasco Street. And it basically cuts through the entire bottom half of the town.
There's basically you have Hood River proper, like downtown. You have State Street that
goes from that all the way through. There's only like 10,000 people in town. Very small
town. There's a State Street that goes all the way through from one point of the city
all the way to the other end of the city. And like out onto the freeway. There's Wasco
Street which is the same thing. It's just farther down into town. If you can imagine
towns broken up into three portions this would be the bottom portion. It takes you by like
the brewery district. Takes you by like the industrial stuff. And then we have the Heights
which is up a giant hill. You have a hospital and you have tons of residential stuff and
that's where you have like 10 different Mexican restaurants and grocery stores and stuff like
that. So that's kind of how the city is divided up. Now Wasco Street is probably the most
isolated of all the streets. Wasco Street you can be walking down at 8 p.m. and not
see anybody even though there's houses everywhere. Such a weird town. Now I used to live on Wasco
Street. I used to have to walk down Wasco Street all the time. And I hated it. Absolutely
hated it. It always felt off. So these are we're going to tell these stories in sequence
because I think that builds up to something. And the first couple you're going to be like
Jason you're just an idiot but stay with me here. It was four in the morning. I leave
my house on Wasco Street. I had my headphones on because I always got to listen to my music.
And it's so dark. If it wasn't for the street lights it would be pitch black. There is no
moon present this night. And I'm walking by this car. And so the car is like facing downhill
and I'm walking uphill. And when I get to where the trunk of the car would be so imagine
the car is on the side of the road and I'm walking past it. I'm walking in the street.
Very rarely walk on sidewalks. I like to have a little more maneuverability room. So not
super safe but anyway so I'm walking by the car and right when I get to where the trunk
is I feel wind on my face. Like so and now have my headphones on. Listen to music and
I felt a whoo. And as I mean it was like someone just blew a big gust of air right into the
side of my face. And as I'm turning my head to the left to see because I'm passing the
car on the left as I'm turning my head to the left to see what it is. I see these two
massive I wouldn't even say two. I would say I saw at least one massive wing come into the
field of my view and just go whoo. And something shoots up off the top of the car. And I see
that wing you know how like it was furling in to get like some thrust and kind of pick
itself up up here. That wing had to have the wingspan of me. It felt like it had a good
three four foot wingspan. And I didn't see it. It was too dark. I looked up. I couldn't
see anything. I felt it and saw that wing while I was still illuminated by the light
the street light and it just took off out of the air. So this is what I think it was.
I think and I've never seen anything this big but the logical answer is it's some sort
of giant owl was sitting on this car for whatever reason. And when I walked by it I scared it
as much as it scared me and it unfurled its wing and it was so close to me that when it
flapped its wings it made me I was able to feel the force of the air hit my head. And
it terrified me and I go well Jason again you're a city boy it was probably just a giant
owl hanging out on the top of a you know Chevy sedan or something so easily dismissed.
Probably I'm sure Alice can get that big. One day I'm walking down State Street. Again
that's kind of the other major thoroughfare. It's five in the morning. And there is a little
like stoplight. There's basically one stoplight in town. So you cross the street from the stoplight
there's a little restaurant called Aig River and they're pretty good but they're really
expensive and then you go past Aig River and then there's basically two hotels or an apartment
complex hotel apartment complex that's where we have a lot of places a lot of residential
places and there's always cars lined up along that road because people there's not a lot
of parking in the river so there's always cars pretty much lined up along this road
and I'm walking it's like four or five in the morning. And I always have this thing like
whenever someone's walking towards me I like to be out in the street I don't want to be
walking on the sidewalk with someone else at five in the morning because I have no reaction
time. I don't know what they're going to do I'd rather kind of walk and walk alongside
the cars as they're walking on the sidewalk. But anyway so I'm always just kind of looking
for movement down the road and I got my headphones on and listening to music and this is what's
so weird about the story is that I can't remember seeing it begin. It's like I either must have
been looking at something else and then turned my head or it's simply blinked into existence.
I think what's most likely is that I think what's most likely is I was looking at something
else and I turned my head to look back in front of me because what I see in front of
me maybe 25 feet away and again this is like four in the morning. I see something that
is about four or five feet high. Just the back of it I see these two long back legs and right
when I look at it the back legs walk behind a car that I have to pass. So there's a car
that I'm walking down the street. I'm walking on the sidewalk there's a car farther up and
I see something. Now I know that's a vague description because that's all that I saw
but basically what it looked like it was a four legged creature and I saw the hind quarters
move I didn't see what the front of it looked like. You're thinking Jason maybe that was
some big old dog. This is what creeped me out. One it had no hair whatsoever at all. It was
if it had hair it had the worst mange possible because it was just basically cadaver white
skin that wasn't super tight to the body it was almost just kind of lumpy. It had really
long back legs and the creepiest part was it actually walked and looked like a man would
if he tried walking on all fours. You know how when people try to walk on all fours their
legs are longer than their arms obviously so they do like that weird. It looked like
someone was bent in such a position they were walking on their hands and feet so their butt
was sticking way up in the air and they were walking with their hands and they were walking
behind this car. Now obviously that to me is far more disturbing if it was some old
naked man walking on his hands and feet hunched over like that walking behind a car that I
have to walk past that's far more disturbing than a ghost because this is some real thing
I'm gonna have to deal with or even like a dog or a wolf because I can take on a dog
maybe a wolf. I'll tell the dog story someday but it unsettled me but what was weird is
there is this weird moment where I didn't panic where I was like what in the world was that
and I actually then step off the sidewalk to see if I could watch it walk across the road
to see what it was and it didn't walk out from behind the car so now I'm like now whatever
it is is behind that car that I have to walk past so I then kind of am walking across the
road and trying to like look at the back of the car as I'm like moving so I'm like moving
in an almost a semi-circle motion to get to the other side of the street and at the same
time keep an eye on whatever that was nothing was there there was nothing behind that car
whatever it was couldn't have fit under the car where I wouldn't have noticed it. The
hair looked like a pale naked mole rat hair that's what it looked like but it was again
it's butt was about up to the size of my belly button so if it's when I said it was about
three feet high that was the part I could see if it stood up it would have easily have
been my height or taller. It was skinny with really long skinny legs and the skin kind
of held like folded up like hung in folds I guess is the way I should say it. Pale white
nothing was there when I walked around. Now obviously I go I must have been imagining
that or that must have been an hallucination or something like that. Must have not seen
that right. Maybe a week or two later I walked down State Street the Walmart used to be open
24 hours a day it's gonna do some shopping buy some stuff for the day where I probably
had nothing planned I was probably just buying chili beans and rice and all of that stuff
said at home watch YouTube and pretend I was an author like I used to do for years. I'm
walking basically State Street and Wasco Street eventually collide and then there's a staircase
that takes you down and there's hills everywhere so there you the Wasco Street and State Street
collide and then there's the Walmart and I get to the Walmart I start to walk down the
stairs now because everything's kind of a series of hills a lot of times you don't have
straight shot vision which is another thing I'm not used to in Sacramento you could basically
look from one end of Sacramento to the other until your vision didn't work anymore it was
completely flat but here you you don't know what's coming up I'm walking down State Street
I'm turning to where it collides with Wasco I get to the top of the staircase that will
take me down to Walmart and now I have a straight shot because basically Walmart is the you
know what a Walmart is it's just a giant box building and it basically sits 10 feet from
a freeway so I'm at the top of the stairs and I can see everything from the freeway
to the stairs where I'm at and what I see come out of the darkness near the freeway
is a giant I would say again maybe three four feet high white quadruped run full speed from
the freeway towards the stairs wasn't a dog wasn't a coyote it wasn't anything I couldn't
even tell you what the head looked like it it was fairly triangular which originally
as I'm watching it run it felt like it was some sort of canine but its behavior was what
was kind of making me think that's not what it was it didn't kind of have like a snout
like face but it was charging me from a good hundred yards away and it was fast and the
way this is so bizarre and the way I'm positioned is that I'm approaching the top of the stairs
and I can see this thing run full speed along the front of Walmart headed towards the stairs
but I'm still approaching the stairs I don't get to see the staircase myself now I immediately
gird myself for some sort of attack like I'm like whatever this is I can't outrun it and
I remember again a very calm sense as this was going on I remember thinking I can't stop
this and it reaches it reaches the bottom of the stairs which is out of my view because
I'm still kind of walking towards the stairs so I'm watching it run and run and run and
I see it fall out of my field of view so now I know it's right at the bottom of the stairs
and I'm waiting for it to run up those stairs completely disappeared nothing was there at
all never saw that thing again I remember when I first moved up here I was on 4chan
and someone happened to post hey does anyone know whatever happened to that story about
that black dog I think it was in some town called Hood River in Oregon and it was and
it was someone just posted it on a creepypasta thing on 4chan no one ever responded to that
and I looked valiantly for more information about this creature and couldn't find anything
couldn't find anything at all I was wondered if how that came about but there definitely
was this white creature running around Hood River couldn't really understand what that
was so that was the only two sightings of that thing but for me that was enough for
me that was enough because whatever it was it didn't have a problem getting close to
people definitely didn't get have a problem getting close to me but I have one more place
to talk about this episode might run a little long sometimes these personal episodes do
run a little long this isn't a cryptid as much as it is a place and it's so funny because
the name itself is so ridiculous it almost precludes it from being scary but it's a
place in Hood River that is known by me at least I've tried spreading the legend catches
on here and there the haunted frisbee golf course the haunted frisbee golf course is
this well it's kind of what it says there's a frisbee golf course that's haunted and it's
on Wasco Street now again Wasco Street is easily the most unsettling stretch of land
in Hood River across the from it there's a skate park where there's I always keep wanting
to go off on these segways and the episode's already running too long I'll do this one when
I first moved up here I was a much heavier I was walking down Wasco Street and I had
bought subway and I'm walking down subway street cannot subway seat I'm walking down
the street by the skate park and I'm carrying my subway I'm this big guy I was wearing glasses
and some 12 year old kid 14 year old kid whatever goes hey look it's Jared from subway and I
I was shocked I was shocked because where I came from you would get your brains blown
out you wouldn't when I grew up if you yelled out something to a random stranger you wanted
to get in a fist fight and or you're you were stupid in your brains just got scattered
everywhere I was floored that some kid would yell because I'm thinking this guy doesn't
know who I am like you would never do that in Sacramento unless you were looking for
a fight and I knew in Hood River people are just like again it's just like this super
it's just a weird town up here you get a fist fight cops show up like what seriously like
the cots in the newspaper fist fight breaks out downtown I'm like seriously this town's
weird but anyways that can't I was like I can't believe anyone would say that to a random
stranger if he doesn't know who I am Sacramento you would never do that if you did that that's
you were looking for a fist fight or you I could say you were an idiot but anyways I
just kept walking because I was like you can't be the shit out of this kid because I'm in
Hood River Sacramento might be different story so the Frisbee golf course is right across
the street from the skate park and it is basically just a ton of trees and there's a couple little
poles set there and you can throw your Frisbee and go like hole in one guys yay ultimate
Frisbee let's do this it's the poor man's version of golf and the lame man's version
of every other sport ever invented Frisbee golf so Frisbee golf course now I had had
to walk past the Frisbee golf course all the time because I lived on Wasco Street and I
didn't really think anything of it but when I was walking by it after again 10pm to like
4am I've been to like places where I've been to like flop houses I've been to places where
junkies hang out I've been to crime scenes I've seen body parts I've been to some pretty
messed up places no place has ever filled me with such despair as walking past that
Frisbee golf course utter hopelessness for half a block it is the most terrifying walk
I've ever done and I used to have to do it all the time I worked late started early had
to walk by this stretch it was so unnerving to me that it actually like I would I didn't
even want to think about walking by it and to walk past that I had to go up the super
steep hill so it was this question of do I want to walk up this hill and like blow my
knees out because again I was much heavier back then or do I want to face my worst fears
when you walk down that half a block it's like you are in you know the true definition
of hell isn't the flames and the burning but it's just separation from God that's what
that street feels like to me there's one street light that if you're lucky works somehow the
light doesn't even illuminate the whole area you're walking through pretty much pitch darkness
and you feel separated I remember once I was walking through I was I was walking through
this street and I remember thinking if that light blows out if that light gave out right
now I would assume that God was punishing me for something I felt soulless when I was
there and I was in a state of panic every single time and you're thinking chasing just
a pussy but see here's the thing this is one of the theories I came up with you know when
you go to church or when you go to a special place you go to a meadow that you really
love or there's a particular classroom you enjoy something like that but I think the
church is the best example when you go to church and the singing is going on and the
praising is going on and stuff like that you actually feel your spirit start to get lifted
up like oh this place it makes me feel good now they've always there's always been that
idea that belief and I'm sure it's true to some extent but when the Catholics when basically
the European Christianity movement was taking over they were destroying pagan temples places
where the pagans hung out and building churches right on top of them and part of the logic
is that way the pagans would know where to go they're basically having their whole culture
co-opted but the other thing is that maybe that place for whatever reason has some sort
of spiritual energy and the Christians moving into the area go this place is perfect to
put a church this place has all this positive energy from all these years of the pagans
doing this stuff it just has a has all this positive energy let's build a church here
if you accept that there are places on the planet that can harness and store powerful
energy or you just accept that when you go to a place that is holy to you you can feel
the spirit inside of you there's an inverse to that there are places that are dark and
dreary and charged with negative energy and if you want to be around that negative energy
you will go to that place like it was a church you will go there to refill your your stores
of negative energy this frisbee golf course a lot of times has like RVs parked outside
of it it's not really patrolled by police that much and that always terrified me as
well it has straight access to the freeway it's maybe a five minute drive you can get
on the freeway you can do any sort of creepy nonsense weirdo stuff you want there and be
gone on the freeway within five minutes but I was thought it was weird I'd walk by these
RV campers and I'm thinking the logical part of me is saying they're here because the police
don't patrol this area much but then the other thing is like if you were a negative person
this is where you'd want to hang out the frisbee golf course itself you go there day or night
now this has been my experience every single time but if you go there day or night it's
completely quiet it's next to us neighborhood so you'll maybe hear like a dog barking on the street
no bugs no birds no squirrels no nothing the place there's something wrong with it we do have a lot
of homeless people in hood river not like compared to like LA which is like 65,000 or something maybe
it's not that high but we have maybe like a hundred 200 homeless people in town they don't camp there
I'll see him camping in other places they don't camp in there because I've gone through with groups
of friends and there at night we never ran into a homeless person ghost hunting never saw anything
with them brought in cameras never saw anything but there is something off about that area so you
have the frisbee golf course itself that whole area just seems really off it doesn't really help
that there's a memorial to a dead teen in the skate park next to it so you have the skate park the
road and the frisbee golf course right before I moved up here some young kid named Forrest was
was skateboarding down wasco street and a car slammed into him and then they built like a
memorial form so when you're walking by there for in the morning that doesn't make you feel any better
you got that memorial on one side of you frisbee golf course on the other side of you to top this
story off they're tearing down the frisbee golf course they're building some apartments there
and if that set of apartments is not haunted I'll eat your hat you pick out a hat and I'll eat it
but only one of you and it has to be a tasty hat has to be made out of pizza so we have all of these
stories stories of cryptids that I've seen one of them was probably just a giant owl but the other
one was that white beast you just have the haunted little section of wasco street that kind of
perfectly sums up how creepy this town is overall now like I said in the beginning I've seen tons
of things in my life tons of ghosts and demons and creatures and things you just can't explain
but it wasn't until I moved to hood river that I saw something that I didn't think I'd ever see
I saw something that while I knew was real thought I would never see one
it wasn't until I moved to hood river and was living on wasco street
that I saw an angel
but that's a story for another episode
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead
rabbit radio twitter is @jasonOcarpenter dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today
have a great day guys
[MUSIC]