A man is the victim of a horrible crime and 911 puts him on hold.
What?
A small town in Brazil uncovers a disgusting pile that may lead to a dark conspiracy.
It's a pile of what?
Who knows?
You have to keep listening.
And then we stay in Brazil to look at a man who had a close encounter of the burned kind.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
First off, it's weird the past couple of nights.
I get this weird feeling in my bedroom.
I have to use the bathroom a lot because I'm old.
When the older you get, the more you have to use the bathroom.
Plus I drink a lot.
I go in to use the bathroom.
It's my bedroom.
I don't want to come out for the past couple of nights.
I don't want to turn my back to the like, it's getting creepy bro.
I sleep in my living room because it's just the weird thing that I have.
Sleep in the living room.
I've been most of my time in the living room.
Sun goes down.
I have to still go to the bathroom.
I go into my bathroom.
It's creepy.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's just me.
I don't know if it's just stress.
Most likely is both of those things rather than some sort of phantasm trying to get me
after urinating.
But yeah dude, it sucks.
So I'll keep you guys informed.
I'll keep you guys informed of my impending nervous breakdown because I think there's
a goblin in my bedroom is how it would be the best way to say that.
Also let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter.
We got Sean in the house.
Sean, thank you so much for supporting the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
You're going to be our pilot.
You're going to be our captain this episode.
Really, really means a lot.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too guys.
Just help get the word out about the show.
Really, really helps a lot.
I really, really appreciate it.
Sean, I'm going to flip you those keys to the carpenter copter.
First off, we are flying out to Macon, Georgia.
We're coming over.
I imagine Georgia has lots of trees.
Right?
Florida is all swampy.
Georgia has a bunch of trees.
Tennessee, I imagine is all bunch of hills and stuff like that.
I don't know.
I don't know anything outside of 10 miles of where I'm currently living.
We're flying over the trees of Georgia.
It's May 19th, 2020, so super recent.
This was a couple days ago.
Now, this specifically, if you live in Macon, Georgia, you can actually visit this location.
This may be a new, like, true crime hub.
Guys, if you live in Macon, Georgia, I know I'm, isn't it Macon?
Macon, Macon, whatever.
If you live in Macon, Georgia, get ready to go out there and start tearing down street
signs because this is going to be an amazing spot for history.
It's on Forest Hill Road and Northside Drive.
I guess there's, like, a CVS pharmacy in the area.
There's a hotel in the area.
We're going to meet a man named Chris Key, so let's land our helicopter in the parking
lot of this hotel.
We're, like, crushing cars and stuff.
We all jump out of the carpentry copter just in time to see Chris Key.
He's 56 years old.
He's a teacher, married teacher.
He's a normal dude, right?
If you're not a teacher and you're not married, you are abnormal.
So we're all abnormal.
We're the freaks, the chuds crawling out of the helicopter.
Chris Key's.
He's a teacher.
He's married.
He's at the CVS pharmacy doing normal person stuff.
He's buying stuff.
He's trading money for goods and services.
So after he's done doing normal stuff, he gets in his car and right then two dudes walk
up and they're like, "Yo," put a gun to his head, "drive to the hotel."
And he's like, "Oh, I'm just a normal person.
I'm a teacher.
I'm married."
And they're like, "We don't care."
Actually, I've heard a tip.
If someone ever has a gun on you, don't say I have a wife and kids or don't be like, like
pleading like that because a lot of times the people who have the gun may have like
a crummy life and they're like, "What?
I don't have wife or kids."
Like don't, you can be like, "Yo, I'll give you all the money and stuff like that.
Like here you go."
But don't be like, "No, my life's totally awesome.
Please don't kill me.
Everything's perfect."
Don't just, you're supposed to humanize yourself but don't brag.
I guess it would be the, what, I have, not only do I have wife and kids, my wife is Brainy
Spears and my kids are millionaires.
Anyways, you should humanize yourself but don't brag.
That's a tip if you ever get taken hostage.
That's a dead rabbit radio tip.
Anyways, I'm a normal person.
We'll continue the narrative.
We don't care.
We're taking you to the hotel and they take them to the hotel and they rob them.
They take us cash.
Give us, give me that money.
Take $70 in cash and they leave.
Now Chris is like, "No, my normal life has now been destroyed.
I've been robbed a single time in my life."
He calls up 911 and for one hour nobody shows up.
911, what's your emergency?
Air quotes, emergency.
We don't, no, no, no, I just got robbed.
Yeah, whatever.
We don't believe you.
So he's doing that for an hour.
Finally the cops show up and the cops go, he tells the cops the story.
"Look at me.
I'm totally normal person.
I got robbed."
The cops go, "Sir, listen, what do you think we are?
Cops?
What do you think it's our job to go arrest people?
We can't catch this guy and even if we caught the guy, there's nothing we can do with him."
Or them, because there's two of them.
There's nothing we can do.
So we're not even going to look into this.
Now Chris is like, "No, this is some, even though I'm a married teacher, this system
is stacked against me.
No!"
Now Chris tells that story.
That story is all well and good.
And I think the fact that I've referred to it as a story twice in 10 seconds should let
you know what's happening.
He tells the story and it goes viral.
Some woman with some friend of his posted on Facebook that whole story being like, "You
won't believe what happened to Chris Keyes."
I don't think she mentioned him actually, but she goes, "You won't believe what happened
at the local CVS."
And she says, "I had a friend who was robbed at CVS a couple months ago and this has happened
again and the police wouldn't show up and when they finally showed up they said they
weren't even going to investigate it and if they didn't investigate there's nothing
you can do."
When you guys go out in public, know who you're going with, make sure you know the surroundings,
run a buddy system.
That's all good advice, right?
The story wasn't true though.
And I'm going to tell you this right now.
Here's another Dead Rabbit radio trip.
If you're going to lie about something like this, don't say the cops are much idiots.
Because what happened was the post went viral and people started complaining to the police
department.
So the chief is like, "Do we have a report of this happening?"
And the cops are like, "No, we were never called out there."
Chief goes, "Okay, you need to find out what happened because either this guy's faking
this story or he didn't report a crime, but either way he's making us look bad."
So if he had just told that story and be like, "I got robbed and I bother not to call the
cops, there's only 70 bucks, I'm lucky I got away with my life."
The post still made it went viral, but the cops would have been like, "Well, it's his
choice whether or not to investigate it."
The fact that he says it took an hour for the police to show up, they refused to help
me and they said they're powerless even if they did help me.
The police obviously look into this.
Now the real story comes out.
Chris Key's married teacher, he wants to have gay sex.
So he decides to put an ad on Craigslist and says, "Meet me at this hotel room."
So he goes to the hotel room, two dudes come in with guns and take 70 bucks from them and
bounce.
Now this episode is becoming a lot of Jason advice.
One, don't cheat on your wife, right?
That's pretty tacky.
So don't cheat on your wife.
That's rule one.
That's life lesson two.
Two, if you are going to cheat on your wife, you should use the buddy system.
You should bring a friend with you in case you get robbed.
It's funny because all of the advice the girl said at the ending of her post, or she's
like, "Know the area you're in.
Know who you're talking to.
Have the buddy system."
If he had followed that advice, he never would have gotten robbed in the first place.
But anyways, he wants to cheat on his wife with another dude.
He puts it out on Craigslist.
Dude shows up, robs him.
He doesn't have the buddy system.
The robber has a buddy system.
The robber has another dude with him.
They take his money and bounce.
The easiest thing would have been to do is to not told anybody.
Right?
I've been a victim of a billion crimes that I've never reported because it's not even
worth my time to report.
Now that actually made me sound like I'm a big old wimp.
But you know what I mean?
Stuff happens.
You get a car accident, whatever.
I'm not going to call the cops.
Stuff gets stolen.
I've had tons of stuff stolen.
I've never called the cops.
People breaking into my car, unless I was trying to get insurance out of it.
If I didn't have insurance, I never called the cops.
Or insurance that would fix my windows.
I didn't care.
Oh man, someone broke into my car, took my bag.
I cared and I would look for my backpack and I was very, very angry, but I didn't involve
the cops.
This guy, he's now in jail for solicitation of sodomy.
Which I didn't even know was a crime.
So that's like their solicitation for prostitution.
Then this one specifically for sodomy.
He's like, "No, we're only going to do mouth stuff."
No, no, but it doesn't matter.
That's the charge.
He could have just gone home and said, "Oh yeah, I lost $70.
I tried playing the Lotto and I lost or I left my wallet somewhere."
She's like, "That's where you still have your wallet."
He's like, "Oh, but I found my wallet and there was no cash."
The fact that he then, the fact that he made up the story that the police department of
Maycon, Georgia is completely incompetent.
They don't know how to do their jobs.
Ends it up busting him in the end because it does turn out they do know how to do their
jobs and they arrested you.
Now he did get robbed.
He did get robbed.
So that part of the story is true.
The woman who posted it was like, "You know, be careful.
People are getting robbed in this area."
Although now I'm thinking her friend who got robbed a couple months ago.
He might have been at that hotel too.
So who knows?
Maybe it is an ongoing mystery.
But that is now a true crime hub.
If you live in Maycon, Georgia, I want a photograph of that street corner.
Send it to me, deadraviradiojmail.com.
Sean, I want you to fire back up that carbonar copter.
We are headed out to Brazil now.
This is a story that was actually sent to me by Bennett.
I got a huge email from Bennett the other day.
He's always sending me gold.
He sent me this big project that we'll be talking about coming up.
I kind of forgot the best way to present it, but he's definitely done a lot of good stuff
for the show.
Really appreciate it.
This is from Bennett.
We're landing in Sao Lorenco, Brazil.
So let's bring that helicopter nice and low flying over the jungle.
We're going to a bunch of different biomes today.
We're landing on like a road and we're hopping out.
It's August 2015.
Now we're on this like dirt road.
That's not racist.
I saw a photo of it.
It's dirt.
I'm not saying all the roads in Brazil are dirty.
There's like a dirt road.
And there's a big carnival going on in town.
Everyone's like...
We can hear the music from super far away, right?
And you wish we were at the festival, but I had Sean land the helicopter here.
We're just in this field by this dusty road.
And off to the side, we see like a big old pile of stuff.
And I go, dude, I'll give you five bucks if you run blindfolded and jump into that pile
of pile of...
Jump into it like it's a pile of leaves.
And you're like, is it a pile of leaves?
And my eyes go from side to side.
I'm like, yeah, leaves as in a verb.
Someone left to something and you're like, that's kind of weird.
But you do it anyways, because you want to have fun on this episode of Dead Wrap Radio.
So you run and I'm in control of what you do.
You run and you jump into this big pile.
Now what you have jumped into with or without your permission, I made your body do this.
150... you're now neck deep in a pile of 150 cat and dog tails.
Jason, get me out of here.
Get me out of here.
And then I allow you to move out my mental powers, even the ability to walk you crawl
out of these.
Now it's 150 tails of cats and dogs.
These piles are found all over the area.
Sometimes there's up to 300 tails in a single pile.
Sometimes the piles are smaller.
Piles of 800 cat and dog tails are found on roads leading to Sao Lorenco.
Now there's photos of this.
I don't suggest looking at them, but there's photos of this stuff.
This is some sort of urban legend.
The first suggestion is someone must have been selling animal meat at the festival.
And they just disposed of all the tails on their way to town to sell the meat.
But here's the thing.
I gave you an incorrect timeline in the beginning just because I wanted to do that little musical
interlude.
The tails were actually found after the fair.
After the carnival is when the tails were found.
So people go, "Wait a second.
If people were dropping the tails off as they were coming to town with the meat, we would
have found the tails as people were also coming to carnival.
We didn't find them until days after the festival ended."
So what happened?
So then people go, "Well, maybe the animals were collected locally, still sold as meat."
And as the people were leaving town counting their money, they were throwing tails out
behind them.
"Binnie, what do you want me to do with these tails?
We're done with them already.
Just throw them around.
Let's sell Lorenco deal with them."
As their little cars are driving away.
But people go, "That doesn't make sense either because none of our animals are missing."
They did a census.
No one was reporting cats or dogs missing from the area.
So now they're thinking, "So wait, these aren't our cats and dogs.
They must have come from another area.
But why are they being dropped off on our roads?"
Two suggestions pop up.
One is the commercial slaughter of animals.
So they're still going down that route.
The other one is black magic.
Someone is sacrificing animals.
They're dropping the tails off here for some reason.
But again, they can't account for 800 tailless animals or even 800 animals missing in the
first place.
They actually put a box in the middle of town and they go, "Listen, we know one of you guys
is killing cats and dogs.
And it's okay.
We're not going to do anything to you.
We just want to know who it is."
So we're going to put a box in the middle of town.
There's a reward of $620.
Anyone can drop a letter in there.
No one has either admitted to it or rat it someone out.
No one in town knows where these tails are coming from or why they're there.
And that happened back in August of 2015 and there's been no update to this story.
It's one of those weirds, and thanks Bennett for sending us that.
It's one of those weird stories that can be either or.
It could be a financial motivation.
Someone just has a bunch of junk laying around.
They've sold all the meat and they're just throwing the tails out of the cars or driving
away.
The other one is someone is ritually sacrificing all of these animals and leaving the tails
is part of the ritual.
But who knows?
Nobody knows for sure where these animals came from, why someone's dumping them off
or what they're doing with the meat.
But I'm sure that in other parts of Brazil, the mystery continues.
There may be other villages along the road that they wake up, "Oh, it was having such
a great day!"
And they look in the mirror.
They don't look in the mirror yet.
Hold on.
They're brushing their teeth.
And then they look up and standing behind them is, I don't know, a giant tail.
That was going to be my joke.
You look up and there's a giant tail standing behind them in the mirror.
It doesn't really work.
They go, "Here's a better one.
Here's a better one."
Now that I'm trying out material on my show.
There's another town, five weeks later, there's another town in Brazil.
They haven't heard about what happened in this town yet.
Carnival hasn't reached them.
This guy goes to lay down in bed and he's like, "Good night, honey.
I'm not going to look at you in the lights off and I'm going to crawl in a bed."
And then he's snuggling up to her and he goes, "Oh, you're more furry than normal."
And you feel more detached and a little bit more bloody than you normally do.
And he's hugging his wife and he starts making out with her.
And then the light turns on.
Why am I even continuing this stupid thing?
The light turns on and his wife's like, "Oh!"
And then he realizes that his wife is standing at the doorway, turning on the light, and
he's making out with a bag of cat and dog tails.
And then there's some dude walking through the city with, I don't know, I want him.
Some dude walked through the city with a hood on and he has a bag of cat and dog tails and
he's like, "I don't know.
I don't think I'm officially lost my mind.
But let's go on.
What was that?
Let's go ahead and move on to the next story while I still have some semblance of a thought
process.
Sean, I want you to fire up that Jason Jalapi.
We're leaving behind the man with the bag of cat tails who's also causing people to
have sex with him somehow.
We're going out to a town known as Araki Gama.
Araki Gama, that's in Brazil.
Now a lot of this story, there's a couple stories on this, but I got the bulk of my
information from an article called "Burning Man of Brazil" written by Dr. Abner Malady.
I don't think he's a real medical doctor.
This is from a website called Warmwood Chronicles.
So thank you, Dr. Abner Malady.
Again, I want to see that.
I want to see where you got your medical degree.
This is a story that takes place on March 4th, 1946.
It's fairly well documented.
There's been a couple different versions of the story and there have been witnesses that
have come forward and things like that.
Sean pulls up to this town.
It's a population of about 7,000 people, so it's a pretty big town.
But on this particular night, on March 4th, 1946, on the outskirts of this town, the way
outskirts of this town, about 2 miles away, there is a house and it is populated by the
Philho family.
And there's a carnival going on.
There's a lot of carnivals in this episode.
There's a big carnival going on.
So his family is not home.
The family of Jau Prestes Philho.
Jau?
How?
Mr. Philho.
Mr. Philho's family is not present.
They're at the carnival.
So Mr. Philho had just gone fishing with his buddy and his buddy and him were walking through
the jungle alone.
Then the buddy peels off to go to his house and Mr. Philho goes home to his house alone.
Door's locked.
Oh, are you kidding me, dude?
My family's 2 miles away.
I don't have the keys.
I didn't really plan this out well.
But I'm skinny enough I will crawl through my window.
So he crawls through his window and he's now in his pitch black house and then he sees
a bright light outside of his house.
Automatically draws his attention and he turns and looks and this fiery orb comes into his
house and then torches him.
He feels a heat beam hit the entire upper half of his body.
In an instant he's burning.
He's not on fire.
But his skin is fried.
Ah!
He begins screaming.
But there's no one around to hear him.
There's no one around him for 2 miles.
The orb disappears.
And he looks down at his hands and they're burned into claws.
He can't even move his fingers.
It's just torched.
Ah!
He can feel the burns on his face.
He can feel the burns on his upper body.
He doesn't have a phone.
He doesn't have a car.
He can't even put his shoes back on because his hands are all melted and stuff.
No!
I shouldn't have taken my shoes off immediately.
He thinks.
But then he also thinks, "Ah!
I'm burning!"
He has to walk for 2 miles barefoot along this dirt path to get to town.
And you're like, "Jayson the dude just got horribly burned."
I don't think he's like, "Ouch!
He stepped on a rock.
But I hate stepping on rocks."
So when I read that I was like, "Ouch!"
It's funny because it's hard for us to be empathetic of pain.
Getting your arm chopped off with a chainsaw, that hasn't happened to me.
So I'm not like, "Ooh!"
But watching someone get like a splinter or peel back a nail, that really...
Some of you guys had to add a reaction when I said that too.
So we've all walked barefoot and stepped on rocks.
I've never been torched by a...
Whatever this thing was.
We'll get into it in a second.
Actually, we'll get into it right now.
As he's walking these 2 miles, he believes he knows what got him.
You see, in this area of Brazil, and it's actually all over Brazil, but...
There's a thing called a "boitata."
A boitata.
It's a fire spirit.
It's a malevolent fire spirit.
And it's basically a lot of times it will attack you if you disrespect nature.
Sometimes they'll just fly by in the sky.
They won't really affect you.
But other times they're like, "Uh-uh, I'm messing this dude up."
And they'll burn you.
When he was younger, he was once leading a donkey thing.
Like a donkey cart.
It was a cart full of donkeys being pulled by another donkey.
And he sees one of those boitatas.
He sees this flaming ball of light streak down from the sky.
And he said, "It came so close to him and the donkeys.
He felt that he was radiating off the orb."
So we'd seen these things before.
Now near the town, there was the mine known as the Moro Velho.
It was one of the deepest...
It's still one of the deepest mines today, up until the year 1918.
It was the deepest mine in the world.
Nowadays it's about 9,800 feet deep.
So a lot of people have died there.
A lot of people have talked about it, you know, like drilling into the earth.
What spirits are being unleashed.
So these boitatas would be seen in the area.
Some people believed it was actually the ghost of dead miners.
But whatever they were, miners as in people mining, not dead kids, people would say,
"We see this phenomenon."
Now this is 1946.
This is before we even have mass UFO sightings in anywhere.
You had World War II pilots talking about food fighters.
But we hadn't had the term "flying saucer" had not entered the consciousness, none of that stuff.
So this even predates all of them.
So they're immediately thinking of some sort of spirit.
They see them in the air.
But none had been attacked by one in this area until now.
Now Mr. Velho was thinking of that.
And when he gets done with that chain of thought, he looks up and he sees town.
He's like, "Oh, that was convenient."
And he walks into town.
He's like, "Ah, I've been burned.
I've been burned."
And they take him to the hospital.
And the doctors are looking at him and they go, "Yeah, you're right.
You are like horribly, horribly burned."
Now there's a version of the story that seems to be the most popular version that when he
gets to the hospital, he's burned up.
And the doctors and the nurses are trying to treat him.
And as they're treating him, they see his skin begin to dissolve.
And then eventually he begins to fall off like soup out of a paper bag.
It just seems to just drip off of him.
And then they watch his muscle tissue get soft, then rot, and then begin to slip off
like chicken at contemporary chicken.
And then he just has bones.
He's just like a skeleton, chattering his teeth, playing his xylophone.
He's just a skeleton there.
They're actually watching this man rot in front of them.
And he didn't seem to be in any pain.
He's just sitting there and his like tongues melting and his skin's melting.
His hair was perfectly fine.
His clothes weren't burned.
But he eventually just melted away.
And they declared him on his death certificate he died of cardiac arrest.
So that's one version of it.
But the way I ended that story, I was suspicious when I first read it.
I go, "Wait a second.
The doctors watched the man melt."
And they go, "But what really killed him was heart attack and not like everything being
exposed to the open air."
A witness case.
So that story's been going around for a long time.
This story is a true story.
But he didn't melt.
Because a witness came forward later, a witness known as Virgilio Alves.
He said he was here.
He goes, "He didn't melt.
I was there.
He didn't melt.
He did show up to the hospital.
He was severely burned.
When we asked him what happened, he said a boy Tata got him.
He tells the exact same story.
He broke into his house.
This thing comes through the window that he had just previously broken through.
Shoots him with this beam.
He walks two miles.
So the only difference between the sensational account is how he died.
The more grounded account was something that did blast him.
And doctors there said it looks like he'd been hit with some sort of radiation.
1946 was long enough after Hiroshima and Nagasaki that doctors were familiar with what radiation
damage would look like.
They go, "It looks like he's been blasted with something."
His clothes weren't burned.
His hair wasn't burned.
But he was horribly burned.
He couldn't move his hands.
He didn't seem like he was in any pain whatsoever.
Except he kept complaining that he stepped on a bunch of rocks.
It wouldn't make sense because at that point, so many nerve endings are burned up.
They classified him.
If you look at the real death certificate, it's classified as cardiac arrest after receiving
first and second degree burns.
So I mean, the dude was burned by something.
The investigators, obviously they're not thinking, "Oh, he was killed by a ghost."
They went out to his house.
Nothing in his house was burned.
They said they noticed some chairs had been knocked over.
Window had been busted, but nothing was on fire.
His clothes weren't on fire.
And he died.
He died that night.
Now, it's one of those stories that you actually have a lot of different people looking into.
UFOologists say it was UFO, of course, right?
A big phoetologist would say it was Bigfoot with a flamethrower.
The UFOologists have looked back and said, "We believe because the radiation burns it
might have been an after thruster or an engine from a UFO blast."
I mean, maybe.
The fact that it was flying around in his house, unless it was that little Martian from Flintstones,
I don't think I've really encountered a UFO that can fly through somebody's house.
That's that small.
But because it's labeled as radioactive damage, the UFO community got all over this one.
The people in the area believe that it was a boy tata, that it was a spirit that for
some reason was angered by him.
Chased him down.
Another logical answer is ball lightning.
And a lot of people have said it could have just been -- it classified as ball lightning.
Ball lightning is seen in Brazil.
Could have came through and shocked him, burned him horribly.
The pushback on that is that usually people who die of ball lightning, they die immediately.
I guess you should explain what ball lightning is.
My great grandma saw ball lightning.
Ball lightning is one of those phenomenon that's so rare that for the longest time people
didn't believe it.
My grandma was younger.
My great-grandma.
She was born in 1906.
She's passed away now.
She lived to be like 93.
She said when she was younger, she was sitting in her house and a ball of lightning just
shh came in through a window and just moved through the house and then hit a door and
like went out the door.
"Oh my stars and garters!
No one would believe that story.
No one believes stories like that for the longest time because it was so rare.
But it's literally a ball of lightning that will just float around.
Don't get near it.
It's not cuddly.
It's just because it's a ball doesn't mean you can go dribble it.
It will blast you.
But normally it's like people don't normally get struck by lightning.
It's funny.
Now I'm going to tell another story.
My great-uncle was once walking through a field with two cans, two tall boys.
No, he's walking through a field with two buckets and there were two pigs walking under
each bucket and he's walking through the field and he's holding a bucket in each hand and
a bolt of lightning hit him, went through him, went through the buckets and killed both
the pigs and his hands were fused to the buckets.
To this day, we still call him Bucket Hand.
No, he's passed away too.
We never got on Bucket Hand.
They did have to work on getting his hands open.
I mean like they just froze onto the metal.
I wonder if that would be weird if my family like, maybe my family has a lightning.
Maybe I'm going to send them to Zeus.
Who knows?
But probably not.
Probably not.
Probably not just a member of a fictional character, but you never know.
But anyway, so, ball lightning will kill it.
This is an interesting story because, one, it involves a dude getting fried by something
completely unexplainable.
If it is the ball, and they checked for like, because they were thinking, could it have
been an industrial accident?
One, his house had no electricity.
There's no electricity in his house.
They go, it's possible that he could have got electrocuted at the mine, that he was goofing
off at the mine, got electrocuted and then walked two miles.
But again, they're thinking, what would he have been doing there?
Maybe he was meeting some people he met on Craigslist.
That's how you construct a lie.
They're like, dude, how'd you get electrocuted?
He's like, I wasn't with two dudes in a hotel room, if that's what you're asking.
He could have gotten electrocuted at the mine and then walked two miles.
But again, they're thinking that type of electrical injury probably would have killed him.
So what was it?
Radiation has a more lingering death.
What is it?
So now that I think about it, why did the melting story get started in the first place?
It almost seems now that I'm talking about it, seems like disinformation.
I mean, it could be the fact that somebody wanted to make the story extra gross and then
that's the version that gets passed on in all these other paranormal communities.
He melted, he melted, he melted.
But when you look back on it, it's probably not true.
It could be that the melting story makes it easier to dismiss.
That's fantastic.
But the idea of someone getting irradiated and then walking and slowly dying, that's
more believable.
So you would start the faker version of the story as disinformation.
When I was reading the story, I had a theory, my personal theory, and some of you guys may
have picked up on this too.
We've covered stories in Brazil specifically before.
It was Operation Plate where the US government may or may not have been using alien or technology
that looked like alien to do experiments on people in Brazil.
Operation Plate and the Brazilian military got involved and the US military stepped in
and all the investigations were ended.
I think that was like episode 80 or something like that.
That's a really interesting episode if you guys want to hear that Operation Plate.
But I thought, secret weapon, I thought someone's testing something out in Brazil.
They saw a guy walking around and they're like, "Light them up."
And all he would see is that bright light coming at him.
That to me is the most reasonable answer.
The ball lightning, you figure it would kill him.
Could be a spirit coming out of the mind because we exist in the world of paranormal.
Whether or not it's real, we definitely entertain those thoughts.
Probably wasn't an industrial accident because there would be no reason for him to cover
that up.
But my scenario, or it could be a UFO again, but the fact that it's in the house, my scenario
was that there were people in the vicinity that wanted to test out one of their new toys
and they saw a guy all by himself in the, really in the middle of nowhere.
No one was around.
His house was there, but there was nothing else within two miles.
And someone, US government or some other government agency or some sort of black book, private
organization, whatever, out in Brazil with a brand new toy, sees a man in the middle
of nowhere, shoots him.
He turns around and he just sees a bright light.
And then the next thing he knows, his upper body is completely burned.
To me, that's the most realistic scenario.
To me, that's the most terrifying scenario.
Because ghosts and goblins coming out of a mine or UFOs that are just passing from our
Earth to the next solar system.
Yeah, I mean, they're scurry in a metaphysical sense, but the idea that humans test weapons
on other humans to me is far scarier and proven time and time again.
So it's possible that this man was the first victim of a death ray that just turned out
to be too unpredictable, didn't kill him on impact.
Couldn't use it in any sort of battle capacity because anyone you shoot with it would still
be able to walk around for two miles, go home and still tell where you were, what you were
hit with.
The thing that killed Mr. Philho maybe sitting in a laboratory somewhere.
Not made on another planet.
Not from the veil beyond our dimension.
Not a rumbling spirit from a deep, dark mine.
But from the mind of a human invented specifically to injure, to kill another human.
An invention that is sitting on a shelf somewhere.
Just waiting for the right opportunity to be used again.
DeadRabbitRadio with gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]