Two men go missing.
And then law enforcement has to ask the ultimate question.
And then we take a look at the story of the billowak monster.
The story itself is half spy intrigue, half sci-fi,
where a creature who's half man and half sheep is all sorts of trouble today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You know what's funny? I would have never watched this if I wasn't doing the show.
I was never a huge fan. I didn't hate them,
but I just never really watched anything by the Logan Paul and Jake Paul, the Paul brothers.
But because of the show, I was like, I should check out that new documentary,
Flat Earth to the Edge and Back by Logan Paul,
where Logan Paul, the trailer he released,
showed him being convinced that the Earth may be flat.
And then they released the trailer and he's like slowly realizing the Earth may be flat.
And a bunch of other YouTubers are like, oh my god, of course, Logan Paul is,
if Logan Paul, if you don't know, is basically Gaston with the YouTube channel.
I mean, that's really the impression that you get when you first see snippets about this guy.
And his brother is pretty much the same.
But they're like, oh my god, of course Logan Paul is so stupid,
he could easily be convinced of the flat Earth.
And that's what the trailer looked like.
The movie is 100% a mockumentary.
The opening scene, a character dies and then comes back to life.
It sets it up right within the first five minutes, I said, oh, this is a comedy.
This is basically a Borat version of conspiracy theory flat Earth stuff.
Because I was like, obviously a guy, his buddy did not die and then come back to life,
or go into a coma and come back to life.
So the first scene set it up, it's a total joke.
And that's exactly what the movie is.
It's a mockumentary.
He really does go to a flat Earth convention and they have an actress who's this super hot Australian chick
and she's a flat Earth or two and they fall in love and like, she's like, let's run away and find the edge of the-
Oh, and his best friend grew up in Antarctica and he found the edge of the world
and his buddy who had flat feet fell off of it.
And it's so, it's just funny.
Like, I actually laughed out loud several times during the movie.
I highly recommend watching it.
Of course the people at the flat Earth convention weren't in on the joke.
He's making fun of them.
By the end, Logan Paul is such a- his character is so stupid that at the end he doesn't believe the world is flat.
He believes the world doesn't exist and that there is no Earth.
And it was really well done.
Definitely, I would check it out.
Like I said, I laughed a couple times.
I've never watched anything from him.
I've seen a couple of rap videos from Jake Paul and I wasn't impressed,
but I was actually very impressed by this.
This guy and his team really went out and made a funny documentary.
Basically, it was this show with a $10 million budget.
It was better than the show.
I mean, you know what I mean?
Like he has a whole crew, but it was the same type of vibe.
It was something I would do if I had access to that kind of money.
I would just troll people constantly who believe in ridiculous stuff, i.e. flat Earth.
So, good job, Logan Paul.
I really enjoyed it and I recommend it highly.
I'm a hard guy to get a laugh out of in a movie.
I'm really...
Yeah, I can't remember the last time I laughed in a movie theater.
Well, I don't go to a movie theater anymore, but I'm not a big fan of comedies in general.
But you want to hear a story that's not funny, which involves a human misery
and mothers crying over their missing kids.
If you want to hear that story, let's go to Florida.
So for our next story, let's go ahead and we're hopping over to Florida.
Literally, because we're dead rabbits, we hop across the country from Logan Paul's house
all the way to Naples, Florida.
And while we're hopping, we actually hop through a time portal and end up in the year 2003.
It's October 2003.
Beautiful sunny day.
Solstice music playing.
I don't know, what do they play in Florida?
Like the big bass...
A Two Live Crew is playing.
They're doing a reunion tour in Naples this year.
In 2003, for whatever reason.
Two Live Crew is back.
It's a They So Horny dot dot dot still tour.
So in this city, you had a young man named Felipe Santos.
Now he was an illegal alien and he was working illegally.
And he's driving through town and he gets in a minor car accident.
Now a minor car accident to most people is like, "Oh, this totally sucks."
But got my insurance stuff.
I got actually hit by two cars at the same time once and neither of them had insurance.
It was the worst thing ever and I was a pizza delivery driver and I wouldn't let him leave the scene.
So I just fed him pizza.
I had all these pizzas in my back seat and they...
Two of the people, they didn't speak a word of English and then the people in the other car was like a mom and a son and neither of them had insurance.
And I was like, "No one leaves until the cops show up."
Took him three hours.
Because at any point, if you get a car accident, even a fender bender and someone says, "I'll just we'll let her hash it out later."
They could just say it never happened.
So I made him stay there and I actually got a fat settlement from my company for that.
Because I totally messed up my shoulder.
So fender benders though, generally.
Getting hit by two cars is a little more than a fender bender.
But fender bender, you're like, "Ah, you know, little scrapes and stuff like that."
But it was a minor car accident.
However, again, you want the cops to come out.
Now, Felipe knew that this was more than just a minor scrape.
Like he is not supposed to be living or working in the United States.
So he's a little nervous.
He's a little nervous.
The other guys bumping some two-life crew to lift his spirits.
He's like, "Yeah, you're right. I am kind of horny."
So the police show up and it is Deputy Steve Calkins, who had been with the force for a while.
He's getting their information.
At that point, he realizes Felipe is illegal.
So he's like, "Listen, man, you know, I'm gonna have to take you to jail."
Felipe's like, "Yeah, I get it, dude. It sucks."
Gets in the back of the cop car.
The cop car drives away.
And the other person involved in the accident is kind of like,
"That's the one that kind of sucked."
Drives away as well.
Now, Felipe's boss finds out that he's been arrested.
And he's like, "Oh, great."
But he wants-- he doesn't want to just have him rot in jail until all this is settled.
He calls up the police station.
This is a boss.
This is a pretty dope boss.
Calls up the police station and says, "I want to pay his bail.
Let's get him out of there.
He can come back.
We'll figure all this stuff out."
'Cause at that point, the boss is like, "Yeah, he's probably getting deported.
But, you know, I just don't want him to sit in jail for 90 days."
He's a good guy.
He's a nice guy.
So he calls up the police department and says, "I want to bail him out."
And the-- well, he called him to jail, actually.
But the jail goes, "No, we don't know who you're talking about."
This guy was never booked in here.
And he's like, "I know he was arrested."
And they're like, "He might have been arrested, but he was never booked in our jail."
At that point, day or two later, Felipe just never shows back up to work.
So people are starting to get suspicious.
They're like, "Where is Felipe?"
He would never miss this Two Live Crew concert.
But the Two Live Crew concert came and went.
And no Felipe.
I actually don't know if Felipe was a fan of Two Live Crew.
I'm just trying to lighten the story as much as I can.
Felipe never shows back up.
And they keep pressing on the police.
And the police go to Deputy Steve Colkins, because they know he was there.
And they're like, "He's a good officer."
They say, "What happened?
Like, why do you know where he could be?"
Because you were the last person I was kind of seeing with him.
The deputy says, "Okay, here's what happened.
There's a car accident.
I realized he was illegal.
I put him in my car."
But as I was driving him to jail, he actually was super polite.
And just kind of a really nice guy.
And I said, "You know what?
I'm not a DEA officer.
I don't really care if you're illegal or not.
I was just kind of following protocol.
I'll just drop you off somewhere where you want to get dropped off."
And he goes, "Circle K.
Drop me off at a Circle K.
I'm going to get one of their disgusting, generic slushies,
and some four-day-old donuts."
And Deputy goes, "Yeah, that's Circle K. All right.
Let me drop you off over there."
The police are like, "Whoa, you should have filed a report."
And he's like, "Yeah, but I just...
I don't want to arrest them."
So what would the report say?
I let an illegal immigrant go.
And they're like, "Yeah, I guess so."
So they tell the boss that.
They're like, "Listen, this is what happened."
He picked them up, dropped them off at Circle K.
Because he was really polite.
And the boss is like, "Yeah, he's a really nice guy.
That's why I wanted a bail amount and stuff like that."
So that sucks.
I wonder what happened to him.
Cops go, "Well, we'll keep looking.
I have for him."
But again, he's an illegal immigrant.
He may just be scared and on the run.
He could be anywhere.
So that was that, right?
Deputy Steve Calkins being wooed,
being charmed by this man,
dropped him off at a Circle K,
and then something bad befell him.
But three months later,
it's January 2004,
and a black man named Terrence Williams
goes missing.
No one can find him.
His mom starts pestering the police.
Rightfully so.
She's not being like a nag.
Her son's missing.
She wants to know where her son is.
She goes to the police.
She's like, "Where's my son?"
And they're like, "Listen, your son is an adult.
He had an expired license.
He could be anywhere.
He could be out partying.
He could have a big hangover somewhere.
Like, give us a couple days.
He'll probably turn up."
But he doesn't.
So the mom keeps looking for him,
and eventually she gets her family involved,
and her aunt tracks down his Cadillac he was driving.
The last night he was seen,
it's in an in-pound lot,
and on the paperwork that ordered the towing
for the car, Deputy Steve Calkins.
So the mom starts pressing the police,
and goes, "Who's this Deputy Steve Calkins?
He must know what happened to my son."
So the cops go, "That's weird.
I mean, like, yeah, we have this towing paperwork,
but we don't know anything about Deputy Steve Calkins
pulling over your son."
And so they go to the deputy, and they go,
"What happened?"
He goes, "Okay, here's what's happened."
I was driving down the road,
and I saw this Cadillac,
and this was a while back,
because it had taken this long for them
to get to this point in the investigation.
But he says, "I was driving down the road,
and I saw this Cadillac in front of me.
And he was driving one night,
and it was driving a little, like, in distress.
Like, I figured that the driver was drunk.
I pulled him over.
There's a dude in the car named Terrence Williams.
And they're like, "How'd you know his name?"
He's like, "Well, I got his name.
I asked him for it.
I'm not a psychic, but the guy in the car told me
his name was Terrence Williams.
And he was begging me to let him go.
Like, he had to get to--
He was late one more time for work.
He was gonna get fired.
And he just seemed really nice and polite.
And so I said, "Tell you what, I'll give you a right to work,
and then I'll come back and I'll process your car.
And if anything's wrong with it, I may come back
and arrest you, or you may get a ticket or something like that."
And Terrence Williams was like, "Thank you, thank you, thank you.
You're the nicest officer in the world,
and you're so buff and handsome.
You're so strong."
And Stephen Calkins was like, "Ooh."
They flattered, and the investigators he's talking to
are like, "Uh, this story sounds made up."
But anyways, Terrence Williams gets in the back of the car,
and Stephen Calkins is telling the cops this story.
Now, I'm not about the handsome part,
but Stephen Calkins is telling the people this story.
They had other cops' story, and he says,
"So I asked Terrence Williams where he worked,
and he goes, 'Well, I work at Circle K.'"
The cops are like, "What?"
So he takes Terrence Williams to Circle K, drops him off,
comes back to process the car, paperworks bad,
license plates are expired.
At that point, he calls up the work and says,
"I want to speak to your employee, Terrence Williams."
And they say, "He never worked here."
Dun, dun, dun.
Stephen Calkins makes those piano noises,
and the investigators are like,
"What? Are you insane?"
And Stephen Calkins was like, "No, no, that's exactly what happened."
Now, at this point, the cops are super suspicious
of one of their own,
because they have two people
who went completely missing under similar circumstances,
and both dropped off at a Circle K.
Now, again, it could just be a coincidence.
But at this point, the cops are now suspicious of this guy.
They had Felipe disappear, and they had Terrence disappear,
and they really start digging into this guy.
They go, he got, Terrence Williams got pulled over near a cemetery.
The cemetery workers say, "That's not what happened."
We saw Terrence Williams getting back to the cop car,
and we saw the cop car drive off.
Then we saw the cop car come back an hour later,
move his car to illegal parking area
so a tow truck could pick it up.
And Calkins goes, "Oh, yeah, no, I did that,
so it would be easier for the tow truck."
And then the guy at the car accident for the Felipe Santos thing
said, "Yeah, Felipe was really polite,
but Stephen Calkins was kind of a jerk to him,
and was saying, "I hate when you people are here illegally
and taking our jobs," and stuff like that.
So the cops are like, "Okay, the story,
maybe he is a secretly racist guy,
but the story could still make sense,
and maybe he did move the car,
but maybe it was to make the tow truck."
They don't have enough, so they say,
"Hey, we want to investigate you,
we want you to come in and really talk about what's going on."
So even Calkins completely shut up, wouldn't talk,
and because he was interfering with an investigation,
they fired him.
And to this day, no one knows what happened to those people.
Disappeared from the face of the earth.
No bodies, no evidence, nothing.
They're gone.
Obviously, when law enforcement commits a crime,
it's more gruesome,
because they're the ones, it goes out saying,
they're the ones that society says you should protect us.
But what's bizarre is I'm wondering,
these two got connected,
and it was because the families were kind of able to track it back to him.
I wonder how many people else that got pulled over by this guy
who just went missing, who didn't have families to report it.
People who were out of town, who didn't know how to track this down.
Is he connected to other things?
He's actually, for the first time in 2018,
started in 2018, he's facing a wrongful death suit
from the family of Terrence Williams.
They're suing him over their son going missing,
which has a lower threshold of evidence.
And he, of course, and here's the thing,
this is what made me think he's more suspicious,
even more suspicious.
He's representing himself,
which either means he's totally broke and can't afford a lawyer,
or he's one of those guys who thinks he's smarter than he actually is.
He's one of those guys who thinks he's the smartest man in the world,
and he can fool everyone,
i.e. someone who thinks they can defend themselves in court.
Civil court actions are not dramatic, really, at all,
unless it's the people's court.
But I'm very curious to see how this is going to pull off
a possible serial killer,
representing himself in court to avoid getting sued
from the family of one of his alleged victims.
Weird.
And again, these two stories,
they just had the people were able to track it back to Deputy Culkins.
You gotta wonder how many other people went missing in Naples, Florida.
Last thing they saw was some red and blue lights behind him,
and a smiling officer with a flashlight,
telling them to get into the back of his car.
I guess he wouldn't be smiling then, but you know what I mean?
Like, what are you gonna do?
Cup tells you to get in the back of the car, you're just gonna be like, fine.
And then once you're in the back of the car, man, all bets are off.
You're lucky if you end up in jail.
But enough of Naples, enough of Florida,
we're gonna say goodbye to sunny, sunny Florida.
Next year, though, is the 25th anniversary of Two Life Crew.
I don't know if that's true.
They're probably like the 40th anniversary of Two Life Crew,
but they're the only band from Florida I know,
other than Florida, Georgia Line.
But we are now going, we're coming back to California.
We should have done this one after the Logan Paul story,
but we're back in California.
We're actually going to a place called Ohai County.
Now Ohai County actually has a lot of ghost stories and monster stories
and stuff like that down there.
It's kind of weird how many they have.
Ohai County has a lot of monsters already, a lot of monsters.
Not like if you go there to tourist boards like,
"Watch out for the sea monster."
But I mean, it has a lot of like legends of monsters, I should say.
But like all legends, they have to start somewhere.
And that is why we're going back to the 1960s.
I had to look over at my notes.
We're going back to the 1960s.
Do-wop-ba-ra-bop-ba-do-wop-ba-ra-bop-ba-do-wop-ba-bop-ba-bop.
The people are, wait, no, that was the 50s.
Okay, anyways, we're back not around us.
We're farther back in time.
So 60s music would be like, "Never mind, never mind.
I'm going to stop doing the music thing."
I just imagined like a 1950s movie. It's 1964.
There are these teenagers walking through the wooded areas of Ohai County.
They've always been told to stay away.
You kids, you stay away from billowak dairy.
Don't go there.
They're like, "Why is the milk tainted?"
And the old man's like, "No, it's just don't go there."
But you know, teenagers will be teenagers.
It's do-wop music and malt shops in 1964 are all the rage.
Kids with switch blades and leather jackets was a crazy time in 1964.
Anyways, these teenagers go off into the woods because they want to explore this abandoned dairy.
So it's late at night because that's the only time to really explore abandoned dairies.
They got their flashlights.
"Ooh, Charles, I'm so cold."
Yeah, here, where are my Lutterman's jacket?
So anyways, they're walking through and these teenagers are kind of shining their flashlights around.
And billowak dairy, even in ruins, is quite impressive.
It was basically a two-story building and the walls have all crumbled away.
And you can actually look and you can see where all the decay has taken place.
You can just walk in through any entrance.
Quite spooky to see an abandoned building that's actually dissolving before your eyes.
But as they're walking around billowak dairy, they hear something.
They're actually walking through the woods.
Like, what is that? It sounds huge, whatever it is. It sounds super big.
And they're like, "Yeah, you need to go do your SATs again."
But anyways, the kids start, keep moving and they hear their "kshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhshhsh
But anyways, the kids start, keep moving and they hear their "chhh" and something's moving through the woods. And again, it's not like little ghost girl footsteps behind them. Something big is coming.
And so the kids turn and they look and they see it.
That wasn't a baby. It wasn't a weird baby jet airplane.
That was a creature, a giant humanoid.
That's a better noise. With the head of a ram, some later will say the head of a sheep, but we'll get into that.
The head of a ram, huge massive curly horns looking at them.
Big old muscular ape body, totally just like yoked out.
Covered in matted gray hair.
SHINK! Large claws. The kids book it.
I think, you imagine they're like looking at the creature from top to bottom. I would just see the horns eight feet in the air and I'd be out of there.
But anyways, they take off and this creature begins chasing them through the forest.
And those are the kids making that noise, not the monster.
The kids jump onto the car and the creature actually picked up a boulder and threw it at them and missed them.
And the kids are like, "Start the car, start the car." I can, I can.
The creature shows up and starts beating up the car.
And just in the nick of time, the car drives away.
Now they drive into town and they're like, "Townspeople, look, 1950s town people who happened to live in 1964, look at our car."
And it was all beat up.
"What happened? What in tarnation happened to you kids?"
A big monster started punching our car.
Townspeople go, "You were at Billywack Dairy, weren't you?"
Kids are like, "Yeah, we went there to go check out the building."
And they're like, "I guess the building checked you out."
The kids are like, "That doesn't even make sense."
But see, here's the thing.
The story of the Billywack monster had long preceded these kids going out in the middle of the woods.
Back in the 1950s, so that's why I got my confusion, back in the 1950s,
a little boy ran home with huge scratches across his back.
Gums and crying, "Mommy, mommy, something scratched my back up."
Now of course the mom thinks maybe he's running through branches or maybe he fell off a cliff or something.
The mom didn't care about him very much.
She's too busy smoking cigarettes.
But he said a monster attacked them.
And that was one of the first sightings of the Billywack monster.
And over the years people had seen it off and on,
but it was people would go out to the woods to just kind of check out the creepiness of the building.
Now the urban legend had been there, but it wasn't super concrete.
But after the teenagers are like, "No, no, we got attacked by this thing,"
newspapers started running articles on this.
Now, newspapers will run articles on anything,
but it definitely doesn't mean that it's true, but it gave the rumor more legs.
The LA Times runs the article saying that these teenagers got attacked by this giant monster.
The police ended up getting called out multiple times to the forest, not to fight the monster,
but to stop kids from fighting the monster.
At one point these cops pulled over a child carrying a sword into the woods,
saying he was going to go fight the monster.
You're like, "Who is this kid? Connor McLeod?
Like, at what point do you think you're going to be able to sword a dude who's eight feet tall?"
Well, I guess that's what mythological heroes did.
But anyway, so this kid thought he apparently was Hercules or Pericles,
or any of the Cleese back then.
At one point a woman called the police.
I don't know what the cops were expecting to find when they got there.
A woman called the police and says, "I got a group of kids."
There's about 43 of them.
The cops are like, "What?"
She's like, "Let me finish. I got a group of kids.
There's like 43 kids in my front yard.
They're trying to go to the dairy.
They're just going to get injured."
The cops are like, "Okay, yeah, we'll be there in a second.
We'll help you."
And then she goes, "Don't worry, I got them under control.
I have a shotgun pointed at them."
This woman had kept 43 kids at bay with a shotgun,
so they want to go into the woods.
That's a weird call.
The cops show up, and of course it's the 1960s/50s.
They show up and they give the kids out,
and they give the mom like a medal.
They're like, "Hey, thanks for keeping the kids from going into the woods."
They don't aim shotguns at them, but you know.
So where did this legend come from?
That's the first thing we got to look at before we go into
whether or not the billowak monster is real.
The billowak dairy is real,
and that story is intriguing as well.
In 1924, billowak dairy was set up,
and it was a state-of-the-art dairy facility.
It was a two-story building.
It had some of the most technologically advanced milk technology in the world.
It had...
How technically advanced can a dairy get would be my question.
Like, they have like, "Lookit, we have titanium vats.
You just keep yours in wood."
Like, I mean, but I'm not a dairy technician.
It was the most advanced of its time.
It was founded by a guy named August Rubel.
Now, he was originally from Sweden,
and he had worked with the American Field Service in World War I.
So there were already people who were like, "Well, that's weird.
Why is this guy from Sweden working with the American Field Service?
A military veteran, but he was working with kind of like an operative group?"
Now he's in California, and he has this state-of-the-art dairy,
a million-million-dollar dairy set up.
Kind of weird.
The rumor started that he didn't just work with the American Field Service.
He worked with the OSS, which was actually the precursor to the CIA.
So now people are really intrigued about this foreigner in their area.
How did he get the money to build this giant dairy?
But everything seemed to be on the up and up.
Dairy was incredibly successful, brought in tons of money,
but at a certain point August said, "You know what?
I'm gonna leave the dairy behind.
My heart calls for me to go back into the field service,"
and he apparently joined up with the American Field Service again.
And the last we know is he blew up in a mine attack in Africa.
They weren't attacking him with mines.
He drove over one.
I mean, that's how mines work, but he blew up.
And over the years, eventually, the dairy went out of business
and fell into a state of decay.
That is when the dairy was discovered to have,
in real life, apparently, I've never been there,
but underneath the dairy was a whole other floor.
Now, I actually have a friend who grew up on a dairy farm.
I was running to my friends today, Paul and Robin, and I said,
when he mentioned he was a dairy technician,
I go, "You know, I'm actually working on a story right now."
Now, I don't know.
Is it normal for dairies to have a floor underground?
Because I don't know.
Maybe that's where the milk gets pasteurized.
Maybe that's where the baby cows hang out before it's time to get milk.
I don't know.
He's like, "What?"
And I go, "Is it-- do dairies normally have
like a secret underground fortress underneath them?"
And he's like, "I've never heard of that."
Now, it doesn't mean that this underground facility,
this secret underground facility that was only accessible
if you poured the right colored milk into the right vials.
Like, you have to put a little strawberry, a little chocolate.
No, it wasn't that secret, but it had a whole floor underground.
Is that normal for a dairy farm?
And he said, "No, that's not."
And so that started the idea that maybe he was running a secret
experiments in this underground lab underneath the dairy.
Because it'd be the perfect cover.
You'd have stuff coming in and out.
You'd have livestock coming in, not leaving, really,
but you'd have livestock showing up.
You'd have big cargo container things full of milk coming in and out.
I think you can understand at my level of the economics
and production of milk is pretty weak.
But you'd have constant traffic there.
You'd have the perfect cover.
You'd have something come in, put it in the lab.
You'd never know about it.
Now, again, he may have found a reason to keep a floor underground
for whatever reason.
So that didn't necessarily make me suspicious.
But what does make me suspicious was that people for years after
the billowak dairy going out of business, which was around the 40s,
people said that they could find checks payable to August,
just floating all over the place.
People said that you could go through the dairy,
because as it was crumbling away, you would look into walls
and see checks for his business made out to him stuffed in walls.
You would just be walking through the forest and find checks made out to him
from distributors and suppliers and stuff like that that were uncashed.
If you had a successful multimillion dollar, or maybe not multimillion dollar,
but if you had a very, very successful dairy,
why wouldn't you cash those checks unless you were getting more money
from somewhere else?
And that was all just the cover operation.
When's the last time that you've gotten checks and never cashed them?
Especially if they're checks for your business,
that your for-profit business that you're running,
you're just stuffing them in walls.
Then as you're building decays, they just fly everywhere.
So was there some secret experiment going on underneath billowak dairy?
I think the answer to that is it's very possible that there were things going on in that dairy
that it was a cover business, because when he left,
the dairy stopped really operating, or it started to decline very rapidly.
Like he sold it off to someone else and it lasted for another 30, 40 years and stuff like that.
State of the art dairy, he leaves.
I think someone took it over shortly, but then it just falls into disrepair.
Other than like, even when a restaurant goes out of business, another restaurant moves in.
You're telling me this dairy, they just abandoned.
But if the purpose wasn't to have, if the real purpose wasn't for it to be a dairy,
but for it to be a cover, once you didn't need the cover anymore, you leave.
So I think it's very possible that the billowak dairy was a cover for something.
The question is, is does the billowak monster exist, and did it come from that dairy?
Now that's obviously a more difficult question.
There has been no photographs of the billowak monster.
There have been no, like, real evidence of the billowak monster, other than what people have seen.
Other than a couple dents in a car, claw marks, which you know what I mean?
There's been no plaster casts of footprints that I was able to find, or, oh, look it, here's where one of his horns molted off.
He must have grown a new one. There's nothing like that.
Does the billowak monster exist?
I mean, again, I really, the answer to that is, do you believe in monsters or not?
There's been no proof that it exists.
There's been sightings of it, and people say they've been attacked by it, and things like that.
But there's urban legends all over the place.
Does the creature exist?
What I find interesting about the billowak monster is that it has an origin story,
rather than Bigfoot who just kind of pops up, or the fey, or goblins, or whatever like that.
Like, this creature is really a product of its time.
The first sightings were in the 1950s out of the sci-fi movie, so it has a sci-fi origin.
It has a location that it came from, a real life secret building underground, an existing building,
that was run by a guy who was rumored to work for the CIA, which sent, or the OSS, which sounds a bit of a retcon.
But it's a cryptid that has, it's a modern day cryptid.
A lot of times you look at these cryptids, and, you know, Bloody Mary started off like in the 1800s,
and then it became more personified in the 1950s.
Bigfoot has been around for the longest time.
Obviously, fairies and giants and stuff like that are cryptids of old.
But it's interesting to look at this one, because going forward, when we...
The world's not even close to being over.
We're going to be around for thousands and thousands of years after that.
And so going forward, the cryptids that are great, great, great ancestors are afraid of,
are going to have these weird sci-fi twists.
They're not just going to be, "Oh no, Bigfoot's been around forever, and he's walking around the world."
This one was built in a lab, an affront to God, a genetically engineered creature,
just like you would see in a matinee for $2.
That's where these cryptids come from.
And it'll be interesting because I think going forward as a society, we'll see more and more of these.
We don't get a lot of new cryptids.
So whenever we find one that's relatively new and interesting,
I think it's cool because we can see how these stories evolve.
Bigfoot evolved because Westerners were coming into uncharted wildernesses,
and they were seeing something, and they created a legend of Bigfoot.
What type of cryptids are we going to have in the future?
Holographic cryptids?
It's funny because if you think about it, AI, the story of these super advanced computer systems taken over the world,
is basically a cryptid.
It's basically a monster of our own making, but it's not hiding in the dark shadows of our bedroom,
it's hiding in our computer or in our internet.
These mythical monsters really say a lot about where we're at as a society.
It's not always about the long claws or the horns on the head or the giant body.
Sometimes it's about what those things say to us.
A man turned into a beast, or a beast turned into a man in a sci-fi setting right outside your neighborhood.
I think no matter how far society evolves or where we end up going,
someday, a thousand years from now, kids on some generation starship flying far past Alpha Centauri
are going to be saying, "Don't go down into engineering. Don't go down there after 3 a.m."
Why not?
Because that's where the goreboard lives, and he'll get you.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[Music]