Is the nephew of a serial killer putting billboards up across America?
Sounds fairly mundane, but trust me it gets weird. And then
Alien week continues.
But this time no sexy cryptids
No presidential talk on UFOs. No
Today we have a horrifying story of the abduction of one boy and
What he witnessed inside of an alien spacecraft today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Kerviner. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day, too. You know I wanted to start off today's episode with this quick little tidbit
Couple episodes back I did an episode on Johnny Sands. He was a country musician singer who was had that
I keep want to say he was abducted by aliens
He had a nice chat with them nothing bad happened and after he met the aliens the men in black
This is his story. I'm not saying any of this is factual
But the men in black asked him to write a song about it and then when I and he did he wrote a song about it
And then when I went to go look for the song
He said it was on myspace.com/johnnystands music. There's no music listed there at all
So and I just kind of said maybe the song is in some sort of government warehouse. I couldn't find it
But marker 646 did marker 646 on YouTube said hey, man
It's this is this song that you thought that no human outside
He didn't actually say all that stuff
But the implication was that this song was locked up in some government warehouse and he's like a dude
I found it on YouTube man
Found it on YouTube 46 views when he sent it to me. Thank you marker for sending that over
So yeah, go and check the song out. I'll tell you this man. It's really good
It actually thumps like you could play it in your pickup truck is your muddin
You can play it in your Honda is you're just driving on the street
It's from the album Trump that and it's it just came out in 2017
So the songs only he wrote it back when this happened when the men in black told him to write this song
But it's a really good song even if you're not in the country music. You really like just thumps. It's a good song
So check it out. I'll have the YouTube link below. Thanks marker for pulling that up
And let's get this guy some views. Let's get Johnny Sanson views because it really is a pretty cool song. How many
Songs have been written about alien encounters and men in black and stuff like well
I guess the song minimum the men in black theme songs, but for the most part, they're fairly rare
They're fairly rare. So check it out. Okay, but let's go ahead and get started with the episode now
Yesterday's episode was our hitchhiker one was our haunted hitchhiker episode and in it while we were talking about driving down
Highway 101 I mentioned Bob's boards now when I was doing research to verify because I have to triple check everything
Backpacker verse says when I was doing research to verify all that stuff
It typed in like highway 101 haunted and this thing popped up this thing popped up
So let's all hop in the Jason Jalopy. We're gonna drive them down highway 1-0
I guess we could have just walked there because basically we ended up that last episode there
But we're there however we get there. We are at highway 101
We're standing in front of a giant billboard on the side of the road the billboard says are you scared?
You should be
Technically is it the height they should be the billboard reads right?
But anyways it reads are you scared?
You should be dot dot dot and then on the right hand side of the billboard our right hand
It's left hand this is getting way too complicated. But anyways, there's a picture of like a creepy-looking dude
Like it looks like a photograph turned into clip art type of thing of a creepy-looking dude on the other side
There's a pair of eyes poking out bottom. It says bobs boards calm now this billboard went up in
2018 and people are complaining about it because it's really creepy and you just drive by it and it's a picture of this creepy guy
And it says are you scared you should be and so people have been complaining about this billboard the billboard companies like listen man
We take money we put up billboards as long as it's not I do
He's the most I just imagine the guy around the company is the most like cigar chomping business suit wearing
Dude ever cuz he's like your kids crying tough look lady
You got more money to pay for a better billboard. I'll take it down
But other than that because people are complaining their kids are crying. This is a creepy-looking billboard
So what is Bob's boards and and ever there's been a couple articles on this billboard and they all go to
Bob's boards calm and they interview the great nephew, so
Bob's boards calm is a kind of a enigma. I I'll tell you what I think it is in a second
But anyways, this is the way that it's set up. It's an average time
It's a website that sells spirit boards we gee boards we gee board is a trademark name
I believe so they have to use the name spirit board, but it's a spirit board that is supposedly
Made by a serial killer. This is the legend behind this thing. There was this guy who stalked lover lanes across the country
So he was killing couples. That was his that was his MO
that's what he enjoyed doing and
He killed a bunch of them and he never got caught
But as he got older he wanted to find forgiveness in his actions. He wanted to I guess I don't have to explain that anymore
He just wanted to be forgiven
So he built he created his own spirit board and use that to contact the victims of people he killed
Now that in and of itself is quite chilling if you can imagine a serial killer
Killing people and then believing he has the ability to contact them from beyond the dead and maybe even torment them even longer like
Be like hey look at this cool video game
You're missing breath of the wild two is coming out and you don't get to see it because I killed you ha ha
Ghosts is like no
But anyways, I guess he would probably also be my friends and family and miss him so much
Anyway, so the serial killer this guy's unnamed serial killer created this spirit board not to talk people with upcoming video game releases
but to ask for their forgiveness and he did contact his victims and they
Like the myth I'm not saying any of this is true, but apparently according in this website
They drove him to the brink of insanity or most likely over the brink into insanity and he's just kind of diss I believe the great
Uncle is dead now
Because a lot of his murders apparently took place a long time ago. So what this story is is that his great nephew?
This serial killer's great nephew found the spirit board found this specially designed spirit board and he is selling it
for the low low price of
$9.95 plus 950 shipping and handling although there is a if you buy more than one board
You only have to pay the one shipping and handling so that's kind of cool
Now the board itself looks like a serial killer designed
It's the standard wheezy board layout, but all of the letters are like the cut out magazine letters on there
You know like that little design each letter looks different a different color and all that stuff and the creepy
Face is in the middle of it
So the last thing I want a wishy-bore to be is even more creepy than it already is
For regardless of whether or not the backstory is true the design of it is quite disturbing and the great nephew said
So this is what I think this is first I thought it was a marketing gimmick
But now I'm starting to think it might be an ARG very expensive ARG
Because there's a challenge according to this board and there's not a lot of information on the website itself
I think it's maybe like four or five pages, but this is the challenge that's listed on the website
We will put in this. Hey, one of you guys might be able to do this. You can smart cookies
We will pay
$50,000 to anyone who decipher the elaborate series of codes ciphers and arcane images that populate Bob's board
Spirit board Bob's great nephew believes that the symbols and codes are clues to where Bob
perpetrated his crimes and if deciphered may solve the decades-long mystery of Bob's board
Was Bob a serial killer as he himself alleged or was he simply insane?
So there may be other stuff on the board that I can't see because I'm just looking at a photograph of it
So there may be like little symbols in there
So you can send in your fan theories and they'll post videos on his website and this one woman who's connecting
Bob to the Texarkana murders the very theme famous string of murders in Texas where a guy was walking around and shooting people at Lovers Lanes
But I'm thinking okay
It's an ARG and this guy's trying to sell these boards and but I don't know how many ARGs you can win like
$50,000 cash the kid the nephew himself
I didn't see his name, but I could have just not I could have just glanced over that
I tried looking for who's actually behind this there is a company that runs that is actually producing the boards and they have a
Disclaimer and they say listen we don't agree with the board. We don't think you guys should use these boards
Spirit boards can be evil and our lawyers are telling us to say that
None of this stuff is real and all people that it's connected to you know fictional or otherwise
You know the typical disclaimer when you have a fictional movie they're like if this matches up anyone living or dead
We're not responsible. It's all coincidence stuff like that
So they're saying that we have to put this disclaimer on here
Which could again be part of the because it is all made up. We don't know we don't know if this is a hundred percent made up
We don't know if there's a little bit of fact. We don't know if it's true
But since the board company can't verify that it's true. They have to put that disclaimer in there. Who knows?
This is a relatively new conspiracy the billboard went up in 2018
The trademark for the name Bob's boards was granted in 2017 and you think okay ARG
So it's just goofing around what's odd is the board itself has two copyrights
one for 2017 and
one for 1982
So if it's an ARG either they fake that first copyright, which is possible
They just you know wrote that down and said copyright 1982
But I would think if they were making it up
They probably would have made it earlier in the timeline because 80s isn't as creepy as the 70s and apparently this guy
That's just a known thing 80s is nowhere near as creepy as the 70s
But it could be that it actually was copyrighted by somebody this board design was copyrighted by someone in
1982 and then it sat in someone's shelf all this time and then someone said I'll come up with a cool marketing gimmick
Who knows who knows but
$50,000 is a lot of money. I mean you do have to pay $30. They do say no
Purchase necessary so I guess if one of you guys bought the board
You guys can post photos of it online and then everyone could help decipher it as well. I don't know
I'm not endorsing this this
Possible
Marketing scheme. I just think it's an interesting story the idea of a serial killer designing his own spirit board to contact his dead is
Something that you could see in a book or a movie or something like that
So if there's even a whiff of it being true, which probably isn't but if there's even a whiff of it being true in the real world
It's always something intriguing to look at but again, you know me. I don't mess with spirit boards
I don't mess with none of that stuff. So go nuts guys. Just do not let me put my legal disclaimer on here
If you get possessed, it's not my fault. It's totally your fault. Okay there. That's from your buddy Jason
Don't get possessed. But if you do don't blame me
Okay, let's go ahead and get moving on to our next story now alien week continues
We've left Bob's boards behind the billboard still stands little kids are still crying
But we are on our way to the caucus cock cock
Cockass mountains, you know, they're in
Soviet Union or when I was a kid it was a Soviet Union
Apparently this I don't know what it is. I don't know where they're at now. I think they're in Russia. Maybe use Becca State
Anyways, it doesn't matter mountain range the caucus mountains. I'm probably not pronounced that right either
now we've started getting a lot of
UFO stories coming out of Russia over the past couple years a ton of them all
with varying I don't know how many of them are true is what I'm trying to say
because
They're very poorly sourced first off people didn't want to really want to talk about that stuff because then the the
KGB would give you a phone call be like hey you saw an experimental vehicle flying around
Why don't you come come to our headquarters? Let's talk about it. You're like no
I don't know so a lot of people weren't talking about UFOs over there
Because you do get disappeared if there's too many clouds in the sky. It was not a fun the Soviet Union
I don't understand how people still look back on that place with rose colored glasses
But it was not a fun place to be
Different in you don't want to be different in the Soviet Union
So if you were a lowly farmer and you saw like a cigar-shaped vehicle land and a bunch of aliens get out and start taking
Readings and eating potatoes like you're like no, there's my potatoes
That's where my vodka comes from and then they get on the ship and fly away. You're not gonna tell anybody
You just you're be like I had nothing happened
There's like radiation scorch marks everywhere and the farmer has like horrible radiation burns on his face from the exhausts of the spaceship
People are like how'd you get that? He's like I walked in with doorknob, you know radioactive doorknob. Don't ask questions
It's soviet union so
There's one of the stories that came out this story is quite interesting. I really really like it
It actually has one of the things that I enjoy about alien abduction stories, which is quite chilling the year is
1948 apparently this was written as a letter to a Russian you and UFO investigator in
2001 there's a young boy whose name is only listed as VZ. We're gonna call him Victor
We're gonna call him Victor because it's easier. So there's this young boy
That's he doesn't really give us an age either. So again a lot of suspicious details, but I really like this story
So we're gonna roll with it in let's say he's 12. I think that works
He's a young boy and him his sister and her friend
go out for a picnic in the caucus mountains and
They decide to go sunbathing oddly enough that's in quotes in the article
I'm thinking is that they insinuating something else? So I don't know but Victor whatever leaves the two girls to do what they're gonna do and
Decides to go on to the other side of this hill where there's some shade and just chill pick a little piece of wheat
Put it in his mouth like Tom Sawyer
Eat it cuz he's so hungry cuz he lives in the Soviet Union and they have no food
But after getting a full stomach after that one little stalk of wheat he takes a nap
He just kind of passes it's like oh, I haven't eaten that much in days
Fall asleep the next thing he knows he hears up
When it's not a bunch of M&Ms coming at him it's not some monks
It's he looks up and he's
Don't know why thought M&Ms would make that noise because all the m's right
He looks up and he sees what he describes as an upside-down plate
Floating in the sky now that's funny because that's the most basic observation if you would never seen a UFO before
Ever and you never saw a movie of one and you saw UFO you would describe it as an upside-down plate
That's the classic version. I mean flying saucers. That's where they get the name from they look like plates flying around
But you didn't know that that's where that term comes from. I didn't know that well
I knew that you know 20 years ago, but when I found that out. I was like really that's where they come
Anyways, so flying saucers because they look like saucer dishes upside down
So it makes sense this kid it goes I looked up and I saw what appeared to be an upside-down flying plate and it lands a little
Little landing pads come out door comes down and three aliens come out
It's interesting because he goes into a lot of descriptors here, but the one thing he's mostly
Vagon is what the aliens look like which is usually the opposite a lot of times people give very detailed idea of what the aliens look like
But they don't really tell us anything that happens in the ship
They just pass out when they go in the ship and that's one of the reasons why I like this story
It's we hear a lot about in the ship. There's quite the adventure coming up. He sees these three aliens
He describes them as tall humanoids three humanoids get off the ship and one of them takes him by the hand and he said
I didn't really even
Understand what was going on. I just knew like I should follow them like I wasn't super scared at this point
They just grab my hand to the next thing and he was walking on the ship and I wasn't even question was going on
he gets on to this UFO he gets on to this alien spacecraft they're taking him down a hallway and
He see he enters over this is when you know things are gonna go south for you
You're already a little iffy, but you're not super scared of these spaceship landed and these people walked up to you
And just put their hand out and you grabbed it, but then they lead you in a room full of cages
You know when I read that I was like that's a little low-tech for a UFO
Like you have a UFO that can defy gravity while airplanes can fly gravity and they have cages in them
But I mean, you know, I mean like it's a spacecraft from traveling from wherever other dimensions or across the stars or whatever
And they just have metal barred cages that seemed a little weird
But maybe it's the most efficient for keeping earthlings this little victor is led into this spaceship now
I want you to imagine you have to pick one of these cages to go into it's almost like there's three cages in a mystery box and
You may put yourself in the mind of a kid who's walking on to this spaceship and these are the cages. He sees in order
first cage he sees
contains a
Quote angry bear so not just any bear a bear that is out of its mind
Trying to get at somebody or something it just wants it which I found super intriguing the fact that aliens are abducting bears that part
I was like this story already has a bunch of stuff that I love
Aliens are abducting other animals and then they just put them in a cage in their UFO
Full of other abductees so imagine
Okay, you I keep saying imagine this stuff because the whole scenario is weird
He walks into this room at the first cage he sees contains an angry bear not sleepy not eating honey
Angry big angry bear from Russia the angriest of all bears come from Russia the next cage over has three men
Praying just praying the whole time and then you're like well Jason
I'd much rather be with the praying men than grizzly bear, but
You probably just try to convert you like I listen man
I'm Christian, but I don't want to be trapped in a cell with three other Christians
Especially when there's a bear next to me because they're just gonna be praying the whole time like let's figure out a way to escape
Quit praying they're praying for the gate to be open. It's not gonna work anyway
So you have the angry bear you have the three praying men
Next to them you have a woman what what Jason you have a why didn't you go to that one first if you said I had a choice
I want to be in the cage with a woman except you didn't let me finish
Victor describes this woman as screaming hysterically
The whole the rest of this time throughout this adventure. She is screaming at the top of her lungs
She is gone mad by her being trapped in this situation. She's completely lost it
So you walk in you see the angry bear trying to like push open the door
You see the three praying men who aren't really trying to escape at all
You see a woman just screaming at the top of her lungs
louder than the bear and
Then the last cage has a man in it
You're like, oh
Man, let's talk on a mystery box because that guy he's calm
That's the scary thing and in spite of all of this that's going on
There's a bear trying to take a swipe at the three praying people and the three praying people aren't praying to be released
They're praying that the woman would just shut up and then the woman's just would blow your drums out
You have this man who's calm throughout all of it when the aliens take Victor and they put him in the cage with the man and
the man says be quiet and stay calm and
Victor's basically frozen at this point. He doesn't know what to do. He's locked in this cage
He feels the UFO lift off and he's like I my sis. I'll never see my sister again. I'll never see my family again
I have no idea what's going on and after a short while the UFOs flying around the aliens are kind of talking to each other and
Then they press a button and a table comes out of a wall like slides out like
And they walk over to the cage with the three praying men and they get one now
It doesn't say if he resists or not and I'm wondering if they have some sort of ability to like make you comply
but
It's probably a combination of both they probably just actually just through being their captors
They have you know and created a sense that they can do whatever they want and the guy didn't seem to resist
There was no note that he resisted they take one of the praying guys
They take him over to the table
They strap him down and Victor's just standing there watching and the aliens pull out their instruments and
They cut him open and while he's still alive
They begin removing his organs and putting them in little like pots. They're weighing them
They're doing tests on them while he's alive. They're just cutting them open
piece by piece and then eventually he passes away and
Everyone watch this even the bears like oh no. Oh no. What's gonna happen to me?
the woman is
10 decibels louder at this point and
They then basically all of the man scraps. They just kind of throw them away
They just basically like are then cleaning the table off
Packing up what's the organs that they didn't want to study and they just basically dispose of this human
They cut him up in front of everybody and he was awake for the whole thing. It wasn't like they gave him an anesthetic
He was watching himself getting cut open by these aliens couldn't do anything about it
Eventually bled out or they just removed his heart and
They just throw him in the garbage
Put him in a hefty bag and they're like throw it out of the ship as they're flying over like someone's neighborhood
And someone's like what happened to my garden?
But anyways they dispose of the human at that point the aliens leave the room and that is when the man is like
Okay, good. He didn't pick one of us. Hi. My name is Alexander and Victor's like what he's like listen
I don't know what's going on here, but I am so glad
You're here because we got to get out of here. That's gonna happen to us. It's totally gonna happen to us kids like yeah
Yeah, no duh we got to get out here and he's like okay, but see I'm glad you're in my cage
Because see those bars at the top of this really old cage that somehow these aliens use and Victor's like yeah
You go you can squeeze through those but you're not tall enough to get through those
So I'm gonna lift you up and I'm gonna push you through that cage and Victor's like then when
Go to that door. I've seen him press that button to open the cages
You just saw him press that button open the cages remember when they pulled the other guy and he's like oh, yeah
Totally I was in shock from seeing a man murdered. He's like yeah happens
So I'm gonna put you up through the bars of the cage. You're tiny enough and I'm tall enough
You drop you'll go over there you hit a button and he goes what about the others
Shouldn't we help the others and Alexander kind of face palm as it goes listen dude
We can release them at some point, but this is our escape plan you want to run through an alien
Run and hide from aliens with a screaming woman
two guys praying and a bear on her ass and and of course Victor's like oh, yeah, sorry forgot about the bear
So he's like just go hit our button
I'm gonna lift you up you go and hit the button that will only release my cage. Okay. Be very very careful about that
so he does Alexander picks up Victor and he pushes them through the top of the bars and
Victor gets out of the cage
And then Victor walks over to the side of the UFO where the button is and he goes press it Alexander's like no no no
That one that's the bear one don't hit that one
So Alex Victor's like okay, okay, and he can't reach the button because he's too tiny
And Alexander's looking at it and he goes okay. I want this is all important. I'm not just basically doing
Tom Sawyer esk escape this all pays off in the end
the
Um Alexander goes okay. I want you to take your clothes off
Victor's like what he's like listen, dude. You want to get out of here?
Just take your clothes off. Don't worry. It doesn't get weird
Put them underneath your feet and that'll give you an extra like a couple inches a foot to stand on
Now keep your underwear on dude. Just get up there and then you can hit the button. It'll open the door
We can make our escape. So Victor does that he takes off his shirt
Takes off his pants stands on top of him is now able to reach the button hits it door opens up and Alexander comes out
And he's like okay first off get your clothes back on as quickly as you can
And let's go and they start kind of rummaging through the shit. They don't know where they're at obviously
They're on a vessel that was never designed by a human. They don't know where they're at and again
This is taking place in 1948
So I don't even know if they're truly aware of they could be in the sky
Or they could be in an outer space like again UFO culture was not super well known
In the rural areas of the soviet union, which is where the story takes place
Alexander said that he was a minor from the url region. So he was just a
Digging out rocks one day and these aliens got him
So they they weren't sitting there watching the day the earth stood still they don't
They just know and actually that movie wasn't even out yet. This was like what two years after roswell around that
They just know that they're not on the ground
But as far as they know they're in the middle of deep space or underwater. They have no idea
But what do you do when you're trapped by a bunch of people in a vehicle?
You don't know where it's at you try to do as much damage as possible
They end up they're running around the ship and they find
What appears to be an engine room? They're not idiots. They know what engines look like and
Alexander's like, oh, we gotta figure out a way. Maybe we can commandeer this boat this blimp whatever it is and take it somewhere
And victor goes. Oh, I know something and he picks a box up off the ground. It says a metal box
I don't know if he like tore it off the ground
Like the hulk or if it was just laying there because the aliens were dirty
He picks it up and he throws it against an instrument panel
And sparks start shooting out
Which is one way to to end your captivity is to destroy whatever you're in
at that point
The aliens who had been sleeping who'd been sleeping through this adventure
Jump up out of their respective beds
And run into the control room
Oh, yeah, I forgot to I forgot to say that when they were sneaking through the ship
They saw the three aliens sleeping which would have been if you want to take
Well, I guess maybe they don't want to murder these people in their sleep
I guess there's a difference between escaping and like cold-blooded murder
But anyways, they did see the alien sleeping and then they went to the control room
And so when they started bashing the place up bashing up real good
The aliens woke up ran in and when they ran in they
They got alexander. He basically put up no fight
And then they took a shock stick and plugged victor in the back of the head and knocked him out
So victor was just one of those guys be like fine. You got me but stands up
Victor's one resisting arrest and they have to pull out their space billy clubs and beat him down
Victor wakes back up in the cell with alexander and now they have two guards the aliens are like
So now they can only sleep one at a time two of them has to stand outside of their cell to make sure they don't escape again
But everything changed after this and the aliens actually now had more respect for alexander
Not so much victor, which is interesting because they go. Well, how did you get out?
Like just tell us how you got out because you're trapped and alexander goes
Well, you know actually I lifted him up through the top of the bars and he fell over
And then he stood on his clothes and he hit the button and then we went we saw you guys sleeping
It's kind of creepy. We could have done anything, but we didn't and the aliens are like did you see what else we were doing?
alexander's like
I won't say but yes, I did but then we went to the control room started mucking stuff up and
The aliens go, you know
Let's I'm gonna be honest with you. We're scientists earth has scientists. We're scientists. We're here simply doing
Investigations and stuff that you would do to other animals on your planet
So there's nothing personal between us and our medical research at that point the praying guys are like you killed our friend
But we don't we we're not here to actually cause any harm
But we're fascinated by the fact that she figured out a way out of this trap
Like no one should have been able to do that. They said see that woman over there. She's totally nuts
Like we don't even know what we're going to do with her. She's like completely gone
And those guys who were praying they're actually they actually were called quote
Lower level humans unquote
So whether or not that means they were like
From some sort of like undiscovered tribe or even the article says maybe they were from another time period
Like lower level as in they were abducted from another period of time. Who knows but the aliens just said they're basically a bunch of dummies
We don't know what we're going to do with them. We're just going to cut them up
The woman probably cut her up. Maybe have some hybrids. We don't know the bear was an accident
The bear we were trying to pick up a hunter. He ducked
Bear got sucked up. We're stuck with this bear and
Alexander goes, why are you guys here? Why are you we get the extra scientists?
You want to cut up a bunch of people and a bear but what's what's going on and they said listen
We didn't know anything really about your planet. Like we knew there was life on it
But once you guys started detonating nuclear bombs
We're like what is possibly going on in this planet. They said radioactive material like nuclear material is quite rare
And it is the main propulsion drive for star ships
And the fact that you guys are throwing it into bombs and dropping it on each other is ludicrous to us
It's it's something that we need to make our ships fly around. That's why we're here now. That's an interesting theory
I've never ever heard that theory before. I've heard that aliens were brought here because the nuclear bombs
That they saw them dropping and they were like we must stop them from destroying themselves
I've never heard the theory before that they're like it would be like if you were poor or you just were kind of getting by
And you saw someone just like melting gold and spraying it with spraying it on people the super soaker
And you'd be like you're wasting all that money and you're like, yeah, but I can like that's how they viewed us dropping nuclear bombs
They're like this is so precious and you guys are blowing each other up with it
But they said Alexander we would like to make you do
We would like to offer you a trip onto our mothership because we think you're probably the smartest human we've run across
We will take you on our mothership with us and you can come to our home planet and tell us all about earth
You'll basically be a representative
And Alexander says I will go on your mothership, but you have to let everyone else go and the aliens actually didn't want to do that
They're like, I'm assuming it takes a lot of effort to actually abduct people
Because the aliens are like, uh fine and they thought about it
So they go, yes, you're a better prize than all these other dudes
So we'll let victor go we'll let the woman go we'll let the two praying guys go
They don't say what happens to the bear. I'm assuming that goes to space with them
But they say, you know, Alexander needs to get this little shot
In him because he got a high dose of radiation when he went into the control room
We're going to give him the shot. He'll be fine. We'll drop him off on earth
We'll give you a shot later because we don't want you dying either, but let's go
Victor gets the shot in his neck and then he passes out and the next thing he knows
He wakes up and his mother and a bunch of other people are standing around him. Apparently he had been
Passed out and missing or missing and passed out. This is where the story gets weird again because we don't
It doesn't say where he was found or when he was found or who found him or anything like that
We're missing a lot of details. But anyways when victor came back like Dorothy from Oz he says
Oh my god, you guys won't believe what happened. There was this bear and this screaming woman and this dude got chopped up
But I took all my clothes off and I hit a button and I let this guy out of a cage and they're like, whoa
Hold on victor and he was telling this story
All over the village and his mom eventually pulled him aside and said listen victor
You can't keep telling that story and he's like it's true though mom mom goes it may be true
but if you keep
telling this story you will be visited by
Somebody that you don't want to be visited by and at that point victor stopped telling that story and when he became a young man
He was in his 20s. He was working in the farm a bunch of troops showed up with a plane with a guy dressed up and just plain clothes
Which are main secret police they always just show up in
Slacks and a button-up t-shirt, but they're flanked by guards
So you know there's someone important and the guy started asking victor about this story because it had got it taken a couple years
But it had gotten to people who investigated this stuff and then they tracked him down
They asked him about the story and he totally denied it said it never happened
Doesn't know what what they're talking about and that went on for quite a while and eventually the the secret police in the military left
And he kept the story under wraps until the year 2001 where he wrote this letter to this russian UFO investigator
alien abduction stories
tend to be I was abducted I have a few brief glimmers of
Memory and then i'm back on her most alien abduction stories seem to be quite vague the victims seem to not
Really been able to grasp or remember what happened and if the story of victor is true
And if it's the norm it's actually a good thing that they don't
How many people have gone through the same story?
How many people have been abducted?
caged
tested and disposed of
Not returned with a hazy memory
Not dropped back on earth after a deal
but simply
disappear
Families and loved ones missed them putting flyers up on telephone poles
along lonely streets at night
Never knowing that the person that they lost
Is simply a footnote
in an alien's medical journal
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadratheradio
Twitter is @jasono carpenter
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
But i'm glad you listen to it today
Have a great one guys
[Music]