A pop singer in Malaysia finds more success practicing black magic.
And then we take a look at a story that I've actually hinted about quite a few times,
but have never spoken about publicly. Today I will tell you the time that I fought a witch
today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Remember,
we're going to do a live episode, a live Thanksgiving episode. It's going to be 12 p.m. Pacific Standard
Time. So grab your turkey or your tofu or nothing. Maybe you're fasting that day, I don't know.
And come and join us for a live episode. I don't know if I'm going to do an episode on Friday.
The live episodes kind of drain me, plus all the, you know, turkey and everything,
but definitely we're going to have that episode come out on Thursday. We're going to have all these
other episodes coming out as well as normal. We'll see what's going on with the Friday episode.
But while I'm trying to figure out what to do with that, let me introduce some of our legacy
patreons, Corio and Nicole. Corio and Nicole, they're coming in. They're doing summer shots.
They're doing like a Cirque du Soleil routine. They're doing flips and stuff. And they land.
They have machinilias hearts. Hi, Cori. Hi, Nicole. Thank you for supporting the show.
You guys are going to be our captains, our pilots this episode. If you can't support the Patreon,
I totally get it. Just help spread the word about the show. Really, really helps out a lot.
So Nicole, let's go ahead and put you in the Dead Rabbit Durgible. Corio is going to be your
first mate. He has a cute little skipper uniform, mom. Look at that. That's so adorable. We are
flying out to Malaysia. Specifically, we're headed out to Kampong, Paris. That's in Ulu Dong.
And Ulu Dong is in Rabu Paeng. And all of those places are in Malaysia. So there, I'm just pointing
down. I know exactly where it's at, don't you? I'm pointing down right at the region we're going to
land at. Nicole brings that Durgible down. We're all walking around in like clothes because you're
not allowed to be naked in Malaysia. We're walking around in clothes. It's a sunny day. We're taking
pictures. We're just tourists. And we see a poster on the side of a building and it is for Malaysia's
top pop star, Mona Fande. But we notice that the poster is a little frayed. And the reason why the
poster is sun-dried flaking off is because this is an older poster. You see, Mona wasn't one of Malaysia's
top pop stars. However, she tried. She self-produced an album. She was able to do a couple performances
on TV shows. But her career never really took off. So she went to the next best thing. Because power
is what Mona craved, really. It wasn't about putting forth her art, but being recognized,
being known, being somebody. And if you can't be a powerful person yourself, you need to be the power
behind the powerful people. This story is really interesting. I'm actually surprised it's not more
popular because some of the themes are going to be talking about. You'll find very familiar with
conspiracy theories going on to this very day. Mona leaves behind her pop music career and she
becomes what's known as a Bomo. A Bomo is the Malaysian equivalent of a shaman or a witch doctor
or a spiritual healer. But they were also known, some of them at least, to not just grind up a
couple herbs and put them in your teeth. They let you know they don't spike your teeth. They're like,
"Ha ha ha, now you're cured of all your diseases." And you didn't even know I was behind it.
That you pay them money. You pay them money. They give you herbs, you know little trinkets. This will
help you find your lost love. A little GPS. It's a GPS tracker you put on your love. But also she
was doing a little bit of that black magic. A little bit of the dark arts. Now it wasn't so much
that she was placing curses on other people, but she was telling people that she could, for lack of
a better term, make their wishes come true. Now, she didn't have a little shack in the middle of a
swamp. She wasn't sitting on some dusty street corner reading poems. Her clientele very quickly
became the rich and the powerful of Malaysia. Heads of state, high-level government associates.
The rich and the powerful begin to visit her to get a little bit of that sweet, sweet magic.
She was weaving all over the country. Is she actually casting spells that are helping these
people out? They believed it. And then we have Maslon Idiris enter the scene. He's an up-and-coming
politician. He's just getting his foot wet in the super corrupt swamp known as politics.
And he hears of Mona. He knows her reputation, so he visits her to see if he can get some magical
assistance. She says, "Come on by my house. We'll take care of it." Now it's not free. It's going
to cost you 2.5 million ring-its. And he's all gold. That sounds like a lot. And when you run the
conversion factor, it's actually a ton of money. It's $609,000 in U.S. dollars to get this done.
She must have had a very well-established reputation. You're not dropping $25 at the local
fortune tellers. If you're dropping $600,000, hopefully you've seen results. Hopefully you're
not the first sucker in on this scheme. But he pays it. He writes off some land deeds for her
and gives her some cash. July 18th, 1993. Maslon goes to her house and there he sees Mona, along
with her husband, Mode, and their assistant, Jirami. And Maslon goes, "Okay, so I want the power that I
know you can grant me. I want to be a very successful politician." She goes, "That's simple enough. Very,
very simple spell, honestly. I need you to lay down on the floor." So he lays down on the floor.
She goes, "I need you to close your eyes." Closes his eyes. He hears the shuffling of feet
around him. The carpet moving under his body every time someone steps closer. And then she says,
wait for it. You'll soon feel money falling from heaven onto your face. We don't really know what
Maslon's thought process is, because there's only a brief second between her saying that and an axe
coming down and severing his head. Jirami was standing there waiting for the signal and when
she gave it, decapitated Maslon. They chopped up the body, disposed of it in a shack nearby their
house for some bizarre reason. This is where the plan started going sideways when they murdered
a person, basically. But this is when it really starts going sideways. They chop up the body,
hide it in a little shack nearby Mona's residence, and then take the money and just go about their
lives. Mona actually goes and gets a facelift. She goes and buys a new car. I think it was a jaguar.
Live in large. Live in large with that dead man's money. But you see, Maslon had actually been missing
since July 2nd. People were already wondering what was going on with him, because they saw him pull
out a large amount of cash from his bank account and then disappeared. He was still alive until
the 18th, but he didn't have any communication with the public. I don't know if he was wearing an
invisible man suit. He borrowed all the money. He's like, "Oh yeah, I want to get one of those cool
suits that's on that movie." He didn't do that. He unfortunately got his head chopped off, but
it's interesting he was missing for 16 days before he was actually murdered. The cops were already
looking for him. But through a weird series of events, and it didn't actually say it in any of
the articles I read, the police ended up narrowing their sights on Jirami, the assistant. And he broke
very quickly. Said where the body was, said what was going on. The cops go and arrest Mona. You'd
wonder if she was surprised when cops walked into her house, but she did just have facelifts.
So you wouldn't be able to tell. She's like, "Oh my god!" Her face is totally frozen place,
not a good facelift. They all get taken, hold into court. The trial starts, and Mona is smiling
throughout the trial. That's a lot of times when you read these articles, they'll talk about how
she was smiling. She seemed so content. She was on trial for murder. Some people say that it was
because she finally got the fame that she had wanted. She would call the people at the courthouse,
and the photographer's taking a picture, her fans. That's why she always had a smile on her face.
I think part of it, again, has to do with the shoddy facelift, but it could also just be the fame.
All three are found guilty. And all three are sentenced to hang. In Malaysia, before you're
executed, you get to... This sounds like torture. This sounds absolutely awful. A day or two before
your sentence to death, you get to spend eight hours with your family. You're like, "Jason,
that's awesome! That's what Thanksgiving's all about!" Yeah, it is, but imagine like you having
to hang out with someone who's gonna die in a day. I mean, I guess you're like, "Jason, you're super
heartless!" But it's like you go and you hang out with your relative and she's like, "Hey, everyone,
yeah, I murdered that guy. There's no axes lying around right. You're like looking around making
sure there's no sharp weapons." First, and here's the thing. One, it seems torturous because you
know this is the last time, you know for a fact this is the last time you're gonna see someone.
Two, eight hours is a long time. Imagine if you were just like a cousin who like kind the new Aunt
Mona and you're like, "Oh man, did I bring a Game Boy? Did I bring a Game Boy?" Were they invented
in 1993 as Mona's like, "I'm gonna miss you guys so much." So little dude's like, "I'm so bored."
He's all drawn stuff. Eight hours is a long time to spend with somebody. Anyone, whether or not
they're going to die, seems like torture for both people. Psychological torture for the person who's
going to die and then actual torture for all the nephews and nieces who'd rather be at home than
be here in this prison. She tells them though, she says this comment quite a few times apparently,
"I will never die. I will never die." But on November 1st, 2001, they bring a last meal
to these three defendants. Now, Mona and her husband said, "We don't want to eat anything. We don't
want a last meal. We're gonna sit here in contemplation as we move on from one existence to the next."
So on another thing that would probably be considered torture, the prison officials go,
"Oh, you want to have like this spiritual awakening before you die and all that stuff,
but by law we have to give you a last meal. So here's a bucket of Kentucky Fried Chicken."
How can you be like on the spiritual path? You're sitting in a cell, you know you're gonna die in
a few hours. You're trying to cleanse your body of all impurities. Someone puts KFC in front of you.
Tell me you don't eat that KFC. Tell me you do not. You're like, "Okay, I'll just take a bite.
My last bite and then you're all hard. You just started eating it. You're pouring it into a horse
trough." Sucking on the bones. How could you? That is so, I mean, I don't care about them. Hopefully
that their spiritual existence thing, I don't care how peacefully they went to death. They were
murderers. But I just think that's so funny. Like I imagine like a monk wanting to be like,
"No, I will go to the afterlife the same way I came and no earthly possessions on me or in me."
And they're like, "Here's some mashed potatoes and gravy straight from Kentucky Fried Chicken
and a biscuit." And they're like, "Ahhh. How can you resist Kentucky Fried Chicken?"
We don't know. The reporters, there's no article saying they chow down. And as they were being
led to the gallows, they're like, "Finger licking good. It's the worst advertisement for KFC ever."
But anyways, they do get taken to the gallows. She was completely calm. They put the rope around
her neck or the noose to be specific. Kick the switch. And they all die.
That's the story of Mona Fande. It's a very, very interesting one because like I said earlier,
it has all the hallmarks of what we think about when we think about modern conspiracy theories.
Satanic magic and sacrifice being connected to the rich and the powerful, the music industry.
Like I'm actually surprised this story isn't trotted out more often. When people talk about
Katy Perry is doing whatever she does nowadays and making music still. But Katy Perry, I remember
early on, it was like Dark Horse was her, like making some Satanic bargain. Rihanna's Queen of
the Illuminati. We see this stuff all the time, these conspiracy theories. And here we have someone
who started off as a pop singer, became a Boma, but actually was also doing the, Boma is supposed
to be like a healer, but it can really, it's a catchall term. She was using her powers to guarantee
other people political power for money. So I'm surprised that this story doesn't get brought
up more because it really ties into a lot of that stuff. The entertainment world, magic,
and secret societies. People at the top using magic. So on that level, I find this story really
fascinating. But what I find is even more bizarre about this story is why did she kill him?
She, I mean, she had been doing this for a while. She had already had access to these
powerful people. Why would she choose to kill this guy? She could have just taken his money,
promised him power. If it didn't come about, she goes, "Oh, the fates, the fates were wrong.
The fates, they didn't get the message. Maybe if he gave me a little more money,
I could pay the fates phone bill and give him a call." You know, that's what these charlatans
always do. So why did they murder him? Because they'd been doing this for a while and they hadn't
murdered any of their other clients. Let's put on a conspiracy cap here for a second. I think
she murdered him because someone else had a request for an even more powerful spell.
One that would require the blood of a gullible, willing instrument. And so to make that spell
work for someone else who paid her far more money, she had to execute Mazlan, a dark magic
blood spell. It doesn't make sense why she killed him when she had tons of other clients. If she had
one client and it was him and he almost found out and she chopped his head off, we've covered stories
like that before. The jig is up. I'm going to get found out. I better kill this person before
my fraud gets exposed. But she'd been doing this. He was one of a hundred customers. But if someone
more powerful than him with more money said, "I need this to happen," and she goes, "The only way
for that spell to happen is for blood to be spilled." He says, "Money is no object." But she goes,
"Jason, that's the case. What was the point of the magic?" She got killed. None of the money's
going to help. She got killed anyways in the end. When she is sitting there and she's telling people,
"I will never die. I will never die." There's two ways to read that. One, she has finally become
famous. Her name will always be remembered in Malaysian culture. Maybe not. Maybe she's not
a mythological figure, but you know what I mean? That is a name, especially if you are into true
crime. You would have never known who Mona Fande was had this not happened. So you could say that.
That's why she was saying, "I will never die." But the other reason why, we could take it as a literal
thing, she may not be able to die. She may have that level of power. So is Mona Fande immortal?
Because here we are talking about her on a podcast 17 years after this murder. Or is she immortal?
Because she crafted a ritual. The only requirement would be human blood. And she found not only the
perfect victim, but she also found someone with enough money to give her a facelift for her new
life. Not like her facelift. I'm sure that after the hanging, the facelift was ruined. But you
know what I'm saying. So that is a good segue to move on to our next story. So Cole, let's go
ahead and put you in that carbonar copter. We got Danielle sitting there as your co-pilot. She got
the little headset on, little aviator goggles. You don't have a headset or goggles. Bugs keep hitting
you in the eyes. Let's leave behind Malaysia. We are headed out to Sacramento, California.
It's funny, I actually, Weisel Horn on YouTube just the other day said, "Hey man, are you ever
going to tell a story about you fighting the witch?" A couple of you guys have reminded me of doing that
story over the years. Over the two years I've been doing this show, I'm going to try to make
it so this doesn't run so long. But there's a little bit of backstory to it. We're going to land
there. We're back in time. It's about 2008, 2007, 2008, something like that. At the time I was living
with my friend, Kara. We were both staying at her cousin Matt's house. And it was basically my,
I was the nanny to her son. Like she worked, she had a full-time job as a nurse. I didn't have a job
at the time. And she's like, "Hey, I need someone to take care of my son when I'm not at work. And I
know you're a total hard nose when it comes to homework." And stuff like that. And he has a hard
time doing his homework. So I need someone to basically break the bat. Like I need some, literally
I didn't walk around the bat. I mean, like just like, that was a Bain reference. She needed someone
to, she goes, "He never does his homework. I need someone who's going to be totally on him about
his homework." And I was. He's great. He just turned 18 the other day. Yeah, no, I was pretty hard on
him. I might actually make up extra homework for him. If he didn't do his homework fast enough,
I'm like, "Tick tock, buddy. You're not wasting my time. I'm staying up late to watch Dexter anyways.
It's you who's sitting in the living room with no television on." I go, "If you get your homework
done, you can play video games until you go to bed. But otherwise, you're doing your homework
until you're basically falling asleep on the table, bro. That's just the way it goes." It took
about a week and he caught on real quick. I had no give in me when it came to that. But anyways,
they're all really cool. They're all doing well. Liam, Matt, and Kara. Now, I was staying there.
And I was a layabout, right? I wasn't telling kids, "Do the homework." I was sleeping on the couch,
right? I love sleeping on couches. So that's kind of my job. If you got a couch, I'll swing on over.
Cole, Daniela, you got a couch. I'm there. Sleeping on couches. And the reason why that's
important, it's not really important in the grand scheme of things. But I would sleep on the couch
a lot, even though I had my own room. Now, Kara's dad was a really nice guy. And he was dating.
See, here's the thing. This is really interesting. I remember this detail now. I had not met his
girlfriend. But Kara's dad, I would see every once in a while. He wasn't in Sacramento area. He
lived somewhere else and he would visit every once in a while. And I remember him talking about
his girlfriend was a witch. And he's a really nice guy. I don't want to sound like I'm not going to
murder anything like that. But the way he talked about her being a witch, I was always kind of like,
are you bragging? Like, that seems like such a bizarre thing to brag about. Oh, my wife's a
train conductor. Who cares? Who cares? That's how I feel about witches. They're about as cool as
train conductors. I'll tell you the story when I beat up a train conductor. I'm sitting there.
And he would be like, oh, my girlfriend's a witch. And I'd be like, yeah, okay, I fought demons.
Like, I didn't actually say that. But you know, I'm like, that doesn't really impress me, whatever.
But again, he's a super nice guy. I'm not trying to knock him. And so she was coming up. The girlfriend
was coming up. And I was sleeping on the couch. And they were doing some renovations in the house
or something like that. So Kara's dad and the girlfriend were coming. We'll just call the girlfriend
Samantha. I don't remember. We have Samantha come in. And I remember I was sleeping on the couch.
And I woke up. Like something woke me up. It also, it was noon. It was super late in the day. But I
remember something woke me up. And the only way I can describe it, I wake up and Samantha's in there
with Kara's dad. They're in the kitchen. They're looking at the lighting. Even though we had no
interaction with each other, we haven't even said a word to each other yet. It was as if
there were two magnets in the room, completely repelling each other. It was a very, very weird
feeling. I felt like I extended out to fill half the room. And something else was pushing against
that. Like you could feel the whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, between us. Now I had not
said anything. Now I have a pretty good read on people. I can tell if someone's going to steal
money from me. I can tell if someone's going to stab me in the face. Those are just things that you
have to do to survive in bad neighborhoods, right? Or you don't make it. But this was different. This
wasn't me like hanging out with dudes because I'm hung out with dudes who do stab people. And I know
they're not going to stab me, so I'm totally fine with it. I would prefer they don't stab. I would
prefer they don't stab anybody. But you know what I mean? It's not just the fact that they've beat
people up violently. That's whatever. They shouldn't, but they've done it or they will do it. It
does involve me. So I don't feel I'm in danger. But this I didn't necessarily feel I was in danger,
but you could feel that. I remember it. I remember it instinctively. I had not said a word to this
woman. She would have had to have been in her 40s. Now I would have been back in 2008. I don't know.
I can't do math right now. What is that? 12 years? 12 years ago? So I would have been like
early 30s. She was definitely, she might have been older than that. She might have been late 40s.
Very attractive woman. But I can feel that energy just like repellent. I felt like I was taking up
a ton of the room. And maybe I always take up a ton of the room. Maybe I always have this
giant energy bubble around me. But for the first time I met something of equal strength that was
pushing back against it. And I can almost guarantee she felt the same thing because she hated my guts.
Absolutely hated my guts. She didn't say it, but I could tell. Absolute disgust disdain.
Now at first she was there for a couple of days. They wouldn't stay there, but they would spend a
long time there. They'd spend like eight hours the day there working on stuff. And I'm sitting on the
couch. This is my place, dude. I'm living here. I heard through the grapevine. I don't remember if
Kara told me. I think she might have think the Samantha maid have told Kara's dad and the
Kara's dad told me, but I heard it through the grapevine. And again, this is after a good two
or three days of me realizing she hates my guts. We've maybe said hello to each other. I'm sure
we did that. But apparently, and I don't remember, it's funny because I can't say for sure that Kara
told me this or how I got this information, but she didn't like the fact that I slept on the couch
and that I wasn't helping put in lights. And I was like, one, do you know how dangerous I am
around any sort of electricity? That's just a disaster waiting to happen. Two, isn't my house
homey? Like, yeah, sure. I'm like living with other people. And I got this awesome friend, Matt,
who's letting me stay there. But I've been there for months, right? I'm taking care of the house.
I'm taking care of the kid. I was paying rent too, now that I think about it. Wait, was I paying rent?
I don't remember. It doesn't matter. I was paying rent in the love I gave to that family, but I
might have been paying actual cash. I don't remember. My point is, is that whether or not I'm laying on
the couch, this is my place. I'm part of this family. You're the interloper. But she thought I
should be up and about. Now you're thinking, Jason, is this just the story about a woman who
says she's a witch who thinks you're lazy? No, it's not. Because I don't think that's the reason
why she didn't like me. I think she couldn't place why she didn't like me. I think she disliked me
because of that that energy pushing up against. And maybe I was a little more astute that I could
figure out, because I figured out very, very quickly, there's something wrong with this lady.
Like this dude may have been talking, she was a witch and all this stuff. And I thought she was
grinding up herbs, she was chopping people's heads off in Malaysia. I don't know. Whatever she's doing,
she's putting off some serious voltage. She's putting off some serious energy. And I think she
probably felt the same thing. She actually tried to get me kicked out. At the very least, she didn't
want me there when they were working. Now again, if someone was just laying on a couch, I'm not
pearl from Blade, I was doing other things. But if you came over to someone's house at noon,
they were sleeping on the couch. Okay, why do you want to get someone removed from that? Or the
very, I remember there was like, should I leave while she's here? And I was like, hell no, I'm not
leaving while someone who's coming here to put in light bulbs. Put in light bulbs, right?
No, I'm not leaving. I had no opinion about her in the beginning. I thought it was kind of funny
that this guy was bragging about dating a witch. I've met a ton of witches in my life. There's
nothing to brag about. When she entered the room, I could tell there was something really off about
her. I don't know if she was meaning to exude that much energy, or if she didn't have control,
or if it was just a natural thing. Who knows? I didn't know I had that type of sphere around
me until something pushed up against it. But I had enough, dude. I'm just sick and tired of her,
dude. I was like, no, done. And I remember one day I'm sitting there, Kara was home. I think Liam
was there too, running around in his PJs or whatever a year old's do. He's like, yippee. How do you do
what he's on? And Samantha and the dad were out grocery shopping, or picking up more light bulbs.
I don't know. At this point, it was like been a week. And I knew that I felt unwelcome in the
place. I had been living there for like a year. I felt unwelcome there. I didn't care. Like, I
didn't actually feel unwelcome, but people were trying to make me be unwelcome. Her. Samantha was
trying to make me not feel comfortable there. Whatever, bro. But anyways, they're out picking
up light bulbs and stuff, buying stuff. And I remember I was sitting there and Kara goes,
so what's your take on her? And I was like, well, you know, she probably actually does have some
sort of, we had talked about it before this, but I was like, I think she probably does have some
sort of power. Not anything to be concerned about. But whatever it is, it's not what you would call
like a white witch. It's not a good power. And then I go, you know what? Let's salt the place.
Kara's like, what? I go, you got a lot of salt? She's like, yeah, yeah, she cooks. Kara is an
amazing chef. I go, let's salt the front door. And that'll tell us everything we need to know.
Now that's an old folk tale. Evil can't cross salt. A lot of times you'll have rituals that
involve circles of salt to protection. I actually made a joke about it a couple of episodes ago.
I go, how can a demon that's existed since before time began not be able to cross sodium?
Like he existed before sodium even existed. So why would that protect him?
But I'm like, dude, as a joke, right? And as a test, we'll just salt the front door. We're going
to put salt underneath the doormat outside. We will leave the back door unsalted. So let's see
what happens. And Kara is doing it. We're having fun, right? We're having fun. And Kara goes,
so she'd done it. And she didn't really believe in ghosts or anything like that. She was just bored.
She was just totally bored. She goes, so Jason, what's your hypothesis? What do you think's going
to happen? And I said, well, there's going to be one or two things that are going to happen. One,
she's just going to walk into the house. And that's going to mean one of two things. One,
the salt doesn't work. It's just an old folk tale. Or two, she's not actually a dark witch.
There's just some sort of weird personality glitch between me and her. Maybe she has something
against couches. Maybe her dad got swallowed up by a lazy boy recliner. I don't know.
That's one possibility. The other possibility is she can't come in the front door for whatever
reason. She can't come in the front door. She'll walk all the way into the backyard, open the little
gate, walk through the sliding glass door. And Kara's like, that's impossible. I go, it is.
It is. But maybe like that'll happen. I don't know. I don't know. Maybe she'll pull out her
broom and fly over the house. But in my mind, I'm thinking, this is pretty funny, right? By the way,
this is super funny. I'm actually salting a witch. So I'm sitting in my recliner and Kara's messing
around in the kitchen. She's trying to cook something. She's like, dang it. Where's all my salt?
She's scraping it off the front door. The car pulls up. Kara runs through the window and looks
out the window. And I'm sitting in my recliner. Because here's the thing. If I had gotten up
and looked out the window, they would have known something was up right in pretty much every part
of the story I'm sitting down. They're like, Jason's on two legs. Uh oh. Something must be going on
in that house. I'm sitting down. Kara's kind of in the kitchen. She's looking out the window a bit.
And she goes, they pulled up. And I'm just, okay. And then what? And she goes, they're just standing
there. They're just standing there in the driveway. And like a couple minutes pass.
And then the dad walks in. At this point, Kara's not looking out the window anymore. She's not that
much of a stalker. The dad walks in and Kara's curious. She goes, hey, where's Samantha? And
the dad goes, she doesn't want to come in the house. And the dad walks by. He doesn't see me
and Kara look at each other like, what in the world? Now, obviously I couldn't chime in here.
That would make it even more suspicious. But Kara asks her dad, she goes, why won't she come in the
house? And the dad goes, we pull up into the driveway. And for whatever reason, she just flipped
out and started to fight with me. So now I got a dad and he walks back outside and we're like, what
in the world is going on? Five minutes pass. Dad comes back in with more supplies. I don't know
what's up with that woman. Oh, I don't know why she just acts up sometimes. Being Kara looking at each
other. Dad walks back outside. Another five, maybe 10 minutes pass. The dad walks in and then Samantha
enters the house. Looking pissed, looking drained. I never saw her again. Now I'm not saying she
disappeared. I'm not saying she turned him a pillow result and Kara used her to cook more food. She
never came back to the house. I never saw her again. Now there's a couple different things we can look
at with this story. One, she saw the salt. That was my first thing when I was telling Kara when the
dad was walking in and out. I go, maybe she saw the salt. Because that is something you put salt to
keep evil out. If you left a home where you know somebody doesn't like you, or I really started
off having no opinion about her, I began to dislike her because I could tell how much she disliked me.
And then you saw salt outside the door and you were all into that magic stuff. You would know
what that salt signified. So my first thing was I go, maybe she saw the salt and that's why she's mad
at your dad. Because it would be the equivalent of a hate crime versus a witch, right? And you'll
try to dunk them in their sleep. We got more information about the fight. It really was
over nothing. The dad could never understand why she flipped out. And when I say in the driveway,
it would have been maybe five feet from the door. They were having this argument right out there.
He said she just got mad over nothing. It was nothing. So she could have said, dude, look at what
your stupid kids did. They salted the door. And because they think I'm an evil witch, I'll show them.
Starts electrocuting us. So one, she could have seen the salt and she got offended by that,
but it doesn't sound like it because she never brought that up. Two, the salt actually repelled
her, but she didn't know what was going on. It might have been the first time she was ever salted.
Just like this was the first time I had ever encountered anyone. I don't like to give myself
superpowers. I think anything that I can do, you can do as far as like seeing, like I've talked
about seeing demons and stuff like that, seeing ghosts. I think anyone can do that. I think everyone
probably has a psychic bubble around them like that. I don't know how big mine is in comparison
to other people, but that was the first time I'd ever felt, and I'm a people person. I talked to
thousands of people throughout my life. That was the first time I'd ever met someone who
pushed against my, I mean, again, it was, it was like a good 10 feet. I could feel energy
pushing 10 feet away from me. Like my barrier was that far ahead of me and I could feel that
reverse polarity against them. I'm thinking, this is my hypothesis, is that it's not like
you get to the door and go, "I can't cross the salt." Her aura bubble, her psychic bubble,
was touching against the salt and she felt it repelling her and she couldn't figure out why.
I'm thinking she probably is a witch, but she's not an adept one. That's my guess. That's 100%
my guess. It seemed like it was very raw energy coming from her, but she wasn't able to tell what
was going on. Again, I will flex on her on this to the point where I woke up, whatever was in
that room, I woke up to her being 8, 10 feet away and I could feel her energy. Like it, and I knew
immediately what it was. It's that person. I wasn't going, "What? Who? Is there any ghosts around?"
Like I knew immediately this person is pushing against me and I'm wondering if she, that's what
was happening. As she got closer to the door, she felt uneasy and she couldn't figure out why she
felt uneasy. She felt more than uneasy. She felt unwelcome and so she flips out. She can't understand
what's going on. Your brain gets reset too. When we get anxious and when we freak out, we're really
reverting to a childlike state when we're scared of the dark, but now we're adults and we're scared
of losing our house. Which is fine. You can be scared of losing your house, but that anxious state,
we go back to being a child. As a child, you lash out. You lash out at your loved ones, even though
it's not their fault. That's what she's doing. Her energy is pushing up against this. And the reason
why she was eventually able to come into the house is because the dad had come in so many times
and while he was stepping on that floor mat, he was breaking the salt. He was moving it enough
that there was enough of a gap in it for her to come into that house. But when she came into that
house, she looked pissed. She looked tired. She looked like she was just done with everything.
She never came back. She never came back. At least I never saw her again. Maybe I was out
shopping or doing something and she's snuck in. She's pouring salt everywhere and I'm like
walking through because that's really the catch to this thing. The hypothesis was that she was
a dark witch. She couldn't cross the salt. If it keeps her out, then she's evil. We did it as a lark.
We thought it would be funny. In the back of my mind, I'm thinking it might work, but probably not.
Again, how can sodium keep out this person? But it did. At least for 15 minutes. And it
exploded her emotions. But she couldn't figure out why. It wouldn't happen to a good witch.
It wouldn't happen to a muggle. It wouldn't happen to one of those guys. But it would happen to a
practitioner of the dark arts. Salt keeps them at bay. At least for a little while. At least until
the line is broken. So that's that story of me fighting the witch. Listen, I hope that she's
doing well. I hope she hasn't been consumed by an army of goblins or a demon hasn't taken her over.
I hope everything is going well. Unless that's what she wants, right? She's a consenting adult.
Maybe she loves to be eaten by goblins. I hope everything works out for her. I obviously don't
mean her any ill will. I can't say the same that she feels towards me again. She started it. She
started it, but I wish her the best. Maybe she was able to harness her power and get rid of that evil
part of it. I don't know. Maybe she goes on nationwide tours now and talks about the time
that a guy slept on the couch. She does tours for people. It's like, is your husband on the couch
all day long? This is how I got rid of him. She didn't. So you basically wasted your money. But
you know what I mean? I wish her the best. I'm not going to say, oh no, she's super spooky and
she's hiding in her closet with an axe. I hope she's doing well. And I hope she's able to harness
that energy and put it towards good use. I hope everything is working out for her. Because if
it's not, well, you know the old saying, there's more salt in the world than witches.
That's actually not an old saying, but that's actually sounds really dope. That's a new saying.
There's more salt in the world than witches, which means good will always triumph over darkness.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com
slash DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
[Music]