Can you make a house out of toothpaste?
And this one isn't funny.
When ghost hunts become deadly today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, thanks for coming back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I probably shouldn't reverse the order of those two stories that I introduced because one,
I can't really say it with a straight face and in the other,
a young man unfortunately lost his life.
It's actually pretty recent too.
We'll be getting that into a moment, but I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day.
Hope you're enjoying this massive heat wave we're having.
You'll hear the occasional car drive by for two reasons.
One, I'm recording during the day, which I normally don't do,
and my window's open because if I had my windows shut, I would become a steam tam in here.
All my fans are off, so at least I'm able to eliminate that noise.
But I gotta have a window open.
We'll try to silence out the cars as much as possible,
but we'll go ahead and I think we're gonna go ahead and just get started.
It's so hot.
So we're gonna go ahead and just jump right into it and see where this little,
because this mystery is a little winding.
It takes you in some weird places.
Now, before I get started, of course, there's always before I get started,
I need to reach out to you guys to see if I'm the only person who does this.
I realized that there's something that I call shower protocol,
right?
And I just realized this the other day.
I take a shower in the exact same order every single time.
I just realized this.
Turn the shower on, obviously.
And the first thing I always do is wash my left arm.
Then I wash my genitals.
Why are they called genitals?
Because everyone only has one.
Is it just my genital?
Because it's just one of them, right?
But anyways, so I wash down there,
and then, man, those cars are gonna drive me crazy.
Okay, I'm gonna go shut the window.
Okay, so in the 30 seconds it took for me to walk to the windows,
shut them, and walk back,
I've already lost 15 pounds in water weight.
I'll probably go on some sort of sweat lodge vision quest
while I'm recording this episode.
But shower protocol, so I'll wash my left arm first,
then I wash my genitals,
then I wash my right arm,
and then I drop the soap for whatever reason.
I always lose the soap at this point in my shower.
And I get it, and then I watch my torso,
then I wash my legs that people do either/or.
I never wash my back either.
I've never like soaked up my back,
I just figured the water takes care of that.
And I realize that I do it the same way
every single time I take a shower.
I'm wondering if that is a Jason thing,
or if other people like,
subconsciously, they always wash themselves
in the exact same order.
Maybe it is just a Jason thing.
Maybe that's the order of things.
Oh, and I wash my butt.
I left that out.
When I say I don't wash my back,
I do wash my butt.
That actually comes after my right arm.
And then I wash my butt.
Then I wash my torso,
which I guess I should probably change that order up.
But I figure soap, soap.
So all the bad stuff kind of gets washed off the soap.
That's how it works.
So yeah, I might want to try to change that order,
but is that just the Jason thing?
I wonder if other people have a particular way
they wash themselves.
And it's never been a conscious decision,
but I'm wondering if I'm basically washing the parts of my body
in order of importance.
So get back to me.
Let me know how you showered, people.
I want to know what you're like,
naked and wet in the shower.
Hit me up at DeadRabbitRadiogmail.com.
Let's go ahead and jump into the story though.
Just wanted to share that with you
and get some feedback on that.
Colgate Fortes is one of the conspiracy theories
that pops up on our always discussed
conspiracy theory iceberg list.
Colgate Fortes.
And actually, that's how I found out
about our last story, Ranny Cott Fort.
On the last episode, I was looking for Colgate Fortes,
and then I was trying to figure out
if that was a code for something.
And so I started looking up Charcoal Fortes.
It took me to Ranny Cott Fort.
But anyways, Colgate Fortes,
the little bit of information I found
was maybe one or two sentences on a website saying
that Colgate Fortes was something
that ex-Russian military officers did.
They took a bunch of Colgate out to Siberia,
and they made houses out of it.
So, of course, a normal person would go,
"No, that's ridiculous."
But me, I began googling,
"What is the freezing point of Colgate?"
"Can you freeze toothpaste?"
"How long does toothpaste stay frozen?"
I think I actually tried looking for stuff like,
"Can you build a structure out of toothpaste?"
Now, here's the thing.
Siberia is blisteringly cold.
I wrote a book about the Siege of Stlynengrad.
I think it was just called Stlynengrad.
It was an amazing book.
So, the story was about a symphony about Stlynengrad
and the orchestra in the city
under siege by the Nazis
trying to get people together to perform that symphony
as like a propaganda tool.
It was a great book.
It's all non-fiction.
It's all 100% true.
There's a bunch of cannibalism in it.
People, women are like giving birth to babies
and then eating them.
There's roving gangs of cannibals
having shootouts with the police.
They had to form an anti-cannibalism brigade.
It was such a huge problem.
Towards the end, the symphony that's
"Leningrad" started off with,
maybe had like 17 people left
because they'd all gotten blown up.
The constant shelling of the area.
It's great.
It's a great read.
Very, very tragic yet uplifting story.
One of the interesting things though was that
the Nazis, they weren't prepared for the winter.
They came in their light clothes,
a lot of paratroopers and stuff like that.
And one of the problems is,
is it got so cold that you just had to poop your pants.
You go, "What does it have to do with being cold?"
And here's why.
In the book it says,
"If you pulled your pants down to poop,
if you pulled your pants down to poop,
your butthole would instantly freak shut
and you would die
because you could never go poop again.
You could never get warm enough
to get your butthole loose enough to poop."
So you just had to poop in your pants.
That's miserable.
Like yeah, being in war is pretty bad,
but being like,
"Oh man, I hope it all gets shot
and I get home to my girlfriend Isabella
and we're gonna have a bunch of babies."
And then your butthole frees his shut
and then you spend the next three or four days
trying to figure out how to warm yourself up
and then you just die
because your intestines explode.
I guess at a certain point you'd stop eating
because you wouldn't want to poop anymore.
But I think at that point you're kind of SOL.
Anyways, so I knew that the area that rushes like super,
it's cold enough to freeze your butthole.
I figured maybe you could spray
and build a structure out of toothpaste.
It could Siberia is even colder, right?
Because it's Siberia.
So I looked all over for,
"Can you build a house out of Colgate?"
And the way that toothpaste is made,
it really doesn't freeze that level.
The water in it would freeze.
And as the more I researched it,
the more I started thinking about
how much toothpaste did these guys have?
I mean, you would have to have a ton of toothpaste.
Like you have your satchel
of your normal survival supplies.
And then you would need basically a house,
enough toothpaste to build a house,
or even a hut or an igloo.
And then once I realized that,
I go, "Why don't they just build igloos?"
So I think Colgate 4, it's as far as this has been going,
is busted.
And then you're going, "Jax, why are you wasting our time
talking about something that is so foolish?"
And even when you're researching it,
you realize it was ridiculous.
Well, this is why.
This is the interesting part.
The second question I was researching,
when I was looking at the Colgate 4,
it was, "Why would Russian military go to Siberia
to build these Colgate 4?"
So they're doing some sort of testing or something.
What happened is during the Russian Revolution,
Russia had a ton of gold, literal tons and tons of gold.
And the anti-Bolsheviks were like,
"There's no way we're letting the Communists
get ahold of all this gold."
So a bunch of ex-military officers did run away to Siberia,
like came from the original Colgate story.
But they didn't take Colgate with them.
They took the wealth of an entire nation to Siberia.
That happened back in 1918.
They've never been able to find it.
They looked all over for it.
There's always these rumors and cryptographers were looking,
because they had a coded sheet of coordinates.
But no one could find it.
People, it was basically the Russian equivalent
of the Lost Detriments' Mind or the City of Gold.
This had become a legend.
What happened to this gold?
Would anyone ever find it?
Last year, they found it.
So fellow Dead Rabbit radio listeners,
if you were in Russia and you wanted to hide something
where you hoped no one would ever, ever find it,
out of the entire continent of Eurasia,
you have everything from Moscow.
Well, you don't want it in Moscow,
because the Commies are there,
but you go all the way, all the way east,
deep, deep into Siberia.
Where would you put something
if you wanted to make sure that no one would find it
and it would be protected?
Would you put it somewhere, say, where aliens lived underwater?
Yep.
Out of the entire continent of Eurasia,
the gold was found at Lake Baikal.
Lake Baikal, you may recall,
was actually the lake that we talked about earlier
in the series, where they had the giant alien creature
swimming underwater apparently,
and they were able to throw frogmen,
not literal frogmen, but Russian frogmen up into the air,
and there were supposed to be UFOs down there.
Of all the places they could have hid the gold,
they hid it there.
More specifically, they hid it in a railway tunnel.
And after a hundred years of mystery
of trying to find this gold,
which may have been dropped there
to be protected by monsters or aliens.
So, you know, maybe like they figured,
"Oh, you know, we've heard legends of monsters out here,"
or they knew there were monsters out there
to dump the gold, or it's also possible
that people who did dump the gold there
began those legends to scare people off from that area.
But anyways, after a hundred years
of trying to figure out this location of this gold,
it was a mathematics genius
who found a Russian mathematics genius
who the media is not releasing his name
because he's wanted by the FBI
for the hacking of Hillary Clinton's email.
It's not Gucciifer 2.0,
but it's somebody that the FBI believes
hacked Hillary Clinton's email.
Not like that would have been super hard.
It was, you know, just an unsecured server.
But that aside, he's the guy
who's under suspicion for hacking Hillary Clinton's server.
It took him an hour once he got to cryptogram.
Once he got this note of this coded cryptogram
of where this gold was that people have been looking at
for their entire lives for over a century,
he looked at it for an hour and said,
"Oh, here it is," and they went there
and it was there as in a railway tunnel under Lake Pekal,
and now billions, billions and billions of gold,
billions of dollar, wait,
what would it be?
Billions of US dollars in gold.
Not billions of gold,
but billions of dollars in gold is headed back to Russia.
They're moving it back.
So he found it and he'll probably get some sort of metal
on his chest, but they won't reveal who it is
because, you know, FBI's a conform.
But interesting story.
All came out of a stupid idea
that somehow you could build a fort.
I'm not denying that you could build a house out of Colgate.
That may be possible if it's cold enough
and it probably is cold enough over there.
My question is, you just build an igloo, dude.
Like how much Colgate would you need?
What would be the advantage?
Wouldn't that stand out more?
You're looking in the woods for a bunch of Russian soldiers
and you see like a white mound of like igloo
and then another white mound of igloo
and then you see like a red, white and blue,
minty, fresh igloo off in the distance.
Where are you going to check first?
Where are you going to look?
I know they didn't have the view.
You know, even if they didn't have like the red and blue
coloring back then on the Colgate,
you could still smell the minty freshness
from across the tundra.
Moose would be like licking on it and stuff.
Just use ice.
The other story I wanted to talk about today,
which was said, I've, you know,
so I was looking for a, we kind of did a series last week,
which was food-based conspiracies.
I really liked doing that.
I thought it gave a lot of structure to the show.
So I was looking for stuff about murderous ghosts.
I think that's going to be one of the next series we do.
Ghosts who have killed people.
And while I was looking for that,
I actually found this.
It just happened on June 4th.
In Seattle, these kids were,
there's this haunted park in Seattle.
And they're like, hey, yeah, let's,
let's go scooby-doo around this park
and we'll take our flashlights.
And maybe we'll see like old Mary Keller,
the ghost who drowned eight babies
and floats here every Friday the 13th or whatever.
And I used to do stuff like that.
Me and my friends used to load up in the car.
Gasoline used to be 99 cents a gallon.
So you could just drive anywhere all the time.
And we'd go to all these sort of haunted locations in,
in Sacramento.
We'd visit, you know, this place would be rumored
and this place would be rumored.
And we'd just go to like creepy wooded areas in general
to see if we could like sense anything or see anything.
One day me and my friends were driving on the road.
We thought we saw a civil war ghost.
And it totally terrified us.
It was this like all gray figure.
And it looked like it was wearing like a confederate uniform.
And it was just like walking down the street.
It was super scary.
We're like, oh my God, it's a, it's like a civil war ghost.
It's civil war ghost.
And we turned around.
At first I thought, you know, it's just us like not,
it's just all of our imaginations or whatever.
So we turn around, we come back.
He's still walking down the road.
And it's like three in the morning.
And we couldn't figure it out.
And his head to toe and gray clothes, a little gray cap.
And we're like, oh my God, it's, he's still there.
It's the civil war ghost.
And we drove back around and we came,
this is again in the middle of nowhere.
There was like an industrial section there.
And then this long road is out in PFE, if you know the area.
Out by antelope.
But we come by a third time and it was a very elderly security guard.
It was not a civil war ghost, which look, one,
we probably scared the crap out of him
because we were driving by three times.
And it's not the, the most well behaved area.
But two, thinking back to it, I think even that night we're like,
why would a Confederate ghost be in Northern California?
That would be quite the well traveled ghost.
But so, you know, we did stuff like that.
We'd go out to all these places.
And this young kid named Ryan De La Cruz
was at Martha Washington Park with some friends
and they're looking around for ghosts.
They're having a good old time, just, you know,
having fun, being kids.
And he gets shot three times.
A car drives by and just opens fire on them.
And the friends call 911 and the cops come
and he's still alive.
But by the time he got to the hospital, he had passed away.
At this point, so that was in June 4th.
As of today, July 24th, they have no leads
or they're not revealing any leads.
They, it's, you know, in the article they say
they don't think it's gang related.
Generally that means that both members weren't members of gangs.
It can be gang related.
It's not considered gang related if a gang shoots a civilian.
The only considered gang related is if one gang shoots at another gang.
They don't think the man was targeted either.
They think it was just, and they, it may be related to another shooting.
What I think is weird is they're really keeping this close to their chest.
The police aren't revealing many suspects about this.
This isn't huge news.
The only reason I stumbled across it was,
and Seattle's fairly close to me.
The only reason I stumbled across it was because I was looking for murderous ghosts.
And unfortunately I stumbled across this story of a man who was murdered looking for a ghost.
So, you know, it's sad and it's tragic.
Hopefully the assholes who did this get caught.
Because, you know, accident or not, if they just thought they were shooting in the woods
because they were drunk hillbillies, or if they were shooting in the woods
because they saw some people out there.
You know, they, you know, there may be different levels of punishment for that,
but, you know, they need to be taken care of.
And, you know, obviously what's going on, these friends and stuff have to deal with this.
I give it a month tops before his ghost, and I'm doing air quotes here.
His ghost is haunting that area.
The rumors have probably already started
that now if you go out into the woods on a Saturday night,
you can see his bloody body floating through the woods, which is sad.
You know, it's easy for us to discuss ghost stories when they're hundreds of years past.
And it's like, oh, Mary Martland fell off this bridge,
and now her broken necked body comes and she tickles you.
You know, that's, you know, that's easier for us to kind of deal with.
But ghost stories do develop fairly quickly.
So I'm sure his ghost story is already there.
People are kids are like, oh, don't go out in the woods.
Ryan will get you. Ryan will get you.
And then of course you could always say, well, maybe nobody shot him.
Maybe it was some sort of ghostly activity to shot him.
I don't believe that.
But again, they, you know, that rumor will spread too.
Oh, they never caught the guys because he wasn't actually shot.
It was this ghost attack and blah, blah, blah.
The reason why I'm telling you this story is because I know a lot of you guys,
if not all of you are interested in paranormal activity, ghost hunting,
stuff like that. Be careful.
I know that when we did it, when we jumped in the car and we drove to other areas,
I always brought weapons with me, bats and mace.
And California is really hard to carry a gun.
I know a lot of you live in other states where that's far more permissible.
But my number one fear when I was going down to those areas was dogs.
And the second fear was hobos.
I don't know if anyone uses the word hobos anymore,
but you know what I mean?
The, you know, coming across transients.
My third fear was ghosts, the Blair Witch, Bigfoot, you know, the lizard man.
But, you know, just protect yourself.
That may not have helped it.
They wouldn't have helped this gentleman if he had a bat.
It's not really going to help him.
But, you know, there is a level of danger when you're going into an area at night.
There are all sorts of things that can go wrong.
Oh, and the other thing is when I brought groups and when I was running with my friends
in these areas, everyone had to have a cell phone on them.
And this was a while back, so not everyone had cell phones,
but we'd want to have at least three or four cell phones.
And sometimes I even had extra cell phones because I'm not going to get into why I had
extra cell phones, but you always want to have that line of communication.
Because really what you're doing is you're going out into an relatively uncivilized area at night.
And nobody knows where you're going because you don't know where you're going.
You hop in the car and you're like driving around and then they're like,
"Hey, yeah, let's go out to Old Potter Man's Creek and see if the ghost is still there."
It's not like you ever had a map.
So you want to be, this is my tips for ghost hunting,
for doing this kind of fun ghost hunting to stay safe.
Bring a weapon, bring a form of communication.
Have fun and be aware of your surroundings at all times.
That will at least give you a leg up over.
And don't go out there drunk either, because again,
I'm not worried about you getting drunk and getting assaulted by a ghost.
I'm worried about you getting a drunk and falling down a ravine.
Stuff like that.
Trust passing, I trespassed before.
I'm not going to tell you not to trespass.
That just comes along with the territory.
Just be mindful of your situation.
If the police show up, just be respectful and talk your way out of the situation.
And if not, you get the ticket.
You know, please show up.
You get busted.
You take the ticket.
If someone tells you to get out, you just leave.
That's those are my tips.
Like that will happen.
Cops show up and you're drunk and you're underage.
Now you have a problem.
Cops show up and you're belligerent.
We've been stopped by the cops before.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm just hunting for ghosts.
Haha, you guys are idiots.
Get out.
Okay, officer.
No biggie.
So those are my tips.
I hope that the killers of this young man are caught.
And I hope they're caught soon.
And I hope we hope they get swift justice.
And I hope his family finds peace.
That's a terrible story.
And I really hope people don't exploit his death to cause some sort of ghost story.
But knowing neighborhood kids, they probably will.
So that unfortunately just comes along with the game.
So be safe when you do this stuff as well.
So that's going to be it for today's episode.
I literally, there's a puddle of water on the floor.
And that is mostly my sweat and maybe some of my tears from having to sit in this hot, hot room.
But I hope you enjoyed my sacrifice.
I enjoyed doing it.
I could have done it later at night, but sometimes I like recording these day shows.
You can hit me up at DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com.
Join us on Facebook at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
We are also on Twitter @jasonocarpenter.
That's my real name.
We're just kind of keeping it casual with that one.
We got our YouTube channel, Dead Rabbit Radio.
That's where we take excerpts from this show.
Dead Rabbit Radio is a daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
We will be back tomorrow with some other great, mysterious stories for you.
and I hope you tune in. Have a great day!