My day sucked and I'm gonna tell you about some other sucky sucky days
I've had and then because this is a show about the paranormal conspiracy and true crime
I'm gonna tell you short story about a guy who gets abducted by aliens. We're gonna make it work today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. Yeah, I'm not having a good day
You know what the thing is is I hope you're having a good day and I hate breaking openings
I like to keep the openings the same. It's funny because as a listener of stuff of consuming stuff
You have a routine and you want to hear the same thing all the time. That's why I've never changed the intro
I've never tried. Oh, let's do something different like it's been the same since episode one. The only thing that's changed
It hasn't been the same since episode one the format's been pretty much the same
I've just kind of tweaked and I think we're at now, but I don't want to lie to you guys either
Today sucked so today's episode. I actually didn't plan on doing it. It's 9 30 right now at night
And I was like I'm not gonna release an episode not gonna release an episode and I thought
99% of life is just showing up. So just show up. You did say you're gonna take some extra days off this season because your
Vacation was kind of wacky, but just show up Jason even if it means you got to go a little off topic now
Maybe at the end of this I'll have a better day. Maybe the end of this you'll have a better day
Maybe your day suck you see the thing is just like my day and sorry this first part is gonna be kind of vloggy
So if that's not what you're here for if your new listener, I apologize
That's not what you're here for and you're an old listener. You're like Jason just tell a story about a ghost
Fast-forward or listen to it at a high speed, but if you just want to hear about my bad
Which I don't know if any of you do anyways, let's talk about it woke up. Did you jitsu and that one great?
That one totally fine no jiu jitsu for next week though
I had a doctor's appointment today that I'd planned the long time in advance. It snowed
I couldn't make it my ride couldn't take me to the city that it's in I
Ended up not going to work because of the
Doctor's visit, but then I could go to work, but I left my glasses at home
So I couldn't go to work and I broke my phone. I
Was goofing off and I broke my phone now. I have two phones. I have two phones. You're like Jason
It's not a bad day. That's not a bad day at all. You had the day off work and you didn't have to go to the doctor
There was snow involved so that sucked and you have two phones
I'm playing about breaking this one phone the phone that I broke I've had for like four years
I have two phones because one I don't even have it activated. It's where I put all my music on and
Then I have a phone so I never have to worry about listening too much music that my phone dies or talking to too many people that which never
Happens, but you know, it's also I'm on the phone on the internet the other phone
I'd use the listening music so it just sucked losing my phone and I just was having I came home
And you're like, yeah Jason you have the damn work. He didn't have to go to work boo-hoo poor Jason
I came home and I sat here and I just
Was sad I was sad
Didn't feel good
So I thought now I'll tell you this right now the bad day experiences you'll probably find quite humorous to me though
I was like I'm at home. My mom sent me a Christmas present. She sent me her Christmas
Jason that's not the definition of a bad day. You're getting Christmas presents
I admit the Christmas present had been sitting here for a while and I said I'm not having a good day
I'm really sad. I'm going to open up my Christmas present. Maybe that will cheer me up now mom
If you listen to all the episodes she doesn't she listens to one every so often if you're listening to this episode
I totally love you and I totally love your gift
But I do have to say that as I was already kind of sad
I owe you guys really Jason. You're so ungrateful
I opened up the present and I got a shirt, which is what I wanted. I got a sweater
Which I actually have that exact same sweater. They step those sweater stain real
Really easily you're like Jason you're super ungrateful. No, no, no, no, I love the sweater
I won't get a stain on this one because I have the exact same sweater with a huge stain on it
She buys me a pair of socks, which I asked for I said
Can I get some nice warm socks because she sent them to me about two years ago? I lost them already
She sends me socks, okay, and it's just one of those things
You know when you're already having a bad day everything is is seems to be wrong
She sends me there's these socks and I look at them and it's size
13 to 15 socks
Now again on a normal day if I had opened that up on Christmas Day
I would have simply laughed but because my day was already just a series of
Unfortunate incidents. I'm thinking just my mom know who her son is. I'm not Shaq
Who has size 13 to 15 socks and so they're pretty comfy though
So I'll give her that and then my mom and I feel really bad about this one actually my mom sent me two gift cards
and
Everyone else has no presents right now. They're like, I don't even have presents. He sends me two gift cards and
It's $15 each one for Dairy Queen and one for Taco Bell and I would looked at him and I'm like
But I'm on Keto too. I can't even spend these right now and I remember sitting back
So I'm so ungrateful. I love you mom so much. I remember sitting remember it just happened today
I sit back in my chair. I'm looking sitting back in the chair and I'm looking at these gift cards
I'm thinking I can take a break off the keto. This is fine. Like this isn't like super
This isn't a bad present. It just goes it's it would I'd have to stop doing my diet to eat these places
But also it's snowing. So I can't even leave my house
I can't even leave my house to walk the mile two miles to the restaurant to use these things today
You know, you know, you don't have to you don't have to eat today
But then I'm thinking well, this is my problem. I think if I'm gonna break my keto on day X
I'm just gonna break it now. So if I know that I may have a birthday party coming up or a
celebration Christmas party on Friday compelling podcasting. I know if I have a
If I have a party on Friday and it's Wednesday, I'll just go well, I'm gonna break the keto on Friday
I'll just break the keto now, which is stupid
But that's what I do. So I get a gift card for
Taco Bell gift card for Dairy Queen and then I order a I had a free Domino's Pizza
If for because I ordered Domino's pizzas in the past. You're like, he's no new pieces
You have to order before a corporation gives you a free pizza. So anyways, so I go I'm going to eventually
But go to Taco Bell. So I'm just gonna eat pizza today
I order a Domino's pizza and I just devour it and then I went and I hung out with the friend
I went took a nap because I still feeling quite miserable
I did end up going to hang out with a friend for the past couple hours and I came home
And that made me feel better and then I came home and said I'll record this podcast
So you're like Jason. Are you really gonna spend eight minutes telling us about how crappy your day is?
Yes, actually, well no because I'm gonna spend more time and the reason why and we're done with that day
The reason why I'm telling you these bad day stories is because maybe you're having a bad day today
Maybe you're having a bad holiday. Maybe you're having a bad holiday. So I want you to hear some funny
Stories miserable Jason stories that I think are quite humorous
So let's see if I can get both of them in and maybe it'll cheer you up. Maybe it'll make your bad and don't worry
I'll talk about aliens. I got an alien story at the end. Don't worry. Don't stop listening to it yet
So that was my bad day today and again, you're sitting there thinking Jason that is not a bad
You're not okay. So this was my bad day. I had jujitsu, which was totally fun. I got the day off work
I didn't have to go to the doctor's office
I ate a pizza
And opened a Christmas present and I'm like oh my day suck here check this bad day story out
So one day I was suit this probably about two or three years ago
So I was 350 pounds at the time and I was super poor
I had very very little to no money at this at the point of the story
I had a zero money all I had was a
Subway gift card that I think my brother gave me now
I didn't subway on before I had enough money on the subway gift card for one sandwich
It was like seven or eight bucks left on the card. No other money on me zero a lot of times people go on broke
They have like a couple thousand and savings. They're like whoa. I'm not touching my savings like I mean
I'm my checking accounts bro. No, I was flat broke. I didn't even have cans to recycle broke
So I go to subway and I buy myself a footlong spicy Italian
Which is what I ate back then and I have this big green jacket. I had this jacket
I think I bought it like shortly after 9/11 so the jacket is like 18 years old
It's this giant jacket with these giant pockets and it's just like just drapes over me
It looks like the jacket the bad guy wore and blade to so that's always I always pretend
I'm that dude. I don't remember his name, but I'm always hiding in the shadows
Distending my jaw so I'm why that was a good movie actually the first one is the best to play through it was terrible
But I am this is not a movie show. I'm walking. Oh, I saw the trailer for the new grudge movie that movies
Terrifying we'll talk about that later, but you're like no Jason talk about the now. That's more on topic
I'm walking from subway home and at this point I have like maybe 35 cents on my subway gift card
No other money. This was my dinner
This was the only food that I had available because I was broke and so I walk home
It's about a mile and a half again two miles from the fast food restaurants to my house
I walk home. I come into the apartment. I start taking my stuff off. I go
I guess I should have said earlier
I put my sandwich in the jacket pocket
put the sandwich in my jacket pocket and walked and listened to my music on my old phone that's broken out
Thanks, but the story reminds me that I'm well
I get really attached to stuff like that because it's been on so many adventures with me. I'm walking down the street
I have this sandwich in my pocket big foot long the its jacket giant jacket huge pockets
You're like Jason. I don't think you have foot long pockets
Well, the pocket had a hole in it
So it went into the interior of the jacket
So use basically like a normal hole like a pocket hole and then you could put your hand through the hole
And then you could be inside the jacket
So it's basically a jacket
It's basically a jacket with a giant hole in the pocket into the interior of the jacket
Does that make sense? You're all of you at one point said yes
And then so I put the giant foot-long sandwich in the in my jacket and it kind of is sticking out
It's sticking basically in my jacket. I remember one day actually got to tell this story too. I always put food in my pockets
I remember once I had this big jacket on and I just bought like three bean burritos at
Taco Bell I put them in my pocket put the whole bag in my pocket
I'm walking on the street this young guys walking on the street. He's walking towards me. I'm walking towards him
This is happening a couple years ago in Hood River - he's kind of like, you know, he's a tough guy, you know walking on the street
And I'm walking I'm like a tough guy walking on the street. We're getting closer and closer. I'm sizing him up like
Oh, you know, could I take him like what if he did this? Could I do this? You know what guys do and
Well, he's getting closer and then I just bust out laughing I start laughing so hard because in my
mental exercise of whether or not I could fight this guy and I imagined him
Punching me doing a gut punch and just be free. I was just shooting out of my pocket
It would be the most bizarre thing if you were in a fight and you just swung super hard and you felt just goo
And just a bunch of just refried beans shot out of a dude
Like oh no, he runs away. Anyways walking on the street with a subway sandwich. I get home
I go to grab my subway sandwich. It's not in my pocket
Now I'm thinking
This is the only food I have in the world right now. I have no other food
So I must have set it down. I must have like the first thing I did instinctually empty my pockets
I'm looking around my apartment. Where's my subway sandwich? It's kind of hard to miss something that is a foot long
But I'm looking around looking on the table. I keep patting down my jacket. Where's my sandwich? Where's my sandwich?
And after about five minutes, I make the grim
Not discovery I come to the grim conclusion that I must have dropped the sandwich somewhere again
The only food that I had in existence at this point with no money to buy more and you're thinking Jason
You could just gone a day without eating. Well sure good, but I
Really wanted that sandwich
And I go I got a backtrack and I'm thinking could I go to subway? This was my logic
I'm gonna walk all the way to subway
Because I obviously it's not before subway
It's not moving on its own and maybe I'll get to subway and I'll explain the situation
Hey, just bought the sandwich and I lost it
Maybe they'll give me another one because I was a regular there, but I was really obviously I was depressed because I hadn't eaten that day
I had no money to buy food
I was really looking forward to the sandwich that I could get with the little money that I had and
I
Had lost it so I walk and I remember going out leaving my apartment
I remember the sky being particularly gray that moment and I thought listen best case scenario is
It's laying on the side best case scenario
It's right there the worst case scenario is it fell out of my pocket while I was walking across the street
It's much of cars have run over it and then there's no salvaging it. I
Walked for a mile just scanning the ground
Scanning the ground every time I'd be like oh there it is. It's just a balled-up newspaper
I
Walk a bit further. Oh there it is
Just a watt. I didn't realize how dirty would river us until I was trying to find a foot long
Wrapping because it was in like that sandwich bag when napkins wrapped around it. So I knew it would be long and white
and walking I
get about a mile out and
I see a
Subway napkin on the ground and I go aha. I'm closed
I felt like basil the great mouse detective. I think his name was basil. I think basil is a
Not a fruit. It's a spice
And I go aha close. I can smell it. I can smell the pepper chainies from here
There my sandwich was a couple feet away
in the gutter
Just sitting there now now it had fallen out of the back
So the bag is just blown away at this point, but in the gutter
There is a perfectly wrapped subway sandwich with a napkin still attached to it the other napkin had blown away and
I remember thinking I'm very
Very very grateful that it wasn't raining because the gutter was told and you're like Jason this story is not going
Or I think it's going as I'm approaching my prize. I
Remember thinking well, it wasn't raining the gutter is dry bone dry
There's a couple leaves blown around the sandwich is perfectly wrapped
It hasn't even been touched not even a squirrel had come over in the half hour this whole journey has taken I
Felt like Frodo
That doesn't make sense Frodo wasn't looking for something Frodo was trying to destroy something
Technically Mount Doom was my stomach
This sandwich was the ring and now I was ready to complete my task. What's funny is across the street. There was a house
And I remember as I bent down to pick up the subway sandwich
I imagine someone in that house was probably watching television flipping through channels and
For some reason that had caught their eye
There was something white just sitting in the gutter a foot long white object sitting in the gutter and they're like
I don't know what that is not gonna worry about it. They're flipping the channel and then a short time later
They see a 350 pound man walk up
Stare down at the object in the gutter
Now like what what I wonder what that was
Guy reaches down picks it up
Looks at it and at that point you recognize that it's a foot long sandwich in the gutter and
Then you watch the three this 350 pound man
Put it in his pocket
And walk down the street dude that sandwich tasted delicious
Because I had to work for that sandwich and I was grateful
I was super super grateful that even though I had to go backtrack to get that sandwich
I was able to eat that night. That was a bad day
That actually was a pretty crummy day, but you're like Jason the poor you got the sandwich. Yeah
Yeah, but I felt so miserable even having obviously like I've been poor most of my life like right now
I'm actually doing pretty good for myself, but I've been there's been a most of my life
I've been like do I eat today or do I drink a Coca-Cola?
Like I've had long stretches of my life like that be and here's why I'm not very good with money
Like even when I was making good money
I made poor money choices now I make less money than I have in the past
But I make much better money choices not perfect money choices
But a big part of being poor is
Making good money choices. It's not gonna solve all your problems
Sometimes you are actually underemployed
But for me now that I'm making better keto helps a lot actually because I've just buy meat and bulk
Yeah, I make better money choices now. So I there's very it's not as likely that I'm completely out of money
I was completely out of money a couple months ago, and that's why Chris K
The founder of the Golden Rabbit Brigade. He's like he got a start a patreon and
He gave me some money because I was talking about not having food or something like that
That used to be a regular occurrence for me now. It's once in a blue moon
I I will always appreciate Chris K reaching out to me like that. That was great
But yeah, I would be like do I do I buy a dollar hamburger at Walmart today?
Or do I buy a Coca-Cola a refreshing cocoa?
It's been a lot of my life like that childhood and
Adult life like that. It's only been recently that I've been more stable with my finances, but anyways
That's why I just it was a reminder of just the abject poverty. I had placed myself in
But anyways, so that was a bad story. I think I have enough time for one more
You're like Jason. Do you have a sad story that actually involves you being sad at the end of it?
If you get it we want to hear a story where you're completely miserable at the end but a funny story
Well, here's another one. I remember this was Thanksgiving or the couple days before Thanksgiving
I was absolutely miserable. The weather was garbage. This was a couple years ago
The weather was absolutely garbage. I
Was miserable. I was homesick. I don't get homesick often, but it does happen. I was homesick
All my friends had moved away recently. I was very lonely. I wasn't happy with my life
This was way before the podcast. This is probably I think might have already said this was like three or four years ago
And like I did at this Thanksgiving
I generally will do Thanksgiving by myself. I buy everything and I think this might have been actually the first time
I was doing full Thanksgiving by myself. I think that's might have been why it was so miserable
I wasn't going anyone's house wasn't
Going to any like local relatives anything like that and I remember
But I'm really bad at like putting stuff in shopping carts
I'll shop just by putting stuff in my arms and then I'm like, oh, I need this I need this and eventually
I'm just like carrying all this garbage through the store now. I'll tell you this
it actually I
You guys might call me wrong on this my female listeners might call me wrong on this
But women seem to be impressed by you being strong enough to carry all that stuff
So
Men if you're looking for love go to Safeway and just grab bunch of stuff and walk through the aisles right now
I just heard the sound of 500 female listeners shake their head. They're like, no you look like an idiot when you do that
You just get a shot in the car
But anyways, I remember I was like, okay
I need mashed potatoes and I need stuffing and I need green beans and I need like these meat dishes like these turkey edible thingy
Well, there it's all edible. But like these prepared turkey thing
Loading all this stuff up and I go I
Need gravy and I don't know how much gravy I need it. So I got three jars of gravy
And I'm walking through the store and I'm like trying to hold all of this stuff
I'm trying to hold a non-prepared Thanksgiving feast in my arms is what I'm attempting to do
And I remember I'm walking through and I just was miserable. I wasn't having a good time
Super just disappointed in life and in myself. I'm walking but I'm going to have Thanksgiving. So everything will be okay
I'm walking and walking and then I hear
And
I turn around and what had happened was one of the jars of gravy
slipped out from my arm and
It made this
Sound as it did it was like if someone was trying to grab a wet melon
But made a glass and containing gravy and it smashed into the ground spreading brown gravy all over the middle of the Walmart aisle
And I just stood there and I was like oh great
Horrible and then I was like this is bad. So there's like junk chunks of glass in here
I remember waving over one of the employees and I was like, hey, sorry about this
I knocked this over or just fell out of my arms and the boys like I you know, whatever that's fine
And I then I debated should I go buy another one I already have this too and I thought I don't know how much gravy
I need for one - I need to put this stuff down
I just can't go grab another jar of gravy start walking through the store drop that one too eventually
There's just a dotted line of broken glass through the store, but I feel really bad for breaking it
It was just another reminder of how crappy you life was going right now
So I went I bought all my stuff I throw it in my backpack now
I have a tendency because I wear big jackets to put stuff in my pockets just like the subway story
Helps distribute the weight nowadays when I go shopping
I'll buy like two or three six packs of dye root beer or dye Pepsi and some of it
I'll put on my backpack and other ones I'll put in the pockets of my jacket or in the pockets of my pants
So I can carry a lot of stuff just distributing it. I'm like a real-life death stranding character
except without a little fetus attached to my chest the
It's funny. I've never played that game, but I think about it all the time
Especially when I'm walking in the snow how you have to keep your balance the I throw all my stuff in and I remember thinking this is again
When I was 350 pounds, so I was like I'm gonna eat I'm gonna eat on the way home
That's how you get to become 350 pounds because I was like I'm gonna cook this stuff
I think the food was for tomorrow or the I don't think it was Thanksgiving Day
It was this was the day before Thanksgiving. I was going to take this stuff home
But I wanted to get Taco Bell
To eat before I had to walk home because I was 350 pounds and that was a long walk
I carried as much as I was so I go to and I also I felt like garbage and carbs was gonna help me feel better
I go to Taco Bell and I'm just sitting there
Eating my burritos all alone
Sad not feeling good not feeling good about myself
Not feeling good about life, but as I'm eating these carbs
I'm on my phone like searching around on stuff on phone
Just reading funny stuff, and I'm starting to feel better and certain feel better getting distracted
Okay, this isn't gonna be so bad. I got a good meal in me now
I think that also had a lot to do with my moods. It was a tendency to go
I don't never eat in the morning
I never eat in the morning and then I would be like noon and I would eat something then I would tend to over eat
So I'd already be a little not feeling good from not eating in the morning
And then I'd overeat and then I'd feel bad after that, but anyways I
ate my Taco Bell
Ready to go so I get all my stuff throw away my garbage at
Taco Bell I go to put my jacket on and I have this tendency to kind of swing my jacket around this ultra
Dramatically way put it on jacket same jacket from the subway story to green jacket with a big hole in the pocket
And as I'm swinging the jacket on I hear a
*gasp* a boop!
And I remember just standing there with my back to what I knew was standing behind me
I immediately knew I recognized that noise. I just heard it about 45 minutes earlier and I
Understand physics. I realized that I had put the two cans of gravy two bottles of gravy in my jacket
And when I swung it around dramatically one of them flew out of the jacket
smashed onto the ground
And I remember just kind of just kind of hanging my head
Now there's nobody else in the Taco Bell except me and there's maybe two or three employees behind the counter
And I turn around and I'm looking at a smashed jar and
gray brown gravy just
And I knew from the experience of Walmart when I was apologizing to the employee there when he was trying to clean it up
How hard it is to clean up gravy
Super hard. You can't really sweep it up. You can't mop it up
You're kind of boned either way and I remember I picked up the glass immediately because I didn't want someone to walk in
And then I walk up to the counter and said hey really sorry about this, but I accidentally dropped a jar of
I accidentally dropped a jar of gravy over in the area there and
The guy goes oh, that's fine. We'll take care of it
I was like, oh, okay
So then I go over there and I kind of finish putting stuff on it and this is it's gravy dude
It is a danger. It's something that someone's going to slip on first off now
Taco Bell smells like great
You could the second you walk in or you're just in there. You just smell gravy
And I'm looking and I'm just standing there and I stood there for probably about five minutes of the people behind
People behind the counter weren't helping I walked back up. I go hey, can I like borrow a broom or some paper towels?
I'll clean it up and they're like no no no we'll get it. It's totally fine because this is the thing as I was leaving the Taco Bell
I go this this is the problem here
I'm the only one in the Taco Bell
Eventually someone else is going to walk into the Taco Bell and they are going to smell gravy which is going to be odd
That's the one thing you don't that's really the one flavor. You don't expect to smell in a Taco Bell
But then you're going to imagine this you walk in a Taco Bell in the middle of the day
You look and on the floor in the middle of the floor is a brown ooze just sitting there
In a place that sells no gravy
It's never had gravy ever in a KFC. You wouldn't even bat an eye
But you're at a Taco Bell you walk in there is a brown there's 16 ounces of brown ooze
Just sitting on the floor in front of you. What would what would go through your head?
Now I don't you could go. I would just assume somebody spilled gravy some idiot
Brought gravy into a Taco Bell and then spilled it
But I remember leaving and I thought that would be that would be so puzzling to me
it'd be the same thing as if you walked into McDonald's and
There was a chicken fried burrito or a quesadilla just sitting on the floor
You'd be like what where did this come from and it's just sitting there the employees are completely ignoring it
You would think that it was a Mandela effect now Taco Bell has always served gravy. What are you talking about? It's always been here I
Walked home now to jars of gravy short completely miserable again felt like
I just was not on a good path and I remember walking and I get to my apartment complex and right then I
hear a hey, buddy and
I look up and my buddy Jonas who had been in LA for probably about a year at this point
He just walked up to my apartment knocked on the door to see if I was there and I wasn't obviously I was
Contemplating my horrible existence walking on the street
And he walked out and he goes hey, I was just at your apartment seeing if you're home
I walked up to him. I just gave him the biggest hug and I'm like I'm so glad you're here today
Because that was the day I needed some cheering up. So now we're sitting at a fireplace. I'm puffing on a big
Pipe and you're like Jason
Those are stories. Yes, they are all sad stories. They're kind of funny. They're kind. I think they're funny
They're you're like oh, they're kind of funny
But they all ended happily they all ended happily that's I've had worse days than you Jason and yes
You have and obviously I've had worse days than the stories. I've told I could tell you miserable days
Where I've lost loved ones or people made horrible decisions that affected their lives or ever I'm not gonna tell you those stories
Puffing on my pipe because this isn't a competition. This isn't a competition the story
There's point of this odd episode where recording isn't I have worse days than you
It's that the point of the episode is one
there's an episode being recorded tonight and two I
Even when we have bad days
We don't know how they're going to end. We don't know how they're going today
I was really miserable, but it had a good ending the sandwich
Subway sandwich story had a good ending the the gravy story in the end in the end
Actually that one jar of gravy when I poured it it had three jars of gravy in it
It was a Thanksgiving miracle. He may know was it was just one jar gravy, but it was enough
It was enough for me. I don't know why I thought I needed three jars of gravy
so
You may be having a bad day. You may be having a bad weekend
But you don't know how it's gonna end so keep going keep walking keep looking for that subway sandwich in the sewer
Because things might work out. I think things always work out in the end. Sometimes it takes a long period of time
But things still get done. I planned on not doing an episode today
I 100% by the time 3 p.m. Rolled around I said nope not doing an episode. I am not doing an episode today
I'm so crummy. I'm feeling so bad. I'm not doing an episode today
Took a nap did everything to avoid doing it and here we are recording an episode and you're like yes
You know quote air quotes episode. Let me tell you an alien story real quick
You're like yes, you're settling in you're putting on your alien pajamas. You're like, all right. I fast forwarded fast all this stuff
For this I found a website. It's specific the part of the I'm sure it does more than this
But the website part that I saw was specifically alien encounters in the year
1988 so I got some good ones
Now this one takes place in Salzburg, Pennsylvania
You're like ooh, this sounds awesome March 18th 1988
This UFO comes down
It's shaped like a V flying around
Wait says on my notes. No sound was heard so
There you go UFOs falling down so this guy
We've got to make this quick because for a time you're like Jason. No, don't you dare make this quick
You just spent all that time talking about eating food out of the sewer
Technically was the gutter not the sewer but anyways, so this guy is traveling to his friend's house
It doesn't say if he's walking skiing driving. It's from 1988. What do you expect this guy is going to his friend's house?
The next thing you know is he's walking around in a grocery store. He's super disoriented. Oh, I don't know where I'm at
I'm super hungry. It's basically me. He's basically me two years ago. He walks in the grocery store
Disoriented he's hungry. He's thirsty and then he looks at his watch and he's like oh
My god two hours have passed. I've just left for my friend's house. I know it
But now I can't see anything
Low blood sugar. He's eating food eating Twinkies. They're like sir sir. He didn't pay for that
He's like a alien abduction get out of my way. He realizes two hours have passed now at first off
He doesn't think that aliens are abducted. He does remember seeing
Something fly over his car. So that kind of scared him then his car stalled
But he's like it might have been connected to that
It could have just been you know my watch broke and I'm just really really hungry
I aren't eating all this food dropping gravy
They're like sir. No, he's like, I don't know aliens are making me do this knocking gravy over
Anyways, it's weird enough. He can't figure it out that he goes to a hypnotherapist and this is what he recalls
He remembers his car stalling out in the middle of nowhere and then a fourth
This is quite short honestly a four foot tall alien
Wait, and he's not a gray because graze are normally short
But it's his four foot tall alien with like a long head and pinchers
Staffs have to have to have he walks up to the car. He walks up to the car. He's wearing clothes graze are always naked
I've always heard that theory that you know the the idea that aliens are
Demons that's a common theory, but the reason like reptilians will tend to wear clothes
The reason why gray aliens don't wear clothes because they never were exposed to original sin
It has to do with how humans ate the apple according to the Bible story humans ate the apple
And then they realized they were shameful because they were naked and they started wearing clothes
Other alien races wear clothes the reason why graze don't wear clothes is because they were never exposed to original sin
I should actually do some more research on that. I think that'd be an interesting topic for show
They're
They're they're pure. They're pure beings
They don't have shame in that sense that other species do but anyways
I mean nudists there nudists you can say don't have shame, but it goes more deeper than that into the psyche
So anyways this reptilian. He's wearing a purple robe purple bluish gray robe
I don't know where I got purple from forget. I said purple bluish gray robe with a fringed bottom
I gotta say this if a four foot tall alien with pinchers was coming at me. I'm not looking at the bottom of his robe
I don't know where that deal to detail come from. It also had an insignia on its chest doesn't get a lot of detail
This whole story doesn't have a lot of detail. This is where I thought was the most interesting and I honestly got a little too excited
Because I misread it here's from this report
The witness was then placed in a jar like object and then taken inside a large
Cigar shaped craft so now I'm imagining like from a 1950s comic book a dude in a jar
Like no, let me out
It's like a cover of like a guy in a jar banging on it
There's like an evil scientist or an alien standing over it pointing at it and it's like amazing tales 10 cents
You can't tell me you didn't just picture that
comic book cover in your head
I was like dude a guy being placed in a what's a jar like object. Just say it's a jar. I guess there
I guess a jar what he's in a jar of gravy. So now that's the cover. He's like whoa
He's swimming in gravy. There's a scientist
There's an evil guy pointing at a jar gravy and then in the background you see me running
He's see me running towards the jar gravy to rescue him to knock it over. But anyways a jar
I don't know what the difference is between a jar and jar like object, but anyways
So this guy he realizes he's putting a big old jar and he's like pounding on the glass comic book covers going on and
then
I'm gonna read this sentence the way that it's written
And then I'm gonna read it the way that I read it
And he'll realize why I was more excited about doing this story
So this is how it's written the next sentence and this is the last sentence actually of this description
Inside the craft the witness was apparently examined by several similar beings
So, you know, he's in a jar and then he sees a bunch of other four-foot aliens come up and tap on the glass selling
Now when I read it originally I was like hot dog and story is gonna be amazing and I did a bunch of other research
I couldn't find any more information about this encounter and what I just read you, but I was like this is amazing
I'm super excited because this is what I thought that last sentence said inside the craft the witness apparently saw
Several similar beans. So I was like, oh, there's other people in jars, dude
So it's like he wakes up and he's in a jar and he looks there's like
50 100 maybe a thousand jars of different alien species all banging on the side. That's so awesome, dude
He's no I miss just misread it. He's just in a jar. There's aliens poking at it. I was like, damn it
I was just reading it
Actually before I started recording this episode that you know what that goes perfect with my bad day because I honestly thought I was
Going to tell you a story about a guy trapped in a jar with a bunch of other aliens like these aliens were collecting species from around the
Cosmos and they're all putting them in jars and then 10 minutes before I decided to record this episode. I
Looked this story up. I read the last sentence and I went
Still an interesting story. How many times do you hear about people being put in jars when they're still alive?
But it would have been more interesting if there was a bunch of jars everywhere
So that's the episode that's the episode I
Liked it. I hope you guys liked it too. I'm having a better day. So I'm gonna go ahead and do my intro now
Hey everyone. Well, I forgot it now
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of dead rabbit radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day, too. I really hope you guys are I'm never gonna do that intro if it's not true
Because that way when I do it, you know, it's true
Dead rabbit radio a gmail.com is gonna be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend guys
You
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]