The world is full of great men who are not recognized for their greatness in their time.
They were once called madmen, but are now hailed as geniuses who saw through the clutter
and discovered the truth.
Welcome to Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Okay, so we are back. We're back for part two of linenmurdertruth.com.
That's the website, but the subject matter is the who shot John Linden.
I'm obviously, well I'm Jason Carpenter. I'm a little more awake now. I think I have some
sort of disease that causes me to be both sleepy and have sore kidneys. At the same time,
I've been battling both of those for some bizarre reason.
I went, I was up till one o'clock last night recording part one, part one of this and you
can see that as the previous podcast. And then I had to wake up at eight in the morning to go
grocery shopping. It was probably one of the most adult things I've done in quite a while.
I have to wake up early. It's been about four or five hours grocery shopping with a good friend
of mine. We talked a bit about the podcast. What did we talk about?
Uh, here's random stuff. I found out what a bully stick is after holding one.
It's a bull penis. I thought it was like a walking stick. No, it's probably about three feet long.
Kind of crazy. I didn't even know there's exist. Well, I knew they existed on bowls, but I didn't
know it was like a dog chew toy or something like that. So anyways, I got done grocery shopping.
I tried cauliflower rice for the first time. It was weird. I bought two bags of it. So I'll
have to eat the other bag, but my stomach's not feeling good either. That's kind of bugging me.
So we're going to go ahead and get on with this podcast on this beautiful sunny day. Then I'm
going to go take a nap. I hope your day is a little more eventful. What we're going to do now
is we were going, so we listened to his introduction last time and it seemed fairly rambling. Even
when I was listening back to it, I was like, man, this guy's really all over the place. That was
him putting forward. That was his best foot forward. That was a Steven Lightfoot, Steve Lightfoot,
laying out his best arguments for what's going on. Now, at the end too, I also said something about
being schizophrenic and or having mental illness and seeing connections where there may not be
connections. I wasn't trying to imply that Steve Lightfoot suffers from those things. I don't know
that is a symptom of that, of different mental illnesses, but I'm not implying that he does,
because I don't know. And honestly, maybe he's right. Weirder things have happened. So we're
going to go ahead and we're going to look at his about me section, which honestly is more fascinating
than his introduction, because we get to learn who Steven Lightfoot is. So again, I'm just going
to go ahead and do a semi dramatic reading of his exact words, because I think his words can
say more about his arguments that Steven King killed John Lennon and also explain just exactly who
Steve Lightfoot is. And I will say this before I get started. I at LennonMurderTruth.com, which is
his website, he sells a magazine, which according to him was referenced by George Bush during the
Bush Clinton debates back in what would that have been a 92. Was it 92? It was 92. So
I bought a copy today. It's only $10. I recommend that all of my listeners, new and old,
go to LennonMurderTruth.com and buy a copy of his manifesto. There's no other way to put it.
He's listed like a 25 page magazine, but I guarantee you this I'm not joking. This will be a piece
of history. It is a $10 investment for a piece of history. You have to understand this gentleman
travels the country, mostly on the East and West Coast, but selling these magazines,
confronting people and trying to build an army of acolytes to spread this truth,
we're never going to have the pleasure of meeting him in real life. If you know what,
honestly, if anything this podcast does, I hope it elevates him. But again, completely
honest, I'm not being facetious. I think it's interesting he's dumped this much time, this
much passion in a 30 year project. We're never going to meet him in real life. He is basically a
living meme that no one's heard of. You can be one of the first people to own a copy of this
magazine. I can't wait. I placed my order last night. I just got paid last night. I was able to
get the web, the web hosting setup for this. I did a bunch of stuff and I ordered his magazine.
Go to LennonMurderTruth.com. Check it out. Right now I'm going to go ahead and read his
About Me section and I will be back for a little bit of commentary when we're done.
Welcome. Side hacked, purchased button not working. Send check to below address please.
Hi. My name is Steve Lightfoot. If you would like to purchase my evidence,
directly please mail $10 cash or check to me care of. Steve Lightfoot is care of himself.
Steve Lightfoot, PO Box 7 3 11, 7 3, so PO Box 7 3 1 1, Carmel by the sea, California,
93921 or email him at LennonMurderTruth@yahoo.com.
As for the rest of you, thousands sold, no refunds requested. It's the real deal
talking about his magazine. If you would like to help me break this story and quadruple your
investment after I am look, check, take. Okay, so I'm gonna get back into character mode. We're
gonna do this shape. Here's the rest of it. If you would like to help me break this story and
quadruple your investment after I am looking for sponsors, I'm even looking for philanthropic people
who want to get some truth for their money in this life for a change. More details are found on my
new developments page, the chapter titled I Need Sponsors. My email address is LennonMurderTruth@yahoo.com.
Regarding what you may or may not have read or heard about me, let me assure you that it is almost
all jealous hogwash. The government has its army of character assassins who want to scare you off
of my findings. By mischaracterizing and marginalizing me with untruths and slanted opinions, I am 100%
pure American hero who discovered hard evidence in Lennon's murder and is brave enough to go public
with everything until the world knows and Stephen King is jailed for murder. Any other portrayal
of me is designed to scare you off of the truth I have uncovered. At present, 5/19/2015, I'm a 61-year-old
athletic, young-looking man who knows more about our sick plan than most of all of you do. I gave
up a dream of playing professional golf after my discovery of government codes and major news
magazines that linked our government and a horror writer to John Lennon's murder took over my life
some 33 years ago. The biggest news story since, I'll say it, since Jesus Christ has not been so well
received by my so-called fellow human being. In fact, I learned that when it comes to grappling
with our collective crime of killing John Lennon, all of you people act as though I have called
all of you in Lennon's murder and maybe that is really also the case. A phenomenon of guilt,
denial, and see no, speak no, and hear no evil on the part of all guilty mankind.
Even Paul McCartney has been exposed as the fair weather friend and a bag of what's he apparently
is just like all the celebrity hood and even my own family members who are also hypocrites. Of course,
Yoko is a government bitch who still babysits the cover up in New York like the Judas cunt
that she is and the US media is too cowardly to do their job, partly because the CIA has taken
over our media. Of course, you all may think all of this to be a little too rich and over the top,
but it is not. I am the messenger. Hi, my name is Steve Lightfoot. I was born in Hell in a Montana
March 1st, 1954, and I was raised in Northern California in a small town called Healdsburg.
Lightfoot is an English surname, and I am also part Scott, Irish, and Yugoslavian. My father was
a doctor and my mother a housewife. I have two brothers and a sister and I had a pretty normal
upbringing. I attended a private parochial grade school and public high school and two junior
colleges. My grades were good and I like baseball and basketball, tennis, and especially golf,
which became a professional ambition of mine while in my 20s to be a professional golfer.
This ambition saw me attach myself to restaurant work, cooking, waiting, managing, and I had a
large number of different jobs as well. It was while back east in Georgia that I found myself
both playing the bigger amateur events and working. I met a young woman at the time who proved to be
quite the traumatized liar. When we met she gave me a phony name and passed and lived with me for a
short time. Many melodramatic events, a breakup, and over a year later I would find out her real
name passed, etc. This experience made me different from most of you because I was no longer naive
about liars or lies. I knew intimately how convincing they could be. My golf career peaked,
missing a birth in the US amateur by one shot. During this period I returned to California
to study golf technique near Monterey. Just as I was crawling my way back to a golf career,
John Lennon was assassinated and I knew instinctively that the story about a lone drifter was
government media hogwash. That huge players were behind the murder and that America and all the
people of the world had just been victimized by evil bastards. Like most of you I assumed they
would not leave evidence the government rarely does, but when there was no trial for the alleged
gunman Mark Chapman, I knew almost for certain that indeed the government killed John Lennon.
He was the hottest political firebrand to threaten the establishment since Gandhi and
possibly Jesus Christ himself. Richard Nixon tried to illegally deport John
Law president, but that was at first a hazy fact that needed refreshing. On July 22, 1982,
a year and a half after the murder and weeks after seeing the tiny buried clipping about
Chapman's closed door guilty plea, I decided to reread the murder reports to see how Chapman skipped
trial. I burst through the library doors sensing drama and a sense of urgency and as I entered
the room I grabbed a year old copy of Us Magazine that happened to be on the first table I passed.
It had John and Yoko on the cover. I went to the magazine section and grabbed all the time Newsweek
and US News and World Report magazines dated December 15, 1980 I could find. Not knowing then
that those issues were released December 8, the day of the murder. I first read the Us
magazine article and learned that Nixon tried to illegally deport John in the early 70s because
of his high political profile in pronouncements against the Vietnam War and Nixon himself.
John invented the term "tricky dick" in fact. I then turned to the issue of time in Newsweek
and simultaneously noticed there was no murder report in the December 15 issues as they were
released December 8, the day of the murder. I also noticed that most of the bullpen headlines read
like a code about John's assassination. In time for example, "watching civilization slide into
barbarism and banality" all the president's magazines, "death trail, double talk, silencing an
almost free press, jailing the news, the FBI's show of shows, unholy ministry, a gambler's luck
runs out, death comes from the prime minister, defiant widow in the dock, who's in, who's out,
fitting together like pieces of a complicated jigsaw puzzle." It was the ominous headline "Who's
in, who's out" above just selected Ronald Reagan that made my heart sink. After all, Reagan was in
and Lenin was out. I then noticed the smaller headline below the photo, "fitting together the
pieces of a complicated jigsaw puzzle," as well as the fact that Richard Nixon's book "The Real War"
was in the foreground of the pictures at Reagan's right hand side. I pulled that book off the shelf
and literally opened right to the page where Nixon writes "The Trendies" who say "war is bad and peace
is good must be removed from the stage of public debate by whatever means necessary a flyswatter
are needed." I felt I had just stumbled indeed onto government codes about John's death hidden in
the headlines of Time Magazine. Newsweek displayed the nearly identical photo of Reagan and The Real
War above the headline "Head Hunting in the Pacific Palisades." I also found the same odd
behavior in the headlines. The December 8th issue of Newsweek printed a week before the crime,
was teeming with bold print in the window up to 75% of the messages plugging into John's
upcoming murder. Pages 30 and 31 which face each other, reveal the consecutive string of headlines,
"Odmin' Out," "Bad Blood," "The Nixon Factor," "Stay Tuned," "Intensity." The body of the article
had passages that read "abruptly withdrew from rising enemy fire." After he was shot down, he
graciously withdrew. He intimidated some of the older guys with his brash brilliance.
At that moment, at that moment I knew I had stumbled onto government codes in Time and Newsweek.
After an hour I became so nauseous I had to leave the library and get some fresh air.
That was the big revelation. Two days later I went to the larger San Diego library and found the
motherload of bold print codes and even told my girlfriend at the time that my life was in danger
and I'd have to move back to Santa Rosa near where I was raised to be safer. I first went to a priest
who advised me to use an alias and rubber gloves for a while. I hitchhiked to Santa Rosa and began
photocopying my findings and distributing them to the media using an alias and hiding behind sunglasses.
Weeks later, I found Mark David Chapman attached to a letter to the editor of U.S. News and World
Report printed three weeks before the murder where Chapman explained he is "armed, waiting to be moved
into a hostile square by the giant hand of Ronald Reagan." Any doubts I may have had were gone
and I almost couldn't believe it all myself. U.S. news issues also carried these codes about
Lennon's assassination but on a more subdued level. I would find that the codes only last for a five
month period surrounding the crime and found that the September issues were very sparse
but then a face rolled by on the microfiche and it looked like the assassin getting John's autograph
that the media show the world. I rolled it back and knew it was him based on the code headline
"One Great Big Zippo Lighter" which describes the murder scene. Then three months to come of a
man in a raincoat at night with a gun blazing fire in the night. I had no idea who Stephen King was,
the man attached to the headline and was under the impression that King was an alias. I compared
the face to the autograph, it was indeed the same exact person. The next day after I had calmed down
enough to actually read the article, a book review about Firestarter, I learned who Stephen King was.
At that explosive moment my first impulse was to credit Nixon for being a criminal genius.
Who would believe any of it now? Nixon, Reagan, and government codes and magazines were plausible,
not Stephen King being the real killer. I had a real job ahead of me now.
A brief examination of the article in King's writings convinced me it was all just too true.
Now I had to wonder was Chapman even a living person or just some convenient lookalike
dead Vietnam vet with no family that the government was using to scam us with a decoy?
I would later learn that Chapman was the son of a wealthy oil executive near Atlanta, Georgia,
much like John Hinckley who allegedly shot Reagan. I would learn that he was doing a stint in Lebanon,
supposedly at a YMCA in the years preceding the murder. I would learn that Chapman was living
allegedly in Attica prison in solitary confinement. People magazine even featured him with photos
taken at Attica in a 1985 article. People is printed by, you guessed it, time.
I think Chapman is only in jail for photo ops and to occasionally scam the other prisoners
that he is there at all. And that the warden on down are in on the scam. I just don't know where
he really spends most of his time. I do know that Hinckley, also an oil executive son, made the
paper saying he shot Reagan because of Lenin's murder in that quote "America's the land where
heroes are shot in the back. When John Lenin died I died, you died, America died, the world died."
Presumably as part of a mind control maneuver to suggest that one would have to be crazy to think
Reagan and Lenin killed. After Hinckley was found and saying no one was parodying that line of logic.
A few months after I had pieced together all the codes and evidence,
Terry Chodish of the San Francisco Secret Service surprised me with a visit
while I was at the Santa Rosa Library. He never denied my claims and even asked me what I thought
about Hinckley. At that time I was as ignorant as anyone else about Hinckley. He took some photographs
of me, warned me I could be arrested for any threats I might make towards these politicians,
and had me offer some handwriting samples and left.
I realized the next day that those samples might be used to forge a suicide note someday.
I called him back and complained emphatically. I saw him years later out of disguise, without his
blonde wig and blue contacts, with his real brown hair and eyes outside the federal building.
After the first meeting, my life turned into a political dissident hell.
See footnotes and new developments page of this website.
Along the way I saw my influence shape events in ways only I could see.
I'm amazed at how big a dent I have already made and yet I'm still aghast at how little
support I have received from my fellow man and Americans. My own mother and my siblings,
the one constituency who should have helped me come forward so I could remove my life from danger,
have taken a step back from my plight. I have witnessed the apathy of my country.
I've come to appreciate that it is fueled by their own sense of shame, fear, jealousy,
and I'll say it, misery. Everyone's afraid where political assassination is concerned, but me.
Even Paul McCartney who endorsed me live at Berkeley, see website,
has retreated singing "words of non-wisdom" lately.
Letting civilization slide into barbarism and banality.
His recent 2002 concert passed without a relevant remark.
I don't trust Yoko to do anything but protect the lie and her estate.
I feel sorry for New York City that they can't see through her.
I feel sorry for New York that they tolerated a no trial necessary remedy for Lenin's assassination.
No wonder America is in such shambles.
New York City is out of control and disconnected, living under government which
Yoko Ono's evil spell. I worry about all of you people for having to have me tell you why this
is important and vital to begin with. When I started I assumed everyone would know that this
expose will unleash more power to the people than at any time in our lifetimes. If you're not excited
by that fact you indeed need my prayers too. Thank you for visiting my website.
Only you can expose this story. It'll never be told until you people change. First, deep inside.
Don't keep me waiting. I need your help and support. Break this story, please.
So that is the About the Author section of Lenin Murder Truth. You know as much as I was giggling
and stuff in the front I'm obviously recording it and listening back to it while I'm editing it.
He comes across just so heartfelt and it's interesting because as I was reading it for
the first time and then again listening back to edit this there's like this looming cloud of red
because he's starting off he's talking about you know the finding the clues and then he talks about
his like golf career. He was he wanted to be like a what was it a pro amateur golfer or pro golfer
something like that and the whole time when he starts going off on this quest to find the truth
you can all he doesn't mention his family and the whole time I was in it I was like oh I know how
this is gonna end because this is how it always ends. The family at a certain point just has to
cut ties it's really sad. I imagine being Steve's friend early on back when this was all first
breaking or being his brother sister whatever but you know what I mean just having that every
afternoon him coming home before if this I can't imagine how this all would have played out if
the internet was around but he was like traveling to libraries and making a day of it and then he'll
come back at the dinner table and he'll be like oh man you won't believe it today I found these three
codes and at first you would be like oh okay okay Steve but after like what how long could you do it
for two three months you eventually you would start getting upset because he's showing you and he
makes references to this a couple time in these manifestos where he's showing you these codes and
to him he's thinking how is nobody else getting this how these codes are so look at this headline
right here kiss kiss bang bang uh what was the other part ouch ouch look at that headline and look
at that date Jason can't you see and I I would be like well it's a headline and the date but no
no no no but then you have to look at this headline and this headline and I look up those three headlines
and I go Steve I you know we've been going over this for months I don't see anything and how frustrated
you would be if to you it was a hundred percent in the clear this is what's going on
and you just can't no one believes you and worse people think you're crazy like legitimately crazy
again I'm not gonna cast I think this guy's a little wacky I don't necessarily I don't I'm
did not qualify to say that he's crazy these these beliefs have as much validity Stephen King
shooting John Lennon at the behest of Richard Nixon has as much validity honestly if you think
about it as 90 percent of the other conspiracy theories out there easily as much validity is
something like flatters easily you could say well building seven has video footage and stuff like
that but and and so it maybe has a little bit of leg up you know moon landing you can look at the
but stuff that is just completely like nope this is just because I think it is I don't know how
gravity this has as much validity as flat earth so you know it's easy to kind of poo poo conspiracy
theories just off hand because they're ludicrous so they don't make sense to you but it's about 99
percent of them are ludicrous and 90 percent of them have as much evidence as this one does supporting
it and we'll be covering a bunch of those so I've been researching conspiracy theories since I was
probably about 15 no no no no it would have been younger than that I remember and back then you
know I'm I'm maybe 20 years younger than Steven like but definitely older than the internet
the internet proper when we all had access to it I was reading books I'd have to go to libraries and
read books so I can empathize with this guy you know I'd go to books I'd go and read these books
about the Mimico triangle about conspiracy theories and missing people and stuff like that and I was
like oh this awesome and I was reading it as a form of entertainment and thinking maybe this is true
and being a little scared imagine though if that wasn't the case imagine if I was like no 100
these people are disappearing because of holes in fabric and I can prove it I can absolutely
prove it I'm reading all these books and every time someone goes missing I'm putting a little pin
prick in a door pin prick in a map and my family going okay at first they're like oh that's interesting
you know Jason kind of has an interesting theory and then at a certain point the family just has
to start going oh Jason because every time someone goes missing they'll be like god damn it I know
the second Jason gets home he's going to talk about the blue hell the blue hell the missing
people go to there is an episode coming up about blue hell but I just you know I feel bad I feel bad
you know it throughout his website and again linenmurdertruth.com go there buy his book
he's selling his cars he's constantly talking about being in financial debt he obviously has
he's held jobs in the past his website goes over so much in detail about not only is his political
beliefs and his conspiratorial beliefs but his life for 20 something years he's been
doing this almost what 30 now he's held on to this and you know like I was saying the
family backing away from him imagine that you had a cause a goal a purpose that was so noble and yet
every time you move towards it someone was grabbing your pants pulling you down grabbing your pants
pulling you down keeping you from climbing up that hill that you believe at the end is the greatest
conspiracy since the time of Jesus Christ and you're living in your van in Southern California
it boggles the mind it boggles the mind to be that devoted to something that
you know has evidence that you can see
I don't know it's pretty insane and I'm like he's wacky I'm not saying he's insane just the idea
of it and it's not what and let me back up I'm not being like oh I don't want to hurt his feelings
when I say that I don't know him I'll probably call other people insane and lunatic and blah blah
blah from here on out I don't he he has some insane beliefs I don't know I don't know maybe
there's a little bit of empathy for um I was talking more trash about other people on the
past couple episodes maybe I just have a little bit empathy for him just because of the amount
of time he's poured into this I don't know now I'm not so charitable I'm gonna give him a bunch of
money just because this I will say this I looked him up on YouTube and he looked way more normal
than I thought he would he describes himself as a youngest looking man I I'd agree with that
um but yeah yeah it's just it's just weird to me it's just weird and I guess that's what this
podcast is about it's just about the weird things that are out there that most of us don't know about
a lot of it's going to be current events a lot of it's stuff that's just going to be happening in
the moment water cooler talk but some of it's going to be a little bit longer and more in depth
with this I hope that you guys enjoyed this just listening to this my name is Jason Carpenter so
we have the new name dead rabbit radio we have our website dead rabbit dot com we were still getting
the pictures up for that but that is uh getting ready to go that'll probably be done this weekend
no let me phrase that that'll be done this weekend and then for right now I'm just using my private
email address because I don't want to set up another email address and then three months from now
not be checking it I want to have so if you want to email me um bas q u e 5150 at gmail.com that's
basque 5150 at gmail.com I you know now that I think about it I never gave that email address out
so how I got those weird emails uh it's kind of weird but I got other emails about this show
I don't know okay well I'm gonna go ahead and wrap this up I still don't have an ending yeah I have
a new title I like rabbits down the hole or I don't know man I gotta come up with something I guess
everybody has like a catchphrase right see you hoppin I don't know we'll figure it out my name
Jason Carpenter and thanks for listening to Dead Rattery