A man, a sandwich, and the ultimate murder plot.
Then we take a look at the bizarre disease known as visual release hallucinations.
What are they, how do you get them?
And did people in the past see cartoons?
It works, don't worry.
And then we take a look at a personal conspiracy theory of mine.
Why did the government pay for us to switch to digital television?
Was it really to give people a better viewing experience?
Was it a way to free up the airwaves for emergency personnel?
Or was it something to protect us from something dark, sinister, and headed this way?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
We're going to kind of jump into this because we got a lot to cover.
I did want to say this real quick though.
On a previous episode I told people to go see Bumblebee.
I think most of you guys know as most of you guys are reaching for the skip button.
Give me a second.
I think most of my listeners know I'm a big Transformers fan.
I did go see Bumblebee this weekend.
Check it out.
I enjoyed it.
It was actually quite different from the other Transformers movies if you weren't a
fan of those.
You know I described it to my little brother and I said it felt more like an early 2000
superhero film on the level of like the original Spider-Man or the X-Men movies.
The whole movie took place in one location.
Which you know what, and I have to say this.
I did enjoy the movie, but I have a personal bone to pick with the director.
The director of it, Travis Knight, is from Oregon and the movie is set in California.
But the whole movie I thought it was set in the Pacific Northwest because it kind of looked
like it.
It's just set in Hood River, bro.
If you're going to make a movie with Bumblebee and Optimus Prime, spoiler alert.
If you're going to make a movie with Transformers walking around on Earth, set it in Hood River.
Set it in a plate.
You grew up in the Pacific Northwest, man.
Set it in San Francisco.
No.
And you don't even know what San Francisco until like maybe the last 10 or 15 minutes
of it.
They make kind of an offhand remark and then they show the Golden Gate Bridge at the ending.
Set it in Hood River.
Set it at least somewhere that I can visit.
But I would have given my left arm to simply see a film set and see the Volkswagen bug
and all this stuff.
I'm like, "Transform, transform, the directors like these aren't real Transformers.
They're just cars, dude."
And I'm like, "Come on, you can do it, Bumblebee.
Transform."
But anyways, I was really, I mean, it was basically on the level of like Herbie or E.T. was more
that kind of story.
There weren't any of these huge war zones that are pretty typical for the other five
Transformer films, but there are some robot on robot fistfights, which was cool.
Definitely had a different feel, but I would definitely recommend going to see Bumblebee.
If you've already abandoned the franchise, but you still have a love for Transformers,
I think this movie will reignite it.
If you're not a fan of Transformers, but you're a fan of like, Bumbling Alien on Earth stories,
you may like it.
But I definitely liked it.
But I'm a fan of the source material as well.
And again, it really gave a new flavor to the story, to the whole thing.
It was weird.
I don't know if they, it was kind of a reboot, kind of a prequel.
I kind of feel they did some rewrites, because this movie was being prepped when Transformers
5 was being released.
And Transformers 5 totally bombed.
Well, it didn't totally bombed, but it didn't make as much money as they thought it was
going to.
So I'm wondering if they did some rewrites to kind of make it more of a reboot, because
it kind of had a toe in each set of water.
But in Transformers 5, it explained that Bumblebee actually helped fight the Nazis, and in this
movie, Bumblebee leaves Cybertron for the first time.
So, and, and I did a previous episode about the theory that Optimus Prime is a murderous
psychopath, and that's Michael Bay's subversive take on American politics.
And this one, Optimus Prime is not a total lunatic killing machine.
So, interesting take on the source material, Travis.
But I did enjoy it.
So, I wanted to go ahead and talk about that, though.
I do recommend saying it's a good Christmas movie, especially if you have kids as well.
Or you're a kid at heart.
And no, I'm not being sponsored by Bumblebee.
The, or who made it, Paramount?
I'm not being sponsored by them either.
I'm not being sponsored by anybody.
So if you want to sponsor me, hit me up, DeadRapRadiogmail.com.
We're going to go ahead and jump into our first story, though.
Our first story, this happened back in June of 2018, so very, very recent.
We don't have a lot of details as far as like what's going to happen with this.
But if you work in an office or you work anywhere that has a break room, we've all experienced
this.
Food bandits.
Human raccoons is what we call them.
Those of us who don't indulge in this.
You bring your lunch, you bring your food to work, you put it in the fridge, and then you
go later to open it up and get your ham sandwich or whatever you bring in.
And there's a bite taken out of it, or it's all gone.
I actually think finding it with a bite taken out of it is more insulting, because then someone
took a bite out of your food and is so callous they could put it back in the bag.
If you just go and it's missing, they're both idiotic, but if you go and it's missing,
then you think, "Oh man, someone ate my sandwich."
But if someone took a bite out of it and put it back, it's kind of like you're spitting
in your face.
I have been the victim of human raccoons maybe twice in my life.
It doesn't happen very often to me, but it has happened.
And I know a lot of people it's happened to constantly.
And the one, both times it happened to me, I was so furious, so mad.
I was thinking of ways to booby trap food.
I was like, "Oh, maybe I could not wash my hands."
And I was like, "Well, Jason, you don't do that anyway.
That's not a booby trap.
That's just normally you."
But you think of ways to dirty the food, and then you realize that you could actually get
in trouble for that if they get really sick, and you're like, "Ha ha!
I didn't wash my hands."
And they're like, "Jason, you never wash your hands."
I'm like, "But this day I was particularly messy."
This story doesn't involve a human raccoon.
It involves something far more dangerous.
So it's June, it's 2018.
We're in Germany.
So you know I'm gonna butcher this name.
We're in the town of Schlossholt Stukenbrock.
Actually, I think I got that right.
Anyways, so we're in Germany.
We're in this town.
And this dude goes to eat his lunch, and he's like, looking around.
He's like, "Good, no human raccoons have been here."
But for whatever reason, before he eats a sandwich, he looks at it.
Now I've never done that.
I've never been like, "Mmm, time for a good meal.
Time for me to turn this sandwich inside out and make sure no one's done anything to
it."
But for whatever reason, he gets a sandwich and he goes, "Hmm."
And he lifts the top piece of bread off, and he notices there's something smeared, some
sort of weird powdery substance smeared on his meat.
And I'm gonna, no sex joke there.
He notices there's something smeared on his meat, and he goes, "This is weird.
I didn't put this on.
I did not add any powder to any, any smellless, tasteless powder to my food.
What is this?"
So he goes to his boss, and he's like, "Hey man, there's this weird powder on my food,
and I don't want to get too like crazy about it, but I didn't put this stuff on here."
I don't know what it is.
And the boss goes, "Well, you know, we have video cameras in the break room, oddly enough,
and the employee's like, 'What?
You're spying on us?'"
And the boss is like, "No, no, no, no, no, just forget I said that.
But I won't go into this room that has all these security monitors that aren't recording
the break room, and I will then walk out with an answer of what happened in the break room.
And as the employee stood there scratching his head, I don't know if that exchange actually
happened.
I don't know why my boss's video tape in the break room, but they watch the video footage,
and they see another employee walk in, pull the dude's sandwich out, and start to sprinkle
a powdery substance on the sandwich.
And at that point, they're like, "What the hell is this?
What is this?
We should figure out what he did."
I guess there's a shorter way to say that, but...
And the two guys are looking at each other, and they go, "What did he do?
What did he put on the sandwich?"
So they must have been suspicious for some point, because at that point, if I had video
of someone spreading stuff on my sandwich, I would go directly talk to the person and
be like, "Yo, bro, what'd you do?"
But they actually had a toxicology report run on the sandwich.
And it came back.
It was something called toxic acetate, acetate.
Toxic acetate?
Acetate?
Anyways, the word toxic should be enough for you.
Acetate is a tasteless, smellless, highly dangerous chemical that damages your organs.
Now when I said they must have their suspicions about this, and that's why they had it tested,
there was a reason to be suspicious.
At this place of business, 21 people died before they were supposed to retire.
This wasn't a...
They weren't police officers.
This wasn't retire any.
This was people just dying in this office building, dying before they were supposed to retire.
They were older, but they were dying.
Two employees in a coma, one awake, survived, but on dialysis for the rest of his life.
So these people were suffering organ damage, and nobody could really figure it out.
They figured, "Oh, maybe they just hold.
That's what happens when you get old, your organs get damaged."
This guy is currently being suspected of killing 21 people, of poisoning their food.
And this one dude just happened... when's the last time you've ever opened up a sandwich
to check?
I don't even do that in Subway.
I don't even do that when strangers make my food.
I guess you get to see them make your food, but they could always put something in the
Chipotle Southwest salsa.
But you know what I mean?
I don't even check food that strangers give me, let alone food I prepare myself.
Bizarre story, but again, this just happened in June of 2018, so he hasn't been convicted
or anything like that.
Hasn't even gone to trial, but we'll learn more.
The next story we're going to talk about is another kind of short one.
And this one is a very, very limited, bizarre disease.
It's called visual release hallucinations.
It affects two types of people.
It affects people who have degeneration of their eyesight, so either it's called by diabetes
or old age, or, I don't know, getting poked in the eye multiple times, but not going blind
from the first time, it's just every single day a twig hits you in the eye.
The other one is very specific.
It's from something called methanol poisoning, which I never heard of, and it most likely
happens from drinking windshield wiper fluid.
Now I saw that, I go, "How many people are like, "Mmm, blue Gatorade glug glug?"
No, that's Windex!
But apparently, that's, it's not like in the top 10, but it's a more common than you
would think way of killing yourself, drinking windshield wiper fluid.
That's so specific that's not like drinking bleach or drinking ammonia or whatever.
I mean, you kind of have to go out of your way to say, "Oh man, I just can't do it anymore.
Where's the keys to the car?"
And they're like, "No, no, no, don't breathe in carbon monoxide."
No, what are you talking about?
I'm not gonna do that.
And then you're like drilling a hole.
I hate to be making light of it, but that's such a specific thing.
Like why would that be your go-to thing?
But it happens, surprisingly, a lot.
Drinking windshield wiper fluid.
I didn't even know that stuff was toxic.
I want to drink it, but I didn't know it could kill you.
Anyways, so if you drink too much of this windshield wiper fluid or you just get poked
in the eye multiple times or you just have diabetes, you can develop visual release hallucinations,
or it's also known as the Charles Bonnet Syndrome.
And this is what you do.
It's basically, it's a set of hallucinations, but they're increasingly bizarre.
The first thing is, is that you'll be sitting there and you'll see an inanimate object.
So you'll just see like a stool in the corner.
And you go, "That's weird.
I don't own a stool."
And then it's like, "Meow."
Disappears.
And you're like, "Charles Bonnet, sometimes you'll see people."
And I'm assuming they're not inanimate.
I'm sure they're like walking by and they're like, "Hey guys, what's up?"
"Meow."
Disappearing.
And you're like, "Ah, I guess I was hallucinating again."
Animals, again, you see animals.
Now what's weird is, those might, you might be really seeing real people and real animals.
I don't know how you would differentiate those from hallucinations unless they evaporated
or they're walking upside down or something like that.
But usually, I guess I should have read a little more of my notes because this explains
why you know it's hallucination.
Generally, you'll see them and they'll be tiny, tiny people.
So, you know, like, go over, I'm not going to talk about go over, travel again, but like
lily-pooshens, like little tiny people walking around, little tiny animals.
Actually, okay, so if you took a six-foot person, my height, I'm a six-foot-five, but
if you took a six-foot person and you made him tiny and now he's this tiny guy walking
on your floor, if you took a cat, that's what, how tall are cats, half a foot, and you shrunk
him down, would he be the scale work?
So if you saw a tiny person who used to be six feet and now he's, I don't know, 10 inches,
and then you took a half-foot cat, would he be also a 10-inch cat?
Because it's all hallucinations.
Or would he shrink down so he's the same tiny cat next to the person?
If there was no person there, would you just see, like, how cats are tiny anyways?
But also, another weird thing is that in 1760, they were talking about this disease, they
said, sometimes they were talking about the tiny people and then they said, quote, "physically
impossible circumstances," unquote.
Now in modern times, what people will see with Charles Bonnet syndrome is they will
see cartoons.
So like Mickey Mouse dancing in front of them, whistling, you know, on the steamboat, whatever.
In 1760, would they have seen a cartoon?
Do you have to see something for your hallucination to be based on?
Would they see, like, wood carvings?
Would they see, like, just a still image of a, that's kind of creepy.
You're sitting in a room and you wake up and there's just, like, a still image of a wood
carving man staring at you.
But that's actually more creepy than the cartoon.
But would they see, is it possible to hallucinate something that's based on nothing that you've
ever seen?
Could somebody, if I was hallucinating, if I had this disease, I may see Optimus Prime
and Bumblebee run by in animated form.
In 1760, I'm not saying they would see Optimus Prime and Bumblebee, but would they see a
cartoon run by them even though they had no concept of what a cartoon was?
How does that work?
Are all of our hallucinations, I mean, I know you can hallucinate fractals and stuff like
that, but that's more of like a mathematical scientific thing?
And you could say, well, I've never seen a fractal before, but once I started hallucinating
I started tripping out and seeing all this crazy stuff.
But could you hallucinate something that you had never, ever seen before?
Not like an eight-headed dragon, but I mean like the style, could someone in 1760 hallucinate
a Rob Liefield type drawing, even though they had no idea of what that would look like?
They had no idea of cartoon or comic books or animation or anything like that.
Could they hallucinate that?
I don't know.
Because if humans can create animation, then the animation is something...
If humans can create something, then that means the human mind is capable of expressing
it?
I don't know.
I mean, does a baby...
Would a baby know what a cartoon...
Could a baby hallucinate a cartoon without ever seeing a cartoon?
Because when it sees a cartoon, it understands what it is.
Therefore, the brain is capable of processing it.
Therefore, the brain should be able to create it itself without having ever seen it in the
first place.
Does that make sense?
I just...
When I read that, I thought, "That would be crazy."
I mean, think about it.
You already think you're going crazy.
You see your uncle and your dog, they're like ten inches tall, they're walking through the
grass and you're like, "Oh, I must be going crazy."
And then you turn around the corner and you see Donald Duck playing a xylophone and you
be like, "I have no frame of reference for that whatsoever.
I've never seen 2D animation before and here's this guy dancing around."
So it's super bizarre.
I don't know, but it would fit.
That would be physically impossible circumstances if someone was like, "No, there was a duck
and a mouse and a dog, but it didn't look like a dog.
It was tall, but then there was an actual dog there and the guy's doctor's like, "Dude,
dude, dude, just here.
I'm going to size you for a straight jacket and just move on from here."
So I don't know.
Sometimes it's just a flash of an image.
Sometimes it lasts all day long.
And watching a Mickey Mouse cartoon for 24 hours sounds...
I would just put my eyes out at that point.
That sounds like the worst torture possible.
Sorry, Mickey.
You were the boringest cartoon.
I'd rather watch Huckleberry Hound or something like that and that was...
Ugh, that was terrible too.
Okay, so our last story.
Now this one I'm putting out there with a caveat.
I have absolutely no proof of any of this at all.
This is something that has been like a half conspiracy theory, half really cool story
idea that's been cooking in my mind for a long time.
I'm always a little more nervous when I put out episodes where I'm like, "There's no
proof of this conspiracy theory, not because I just think it's gibberish, but because I
always worry that it's actually true and the reason why there's no proof of it, because
everyone who tries to talk about it ends up getting shot."
But I remember when this happened, I thought, "This is really bizarre that they're really
concerned about this."
So back in 2009, the governments of the world, the United Nations was involved in this, said,
"We're going to move away from analog television and we're going to move to digital television.
We're going to do everything digital."
And the US government had a program where they actually gave people money to buy a digital
converter.
I remember when it was going on and everyone was getting their vouchers and stuff like that
and I thought, "Why does the government care how good our broadcast signal is?
Why is the government actually giving its citizens money to buy a digital converter box?"
Now the reason why we switched from analog to digital, the official reason is twofold.
One, it's for better picture quality and sound and channels could broadcast more programming
on a single channel.
So you can have channel three and then channel 3.1 and 3.2 and all that.
And the other thing is they wanted to free up the analog airwaves for emergency personnel
and nobody questioned that.
And again, this was a worldwide shift.
The United Nations said, "We need to have everyone over to digital by this date and
countries all over the world switch to it."
Not all of them, some of them it was a phase in, but why did the United Nations care about
the analog signal?
Because the jamming up too much so a cop couldn't pick up their radio and say, "I need backup,
I need backup," and instead like reruns of "Welcome back, Cota!" are playing on it, it
didn't make sense to me.
It still doesn't make sense to me.
But here is my conspiracy theory.
Again, no proof to back this up, but it's just a hunch.
It's a fanciful hunch.
Whenever it shows a broadcast in analog form, they leave, they're basically bounced, they're
basically broadcast as like a circle and they spread out.
Now low power broadcasts cannot penetrate the ionosphere of the Earth and they just stay
trapped here.
But high powered broadcasts can leave the ionosphere of Earth and then they move through
space at the speed of light.
There's actually a really cool website, I'll link in the show notes, where you can see
like on this day what star system would be, what show this particular star system would
be receiving today.
And it's kind of guesswork.
But they're saying a star 44 light years out right now would be watching something that
happened 44 years ago and they'll show you a little YouTube clip.
It's just kind of a neat novelty website.
Because once it leaves the atmosphere, it's moving at the speed of light.
The first most powerful broadcast to leave Earth would have been, well according to Carl
Sagan, it was the Nuremberg rallies, Hitler's Nuremberg rallies, but that's actually not
true.
It was Hitler, it was still Hitler, but it was at the 1939 Olympic Games.
I think it was 1939, it doesn't matter.
It was at the Olympic Games.
Do they have Olympic Games in odd years?
I think they're, so whatever, 1938.
The point is, Hitler was the first thing to be broadcast that escaped the atmosphere
and went into space.
But right now, let's see, if we went 50 years back, that would put us around, you're like
Jason, don't do math right now, that put us somewhere around 1968, somewhere around there.
So they'd be watching footage of American Vietnam and stuff like that if they were 50
light years out.
The question is, really they say the thing is, the way that our transmissions are based
is because they're that circle, that "wum, wum, wum" and not a direct beam.
Even if they do get 50 light years out and picked up by something, it'll be very diffuse.
It'll be very hard to separate from background information.
Now we've tried to make a beam of information, the SETI, the search for extraterrestrial,
whatever.
They look for aliens.
They wanted to make a beam, a super powerful beam and they shot it up out of the atmosphere.
And they said this way it won't diffuse over the light years.
But if they want to watch the video footage of it, the aliens are going to need an array
that's 7 miles wide.
And if they just wanted the audio, because audio tends to lose itself more, or if they
want to watch the video with the audio, they would need an array that was 500 miles wide.
So even with this super concise beam, it would be really hard to pick up.
So our "I love Lucy" episodes, really they don't have a chance of being picked up.
So the first theory that I had was that the reason why I switched to analog and digital
was basically to go black, to go dark.
Cable doesn't send out the signals, streaming doesn't send out the signals, internet doesn't
send out the signals.
It's just these big, high powerful broadcasting analog towers that would.
And so if the government said, "Listen, we're letting everyone know where we're at.
And we're just sending out wave after wave after wave of information of where we're at."
And it would be equivalent of you're basically hiding in a forest from a bunch of predators.
You're lost in a dark forest surrounded by wolves.
And you don't know where the wolves are, and they don't know where you are.
And then you break out your boombox and start playing Steve Winwood top volume.
And now they know where you're at.
And you still don't know where they are.
Until it's too late.
They're too close.
So the first idea was they hid that.
That we're going to go dark.
And then you would have to roll into that, that all of this SETI building the beam and
stuff like that.
That's all fake.
They didn't really do that.
The reason why that theory didn't necessarily wash with me is because we have, I mean, assuming
that NAS is not totally lying to us and all that stuff, we've sent out satellites, we've
sent out voyagers, SETIs doing their thing and stuff like that.
But what if the reason why we switched to digital television is to not hide ourselves
from some other race out there, but to hide them from us?
Because it would work both ways.
If a broadcast signal was headed towards Earth, the analog stations could pick it up now.
And I did earlier say you would need a concentrated beam and a receiving array that's, you know,
5 to 500 miles long, 7 to 500 miles long, whatever it was.
But and that's based on our technology.
But what if their technology that's broadcasting is far more powerful and it could be picked
up by your local neighborhood antenna?
They're broadcasting an analog signal.
They haven't moved to digital and we've detected it coming towards this planet.
And the step was, was the United Nations saying, listen, there's one or two things that are
going to happen.
One day people around the world are going to turn on their televisions and they're
going to begin receiving these transmissions from an alien race or we just take all of
our analog towers offline and everyone has to do digital.
So those waves just pass right through the planet and we never know that they came.
Now there are still low power analog antennas in some countries.
There are still things like ham radio operators, CB radios and things like that.
But there's a big difference between having say 5 billion people watching a signal and
1% of them actually getting enough clarity of what the image looks like to be able to
make a determination like something's really wrong here versus 500 million people on their
ham radios, low power antennas, CB radios, what have you and 1% of them picking up that
signal.
It's a lot easier to hide if you just say, oh no, no, no, that was just some glitch.
But if some guy's just working on his ham radio and one day he picks up blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, he may log into something weird, he may record it, but that's a lot easier
to dispute than the population of the world picking that up.
Because here's the thing.
When we talk about aliens, we imagine them to be, you know, you have the fictional aliens
where they have their ships, they fly around, they blow stuff up.
And then you have the aliens that people say exist like gray aliens or reptilians or the
blonde white people, what are they called?
Illuminarians or something?
The Pleidians.
And they seem to be, like the reptilians are supposedly evil, but it's a very like antiseptic
evil.
It's a very like human evil.
But imagine getting a broadcast from an alien planet.
We think, imagine if an alien planet saw the Nuremberg rallies or an alien planet saw
news footage of the Vietnam War.
Could you even imagine the horrors that could come from an alien planet of their broadcast?
We always see the grays as kind of like just walking around the ship kind of tooling around
with instruments or the reptilians kind of like V where they're kind of like this regal
enemy that eat people, but then they also like walk on two legs and stuff like that
and they shape shifts and all that type of stuff.
But what if we saw a television broadcast, a true television broadcast from an alien
planet?
What type of evil and filth and truly like it's alien, our brains, even a reptilian is
familiar to us.
But something from another planet that is evolved along a completely different path
that shares none of our DNA, just like I was talking about on the previous segment, can
you imagine something that you can't imagine, that you have no concept for?
That's what it would be like to see an alien broadcast.
Would we even be able to recognize things like individuals in a crowd, some sort of
narrative, some sort of character?
We wouldn't.
You would see an alien broadcast and it would just fill you with revulsion because it is
something that is so unnatural for a human to see.
You can show me a video of grays dissecting a human being.
You can show me a video of a reptilian eating somebody.
Those are still familiar things because I've seen things being devoured and I've seen
dissections in the science class.
But imagine seeing something alien, doing something alien to another alien thing.
It would be the definition of HP Lovecraft's Cthulhu level horror.
Even if on their planet it was something completely mundane, to us it would be so disturbing.
On their planet it could be the equivalent of a sitcom, but to us we would see nothing
but pure horror in it.
Because what we're experiencing, what we're seeing and hearing is truly incomprehensible
to us.
It is on another planet with another life form, another culture, another language, another
I mean you could go there's you couldn't you could you even see that they were talking
to each other or would it just be horror upon horror upon horror imagery and sound
that was coming from this alien planet.
Whether or not they would ever reach us wouldn't matter.
But if we got this alien broadcast and we saw these incomprehensible inhuman things
it would fill us with such dread we would never want to go out.
We would never want to see what's out there.
Because we would know that the universe isn't full of life like us with two arms and two
legs and brains and eyes and they have power struggles and they're fighting for control
of earth and the reptilians are over here and the greys are here and the conformers are
here and the pleiadians are here and they have these structures you have the Starship
Athena you have all this stuff 2012 Antarctica ice bases all these things are human concepts.
We see the universe in a very Star Trek Star Wars type of way where you could go to a bar
and sit next to an alien and not throw up because he's so gross and the smell of him
is so toxic because he has a different evolutionary path on a different planet that you've never
been to.
We see it I'll be like hey Spock Spock would stink like a mofo Spock would be the most
disgusting person you could well maybe not Spock because he's half human but you know
what I mean like you would have these well you wouldn't be able to bang another alien
but you would have these huge differences it's just like we do it here when we build
a robot that looks too human or we make CGI that looks too human it's called the uncanny
valley it makes us sick times that by a thousand and you have what it would be like to look
at an alien broadcast.
So is that why we went dark not to hide us from them but to hide them from us because
if we knew what was truly out there in the darkness of space forget the probes forget
SETI forget sending these messages of recordings of Beethoven and pictures of a man and a woman
that would all be done in an instant and humanity would be that kid in a forest surrounded by
wolves and just trying to close their eyes and hope that they are never found.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true
crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to
it today have a great one guys.
(upbeat music)