Today we're gonna look at one topic but different sides of it.
Sherry Schreiner, she's back but we got the serious stuff out of the way.
Today we're gonna talk about the prayers that you can use to fight the reptile alien overlords
today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Garbinder. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Let's go ahead and move on to our first story. Now our first story is a continuation of the
Sherry Schreiner thing. Now on Monday we did the episode that talked about a murder that involved
two of her cult members. Followers however you want to describe it, disciples. She obviously
doesn't think she's in a cult. They don't think they're in a cult so whatever. But one of them
murdered the other one. It was interesting that was Monday's episode if you didn't hear it.
On Tuesday's episode we talked about the life of Sherry Schreiner in her own words.
She talked about her journey of being tormented by Lucifer or act technically. Lucifer is top
general from childhood because she is set up to become one of the main players in the
Battle of Armageddon. She is destined by God. God tells her through Bible codes. I didn't get
into that yesterday because it's just way too complicated. But God talks to her using the
Bible. She does this Bible code thing and finds her name and all this stuff in it. She's
King David's granddaughter. And she believes that Lucifer is using reptilian, alien, demonic
beans. They're all just squished into one. Just all those stupid things morphed into one big old
dumb thing. Floating around attacking people. Trying to soul scalp us and live in our body.
Trying to basically be the big bad of the universe. And it's her job to work with God
to stop them. There's a bunch of stuff too which I haven't been able to make heads or tails of
about how Jesus isn't really Jesus and Jews are terrible people. And I'm like I thought you were
Christian. It gets really bizarre but at a certain point I just had to call it. I had to be like
okay I've done enough research on this. Maybe someday I'll address her bizarre "I hate Jesus"
stuff. But let's go ahead and move on to this segment. Now this was again a thing I go this
I can't cram all this into one episode about Sherry Schreiner. Because on her website
she has a frequently asked questions. Which you guys are like wait no no it tells about her
eating Jesus thing. Maybe someday. Maybe someday. But on her website she has a frequently asked
questions. Which is very very common. Every website has these. That's nothing out of the ordinary.
What is out of the ordinary though are her frequently asked questions. Now obviously if you go to
Bank of America's frequently asked questions they're going to be things like
how do I set up a checking account. How often can I withdraw money from a savings account?
If you go to Alex Jones frequently asked questions there tend to be stuff like
who are you. The most frequently asked question would be like who are you and Alex Jones would
be like I'm this guy. And then you'd go down a couple questions and it'd be like
why do you think the Illuminati's trying to take over the planet. He'd be like well this is why
Illuminati's trying to take over the planet so on and so forth. Frequently asked questions.
The questions you get tired of answering all the time so you just put them in a form.
And generally the first question is the one you are asked the most. Right? Because you just want
to cut to the chase. You want to know how to open a checking account. You want to know who Alex Jones
is. Frequently asked questions. Her very very first question on the frequent and this sets the tone
for the rest of them. Her very very first question on the frequently asked questions is
it's actually not even a question. It's a statement which I imagine people were writing in all caps
to her and she goes I should create a frequently asked statement. I mean questions.
Very first one. I'm hearing voices. If that's the most frequently asked question you are being asked
and you're not a psychologist or psychiatrist you might want to reevaluate your audience base.
The number one question people ask and it's not even a question. They're just saying I'm hearing
voices and she's like yeah it's because you're under attack from the evil forces. Next one.
I'm being followed. Again not a question and it really you're like obviously the people that
are communicating. There's one of two things. She doesn't know what a frequently asked questions
is. Sherri Schreiner has no idea what this is supposed to be but she seems a little more savvy
than that. It could be she's tired of getting emails where people saying I'm being followed.
I'm being followed and so she put this up here. Spoiler alert. The answer to I'm being followed
is the same one as I'm hearing voices. You just pray. You pray to Yahshua not Jesus not Jesus
to Yahshua and he'll protect you. I'm being harassed. Now this one she gets a little more
specific and not a question. I'm being harassed. Ask Yahweh to stop the harassment being targeted
against you. That's reasonable. And to chain them and cast those involved into the abyss.
Bit of an overreaction. And though you're thinking oh she's quite cruel to people and I'm like no
no no you don't let me finish. She goes on to say if they are humans that are behind the harassment
instead of those reptilian demons flowing around. If they are humans behind the harassment.
Ask Yahweh to break their equipment beyond repair. No chance. You can't take it to geek squad.
Like this stuff literally disintegrates in their hands. It has to be beyond repair
and send them into derision in the name of Yahshua. Now I don't know if into derision is a thing.
Glarium maybe? Isn't derision where someone makes fun of you? But anyways that's her thing. Next
question. Again none of these are questions. I think I have chip implants. This is like
number five or six on her list of most frequently asked questions. Easy fix though.
If you think the aliens have implanted you with something she says you can deactivate chip implants
with neodym magnets. Now what they are there's little magnets that you put in your ear. Super
powerful apparently because we'll get to that in a second. You put the magnets in your ear.
You put tape over it and you wear it for 24 hours. I would do a side note to that advice.
Don't leave your house for 24 hours because everyone you see will go "what happened to your
ear?" and you just be like "mh magnet aliens put a chip in my head." Yeah you want to avoid that
conversation. So if you do do this if you put a super strong magnet next to your brain and tape it
there just stay inside. Next question. This is actually a question and this is a very important
question. It ties into the last one about taping magnets into your ear. Next question. I have
a defib... I'll try pronouncing this right. I have a defib... I have a defib... I have a defib...
I have a defib... you know okay that stupid thing. The thing that um... defib... the thing that um...
defibb... this isn't a bit. I can't say it. A defibbrelator. I have a defibbrelator and I'm
wondering if it is safe to use the neodym magnet on my body. Actual question. It took us a while to
get to one of these. Great question. This is a response. Neodym magnets are very powerful and
strong. I would not use them if you are on a defibbrelator, pacemaker, or any any type of machine
without approval from a doctor first. And the reason why I'm including that one in this list
is I would love to hear that conversation between a patient and a doctor. Dude as a pacemaker
comes into the doctor's office and says "Hey, I hear from my check up. Yeah, everything's going.
Doing a check and stuff out. You look great. Hey doc, before you go, I was wondering... I have a
question. Can I tape magnets in my ear? The doctor would be like "What are you talking about? First
off, no. You shouldn't even be around magnets. You shouldn't even be around people with magnetic
personalities. You can't even be around a Mr. Rooley toy. Not at all." And he's like "Ah, because
I think I got a chip in my head." At that point your doctor's writing you a referral to somebody
else. But I would love to see a conversation between a patient and a doctor about whether or not
they can tape powerful magnets into their head. Here's another great... Here's another... Again,
if this is a question people are asking, you're either in the wrong line of work or you are
having a ball. Because this is actually a pretty dumb question, a statement. "I have laser beams
coming into my house through my windows." That's kind of charming. It's kind of like so sci-fi and
paranoid and so ridiculous. Like I'm hearing voices. I'm being followed. That could be someone with
like a serious mental disorder. But if someone comes to you and is like "Oh man, you won't believe
my thing today." Laser beams came through my windows and started bouncing around my house. That is
beautiful. You know what's really weird? I just had massive deja vu. I'm pretty sure I told a story
or did a segment before about laser beams coming through windows and that whole setup. I think
it was either deja vu or I did that exact same bit episodes ago and I can't really think of what
episode it was. Weird. Like super deja vu. As I was saying it, I was like "I did this bit before. I
made this joke about someone going you won't believe my day." Anyways, this is her advice. The laser
beam messages come through my window and giving me deja vu. This is her advice. "Cover the windows
they are using to hit you with laser beams with mylar blankets. You can get them at Amazon for
dollars for 12. Really? What was this written? 1994? That's super cheap. Oh and then it says
"Also ask y'all way to break their equipment beyond repair." Yeah just do that too. Throw up
the mylar blankets and then pray to God and just make all of their laser beams malfunction,
which is actually very very dangerous prayer. God's like "Yeah sure whatever" and all of a sudden
the entire town gets vaporized by these things. So you're like "Jason, yes frequently asked questions.
It's all well and good, but you promised me. You promised me space brother. You promised me
how I could defeat the evil ones and protect them myself." And you're right I did space brother.
That's a term that's used on her website quite a lot. Derogatory too. There are no such thing as
space brothers. Only Yahweh and Yahshua can help you. I don't know how many people go around using
the term space brother, but anyways. Except for us now. Here's some prayers. These are prayers that
you have to repeat verbatim. Very very important because it's almost like a spell. You can't fiddle
around with these. These are prayers that you can use to protect yourself and to launch retaliatory
attacks. There are dozens of them, but I've selected two because most of them are really in the vein
of what we're going to talk about. The first one is a general prayer. It's just a general protection
prayer. We have just the standard "Now I lay me down to sleep, pray the Lord my soul to keep."
And then what's the Lord's prayer? "Our Father run in heaven, how would be they name?" All that stuff.
General prayers. This is her version of that. Heavenly Father. Bow your heads guys. Bow your
heads. Now first off, let me say after doing that joke, I'm not making fun of prayer in general.
I'm making fun of this nonsense. When I was preparing this thing, when I was like, "Ah,
maybe this is a little sacrilegious, but so everyone close your eyes, bow your heads."
Heavenly Father. In the name of the Lord Jesus Christ, weird, not Yahshua, but in the name of
the Lord Jesus Christ, I asked you in Jesus's name, so bizarre. I'm wondering if these were
copy pasted or somewhere else, because she doesn't seem to be a huge fan of that dude,
or doesn't use that name, but okay, sorry, it's not an interrupt our prayer. It's all in a moment.
Heavenly Father, in the name of the Lord Jesus Christ, I ask you in Jesus's name to please send
hundreds, hundreds, hundreds, and hundreds of millions of legions of angels to surround me,
and encamp around me, and set up angelic shields, protective devices, impenetrable force fields,
and angels to protect me against every attack of the enemy. In Jesus's name I pray, amen.
Please put upon me the full armor of God. Please put upon me the spiritual camouflage
to make me invisible to the enemy. Please put me upon the armor light, the breastplate of righteousness,
the shield of faith, the helmet of salvation, and the sword of the Spirit. In Jesus's name I pray,
amen. Walking slowly away from an explosion. Now the spiritual armor is really in the Bible,
like they do talk about that, it's allegorical, but they do talk about the spiritual armor. I've
never heard of the spiritual camouflage to make me the ghillie suit, the holy ghillie suit, so you
can like creep around as all the demons are like, where did he go? And you're just like disguised
as a rock in the corner, demons like, I'm gonna sit on this rock. You're like, oh, these guys live
to be quite long, this could take a while. But anyways, very specific. Set up some angelic shields,
that's kind of a sweet imagery. Protective devices, what gear does an angel carry? Do they have like
a Batman belt? And they're like, oh, better get my anti-reptile spray. Are they setting up like
little Geiger counters in case any sort of radioactive alien? What protective devices?
In penetrable force fields, is there any other kind? Who, who, who requests a penetrable force
field? Why do you need that extra word in there? What type of force field do you want? I don't,
I don't care, it can be penetrated, it doesn't matter to me. They should all be in penetrable.
Anyways, then there's a bunch of other prayers regarding a bunch of other kooky stuff, but they're
really, again, verbatim and, and I can't figure out, first off, I don't think I'm gonna be able to
make it all the way through this, but I almost feel like I have to because it just keeps getting
weirder. So this one is to break attacks on yourself. So let's say you're like, I think someone
shooting laser beams through my windows. And she's like, check the frequently asked questions first,
and then come back and I'll have a prayer for you to break an attack on yourself. And you're like,
okay, so you have a prayer to break attacks from laser beams in my windows, and she goes kind of,
I have one to break attacks on everything. You're like, that sounds awesome. She's like,
sit and pray with me then young man, heavenly father, in the name of the Lord Jesus Christ,
I break, crush, dissolve and destroy every satanic attack. And you're like, oh, that's cool.
Satan, Satan, Satan worshipers use lasers. That's cool. You know, let me finish. Druid witch attack,
Wicca witch attack, cabal a witch attack, wizard attack, shaman attack, witch doctor attack. When's
the last time someone has been attacked by a witch doctor? When was this written like 1600s?
Witch doctor attack, witchcraft attack. And just when you think, oh, okay, he's just going to list
stuff all is when I was reading and I was like, oh, there's like right when you start to lose interest.
She says vampire attack, werewolf attack. So now these things are real too. Vampire attack,
werewolf attack, Santaria attack, playing too much to blame, voodoo attack, magical attack,
which for some reason that's not already like bundled in with all the witch stuff, sorcery attack,
Luciferian attack, demonic attack, satanic attack, psychic attack, telepathic attack,
mental attack, remote viewing attack, mind control attack, radio onyx attack, psychotronic attack,
psionic attack, death signal attack. Why would you need any other attack if you had options
to pull a death signal attack? And what is it doesn't say just moves on to disease signal attack.
What? Use those. I'm not worried about the witch doctor attack. And again, if you're only being
harassed by a witch doctor, if you are alvin and the chipmunks looking for a map or whatever they
were doing in that movie, you still have to say please don't attack me with the death signal.
You have to do this whole thing. Scalar wave attack, tesla wave attack, laser wave attack,
see that's why we got into this prayer in the first place. We had to do all of that ELF attack,
RF attack, microwave attack, magnetic attack, acoustic attack, that's a dope name for a band,
infrared attack, and every kind of attack that I don't know the name of.
So why don't you just say please lord protect me from any sort of made up nonsense that some
lunatic could have gotten ahold of, found an ancient book or some UFO technology and is using
it against me. Thank you amen. But you have to list them all. Because technically you don't know
and that catch all at the end, I may not even know what it is that's attacking me, but I have to list
all of this stuff, but we're not done. That's just the first part of the prayer. So you're saying it
and you're like great I'm not going to attack by aliens anymore. Now I need a time wasting attack
as this person is still praying with you. This is the rest of it. Every person plays thing,
witch, a cult source, psychic source, machine, any machine, cash register or terminator, they both
apply, satanist, druid witch, wickowitch, cabala witch, wizard, this is, I'm not just listening
stuff, this is actually part of the prayer. First one was against the attacks, now we have to protect
ourselves from the people listing the attacks, which is oddly more than the attacks themselves.
Cabala witch, wizard, shaman, witch doctor, this guy's back, I want to meet this dude. Vampire
werewolf, they're still around, santeria practitioner, voodoo practitioner, remote viewing
operator, radionics operator, psychotronic operator, psionic operator, pine gap group,
who are these dudes? Who, again, right when you start losing interest, now a bunch of
made up stuff shows up. Who are the pine gap group? What puts them on the same level as a vampire?
Or a witch doctor? Pine gap group, never heard of them before, some probably some,
they're either one of two things, completely made up or some super obscure conspiracy theory.
I'll see if I can find more information on them. MIB, they're listed here, ACO, ACO,
PsyCorp, we're getting some acronyms here, so I'm gonna skip those. Military group, intelligence
group, army group, navy group, air force group, marine corps group, where's Coast Guard? Coast
Guard group? They're not coming after me, a bunch of more acronyms here, MI5, MI6,
Mars defense force group, and then finally the reptilian group, the draconian group, the gray
group, and the insect group, and every name, and every group I don't know the name of.
So just say everybody, just say please lord, protect me from every attack, from every person,
ever, please. Also, no more lasers in my house, and God's like, I'll see what I can do.
So, and then that has the standard like, thank you Jesus, I'll pray to you, just that's not
technically the end of it, but the rest of it is not funny, it's just normal prayer stuff. So if
you're like, God damn it, they said I really needed to stop the witch doctor sending laser
beams in my house, you can look it up in the show notes. But before we go, yes, there is more,
because we want to see how well these spells work, obviously, right? We want to see how well
these spells work. She has a list called "Fun Things to Do as a Warrior for the Most High." So
using the prayers she has taught you, and the knowledge she has given you to fight the good
fight against the draconian alien overlords led by Lucifer to herald in Armageddon, here's some
fun things you can do. There's 61 of them, I'm not going to read them all, because they start to get
pretty derivative after a certain point. So once you've studied about her, and you've studied her
teachings, and you've learned all of her prayers, you can say them, could you imagine memorizing that
prayer? I mean, the Lord's Prayer is pretty simple. It's not "Our Father in Arna Heaven,
please protect us from witch doctors and voodoo priests and kabbalah priests." Like,
imagine having to memorize that. I'm sure some people do. But anyways, you memorize the prayers,
learn the teachings. These are things you can do. Fun things you can do as a warrior for the most
high. Number one, their automatic doors and their underground bases don't work for a day. For "Yah,"
who's basically Yahweh, she's on a first syllable basis with God. She can just call him Yah. For
"Yah," to put them in confusion as to what's wrong with them, and don't let them be able to be fixed
for 24 hours. That'll teach those reptilian demons that are eating humans and taking their souls.
Their doors won't work for 24 hours. You'll notice a trend that all of these fun things you can do
with your special powers take place in underground remote facilities where you can never see if
they're true. So you can basically pray and then go, "Take that automatic doors and go about your
business and assume that somewhere down there there's a reptilian trapped in an elevator." But
you don't know. So that's the first one. Their automatic doors and their under... That's the
first one too. That was the first one she came up with. That's her most clever one.
The automatic doors and their underground bases don't work for a day. Number two,
the water sources get mysteriously blocked and stop flowing into the underground bases in cities for
a day. Now at this point I'm thinking, yes, reptilian demonic aliens are plotting the overthrow of
the planet and the death of God, but you know there probably are some like elderly ones down there.
They've been here for quite a long time and they're just kind of frail and they have like their
little hover walker and stuff like that and they're like, "Oh, I gotta watch the molding girls." That's
our version of the golden girls where they're just moldy because they're reptiles. It was a stupid
joke. But anyways, he's floating around down there and then the doors don't work and there's no
water and he suffers and dies. Like I get that he's a demon reptile, but there's demon reptiles on
defibrillators down there. And the doctor's like, "I don't know what happened. I tried getting in
there. He died very slowly. We tried giving him some water. There was no water and people are
going, "What's going on with the state of the art facility? This should be amazing. Why did my uncle
reptile die? He never got to see the end of the molding girls." Never saw that end. Number three,
their computer is malfunctioned and everything has to be reformatted. That's come on, man. That's
basic. Four, elevator stop working and grind to a slow halt. Wanted to be better that they just
stopped working and the people in them plummeted to their death? You're at war. You're at war with
these reptile people. I know it just builds up the image of a sympathetic grandpa alien demon,
but you're at war with these people. You want to just go to a slow halt? Five, this is actually
disgusting and this kind of sets off a trend. Their food supply gets covered in worms. Now,
if I came home and all my food was covered in worms, I'd be pretty grossed out. But if I was a
reptile, I don't think that would bug me. If I was a human who had the soul of a reptile, I would just
be like free grub, literally. Don't reptiles eat worms? Aren't you basically then they're like,
"Yes, our prayers come true. More worms!" That's what everyone's celebrating down in the city.
Number six, the power supply intermittently goes on and off of that warning. Again, poor grandpa
demon sitting in bed. His life support. So bizarre. But anyway, okay, seven, underground
vehicles, not vehicles. You can confirm underground vehicles get flat tires for no apparent reason.
Basic stuff. And it's weird because some of them are straight up like plagues of Egypt,
where you're making worms magically appear. And then the other one is some guy, some reptilians,
like, "Golly, my tire is flat and I don't know why." Is there an underground tunnel and they're like,
"Guess we'll just walk." Nine, we're skipping, we're gonna start skipping some now. Nine,
their consciousness becomes seared with the judgment and righteousness of the most high.
That's some ghost rider stuff right there. That's basically like people have a flat tire,
they're stuck in an elevator, uncle reptile just passed away because the electricity went off,
there's a bunch of worms everywhere. And then all of a sudden they're seared, all of a sudden their
brain is filled with the image of every sin they've ever committed and what the afterlife is going
to be like, that's a total like, that should be your first one. Not people like, "Mmm, I wonder
why this door won't work." And then they're like, "Oh my god, the righteousness of the one creator of
the universe." Like that would be the equivalent of humans being the whole Senate Cthulhu existing
in every human brain at once, would drive you mad. Not that, a flat tire versus that, versus eternal
torment in a split second in your brain. Yeah. Anyways, 10, all bread mysteriously becomes moldy
and inedible, food and machines won't work and the coffee becomes infested with bugs. That's after
the everyone's soul is seared for a brief moment in time with the beauty of heaven and what they
were never achieved. And they're like, "Oh my god, what happened? Oh my god, what happened? I need
some coffee." They go to the coffee thing, a bunch of bugs everywhere. Next one after that, again,
she peaked. She really peaked at nine. Next one after that, cell phones won't work as connections
can't be made and they waste their minutes and time in roaming into oblivion one. When's the last
time you ever counted your minutes on your cell phone? Two, she basically just described all of
their cell phone carriers being sprint. That's it. It's not really a curse. That's just bad
planning on your part of who you decided to go through for your cell phone provider.
Now we get into the poop jokes. Now we get into the poop curses. Did you know? Did you know? I
can never get that right. I can never do that voice the same each time. But did you know that
reptilians and greys, they don't have buttholes? That is something you learned today on Dead Rabbit
Radio. Due to Sherry Shryner, reptilians and greys do not have buttholes. They actually eliminate
their waste through their skin. So if you try wrestling one and all of a sudden it starts to
get slick, it's because it's peeing. And I'm pretty sure I did that joke before, honestly. I don't
think I'm having deja vu unless I'm having a massive stroke. I think I've told that joke before. But
anyways, reptilians and greys eliminate waste through their skin. This is number 12. Pray that
their pores get blocked and they become constipated. See how they like that. I think they would just
explode. If all their pores are supposed to release waste and their pores get sealed,
actually that would suffocate them as well, because that's how we breathe at least.
Oddly enough, number 23 gets personal. The guy who ran over Sherry's cat gets a
demotion for pushing her buttons. What? That's it. Just a demotion? They're like,
"You used to be the grand architect of hell. Now you're just the architect." No!
Like, that's it? All this other stuff you're doing to torment cities full of people.
And this guy just gets a demotion for running over a cat. Anyways, number 24 blocks sewer lines.
This is verbatim. This is not me adding anything in here. Blocked sewer lines. So the reptilian
turds will back up and float through every little nook and cranny. Oh yeah. Swim in your own
kaka, you slime bags. I didn't add the "oh yeah" I didn't add the kaka or any of that ending that was
all written down. But here's my thing. Weren't we just told that they eliminate their waste or their
pores? How big can their kaka actually be? It would be like smaller than a rabbit's.
But anyways, reptilian turds, which is also a great name for a man, will float through every
nook and cranny. Number 45, they start to feel the true power of combined prayer from the most
high people and wet themselves profusely. Not again just like they start to feel sorrow for the
path they've chosen in life. They just start peeing everywhere. That's the goal of that prayer.
And number 47, toilet paper stocks mysteriously vanish. 48, toilets and sewers get mysteriously
blocked and back up causing floods in bathrooms and buildings everywhere. When you have the power
of God at your disposal, what better way to fill the world with poop and pee and kaka from alien races?
I don't think I've ever found a more- this was all on one page. It was frequently asked questions
and I was doing the notes for that and I was like, "Oh, that'll be an interesting segment."
And then I scrolled down a bit and it's like spiritual warfare. I was like, "Oh, okay." And
then I'm reading those prayers and then I scrolled down a little bit more and it gave us 50 fun things
to do. And I honestly don't think I found a more entertaining webpage ever on the internet. I think
I had so much enjoyment reading this that I was like, "This is the internet to me." And what sucks
is this stuff is so hidden. There's- we can estimate probably about five to ten thousand people who
believe this stuff. They may not actively be following Sherry Schreiner, but I think that's a
safe estimate given how much money she raised with her GoFundMe, which was $154,000. It was over the
course of two years, but still they were all small donations. So I'd say probably around 5,000
people, 6,000 people, believe her and it could be a lot more. Could be a lot more. That's what I'm
saying, five to ten thousand. But to you and me, we read this and we laugh and we think this is
hilarious. I think it's hilarious. You guys may have shut it off by now, but it's just this odd
look at these beliefs these people truly believe. I just think I find it so fascinating that no
matter how much nonsense you can throw out there, people will still believe it. But what intrigues
me even more is that this story was submitted to me by Gary V. E-mail, just the Sherry Schreiner
murder thing in general, and we've gotten all this information from it. And you wonder how many
other groups are out there like this? How many other treasure troves of information do we have
that are just lost somewhere on the internet? I feel like an internet archaeologist.
I think sometimes it would be interesting to actually believe that this was real. I think it
would be maddening. I think if you truly believed that there are people who believe in aliens,
there's degrees. People who believe in aliens. And then there are people who believe that aliens
are demons. And there's a sizable amount of both of those groups. Millions, I probably say,
billions of people believe in aliens and millions of people believe that aliens are actually demons.
And that's totally fine. I don't have a beef with that, even if I did it wouldn't matter,
because it'd just be my opinion. But I think it's fascinating that they've, out of those groups,
they keep whittling it down to you have a group, a sub-sub-subgroup, who believe that aliens are
demons and Lucifer is planning to take over the world. And there's going to be a final battle
of Armageddon. And those are all really well-known conspiracies. But then they believe that they
are under assault because they are so important to God's plan for protecting the planet and the
universe that Satan has singled them out. We talked about that a lot in yesterday's episode about
the mythology we create for ourselves. And sometimes the mythology someone else creates for us to make
us feel important. And they feel important because they feel like they are on the front lines of this
war and they have this secret knowledge and they have these secret prayers and these powers and
they're making doors not work 300 feet under the ground. But come on. Like at a certain point,
it's so weird to me that people can watch your videos and people can believe all this stuff
and then find that page I just read to you and still believe in it. But maybe that's just human
nature. Maybe it's one of those things when you're talking to someone who has political beliefs
different than your own and you have knowledge that says that this political party has done this
bad thing or is doing this bad thing and you're trying to explain it to your friend and they're
like, "but, but, but, but, but," and they'll run those circles. They'll try to rationalize it. And
then after that conversation, you guys will go your different separate ways and generally people
will maintain the same political or religious views even when evidence against it is put forth.
Like factual evidence, not just feelings. Like actual factual evidence. So maybe it's just human
nature to double down on the nonsense. At the end of the day though, if you think about it,
is that if someone is having some sort of mental problem and they believe laser beams are coming
into their window, I'm either going to laugh at them, probably not to their face, or say you might
want to go see a psychiatrist, you might want to go check someone out. But to that person having that
mental issue, that mental disorder, whatever it is, Sherry Shreiner is offering a concrete answer to
that. Maybe that's the key. Maybe that's the key. It's not necessarily whether or not the questions
are frequently asked. It's whether or not the answers sound good to you and work for you in the
mind state you're in. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also
hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio. Twitter is @jasonowcarpenter. DeadRabbitRadio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
Bye.