A maid in Singapore teaches us to never, ever eat food prepared by a maid.
And then we take a look at a haunted hotel where the ghost of a woman and her child continue
to haunt it to this day.
But this isn't just any ghost story.
This ghost causes NBA teams to lose.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a ton of stuff to cover, a little old ton.
So let's go ahead and get started here by giving a shout out to our newest feature on
supporter, James Magrum.
James everyone give a round of applause for James.
He's doing the snake.
Yesterday the guy did the worm.
This guy's doing the snake.
It's kind of the same thing, except I don't know, snake ear.
James you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you have to work with a patreon, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That also really, really helps out a lot.
We help James up off the ground.
We dust him off.
We realize he's reptilian now.
We realize he's part of the conspiracy.
But that's okay.
We're still going to give him the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're going to fly on out to Singapore.
Durgible is flying over the Pacific Ocean, I believe.
We're headed out to Sengkeng in Singapore.
It's December 2018.
Durgible lands in Sengkeng.
We're all walking around wearing clothes from 2018.
Probably still own those clothes.
We're probably currently wearing clothes.
We wore in 2018.
We see a house in Sengkeng.
We see a family inside doing family stuff, playing with Parcheese or whatever.
Then we see a maid walk in.
She leaves the door open so we sneak in.
We sneak in behind the maid.
We're going to...
And then when we're done sneaking, we're just standing in our living room.
How'd you get in here?
We're like shh.
The family's like, "Okay, that's a little creepy."
But that's nothing.
A bunch of people appearing in your living room is far less bizarre than what's about
to happen.
Everything's alleged.
We'll start off by saying that.
Nare's Rowan Ola.
She's a 43-year-old maid.
But oddly enough, she's not this family's maid.
So even though we snuck in after the maid, she doesn't even know this family.
As far as we can tell, the police have not said that she knows this family and in any
way, shape, or form.
She's just a random maid.
She's the Uber of Maids.
But you don't have to call her.
She just doesn't fit your house.
Starts doing maid stuff.
She prepares food for this family and...
Mmm.
My goodness.
Bizarre maid that I didn't hire.
Nom, nom, nom.
This isn't suspicious at all.
And this food is the bomb.
And they're eating it.
And she goes, "Yeah, you can almost say it's bloody good."
If you were British, they were like, "Well, we're not British.
We're in Singapore.
So we're not going to say that."
And she's like, "Yeah, but imagine you're in Britain.
Wouldn't you say the food is bloody good?"
And they're like, "I guess.
I mean, now that you're saying it, I do notice that this is a little pinker than normal, whatever
this dish that I'm eating is."
I'm super delicious.
And she's like, "Yes, yes.
You could say...
They're like, "Quit making buns.
Quit making buns."
She's like, "Okay, but I'll just say this.
If you continue to eat that, well, then..."
She's trying to figure out how to grammatically make this correct.
They're eating this, this bloody good food.
And she goes, "You know, if you continue to eat that, I'll say that you're in trouble."
And they're like, "What?
That doesn't even make sense."
But, but now they're starting to put two and two together.
I don't think she made puns.
I don't think the maids did there and made puns the whole time.
She's not the riddler.
But what happened in real life?
She made this food for this family that she doesn't work for.
Maybe it was their neighbor.
Maybe it was her neighbor or something like that.
She made this food and in the food she put in her own urine, which she kind of got from
that joke, and then her own blood.
But not...
Listen, this might sound sexist, which is a horrible way to start a sentence that you're
about to say next.
This might sound sexist.
I get that it's the same, but with a slight difference.
She put blood in the food, but not just any blood.
She put in menstrual blood.
Which I get it, blood's blood.
But knowing there's like an egg in there, right?
There's...
My knowledge of human biology is non-existent.
But when a woman menstruates, there's a little egg, isn't there like a little microscopic
egg?
Because it's like all of the...
Basically, when you...
The fact that it comes out from your vagina, that doesn't bug me.
That's not...
I mean, it could come out of there, it could come out of your foot, blood's blood.
But I'm pretty sure there's an egg in it.
There's also, I imagine, like fibers as well.
Although I'll say this, if someone had...
If I had to eat two bowls of something...
This video's not getting monetized.
If I had to eat two bowls of something and one of them contained arm blood, and one of
them contained menstrual blood, and I had to choose one, I wouldn't...
I would not choose the menstrual blood one.
I don't know.
Is that wrong?
Is that my sexist?
For not wanting to eat menstrual blood?
Haven't mixed it with my food?
So she's under arrest for this.
She's under arrest, and again, this is all alleged for putting urine and menstrual blood
into their food.
What's bizarre?
I mean, that's bizarre in and of itself.
That happened in 2018, and she's currently like under trial, in January of this year,
in 2020.
Another maid.
In another part of Singapore.
Did the exact same thing.
However, she, her name's Diana, she put it in the family that she worked for, which makes
more sense.
She put in her menstrual blood again and her urine and spit.
As if that was the missing ingredient.
She's like, "Aha!
Memento blood and urine, that's what that other maid did, and she got caught.
However, I will spit in it as well.
I will leave that telltale, slimy little loogie floating around."
She did this in their water and rice, which would be soup.
I don't know if these people ate it.
I actually, let me scroll down on my notes.
They ate it.
That sentence was literally blocked at the bottom.
They did eat their food.
How did you not notice the rice and the water was pink?
Who knows.
But anyway, so apparently you have two people in Singapore, that makes it an epidemic.
That makes it an epidemic at this point.
Two different maids in Singapore are peeing and spitting, only one of them spit, and putting
menstrual blood in your food.
So now that's my new stereotype.
Someone's like, "Hey, my maid prepared- I'm not going over to people's houses."
And they're like these super mansions and they got maids.
But if anyone ever says, "Oh, my maid prepared this," I'm immediately going to overturn the
table and say, "How dare you?
You want me to eat menstrual blood?"
And I walk out.
Everyone's super shocked, but I saved them from eating a little bit of their maid.
Moral of the story, flip over tables in rich people's houses.
James, let's go ahead and fire up that.
We're going to rabbit dune buggy, because we're going to leave behind Singapore and
we are headed out to do a little quick follow up story in the middle of the desert.
Dune buggy's driving through the continent of all of wherever we were at Singapore.
I actually think it's an island, right?
But it doesn't matter.
We eventually get to New Mexico.
This is a story we have talked about so many times on this show, and I got to give a big
shout out to Misty Van.
I always mispronounce her last name.
I pronounce her right once.
Misty Van Appledorn.
No, Misty Van Appledorn.
I believe it is.
I'll find out.
She always emails me when I get it wrong.
She broke this story.
This is something that I'd been looking at off and on over about a year and a half.
She sent me a crucial piece of information, so Misty, you're a total rock star.
You guys remember the Sunspot Solar Observatory story?
We covered it back when it was happening.
Quick overview, back on September 6, 2018, this observatory got shut down.
There was Black Hawk helicopters.
There were FBI agents there.
Ton of conspiracy theories about it.
People said that it saw asteroid that was about to destroy the planet.
Remember when that happened, all life on the planet was destroyed.
Some people said it spotted an alien spaceship that was about to show up and start taking
over the planet.
Remember when that happened, all the aliens that go over it?
It's so funny because all these conspiracies, at the time, that week, people were like,
"Oh my God, this is totally going to happen.
All these observatories have been shut down around the world.
They were scheduled maintenance.
You had a bunch of observatories that were still there."
You guys remember that panic, though?
I always want to remind you guys of that.
Because going forward, when we look at these new panic events, remember the stuff that didn't
pan out, like Sunspot Solar Observatory?
The world was supposed to end all this past that was going to happen.
And then you had more reasonable things like Chinese infiltration of the facility.
The story ended up being, and I remember being very, very suspicious of it at the time.
I've talked about this over the past year and a half when this happened.
Was that a janitor was caught downloading child sexual abuse material, child porn?
And that's why the FBI was there.
The observatory was shut down because of that investigation.
And a lot of people kind of, "No, no, there's meteorite coming.
We're going to be killed any day now."
And obviously that didn't happen.
And then the observatory opened back up.
That was the story.
And I've said this several times on the show.
I was very suspicious of that story because it's a criminal case.
How do we not know the name of the person who was arrested?
I said that as recently.
It might have been, it was a live stream.
It wasn't the Thanksgiving one, but one before that, that I'll do Patreon exclusive live streams.
But I might have even mentioned an episode recently as well where I'm saying, "How come
we don't know the name of this guy?"
If this is real, if that's the real story, how come we don't know the name of this guy?
So Misty, the rock star, found his name.
Joshua Lee Cope.
32-year-old man.
Court documents totally explaining it.
I think this case is closed.
I think this case is totally closed.
The court documents have been filed.
This guy, Joshua Lee Cope, he's being charged with one count of distribution and two counts
of possession of child sexual abuse material of under the age of 13.
He was actually indicted back on July 2nd, 2020.
So it took a while for them to get everything put together.
Oh, and I should say this, he's walking free right now.
He's on bond.
So if you live in the New Mexico area, this dude's probably jogging next to you.
And he's not going to start trial until January 2021 at the earliest.
So we have a name now.
The reason why they shut it down was his laptop had gone missing.
And obviously he was freaking out.
He was taking his laptop to work.
He was a janitor there and downloading the stuff from their internet.
And then his laptop went missing and he started freaking out and he started telling the other
employees that he thinks a serial killer is loose in the area and he's afraid someone's
going to come in and start killing people at the facility.
So they shut it down and then called the FBI.
And what's really kind of concerning is one of the directors of the Sunspot Observatory
apparently discovered this material on his laptop, but then had more pressing matters.
Like you know, pointing a telescope at a son.
There is an alien ship coming in.
He's like, "Oh, the child stuff can wait."
But no, he just, I don't know, had to go co-olate some star charts or something like that and
didn't report it immediately.
So there we go.
I always said if we don't have a name of the person, someone's covering it up or maybe
that was a false story.
There we go.
Misty was the total rock star for finding that.
And in the show notes you can see all the documents, the court documents and everything
like that.
I also want to say this too, since we're on the subject of telescopes, James drive us
now in that dead rabbit dune buggy down to Puerto Rico.
I was actually talking to Kristen Davidson about this.
Another listener of the show.
Thank you very much, Kristen.
Arcebo Telescope.
This is another follow-up.
I did a story earlier in the year.
A cable broke loose and smashed the Arcebo Telescope.
That telescope for us, for us paranormal alien nerds is important because that's where the
telescope is built to do a bunch of science nerdy stuff that we don't care about, but it's
also built to detect asteroids coming in.
That's cool because stuff blows up.
And it was used for SETI, the search for extraterrestrial intelligence.
It was used to broadcast the Arcebo message, which is one of the very famous messages we've
sent out in space.
The Voyager disks is one of them and then this one.
Kind of showed a little map of our solar system and a bit of our DNA.
It was like this digital beam, digital code and information that we shot out of the Arcebo
Telescope.
It's very, very popular in the paranormal alien community.
It's also in the movie Contact.
No one cares about that.
It's also in the movie The Losers.
You guys should watch The Losers, dude.
That movie's dope.
That movie's really, really good.
It had Chris Evans and Jeffrey Dean Morgan and I think Zoe Saldana.
And it was based on a DC comic book.
It was really good.
It's totally slept on.
You want a good action movie, watch The Losers, but the Loser has nothing to do with the
Arcebo Telescope.
A quick update to that.
We did a story where a cable smashed open that thing and they didn't know how the cable
snapped.
I remember saying maybe aliens did it.
They were just putting on our conspiracy caps.
There was some sort of conspiracy saying maybe they were just smashing it so we didn't get
any information.
You know, it's funny because I'm poo pooing the sunspot thing and I'm like, "But this
one!"
But you know, we're just having fun putting on our conspiracy cap for that one.
A cable smashed that dish and scientists were like, "We don't know if we can fix this,
but I'm sure we can.
You know, we don't have a lot of funding to begin with, but we'll figure something out."
It's done.
The Arcebo Telescope is completely destroyed at this point.
Just a couple weeks ago, I guess, one of the main cables, as they were inspecting and they're
like, "We could probably figure this out."
One of the main cables snapped and completely smashed the telescope.
And they can't even, they can't even get near it to see what they can do to fix it now.
And again, though, with the main, they're like, "We didn't expect it."
It was one of the big support systems for this.
It shouldn't have broke.
Still mysterious how the first one broke.
This one's mysterious how this one broke.
But it's done.
At this point, they're saying there's no way they can fix it.
It's the area that's already battered by hurricanes.
It's surprising that it lasted as long as it did.
And then we have these two mysterious cable snaps in a couple months.
But that sucks because that is kind of a main state of, and it sucks, obviously, for science
and all that stuff.
But for us, it sucks because it is a kind of iconic symbol of extraterrestrial contact.
So yeah, unfortunately, everyone pour a little liquor out for Arecibo Telescope.
That is, as of now, finished.
So that is our new segment.
We have Telescope Tuesdays.
It's a new thing we're doing every Tuesday.
I'm going to provide you a new story about a telescope.
James, let's toss you the keys to the carpenter copter.
We are leaving behind the sad little Arecibo telescope.
Maybe someone will figure out a way to take care of it.
We are headed out to Oklahoma City.
James, I want you to land that carpenter copter right in front of the Skirvin Hilton Hotel.
We're knocking over much of Valhalla's, crushing cars, and stuff like that.
We all jump out.
We laugh at the wreckage we've caused.
And then we blame it on James and his little copter arresting him.
We're like, thanks for supporting the page, Ian.
He'll figure a way out.
We walk into the Skirvin Hotel.
Now I got most of my information for this story from an article written by John Branch
for the New York Times called "Fright Nights in the NBA."
Very, very good article.
A lot of good research in this.
So thank you very much, John.
And right when I finished that, we see James is shaking off the cops and is now walking
in the hotel behind us.
The Skirvin Hotel was built in 1911.
And then, you know, like all businesses has its ups and its downs, but eventually the
Skirvin Hotel went out of operation.
Just kind of sat there in the middle of Oklahoma City.
It's a national landmark, so they couldn't really do anything with it.
But you know, you kind of want to do something with it.
You just don't want to leave a big old abandoned building in prime real estate.
So the city gets together with these private partners and they go, "Let's revitalize this
hotel.
We'll restore it to its natural beauty and actually make it a working hotel again."
So in 2007, they do that.
They're able to revitalize that hotel and they knocked down all much of walls.
Originally it had like 500 rooms.
Now it has 225 rooms.
It's a luxurious hotel with these giant rooms.
And so of course, people who visit the town are going to want to go there.
And it's a perfect spot, because it's so luxurious, that if you are a visiting NBA team and you're
coming to play the Oklahoma City Thunder, you know, it'll put you up in the old Skirvin
Hilton Hotel.
It's beautiful.
You got like royalty staying here.
I guess I didn't look that up, but I'm sure at least one royal member stayed there.
Very, very expensive hotel.
NBA teams come there.
They stay there and then the next day they're playing the Thunder and then they go home.
And that just kind of is how it works.
They go home.
They go on to the next game.
They're like, "Aw, man.
That was the only game I got to play this year."
And then they go and they sit in their mansion.
No, they continue on with their career.
But they come to Oklahoma City, stay in the Skirvin Hotel, play Oklahoma City Thunder,
and then move on.
In 2010, a story appeared that was a little unexpected.
And it's one of those things where coaches are just like shaking their head.
They're like, "Dude, no.
Don't, don't quit saying that.
Quit saying that in interviews."
The Knicks are there to play the Oklahoma City Thunder and they lose.
They lose the game.
And the next day reporters are like, "Hey, why'd you lose that game?
Why'd you lose that game?
I had $20 on that game."
And you had a couple Knicks players go, "We didn't sleep well the night before."
Which sounds like just a normal excuse.
But then they go, "We didn't sleep well because of the ghost."
There's a ghost walking around the hotel and people are like, "What?"
And they're like, "Yeah.
That hotel is super haunted.
I hate that hotel.
I hated it before.
This isn't the first time I've been in that hotel.
There's a bunch of ghosts running around."
The reporters are like, "What are you doing?
You really blame me the loss of a game on a ghost?"
You had ESPN analyst Bill Simmons go, "Oh, no.
Skirvin Hotel?
Yeah, no.
I was there because I had to cover a game for the Oklahoma City Thunder.
Super Haunted."
What are you talking about?"
He's like, "No, no, no.
I woke up in the middle of the night.
Lights off.
Totally luxurious bed.
Great sheets and stuff like that.
Apparently this has become an ad for Skirvin Hilton.
But I woke up in the middle of the night.
I heard the sound of a baby crying.
And not like a baby crying in the room next to me.
A baby in my room.
I don't have a baby.
I don't know.
Bill Simmons might have kids, but he didn't have a baby with him.
If you're like, "Why are you talking about?"
So looking into this, a ton of NBA players complain about this hotel.
It's a known secret in the NBA that it's haunted.
Now, coaches are like, it's utter nonsense.
Some of the coaches will be like, "I don't know what you're talking about.
It's their eyes shift from side to side."
Other ones go, "Listen, NBA players, athletes in general are very superstitious.
Very superstitious.
They have these rituals before they do games."
So it's not surprising that the players would believe in ghosts because they're superstitious.
So the coaches are kind of blowing it off.
They're like, "Guys, just focus on the game.
Don't focus on Bloody Mary and the mayor."
The players are like, "Bloody Mary's real."
The coach is like, "Dang it, why did I even bring that up?"
You had other reports in this hotel, so it's not just babies crying in your room.
That seems to be a common theme.
A lot of people are waking up to babies crying.
But you had NBA players saying that they woke up to the sound of a slamming door.
And when they jumped up out of bed, their bathroom door that they had left open was now
shut.
Spooky, but you know the wind, something like that.
Some guys say that when they're walking around the hotel, they can hear a whisper of a voice
in their ear, a woman's voice, propositioning them.
"Hey, big boy, you want to dribble that ball down my court?"
I don't know.
Obviously, I'm not a woman picking up a basketball star.
I guess the obvious one was, "Hey, boy, how about you put that ball in my hoop?"
But it's still that soup.
That's like not sexy at all.
Anyways, NBA, I don't know if she's actually making NBA puns.
I don't know if she's actually making NBA puns while she's doing it.
Oh, looks like you are a straightforward, I don't know about basketball to even make
these jokes.
Anyways, that could be imagination or wishful thinking.
This woman, this ghost, will get into her legend, but I just want to creep you out even
more.
People say, it's always men who see this.
Which is, again, a really odd thing.
Yesterday we covered all the men drowning at that lake in Zimbabwe, or that river in
Zimbabwe.
This one, it's always men who are seeing this, experiencing this.
They'll be taking a shower.
I have a love-hate relationship with this one, because I've always said the scariest place
a ghost can appear is in your bathroom, because it's super dangerous to be in your bathroom
anyways.
But I'm thinking of me taking a shower and me turning around, and I have that old shower
curtain, and on the other side of it I see a silhouette standing outside of it.
That's what I think of when I think of a ghost in a shower.
This one you're taking a shower and you turn around and there's a naked woman.
There's a naked woman ghost behind you.
So I gotta say, I gotta say, yes, ghosts in the shower are super terrifying, but if I
was taking a shower and there was a silhouette outside of my shower curtain, immediately
I'd be like, "Huh?"
But then if the drapes, the curtain moves aside and the super sexy ghost gets in, I'm
gonna be a little more relieved at that point.
I'm gonna be like, "Oh."
But probably not as still an undead wraith in your bathroom as just a hot one.
That one's a little harder to chalk up to.
The wind did it.
Rusty pipes or something like that.
World meta piece.
Basketball player, formerly known as Ron Arntest.
He actually wanted to sue the hotel because of this.
Because he said he was sexually assaulted.
I wasn't able to find details on it, but apparently he actually tried to sue them.
He was so outraged by whatever this ghost woman did to him that he tried to sue the hotel.
So that's interesting.
What all this means really is, this is fascinating because we rarely see ghostly events have
this sort of impact, Oklahoma City Thunder has the second most winningest records for
home games.
In the entire league.
If you're playing Oklahoma City and you're playing against them in their city, you are
most likely going to lose that game.
So the fact that this place is haunted and that is where they are putting up the NBA
teams from out of town, that's hilarious.
Because it's actually probably helping them win.
You don't get a good night's sleep.
You do get a good night's sleep.
The guy next to you, the guy in the room next to you, didn't get a good night's sleep.
Doesn't want to take a shower.
Super smelly the rest of the day.
You got babies crying here and stuff in your ear.
That is perfect.
That's the funniest tactic.
And I'm surprised that more people don't try.
I'm surprised more teams aren't trying to find haunted locations and then like really
trying to anger the ghosts.
They're like, "Hey, Michael Jordan, go down there and summon a goat monster."
What are you talking about?
I don't even play for the NBA.
They're like, "Yeah, that's why it's perfect.
If you get killed by the goat monster, then you know, you're a legend."
But he's like, "Wait, what?
No, no, no, no, no, just go down and go down and stay bloody merry in the mirror three
times."
I'm not going to do that.
But you would get someone else.
You get some new guy who really wants to play basketball and be like, "We'll put you
on the team."
But first, you give him a summoning goat monsters for Dummies book.
Go down to the basement of this hotel.
So we have a real life effect on the sport of basketball.
And it's funny if you're actually betting.
I've been researching gambling addictions a lot recently.
We'll talk about that in a future episode.
But if you're betting on teams, you almost always want to bet for the Oklahoma City Thunder
if they're playing.
Don't gamble.
If you advise, this is a sure bet from Dead or Ever Radio.
It appears that it can really mess you up.
But if you are going to gamble, always bet on Oklahoma City after home games, because it's
most likely the other team got spooked out.
Now we have a bunch of stuff to cover.
I don't have a lot of time to do it, but I want to go into the legend of this story.
And that's again where Jon Branch did an amazing job at putting this all together.
You have this woman ghost.
She's whispering in ear.
She wants to dribble your bowl.
You have a baby crying in your room.
Sometimes there's an image of a woman pushing a baby carriage through the hotel.
Why are these two things so connected?
This is the story.
A long time ago, we're talking like pre-1930.
The hotel was only about 10 stories high.
Now it's 14.
When it was 10 stories high, the 10th story was known as a "din of vice."
You'd have gambling up there and things like that.
And you had a young housekeeper named Effie.
And she had an affair with the hotel's owner, the hotel's founder, W.B.
Skirvin.
Classic story.
She gets pregnant.
He wants to cover it up, so he says, "Go live on the 10th floor in this little hotel room.
I'll provide for everything."
But she's basically a prisoner.
She's trapped up there.
And even after she gives birth to her child, she's still not allowed to live.
She's not allowed to leave.
So eventually this takes a toll on her, so she jumps out of her window holding her baby
and dies in the front of the hotel.
This is the most common ghost story you hear.
Effie is a nickname that people have given her, but the most common story you hear is
that one.
And the New York Times looked into this and they go, "We could never find a record of
anyone named Effie."
But it turns out that was just a nickname.
But they go, "We've never come across anyone who jumped out of the hotel with their baby
and died."
You even had local historian Steve Lachmeyer, he's a reporter for the Oklahoma.
He said, "We looked into this.
I wrote a book about the scurvin.
We looked into this.
It's a really well-known story in town.
There is no record of this happening."
And he goes, "Back then it was a small town.
That would have made huge news.
There's no proof of a housekeeper jumping out with a baby and dying in front of the hotel."
The earliest reference, John Branch was able to track this down, the earliest reference
of this being written down.
This story comes from the mid-90s on a haunted places website.
So it may have been a local story that was going around that only particular, like you
know, you may have a bridge in your area that's kind of spooky, but if you move five miles
out of that area and nobody knows of the story, this must have been a super local legend.
Because there's no books written about it long ago.
But in the mid-1990s there was a haunted, like a ghost research website.
And New York Times tracked down the guy who wrote that.
His name is Jason Gammon, who currently has a ghostly website.
Jason Gammon said, "This is what the story I heard."
Like he goes, "Yeah, I posted it online back in the 1990s.
This was how I heard of the story."
He goes, "We used to hang out.
There was like a parking garage near this hotel.
At this point it was abandoned.
He said, "We used to hang out.
It would have been like in the 70s, the 80s."
And they befriended an elderly security guard there.
And he told us the story about a woman named Julia who was in room 832.
And she with her baby fell out of her room, fell out of the window, and landed in front
of the hotel and died.
So that was the story Jason Gammon told.
But there has never been a room 832.
That room has never existed.
The most rooms that hotel ever had was 500 rooms.
Now there's 14 floors, but it still has only had up to 500 rooms that they've now turned
into 225.
So we're basically at a dead end with the legend.
Because that story just isn't true.
It's probably a bit of truth in there, but it could also just be an old man making up
stuff to impress a bunch of kids.
That's the most likely thing.
It could be that the story is partially true, but he just got the number wrong.
And maybe there wasn't a baby involved, because again, you think that would be in the news.
You don't think some just elderly guy would be like, "I am the true guardian of the knowledge
of Oklahoma City."
And he has this staff, "Welcome to my repository."
People did have newspapers back in the 1930s.
And this would have been a story.
It's super salacious.
This is a fascinating story, because I believe this ghost is real, but it has an unknown
origin.
I believe these incidents of the baby crying and the ghost woman are real for two reasons.
One, you have a ton of witnesses to the activity.
You have a ton of witnesses to the activity, and it kind of fits that only men are hearing
it.
Again, that is a detail that seems to make it stand out more than you go into a room,
you feel a cold draft, anyone can feel the cold draft.
I find that detail intriguing.
Also the fact, and I've talked about this a hundred times on the show, the hotel absolutely
does not play this up at all.
They don't talk about it.
They instruct all of their employees.
If anyone asks about the ghost, tell them you don't know what they're talking about.
They have an official statement.
You do not talk about the folklore of this hotel.
That is extremely suspicious.
They could easily cordon off a little room and say this is Effie's room and charge a
little bit more.
And then on Halloween, charge people to go through on ghost tours.
And even though it's a luxurious hotel, you'd have people paying extra money just to stay
in Effie's room.
No, they want no extra money.
The ghost does not exist.
As far as the management of the hotel is concerned, it is not real.
That makes me think it's real.
Because almost every other company would be like, "Yes, this is a haunted sewage treatment
plant."
And on Halloween, we open it up and we make an extra thousand dollars.
I think it's real.
I think this is a real ghost activity.
We don't know the legend.
We don't know where she came from.
We have to...
Based on the evidence, we would assume that it is a mother and her child.
But it almost seems like a mother ghost who, even though she has a kid, is still looking
for a little something special on the side.
She's always hitting on dudes, getting into their showers naked.
Who knows what she did to metaworldpeace, but she's definitely out there still looking
for male affection.
Bizarre story.
It's a creepy story.
Just as a standard ghost story, it's more than just, "Oh, a ghost walking down the hallway."
We have a very active spirit.
We have management denying it exists while multi-millionaires in front of cameras are
saying, "That place is haunted."
Again, it's not just people off the street going, "Oh, I went and saw an orb."
We have people whose mental and physical abilities are worth millions of dollars and even more
money is being bet on them every day and they're coming forward and being like, "There's a
dead baby in my room.
I don't like playing this team."
All of this takes it to a level above just orbs floating down a hallway.
The ghost that exists in this hotel is actually costing people money.
If you bet against Oklahoma City Thunder at a home game, you will most likely lose.
Fascinating.
I can't think of a ghost story that has had such a financial impact on the people around
it than this one.
So if you ever find yourself in Oklahoma City and got a couple hundred dollars to spare,
why don't you check out the N.R.A. man.
I guess if a woman you go, it's just a nice hotel.
But if you're a man in Oklahoma City and you have a couple hundred dollars to spare, check
out the Skerven Hilton Hotel.
At the very least, you'll have a nice night in the luxurious hotel and then the next day
you can take in the sights and the sounds of the city.
But you may possibly not just be paying for a room, you may be paying for a paranormal
encounter that involves a hot ghost in your shower.
Lathering up your back.
I don't think she can hold the soap.
But just for this scenario, she's lathering up your back.
She's whispering sweet nothings in your ear.
You may have the opportunity to make love to a ghost woman.
You leave the next day.
You don't have a basketball game to play.
You don't have to worry about the stresses of that.
You just go back to your daily life.
However, nine months later, someone else is staying in that hotel and they wake up.
They don't take a shower with a beautiful woman.
They wake up and they hear two ghostly babies crying in the darkness.
You thought you were having a one night stand with a specter.
Instead.
Now your Casper's dad.
It probably would have been funnier if I had gone it out.
And I know I made a Casper joke last week, but what are you going to do?
DeadRabbitRadiotGmail.com is going to be our email address.
Casper is not a baby.
Casper I imagine was like 10 or 12.
And he didn't cry like a baby.
But anyways, you guys get it.
You guys get it.
DeadRabbitRadiotGmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadiot.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadiot.
DeadRabbitRadiot is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
(music)