So I've actually decided to break this episode into two parts.
So we are doing my health issues first.
And then for those of you who just really don't care about that
or new listeners of the show, they're like,
"I don't care if this guy's sick or not."
You can go ahead and skip that and jump right to part two.
This is part one of episode 333, Halfway to Hell episode.
And we're gonna be talking about some crazy ghost stories
that have come across, but we're breaking it up into two parts.
So part one's gonna be me talking about
what happened yesterday with my health.
Part two is where we talk about a bunch of ghosts.
So if you just wanna get to the ghost stuff,
jump to part two and the episode starts now.
(upbeat music)
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of
Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
My voice is a little hoarse, so I apologize for that.
And if you're a new listener,
the next five minutes will probably be kind of boring.
But for the existing listeners,
let me guys tell you what happened.
'Cause there's been a lot of questions
about what happened to me yesterday, a lot of theories.
I was shopping, my heart rate was super high,
not because of the great deals at Walmart,
but because of something else.
I could feel my chest was flip-flopping.
Now, I've talked about before I have anxiety attacks,
and most of the time my anxiety attacks
present themselves as heart attacks.
So I tried calming down, but something really fell off.
Like I could physically feel, I put my hand in my chest,
I could physically feel my heart starting and stopping.
So I go to the pharmacist, and this is a tip too.
If you guys are ever sick with something,
you can go to the pharmacist at like a Walmart
or a Rite Aid or something like that,
and they'll be more than willing to dispense advice to you.
They can't necessarily give you a lot of medical advice,
but they, she was able to feel my pulse and she goes,
it does feel irregular.
So I use their little blood pressure machine they have there.
I had a pulse of 120, so I was like,
okay, I'm gonna go to the hospital.
So one of my friends takes me to the hospital from Walmart,
and I go up there and I get down on the bed,
the little bed thing, and I'm like, yeah,
my heart feels weird, and they're like checking my pulse,
and they're like, yeah, okay, so let's get you into the room.
And they start hooking me up to machine,
and I look over at it, and I go, that's not,
my pulse really is in 170, right?
And the nurse looks over, she's like,
oh no, no, no, that's your pulse.
And right when she said that,
my pulse jumped up to 200, 'cause I was like, uh-oh.
And I go, guys, should I be concerned
about what's going on right now?
And they said, listen, we're not in a hurry.
This is a pretty common thing.
We think you're an AFib, which is like,
AFibulation, they could pronounce it, I can't.
But we think you're an AFib,
this is something that happens to people.
We gotta find out why.
It normally happens in older people.
So anyways, long story short,
they did all this blood work,
they took X-rays, I watched World's Funniest Weather Videos.
It's an actual show on the Weather Channel
where it's bloopers of newscasters.
That's a show you would only watch
while you're trapped in a hospital.
At no other point in time would you watch
World's Funniest Weather Videos.
So I watched that, I've watched the whole thing,
and then I was flipping through the channel,
and I watched probably the fur,
I was there for five and a half hours at the hospital.
I watched maybe the first hour of the fate of the furious,
and I was laughing out loud.
Mind you, I'm in an emergency room.
People, they're like grieving families nearby.
There's woman moaning to the laugh,
she's like, "Ugh!"
And I'm like, "Ha ha ha, laughing so hard."
Every time something ridiculous happened,
I had never seen fate of the furious before.
Watch the first hour of that.
This is what you guys been waiting for.
The diagnosis.
So when I go in, I said, "Listen,
here's the things that I've done recently to mess up.
I've been doing keto."
Now I don't consider that a mess up,
but I know there could be some health risks to that.
I'm doing keto and the doctor's like, "Okay."
And I go, I was, previously to this,
I was testing out weights at Walmart.
I was picking up weights and throwing punches with them,
so I might have pulled something
and put some pressure on the heart.
She's like, "Uh, okay, Rocky, don't do that."
And I was like, "Yeah, I know, it's bad form."
'Cause recently, as I've been walking,
I've had these little hand weights
and I'll be throwing punches on them, walking through town.
And I wanted to see about getting some heavier weights.
She's like, "Okay, yeah, but don't do that anymore."
And I was like, "Yeah, done and done."
And I said, "I did have a lot of caffeine lately."
And she goes, "How much?"
And I go, "Well, in the past 24 hours,
I had like a large coffee from Dog River.
That's where I do all my research."
I said, "I've probably had about four or five diet pepsis."
And she's like, "Mmm."
And then I said,
and I think I've told you guys about this before.
I said, "You know, recently I gave up,
I was chewing tobacco for 15 years.
I switched that out with the Lawsonge,
but I think the Lawsonge had too much sugar in it
for my keto, so I dropped the Lawsonge.
And then I switched to a chewing tobacco alternative.
There are little pouches full of coffee."
And she's like, "What?"
Wait, she goes, "Really, that's a thing?"
And I was like, "Yeah, a little pouch of coffee."
But each pouch only has one third of a cup of coffee in it.
So I figured it's not too bad, right?
And she goes, "How many have you had
in the past 24 hours?"
I was like, I don't know, maybe like 12 or something like that?
And she goes, "Do you have them on you now?"
And she's like, "Yeah."
I was like, "Yeah, yeah."
And she's looking at them and she goes, "Here's the thing.
These might only have one third of a cup of coffee in them,
but you're putting them directly into your bloodstream.
You're not digesting it as coffee."
So she goes, "Listen, we did your blood work.
I asked, I go, could the keto have caused this?"
And she said, "Most likely not."
She goes, "We did your blood work
and came back totally fine.
So I don't have any cholesterol issues."
She goes, "Your blood pressure is fine."
She goes, "This whole event caused no stress
on your heart or your lungs.
You had no major complications from this."
The doctor says, and she put it in the paperwork,
"I'm almost for sure this was caused
by a caffeine incident, i.e. overdoses, my word."
She didn't use the term caffeine overdose,
but she says, "This most likely was caused by the caffeine.
If you stay away from caffeine."
And she goes, "Don't take the pouches anymore."
And I was like, "Yep, done."
So she goes, "That's probably what caused it."
So a lot of people have, these were the,
sorry this is going so long for new listeners,
but I wanted to clear the air,
so there's nothing going on.
A lot of people thought it was the turmeric,
which is funny because just two days
or three days before, I thought,
I'm gonna stop messing around with the turmeric
because it's obviously having some sort of bad reaction.
That's not what should happen when you take turmeric.
So I actually had stopped that, like on Thursday.
I was like, "I'm not gonna mess with it anymore."
Some people, and that's a rational thing.
Jason, you're taking a pill,
you're taking a pill in the form it's not created for
and you're telling people, making you sleepy.
Wasn't that though, I'd stop doing that.
They, some people thought it was Veronica the haunted doll.
It was not the Veronica the haunted doll,
I can assure you of that.
Right, Veronica?
Yeah, no, she's just been chilling over there
with my pig, stuffed pig and puppy dolls.
She's totally fine, it wasn't Veronica.
And then what was the other,
oh, other people thought it was because I was dieting
or it was the keto itself.
So it wasn't any of those things.
Well, Veronica put a little asterisk maybe,
but most likely not.
It's most likely the caffeine.
So they said, "No more chewing,
"no more putting coffee in your mouth for hours on end."
'Cause I would take one out, put another one in,
just like I used to do chewing in a becca.
And they said you can maybe have one to two caffeinated,
for right now don't have any caffeinated beverages
if you can help it.
And I haven't had any sense.
And they said, "In the future,
"limit yourself to one to two caffeinated beverages a day."
Also don't drink.
And I don't drink anyways,
but they said if you drink,
they could cause it again.
They said this is very common.
And they said it's super treatable.
Doesn't really cause,
it can cause health problems down the road.
So I don't want you guys,
I first off, I'm in the hospital cracking up
but all the comments people are leaving me.
So I really appreciate all the comments,
all the support, all the love I've gotten from you guys.
I really, really appreciate that.
Secondly, don't worry about me
because this was a one-off, most likely,
I have a doctor's appointment tomorrow
and I'll probably have to see a cardiologist after that.
But this was most likely a one-off event brought
by a rolling 24 hour period of massive caffeine use.
So don't worry about me.
But I really appreciate the support
and I really appreciate that you guys let me rant on
about that for eight minutes.
Now, that being said,
I did say that I have a doctor's appointment tomorrow
and I'm on a medicine right,
I apologize for taking so long,
but this now I'm,
this is saying what's going forward.
I'm on a medication,
they did put me on beta blockers,
which actually limits how fast my heart can beat
because when I left the hospital, I was still in AFIP.
I was still having,
you know what, I might actually break this
up into two episodes.
I might have this episode just be the health episode
and then I'll release a ghost episode after that,
but we're gonna split it,
so we'll figure that.
So you don't have to listen to all this stuff
if you just wanna hear about ghosts.
The, so, but where was I going with that?
Oh yeah, yeah, so when I left the hospital,
my heart was still out of rhythm.
So as far as I,
it doesn't feel like it's out of rhythm right now,
but as far as I know, it's still out of rhythm.
So this, we're gonna do,
I'm gonna do this episode today.
I will not have an episode come out
I feel really bad about this,
but I will not have an episode come out tomorrow
because I gotta go to the doctor
and I'm feeling really, really tired.
So that's where we're at right now.
So we have today's episode,
we won't have an episode tomorrow,
we should have an episode for the next two days of the week.
So I apologize for that,
but I have to take these beta blockers in the morning
and at night and I'm gonna take one two nights
and then I'm gonna just go to sleep
all the way to the morning,
which is what humans normally do.
And then, oh, wake up, that's the next step.
Wake up and then do, go to the doctor's appointment.
I'm not gonna worry about busting an episode out
quickly in the morning and all that stuff.
So I apologize for that,
but I'm healthy, everything going for,
supposedly healthy, most likely caffeine,
everything else going forward, we're gonna be good.
Let's go ahead and actually get started
with the episode though.
Let's go ahead and get started with the episode.
So thank you for your patience.
I'm sure a lot of you skipped past that,
but I don't care, that's totally fine.
Give me the ghost is what you're saying, give me the ghost.
So.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]