What would you do if you're home alone and one night you hear the sound of a child crying out in the darkness?
And then we travel to the year
1676 where young nun is found unconscious in her room
her face covered in black ink and on her desk a note
Written by the devil himself today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too freezing cold though super super cold
I'm gonna try to record this episode as fast as possible because I have a heater running in my bedroom
I'm gonna take my laptop. I'm gonna edit it
Bam, let's see if I can record this in one take half hour probably won't but let's see if I can at least get it close
You might hear the occasional sound of me rubbing my little paws on my pants to keep my hands warm
Currently wearing thermals pajama pants jeans
Coat a coat inside. It's that cold a little baklava from my ears
I'm cold but you guys want an episode. I want to record an episode. So let's do this our first story
Let's hop aboard the carboner copter guys get on board
Got to scrape the ice off put the de-icer on the helicopter
We're taking off we're headed to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. This first story is actually a recommendation from
Scaryman Esquire long-time listener of the show. Thank you so much scaryman for this
We're headed to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
Specifically the south side of Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. This one's gonna be a little spooky. So we're on board the carboner copter
We're flying out to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, and it's night time by the time we get there and we're gonna land in like this
Soccer field right?
They're still playing soccer. They're like, oh look out look out
We look out for no one
Crush and we pop their only ball whole city of
Pennsylvania wait, that's not a city whole city of Pittsburgh is like oh like no more soccer
We're strutting off the helicopter boo soccer and
We're walking around the south side of Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
We see all these little houses and dorms and apartments and stuff like that and we see
Across the field we see this young woman kind of looking outside of her door
We see she has a scared look on her face not scared because of us not scared because
She really loves soccer balls and she's afraid that we're gonna pop hers
We just noticed she's kind of spooked out. So we were like hey lady. Hey us. Yeah, we're total strangers
But we're gonna come in and talk to you so we walk over into her house and she's like oh I'm so glad you're here
I just heard the craziest noise outside my door now. This is something that's been happening all over
Well, I shouldn't say all over so this is what's interesting
There are four you're like Jason
There's a big difference between all over and four but hold on hold on there are four
known reports of
This in the south side of Pittsburgh
and
You'd have to say that it's possible. There's only these four or
Other people have experienced this and they haven't gone through the trouble of reporting it
But four reports have come through
Primarily college students
Generally later in the evening sit at home doing your homework
Looking up the physics of a helicopter a helicopter landing gear on top of a soccer ball
You're like my thesis is that the helicopter will pop the soccer ball and
Then outside your door
Help me help me
You're like what what huh? That's weird normally those voices are coming from inside my head
But now I'm hearing them out in the darkness of my door
They're not shrinking. He's not the voices of people in 1950s movies slowly shrinking help me
You're like looking for ants that they're writing on the back of
people are hearing the sounds of babies or toddlers crying and
Young children calling up for help
You give the point you get the point I don't think I I think we've all heard children calling up for help
Hopefully not in real life kids are like falling off a cliff and you're like theater of the mind my friend theater of the mind
In movies, I mean
Right, I don't think I've ever heard a child in real life go help help me
But I would know it if I heard it so anyways
They're calling up the police you open up your door or maybe not maybe just hear these horrible noises outside
But either way there's nothing out there and
The police actually issues people are calling up the police the police send units out there because you know
It's it's something that you want. There's enough
If someone's keen your car you want the police to be able to take care of that
But unless you're the one doing the keen then you're totally fine with it
But nobody's pro children screaming in the darkness like no one's gonna be like what a waste of tax dollars
The police showed up and there was nothing there
Well, I hope the next time a child begs for his life the police don't show up that'll teach them like everyone's like
Yeah, yeah, it's either a prank or something scary
Police are showing up and they don't know what to make of it. They have not caught any suspects
They have issued these statements the police. This is from the Pittsburgh deputy public information officer. This is Cara Cruz
She's Lois Lane's cousin. Here's a quote
Police have received multiple reports recently from people in the South Side area of the city of Pittsburgh who hear what sounds like this is interesting
I should have stated this too before I got in school. It's not the sound. It's not the sound of a child crying outside your door
It's the sound of a recording
Of a child crying outside your door
So if the marinade on that for a second, let me go back to this quote
People have received multiple reports recently from people in the South Side area of the city of Pittsburgh who hear what sounds like a record
of a baby crying or a child's voice asking for help zone three officers
That's not some sci-fi. That's not some like sci-fi hologram cop
Sting zone three is the area this take place in zone three officers have responded to each call in each case for altogether
Officers did not hear the sound or locate the source of the sound
However, we asked that anyone who hears something similar to these reports call 9-1-1 immediately
No one from Pittsburgh police will be commenting on this at this time. So they're definitely taking it seriously
They're not saying it's a prank so much as if you hear this call us, but we're not answering any more questions about this
So they want to get to the bottom of it. It's not like they're like oh
We think it's some fraternity frat prank. They actually want to get the bottom of this the question is this
And this is an ongoing story this thing's happening right now right now
It's happening outside your house if you turn down the volume of the podcast. You'll hear it
But here's my question
What's creepier to you the sound of a child in the darkness outside your house help me
Help me. I'm assuming it sounds a little more realistic than that
It's not obviously the sound of a 43 year old man imitating a child's voice. It's sound of a child's voice
But what's creepier the sound of a child's voice outside your house in the darkness or the recording of a
child's voice outside in the darkness
Because let me say this if there's a kid outside your house calling for help
This is what I personally think the recording is creepier because if there's a child outside your house calling for help
Theoretically you could run out and help that child in the moment, but if it's a recording
Whatever they're calling out for what's ever causing their misery has happened
long ago
You're just hearing an echo of their pain
So I think on that level I would much rather
I don't want to hear either one honestly, but if I was in my house and I heard someone go
Oh, help me help me and I opened the door now if I didn't see anyone there
I think it was a ghost but when I hear that noise
I think maybe I can go out and help this person
But if it sounds like someone's just playing a tape recording that means somebody's already done something awful
It's not an incident where someone might need my assistance right now
Someone's already been hurt and in trouble and that situation has been resolved
And I'm just hearing an echo or a memory of that pain
Coming from the shadows beyond my house and there's nothing I can do to save that person
So that to me that's way creepier. Let's go ahead speaking of creepy. Let's move on to our next story
Now our next story is one I just found out about today, and it's absolutely
Fascinating to me. We're leaving the south side of Pittsburgh. Hopefully this mystery is solved
Hopefully it's just a prank. No kids were harmed in the making of this wacky escapade that's going on hopefully
But we will keep you updated as we leave Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
So we leave the city behind we're headed off to Sicily, Italy, and we're going back in time to the year
Helicopter is flying over a convent the Palma de Montecario. I have no idea. I Palma probably means like
hand right and Montecario
Monty is like
Well, there's the count of Monty Cristo so Mont mount
So maybe that means like the the and Charo means darkness, right?
Oh, man if this story is fake either my either my Italian is really bad or the story's fake or both
But Palma de Montecario does that mean like the hand of the dark mountain convent?
Maybe but anyways, let's forget that that
Let's forget that that might be like a trick the whole time I was reading the story
I thought this story is too good to be true
So I was looking for anagrams and stuff and some of the names
I didn't even think about that now again. Like I said my Italian is non-existent. I don't know any Palma de Montecario
Could mean all sorts of stuff
But anyways, I hope it doesn't mean hand of the black mountain because then that's just a creepy convent and it would make us
Thank this whole story fake, but we are land
I vetted the story as much as I could because again
I was enthralled by it today and looked it up in a bunch of different sources seems to be accurate
But but anyways, let's quit building it up. We're gonna land at this convent
And we're walking around the nuns come out and they're like hey people let's like shaking our hands whatever nuns do do they bow
I don't know they do something they greet humans in some way or fashion and after we're done doing the traditional nun greeting
They're like hey, do you want to check out the convent? It's a pretty cool place
It's on the spooky black dark mountain in the shape of a fist of God's fist to punish all the evil doers
It's holding a giant ruler really good
And it's scarier because the rulers in the metric system because we're in Italy. We're like a double or we go into this convent
We're walking around there showing us all this stuff and they're like this is where we like do pray
Right, and then this is where we like do some more praying because we're nuns and that's all we do
We're like it's pretty interesting and then we come to this like room and we go what's in there and they go
Oh, that's just sister Maria
As they're looking over at their notepad file on their computer. They're like, uh, yeah, let me look that up
That is sister Maria
crocifissa
Della
Concezino
And then we're like we like are you sure you pronounce that right and then head none
Whatever they're called the mother Teresa person the mother the head head mother the din mother
anyways, she goes
Um, I guess I've spent so much time trying to prove this story to be true or false
I didn't even look up basic nuns nun facts the mother superior. That's it the mother superior goes
Yeah, I think that's how you pronounce her name. She before she came to the nunnery
She was known as Isabella tomasy
So anyways Isabella tomasy a k a sister maria
crocifissa Della concienz
zion
And we're like can we check on this chick? We want to see if she has such a wacky name that no one can pronounce
Knock on the door and we don't know. She's not getting up. We're like, that's kind of rude. We're knocking again
Come on open up. We want to talk to you. We we want you to like
I don't know preach to us and stuff. What what what do nuns do and she's still not coming in
So mother superior gets her master key and she opens up the door
And there is this young nun. She's in her like 20s
mid 20s laying on the ground
unconscious so she's not making a noise
And we run over and we're like wake up wake up dude. You're you're like something's wrong
You're not dead so we can see breathing. She's like rolling around. She's like, oh man
What and she rolls over and her face is covered in black ink. She's like, oh man
That was unexpected. But then we remembered back in time. They didn't have like pins and stuff
They just had a bunch of ink laying around them like little bottles
And when you wanted to write something you took something sharp like a feather because I I I don't I've seen this in movies
Okay, I'm not an ink inkologist. You take a feather or something sharp
And you stick it in the ink. I don't know why I'm explaining it to you guys. I'm seeing the same movies
I have anyways her face is covered in ink and
there's a bunch of ink like on the table and
Then there's a letter on the table as well. And so she we help her to her feet. She's all slipping in the ink
Whoa, whoa, whoa, and then we let her fall because it's funny and she's like jerks
We help her back up and we're like, dude, what happened? You're like knocked out. You all covered in ink
Like what's going on and she goes you won't believe
The night I had you won't believe the night I had
Go pick up that letter. We we pick up this letter and it's completely indecipherable
It's a combination of greek letters and
Krillik shrillik letters krillik shrillik shrillik the cyr l l ic krillik
Anyways, it's a bunch of those letters too, right? It's greek letters and and krillik letters
And a bunch of other letters that nobody can decipher and we're like, what is this like? What were you doing?
And she goes dude, uh, it's totally sucked
Can I at least get a towel to wipe this ink off my face?
So then we give her a towel and she gets all clean and then she tell comes back and tells us this story
She said last night. I was just chilling in my little convent hole
Praying and stuff, right?
And the devil came to me and everyone's like, oh
The devil wanted me to write a letter
And I said no no, no, I'm not gonna do that and then the devil started to like beat me up
Now, okay, so here's the thing, right?
Obviously we're sitting in this monastery in 1676 and we know these people are like super religious
They've given up their life for their religion
it's
Not it's not super dark ages time, but it's definitely not
Like the most enlightened time is it's kind of that in-between phase
I think the Renaissance was kind of in full swing, but still like
1676 in a nunnery
You know, we're just kind of looking at each other. We're like, oh, you know
Yeah, the devil came to you and like beat you up and made you write a letter
Now the letter is gibberish. You can see it in the show notes. It is it's written out as words and sentences, but
Makes no sense. You're like Jason. You can't even pronounce the word
Srillik or Krillik or whatever. How do you know what their alphabet looks like?
Well, even back then and even today they're saying it just doesn't make sense
So we have this basically an art a letter written in gibberish
That conveniently fits on one page from this woman who was all by herself who deeply is
deeply the vout person
Satan shows up beats her up and makes her write a letter that nobody can decipher
So we're kind of like it's kind of like speaking in tongues like what's going on here
And she says so the devil wanted me to write this letter now. I know what the letter says
So we go, what does the letter say? She goes, I'm not gonna tell you
But I know what it says. It actually makes sense, but I'm not gonna tell you what it says
Oh, okay. So now again, it's super suspicious
There's one word that is decipherable in the letter
Omi like oh me or alas is another way. It's been translated
But other than that everything is this weird language and she said that was the one time I was able to break satan's control
And I wrote omi
On there or omi. It's it's written. It's an italian. Oh, oh me. Oh me
But anyways
That is where we're at with that now
She says that she wrote it. She says that it was dictated dictated to her by satan satan made her do it
She broke his control for just a minute. She wrote omi then she became paralyzed
And he made her finish writing it
And she and then at that point the church elders got a hold of the letter and they believed her story
They said we actually believe this like the way this is structured. We think it says something
but
she won't tell us what it is and
That's that really now before she died 14 years later
And she said in that time period satan came to her two more times
Wanted her to dictate more letters and she wouldn't do it and satan beat her up. She wouldn't do it at all the first letter
She kind of had to like she got beat up and then she wrote it down
Then he appeared two more times and she would never say what the letter was supposed to say and she didn't write the other two letters
But she ended up the church elders did believe her story
She ended up beginning venerated. She wasn't a saint
But people really believe that she had this bizarre connection to God and over the centuries two possible theories popped up regarding this letter
One it was a letter that satan wanted to send to God satan wanted to send a message to God, but didn't want to do it directly
So he had to use an intermediary
Which would have been sister maria, but satan didn't want any human to know what the letter said so he wrote it in this crazy language
When I find that kind of creepy to me that reminds me
Something you would see on an episode of supernatural now getting this story is throwing up a lot of alarm bells for me
This is one of them
because that involves there's something so
fictional about that
Like it doesn't necessarily make sense, but it's a kind of a cool gimmick where you could have a story where
You have satan and god these two
supremely powerful figures
having to use little people us to
Send messages back and forth and then this would be the prologue and then eventually
You would jump to the year 2020 and you would have sabina a 16 year old girl in idaho
Who doesn't have a really good home life and she's not good at school and then she becomes the messenger of satan
And you have this whole and then she meets these really hot guys and they start fighting over her and then one of them turns out to be an angel
The other one's just like a billionaire
You know and you could see this
mythology being born out of this this idea of
Satan simply wants to send a message to god, but he can't do it directly. He has to find you know what I mean like it sounds
Too good. It sounds too interesting. It sounds too much like an episode of supernatural or a series of teen novels
The other theory is that the devil actually
And again, this kind of falls into that fictional thing that maria was some sort of prize and the devil was trying to torment her directly
By getting her to write this letter and that's why he kept appearing to her and not other people
And the devil and god were fighting over her devil wanted to break her soul and god was testing her letting him try this
She ended up dying in her 40s. So she did end up dying quite young
But the the letter was kept the letter was studied for centuries and people just thought
Gibberish eventually people started to say she's probably having some sort of mental breakdown because the cloistered life was so hard
You know, you're going you're just praying all the time your knees hurt. You're dressed in all those drab clothes
It's not the best place for someone who might be a free spirit
she joined the nunnery when she was 15 years old and she just might have had a mental breakdown and
You have the skeptics believing that you have the church believing this was a legitimate letter and now we travel to the year
2017 and all of that stuff was I think an interesting little story, right?
And normally that would be the way I'd start off an episode
until 2017
2017 again people studied this letter for a long time 2017
There is a museum in
a katani
Katania Sicily Katania Sicily. It's the Ludham science museum and they came across
software a basically a cryptography
Software a code breaking software that was developed by the government of turkey to crack
Isis codes
That were being used on the deep web
And someone gets the bright idea. What if we took this
Program that's used to crack these near indecipherable codes that terrorists are using to plan attacks across the world
What if we use this program to decipher this letter from 1676?
What do you have to lose right?
It really would prove if the letter if you're using this advanced cryptography program and the letters gibberish
Then the letter is gibberish
But what could happen if you ran this program?
Now i'm about to read you this translation because this actually worked
There is a bit of a little asterisk to this so so there's a listener named neo
He sent me a bunch of stuff recently a lot of it involved the region where he's from which is in italy the
Friuli region because we did an episode a while back on the the benedonte witches
And warlocks. He's from that area. He's not a witch or a warlock at least that i know of but
He sent me a bunch of stuff
I found this story on a website. He said he didn't directly send me the story
But he turned me onto this italian paranormal website. So thank you for that. I'm about to read you an english
a google english translation of an italian website
That's trying to translate something from ancient greek or classical greek and
Cyrillic
I think that's how he ran it actually Cyrillic alphabets run through
A turkish design program to crack
Isis codes, okay?
But i'm going to read you the quote that i have and then i'll read you what people think this means
So this is trippy letter written in 1676 here we go of symbols that i who claws live go
No source a misfortune perhaps
Now certain sticks
And then there's two words that are unpronounceable
Since i christ Zerosto
Follow the ancient ways or seamstresses sewn by men
Oh me
Restore me to serve nobody
This is ballast system are the three a god that i feel free mortals
Z this is why they are always
The fact that you're even able to get that much
That is comprehensible real words
From gibberish written in classical greek and that other language that no one was able to translate because
And i should say this they could look at the letters and go those letters make sense
But they're not say spelling out words
So they look at the greek letter for alpha and they go well we know what alpha is
But that word that it's in it doesn't make any sense. It was written in a code
And you go but jason that's just a string of words. This is what people
Think the letter is is meaning i got this quote from another article
God thinks he can free mortals
This system works for no one
And it also says that that's just one part of it. They're also saying that there are words like when it's talking about christ
It's talking about god. It's talking about zorostar, which is another ancient deity old old world
Deity when it talks about the river sticks when it makes the reference to sticks
When it talks about the seamstresses sown by men people believe the letter is making a reference that god and when it talks about the
Three a god that i feel free mortals
That god and the trinity are made up by man
seamstresses sown by men
And that's when she writes. Oh me
Like that's when she interjects this letter is basically saying god is made up
The trinity is made up
I find it absolutely bizarre
That anything came out of the letter and it's funny when I was reading the article
I thought well, this is interesting. You know a nun had a nervous breakdown and wrote this
But then when you jump ahead
for what four or five hundred years
Run a computer program and something decipher not only does something come up
Something comes up that makes sense in the context of the history of the letter
It's not alphabet soup. Yum. Yum. Yum. It's
A nun saying she got this letter from the devil and the letter is in code saying
God doesn't exist
It's all a joke
now I've
Now it's pot this story really does sound
Too good to be true. It's been reported. It's it's a pretty obscure story, but it's been reported in a lot of
places
The actual letter being translated that was reported in the mirror, which is a british newspaper
And um life science actually did an article
About the translation. So it's not a movie hoax that I know of it's not like the
Mountain devils that we covered or you know the bigfoot beating people up and then getting shot
Which turned out to be fake as well
Lone pine devils that was a story that ended up being a viral marketing thing which we covered on this show
This story appears to be true
Let me say this let me back up the story the elements of the story appear to be true
There was a letter that for four or five hundred years was indecipherable that was recently run through a
anti-intelligence
Cryptography code breaking software and it came out with a message that is
Related to the story of it being written those elements are true
Your mileage may vary on whether or not the devil showed up at this young nun's room and forced her to write this letter
But I think it's highly possible. That's what happened
Highly possible
Is it possible that the people running the program had an interest in getting a certain message out? Sure
possible
But it feels
True
The devil saying god doesn't exist. That's nothing new
The devil trying to tempt humans
Nothing new break their will
distort their faith in god
Nothing new
But the devil's showing up
Forcing a woman to write a coded letter
Even him knowing full well unless she revealed the contents of the letter it would be indecipherable
That's all new ground
The devil putting out a message that no one would know about for hundreds of years
Until technology had advanced to the point where it could decipher
Ink on ancient parchment
There's a couple questions that come up obviously one why maria
Two why this message
Three
What were the other messages that maria refused to relay?
But the most important question I feel is this
Could it happen again today?
Is it possible the next time that you're home alone?
Sitting in your room all by yourself
The ink well is long gone
But your laptop your tablet your phone is always accessible
And when you're alone in the dark
You feel that presence
Just outside of your field of view
It has a message it wants you to deliver to the world
A message that will destroy the faith
Of all around you
Will you have the willpower
To fight the urge to write that letter or will you be
Convinced by the darkness
Will you just become a tool?
Of the prince of lies
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be her email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio twitter is @deadrabberadio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]