What would you do if you were a Catholic priest and there was this possessed girl in front
of you going "Ahhh, I like spinning around her head's like throwing up and stuff" and
you're like "The power of Christ compels you and you're throwing holy water at her"
but then you realize that the ghost is from Asia.
What would you do?
Like, "Jayson, that shouldn't make any difference."
I don't know.
We're gonna figure that out.
And then we travel to a comedy club to meet a man who says he had the worst night of his
life there was.
It wasn't Michael Richards.
That's not who we were talking about.
We go to a comedy club to meet a guy who says he had the worst night of his life ever and
we are forced to ask ourselves the question.
What's more dangerous?
A pedophile or a crazy pedophile?
Day on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jayson Carpenter.
I'm having a good day.
I hope you guys are having a good day too.
I'm actually really re- you know like long time listeners of the show know.
I don't talk politics, but politics.
That's my super boy.
That's what I love.
I love politics.
I love watching all of the debates and the returns and stuff like that.
You're like, Jayson, you don't sound normal.
You don't sound like you normally do.
I drink once every two years and it was last night.
I drank and I'm hungover.
I'm super hungover.
I ate too much.
I ate too much gross food and I drink too much gross beer.
Sorry for that Budweiser sponsorship.
So I'm a little hungover.
But it was fun for half of America and the other half of America.
Probably not so fun.
But that is my super boy.
I love crunching numbers and why I always have two or three streams.
I have a conservative stream on and I have a left leaning liberal stream on and I'm going
back and forth and you're like, Jayson, you just don't do an episode tonight.
Maybe you just don't do an episode tonight.
No, I want to do an episode and I got some really good stuff to talk about.
And walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now, bringing me some Tylenol, is one of our
legacy Patreon supporters.
Everyone give it up for Painted Demons.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on into Dead Rabbit Command.
Juggling those paint killers in that glass of water.
Painted Demons, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
Trust me, I do.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That helps out so much.
It really, really does.
If you get any value out of Dead Rabbit Radio, please pass it on.
Also, we're coming up to the end of season 19.
Friday is going to be our last episode until December 1st.
We are going to do a Thanksgiving live stream episode.
Thursday, November 24th at 12 p.m. Pacific Standard Time.
Join us on the YouTube channel.
It's always a lot of fun.
And we're not going to do any classic episodes this break either.
I'm just taking a clean break, but the classics will return in our next season break.
Painted Demons, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the...
Jason Jalopy, we're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to this house in the middle of the suburbs.
Painted Demons is driving us out to this house in the suburbs.
And when we get there, we hear someone screaming in the house.
They're just raising a holy hell.
No pun intended.
We're walking, but we notice that there's a line to get into this house.
We see a Catholic priest and a Jewish rabbi and a Muslim cleric.
We see a couple of Buddhist dudes on the front lawn.
There's a scientist there with like a scale.
He's the hardest one.
I guess he could be wearing a lab coat, but he also has like a little scale and an astrolabe.
He goes, "I'm a scientist."
So we're watching all of these people from all these different religious sects and then
you know the atheist scientists, dude.
They're all waiting for their turn to go in and we're like, "What is going on?"
So we dress up like Mormons so we can sneak on in.
We got on our little business suits and we walk in and there is a young woman with her
head spinning around.
She's throwing up everywhere.
That's kind of how I feel right now.
Her head's spinning around.
She's throwing up everywhere.
She's levitating three feet off the bed.
Her family is in the corner crying and we see a Presbyterian minister kind of throw his
shoulders up because I don't know what to do for her.
I don't know.
I tried my best and he walks out and then in walks a shaman and he's like, "Maybe medicinal
magic will work.
Maybe if I give her these mushrooms or if I give her these psychedelics, that'll cure
her insanity."
And the reason why we're kind of in this queue, we're waiting to see what happens here is
because recently on the Patreon Discord we were having a bit of a conversation about
if you had a demon from Jewish lore, would a Buddhist monk be able to wrangle that demon
in?
Could a priest exercise a jinn?
Because every...
It's kind of an interesting thing and I could go on forever about it, but I can't.
But it's kind of an interesting question because what we're basically doing is we're
turning this world of the supernatural into Pokemon.
Because let's say you have a demon that is one of the fallen angels that was thrown down
by God during the first war for heaven.
So that is part of Christian lore.
That demon fully falls into what we know of biblical demons or Christian demons.
Could you have a Shinto priest?
Could you have someone from an Eastern religion use their tools and tricks to exercise a Christian
demon?
And I don't know the answer to that.
I really don't know the answer to that.
On the one hand, this would be the most logical answer.
This is kind of what we were talking about on the Patreon Discord.
It was me and Grant and Madame Gwynnar.
We were having a discussion, but there's two ways to look at this.
One is that the terminology may be different between a jinn and a demon and a yokai and
all these different versions of these same creatures.
The Minotaur of Greek mythology really in a sense is a Nephilim.
It's an angel that came down in the book of Genesis and had sex with human women, created
these monsters or these heroes.
Really it's six of one, a dozen of another, right?
It doesn't matter what religion it's from, that's just the terminology.
A demon is a jinn.
A demon is a demon is a demon.
It doesn't matter what region of the world it's in.
So yes, you could have a Shinto priest being able to exercise Lucifer's second in command.
Or you could have a Catholic priest bless a house and keep one of those butt-devouring
demons that crawls out of the Japanese ponds every once in a while.
It wouldn't matter, it's just a terminology thing.
That would be your most basic answer.
And I think that's the answer that the leaders of those faiths would give those things.
They probably wouldn't even address it if they walked up to a priest and said, "Hey,
do you think if I got possessed by the ghost of a Buddhist monk, could you get rid of it?"
And he's like, "I can get rid of you.
I can get rid of you by asking you to leave."
Also, don't talk during the sermon next time.
I think that would be the typical answer, but then you do...
I think that there might be a Pokemon-ness to it.
Where if you don't understand that if you're over the age of seven, you don't understand
what I mean.
When I say Pokemon-ness, if you have a Pikachu who's an electric type, and then you have
a Machomp who's like a punching type, there's weaknesses and their strengths.
So a Pikachu...
Let's just...
I don't know much about Pokemon either, but let's just say, for example, Pikachu is very
weak against a water type.
So you would rather use your Squirtle than your Machomp to beat it, because it's weaker
to that.
But the Machomp is more weak against an electric type.
So then you would get the picture...
Okay, now I'm even getting confused.
Those are the only three Pokemon I know.
But my point is, or a...
Remember Battlebeast?
I'll never mind just forget the toy analogies.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors might be a good example.
Where you would say no.
That if there was a house haunted by a jinn, a Catholic priest could not get rid of it.
It actually is from a different...
Completely different theology.
The roots are all the same, right?
They're all from the Middle East.
But Christian minister, a Jewish rabbi, and a Muslim cleric, they would be able to tack
the demons within their theology.
They'd be able to exercise those demons, but could they exercise demons from other theology?
And really, all Islam and Judaism and Christianity, they're all based in the Middle East, so there
might be some crossover there.
But then talk about the Asian demons.
Talk about the demons from India.
The demons from Aboriginal lore or Native American lore.
If someone got possessed by the trickster fox of the Native Americans, they're constantly
pulling daffy duck stunts all day long, could a Muslim cleric get that fox out of them?
I don't know.
I don't...
I think it's a super interesting question.
But it's really kind of more than a thought experiment, because we see this so often in
interplaces reports and demonic possessions, stuff like that, where they say, "We brought
in like three or four priests to bless the house, and nothing ever worked.
If anything, it made it matter."
It's kind of a common trope in stories of hauntings and possessions, because generally,
I'll tell you why that trope exists.
If your house is haunted and a priest shows up and gets rid of it, well, that's the end
of the story, right?
That story's probably not even going to be in the news.
Just exercise, "Okay, it might make your local news, right?
If your house is haunted and a priest has to come out."
But you know what I mean?
We generally, the general public, really only hears about the hauntings that get out of
hand.
So if the priest shows up and it's gone immediately, it's just going to be something people in
the family say, "Hey, Nancy's getting married.
You're showing photos of her floating above the bed.
Throwing up, you're like, "Oh, look at what you're marrying, Bobby."
He's like, "What?
Is that Photoshop?
Is that real?
What's going on?
She's all embarrassed."
But I wonder if that's what could be causing it, is the reason why when you have these
stories, and it's, again, super common when we look at haunted houses, where they bring
out people, the people in the house are Southern Baptists.
They bring out a Southern Baptist minister.
Southern Baptist ministers don't bless anything, but just Southern Baptist minister comes out
to pray with their family and stuff like that, and the activity simply gets worse.
So then they bring it out another Southern Baptist minister, because that's the faith
of the family that lives there, and it doesn't work.
And I'm wondering if the reason why it doesn't work is because that's not a Christian demon.
I think my neighbor just busted out a chainsaw.
Can you hear that?
It's 6.20 at night.
Just so you guys are clear when I'm recording this.
Someone's walking around the chainsaw.
Okay, I'm going to have to move out.
I'm going to have to move the studio.
Hold on a second, guys.
Quality is going to change, I don't know, for the better or for the worse.
Oh, he walked away.
He walked away with the chainsaw.
Yeah, I'm a good.
So anyways, it's just an interesting question, because that could explain why sometimes, like
even now, I'm imagining the chainsaw in my head.
Okay, here.
We're going to move.
Okay, so we're in the living room now.
No more chainsaw.
I hope if I start hearing the chainsaw in my living room, someone's coming after me.
Anyways, I just, I got one more sentence to wrap it up.
It's the same sentence I've been trying to say.
It wouldn't make sense.
It wouldn't make sense why some hauntings or possessions or anything in between, right,
when people call out their spiritual leaders because they're the ones living in that house.
It doesn't work.
They're like, yeah, we consulted all these priests and we just couldn't get rid of this
demon.
It could be because the Pokemon theorem.
That's what we'll call it, the Pokemon theorem, that you can only fight against demons from
your canon.
You can only fight demons that are against your God or savior.
I have absolutely no proof to back this up.
Just tons and tons of stories about people trying to get rid of ghosts and them not being
able to.
I'm just not being able to.
Which opens up a whole can of worms, right?
I figure if that was the case, if I was a Jinn haunting Tanzania, I'd be like, yo, I'm
going to go out to the Red Woods.
I'm going to go out to the United States.
I'm going to get a little camera and a little bag, a little bag of human souls, and I'm
going to travel from a place where everyone knows how to fight me to a place where nobody
knows how to fight me.
But I don't know if it's actually true.
Again, theologically speaking, you would figure the power of God should be able to overcome
any dark force.
It would be very interesting though if there was this breakdown.
As far as that goes, it would make sense in a sense.
But again, if you asked any religious leader this, they'd probably be like, stop listening
to that.
Stop listening to that podcast.
That guy obviously doesn't know what he's talking about.
And then you leave and they're like, oh no, oh no.
There's a bunch of demons in their office.
They're like, that's why I wasn't able to get rid of these demons.
They're from Indonesia.
Paint the demons.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the world famous carpenter copter.
We're leaving behind this suburban neighborhood.
We hope that girl gets the help she needs.
That fictional girl, I made it just for an example.
Hopefully she stops being possessed.
We're going to leave behind this suburban house.
Take us all the way out to a comedy club.
We walk into this comedy club and there's a guy up on stage.
He's cracking jokes.
The audience is like, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Tony is sitting at this comedy club and you're sitting right next to him and he's about to experience, according to him, the worst night of his life.
Which I'm not going to argue with that at all.
That is not, that might be anything, that might be an understatement.
The worst night of his life.
So he starts off by telling us this story.
He goes, listen, I have a lot of problems.
I suffer from obsessive compulsive disorder, depression.
That's why I'm at a comedy club.
Maybe, maybe it'll cure that.
I suffer from obsessive compulsive disorder, depression.
He's bipolar, dyslexic as well.
And he has actually been on tour with his favorite comedian.
Not like a roadie, right?
Not like an opening act or anything like that.
He's just following his favorite comedian from club to club.
That actually sounds pretty dope.
Not for the comedian, because he finds out that this guy's one of his fans, but it's his favorite comedian.
He's been seeing all of these shows over and over and over again of this dude.
Well, one night, the worst night of Tony's life, Tony is sitting in the audience and he ruins...
[laughs]
He ruins one of his favorite comedians, punchlines.
Because he knows them all, right?
This is like the fourth, fifth time he's seen this guy in a very short amount of time.
He ruins one of this dude's punchlines.
Listen, that would be the worst, right?
It's not like singing a song where like you're like rocking in the USA.
What? I'm rocking in the USA.
Oh, I'm rocking in the...
And someone from the audience goes, "USA!"
You don't stop the song and go, "I'm the singer. I'm supposed to be the one singing it."
They're singing you're allowed to get down with.
They want you to sing along, right?
But with comedian, like with a live show...
I can see that being pretty bad, right?
The comedian comedy is all about suspense, not knowing what's coming next.
If you go to a live show of Romeo and Juliet and the first act you go, "I bet you they kill each other at the ending."
Well, first off, you'd be factually wrong. They don't kill each other.
That'd be more interesting.
But I bet you they both die by the end.
When they mentioned StarCross lovers, I knew.
This Shakespeare fellow is quite the heck.
I totally knew what that meant.
You know, people are like, whatever. It is annoying.
But a comedian jumping on a comedian's punchlines, giving it away,
that would be bad.
Well, Tony does admit to jumping on the stutes punchlines,
but it wasn't his fault.
And this is where this comes from just being an embarrassing post online.
Like on the one hand, you could go, "Jason, you're clearly making fun of this guy who is dyslexic and has OCT or he calls it D.C.O."
Okay, okay. He's dyslexic. He has OCD. He has depression.
You're clearly, you're just going to be making fun of this guy with these things.
Well, this is where it goes from someone just writing something embarrassing online
to where we have to start to wonder, just like Inception itself, what is real?
This is a really fascinating post, because on the one hand, it was just a guy who is dyslexic
and people were making fun of him, whatever. I mean, I just did that multiple times.
I just did that, but it's okay. I'm just dyslexic too. I can do that. I'm allowed.
Is that all I'm doing? Is that I'm just making fun of this guy?
Not necessarily, because this is so weird. And this is where it starts.
This is where you start to think, is this guy crazy?
Not like crazy because he has depression, like hallucinatory.
Like, where is his reality? Where does it stop being the real world and start being life for this guy?
So, traveling comedian, he's going all the shows, he does the punchline fine.
Then he goes, "That wasn't my fault though. I didn't mean to jump on your punchline.
Someone in this audience drugged me.
Someone in this audience here put some sort of drug in my drink and I have no control over what I'm doing or saying.
Except for this part, except for me explaining. Except for me explaining why I'm crazy.
I can say that, but everything else.
Someone drugged me and you read this and you go, "I don't think so."
The first time I read it, you know, I had an open mind, right?
But as I read it a couple of times to get it ready for the show, I thought, "No, no one drugged you."
But he, in his mind, he believes that someone at the show put something in his drink for...
Now that could be possible, right? People put stuff in people's drinks all the time.
He sees two ice cubes in there. He's like, "Ah, the madness!"
But people do put drugs in each other's drinks.
But as you read this, you start to go, "Well, why would they drug?"
Like, basically he's saying they drugged his drink, not just to take advantage of him.
They drugged his drink so he would ruin his favorite comedian's punchline.
That was a small plane taking off right outside my house.
So this would be heartbreaking, right? This would be heartbreaking.
His favorite comedian, he's up on stage, his favorite comedian, begins to bully Tony.
Begins to make fun of him, right to his face. I don't know what I would do.
If one of my heroes started making fun of me, I'm like, "No Peter Parker, no! No! You're my favorite!
I was hoping you'd bite me and give me powers!" He's like, "What? This is not how it works also! You're a dork!"
That would be horrible. I'd cry.
But he's being made fun of by his favorite comedian.
And people are physically pushing him around. You're sitting next to this guy, too. Remember?
And kid his friend, too! Kid his friend!
They're physically pushing him around. See, this is where I'm reading this, and I go,
"I imagine that the comedian would start making fun of the guy."
But I don't think the audience would then begin starting a mini mosh pit, but they begin pushing him around
and Tony, whether it was because of his drug to drink or just because he got pushed a little too far that night,
he said that he started lashing out. He said, "I let it all out. I gave into the hate."
So let's look at this from a normal person's point of view.
Imagine we're sitting there in this comedy club and there's a guy up front who accidentally ruins the comedian's punchline.
And the comedian makes a joker, too, about it, and then people start laughing about it,
and you just see this guy in the front start to get quiet and a little ashamed, embarrassed, I guess would be a better word.
And then he stood up, just out of the blue. You're like, "Okay, comedy club, the comedian's doing crowd work, whatever."
The guy then stands up and begins to say racist things. That's what Tony said happened. He didn't give us any specifics.
But he says, "I let it all out. I gave into the hate." Then he begins saying racist things, which out of context would be kind of funny
because we don't know what race he's saying racist stuff to. If he all of a sudden, he starts doing all of these,
he's like, "Scottish people are the cheapest people around!" We're like, "What?"
What are you talking about? They're all like, really, really old school, really, really old school racism stuff.
"Oh, Irish people coming over on them boats!" We're like, "What are you talking about?" He's like, "Old school."
I mean, obviously, I'm making a joke about it. This guy was probably saying some really hateful stuff.
This guy probably just stood up and was just letting fly. Just letting the worst.
When someone says like, "Ciderational things" and they don't give you any context, you know it's the worst, right?
You know it's absolutely the worst. He's not like, "Italians have greasy hair!" No, it probably wasn't anything like that.
It was probably, you could probably hear a pin drop in that comedy club when this guy just stood up and started screaming at racist things.
And that's alarming, right? That's super alarming. And then you're like, "Mumma mia, you're eating your spaghetti."
You're like, "Oh, what did he say about my mama?"
Not only does he stand up and start screaming at racist things, modern-day racist things, most likely,
he then begins to scream out that he wants to have a shootout with the police.
This went from a guy ruining a punchline to now threatening...
I mean, that's pretty bold, right? It's one thing to go, "I want to shoot you."
So another thing to go, "Oh, I want to shoot a bunch of people. Don't clip this, lawyers. Don't clip this and use it in a trial, please."
I'm going to shoot you in the face. That's alarming, right? It depends on the situation, right? You could be playing Halo.
And then it's not that alarming. But if then they go, you know someone who goes, "Oh, I'm going to shoot up a bunch of people tomorrow."
Their voice changes, their voice changes whenever they say this. They're like, "Ah, it's voice changed. It's extra spooky."
That's alarming. But when someone's willing to have a shootout with an armed force, right, you're basically taking it to 11.
If someone goes, "If you're in a comedy club and someone goes, "I got a bomb on me."
Actually, that'd be super alarming too. I was originally going to say, "That's not that scary. That would be super scary."
You're just sitting in a comedy club and you're like, "This comedian bombs and so do I."
And he lifts his shirt up. There's a big bomb on him. I'd give him points. I'd give him points for creativity before he blew me to some of the reins.
But if someone's willing to go, it would be the same thing if someone goes, "I'm going to beat you up."
I'd be like, "Okay, let's go." But if someone came up to me and goes, "I'm going to beat up Conor McGregor."
And then I'm going to beat you up. I'm super scared now.
First, he wants to fight like a super tough dude. And then I'm like the dessert. I'm the crème brûlée.
I don't want to be the crème brûlée. So the fact that he's talking about wanting to have a shootout with the police, that's alarming.
I mean, if any of that would be alarming to someone, if you're walking on the street and someone goes, "I'm going to shoot you in the face."
You're like, "Are you playing Halo right now?" or something. You would be alarming.
But it's more alarming if you want to shoot other people with guns, like the escalation.
You're like, "You're still just shaking your head. You let no Jason." It's all alarming. It's all terrifying.
I don't know why you're fixated on this police shootout.
Anyways, he says he begins to say modern day racist thing.
"Want to have a shootout with the police?" And then one of the comedians, not his favorite comedian,
but I guess like an other comedian came in from the side and was like, "What in the world is going on out here? I'm coming up next."
One type of man is happening. He comes out and the comedian says, "Give me your phone. I want to see your phone, dude."
And Tony's like, "Oh, no, not my phone." And the comedian gets the phone from him and he goes, "Give me your code. Give me your access code for your phone."
And I don't know if it was the drugs in his drink. I don't know if it's because this is a full blown hallucination.
And really in Tony's mind, he's probably just sitting in the comedy club and he just gets up, starts to swear. I mean, I don't know. This is so weird.
Tony then give, he felt so threatened by this guy, he gave the comedian, this other comedian, the password to his phone.
And the comedian's like, "Dude, he's the first off. He's the lame password." And he starts making fun of the guy.
The audience is all laughing. They're writing down his password. They're like, "Get his pin number too."
The comedian gets his pin number and goes through his phone. And again, you thought this was going to get any weirder, right?
First off, there is this guy, this depressed guy sitting in a comedy club, which is just like a painting. That's like a painting you'd see some college freshmen having, right?
He messes up the guy's joke and they just say the rest of the stuff. This is where it hits 11. Just when you thought it couldn't get any crazier,
the comedian starts going through his phone and he, Tony says, "Listen, there was no child porn on it."
Which, it should just be a given, right? It should just be a given on every phone.
You shouldn't have to say that because it shouldn't exist on anybody's phone.
But when somebody is telling you about their phone, when somebody is telling you about their phone and they go, "Well, there's no child porn on it."
I don't know. I would quantify that. I mean, good, right? That's a good thing.
But then I would start to think, "Is this a good thing? Are you saying there's no child porn on it now?"
What it used to be, I don't know. I don't know. He has to clarify.
There was no child porn on the phone, but this is a sentence you never want to add a butt to, right?
There's no child porn on my phone, but he did have screenshots and saved videos of kids and teens from YouTube and Instagram.
And, oddly enough, that's already, you're like, "Whoa, Jason, you totally dropped a bomb on him. I wasn't expecting this at all."
He has basically, he's watching YouTube videos and taking screenshots and saving those onto his phone.
Apparently, he's taking these screenshots of kids and teens when he's watching YouTube videos and keeping them on his phone.
Well, they find these pictures, which, according to him, is not child pornography.
I mean, I mean, I guess that's a philosophical question at a certain point.
If you're using, if it's a photo of a kid and you're using it for lurid purposes, it may not be illegal,
but I don't think you can honestly, I don't think he would pass a lie detector test if they asked you, "Do you have any child porn on your phone?"
He's like, "No." But then he has like 50 gigabytes of just screenshots of not child porn.
He also has notes on his phone. Like, he's been writing a novel, writing these little short stories on his phone.
He says he talks about the dreams he has involving girls from the photographs.
So he was writing basically fan fiction for these screenshots.
He's like, "That's it. My niece is no longer allowed on YouTube. I'm shutting the account down. They're getting all shut down."
You know, this is the reason why they had to remove comments from kids' videos on YouTube, because these perverts were writing down screenshot numbers.
So like, 29 Seconds In is a perfect shot, and you could just click on that and it would bring you right to the shot where she's doing like a somersault or a backflip and the, da-da-da-da-da.
That's why they removed that. Because people were taking innocent videos and basically freeze framing them and turning them into stuff like this.
Right? I don't want to get into the details. I think you can use your imagination.
But yeah, that's why YouTube no longer allows those comments on them.
He said, "Listen guys, because he's defending himself now. Basically he's surrounded."
And that's the question though. Is this physically happening or is this all in his head?
Because it gets even worse.
What Jason, there's no...
Jason, first of all, I don't think it can get worse. And secondly, if it does, I don't want to hear anymore. I don't want to hear anymore.
Don't tell me it gets worse.
Well, I mean, just imagine, I can't put myself in this guy's shoes, but a comedian, a guy who specializes in the same funny stuff at the drop of a hat,
has your phone, not your phone, that's gross, but has somebody's phone and it has not just screenshot.
Enough that it's noticeable. Right?
If there's a screenshot of like one Dallas Cowboy cheerleader in a folder on your phone,
no one's going to accuse you of stalking the Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders.
But if there are so many photographs of the Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders that all someone has to do is open your phone, right?
Just literally put in the password and it pops up and all your icons, all your icons are of Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders.
Your wall screens, Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders, every... I mean, it would have to be that obvious.
I don't think they said grab his phone and you download a download a file search program.
We're going to scrub his phone. We're going to find everything.
It had to be noticeable enough that they just turned it on and they go, "What?"
Anyways, they have this phone with all of these photographs and these detailed vivid dreams.
He's had quote unquote dreams, right? These vivid dreams he has about these girls.
Again, he can't take any responsibility for it. He's obviously like into this disgusting stuff, but he's like, "Oh, no, no, no.
It was just the dreams." And they're like, "Why did you write it down?"
And he goes, "Because I was drunk. I was drunk. I'm drunk all the time."
He says, he's very clear to us. This is not reassuring, but he goes, "Listen, guys, I haven't talked to a minor.
I have not talked to a minor for five years."
And they're like, "Why'd you have the last part? Why'd you have the last part?"
He should have just said, "Never, ever. You've never talked to anyone under the age of 18."
And again, he's talking about when people say teens, a normal person goes, "Oh, like a 16, a 17, an 18-year-old girl."
No, no, no, no, no, no. That's not what these perverts are into.
That's the problem with terms like child porn.
The average person goes, "Oh, is it like Sherry Lorde's? Is it like some 16-year-old girl who looks like she's 19?"
That's not what this is. This is like pre--- they use the term teen.
It's the same thing when someone asks you, "How often do you drink?"
If you say sometimes, that means a lot.
And if you say rarely, that means sometimes.
And if you say never, that means rarely. Like, I always say never. I drink once every two years.
So people kind of always downplay what they do. These are young girls.
Anyways, he says it's not like he had spent five years since he talked to someone who was 18 or 17 years old.
We're talking like 13, probably most likely 13 and under.
If anybody hasn't talked to one in five years, you gotta give him a brownie point.
Not a brownie point. Not a brownie point.
The brownies are safely back in their clubhouse.
He says, "Listen, and before anyone thinks I'm a pervert," which he stated this real late in the game, right?
We're already believing this stuff. He goes, "Listen, before anyone thinks I'm a pervert, I want to be very, very clear about something.
I have never, ever paid any of them to have sex with me."
But, again, this is not a time you want to use the word "but." He's never, ever, ever.
What type of monster do we think this guy is? He has never, ever, ever offered one of these girls money to have sex with him.
But, he has offered to take them on dinner dates.
That's not... No, it's gonna go all okay then.
You're not... You don't have some crippling mental illness.
You just want to date the 13-year-old girl. You don't want to pay money for your...
Like, how was that? In his mind, I'm sure that is a... See, look, I'm a good guy, man.
I'm gonna go on on dates. I don't know what his thought process is. They're both terrible.
Anyways, well, he's about to get his wish. Somebody... Not... Not that wish. Not that wish.
There's some nine-year-old in the audience. She's like, "I kind of like the cut of this guy's gym."
No. Somebody called the cops. Somebody called the cops in for a man who wanted to have a shootout with the police.
That wish. Somebody calls the cops and when the cops show up, according to him...
And I don't... I'll be honest. I don't put this past the police. I don't put this past the police at all.
But according to him, the police, when they showed up, beat him up.
He says that they beat him up. They stomped on him. They choked him.
They spit on him. And... This is so interesting. I didn't even think about this when I wrote this down.
This actual... His actual quote was, "Beat, stomped, choked, spit on, and..."
This really goes to show his mind state. Think about everything that's happened to him up to this point.
And when the cops show up, he gets beat, stomped, choked, spit on, and humiliated.
Like, that's the way he ends his list of assaults. Humiliated.
That seems to be the worst thing for him. That seems to be the thing he fears the most.
And that's kind of what this whole night has been. It's a humiliation ritual.
Then he also said, "And then they made fun of him, and then he goes on and says, 'They pushed me down some stairs.'
Which again, I don't put that... I'm not going, 'What? The police?' They would never do that.
This guy's putting false allegations against law enforcement. Look, I'm up.
I'm pretty sure that happened. I'm pretty sure the cops showed up and were like,
'Oh, let me see your phone real quick.' And then they pushed him down the stairs.
And they don't put that past the police department. If they get a call, there's a child molester here who said he wanted to shoot cops.
I'm pretty sure you're going to get pushed down the stairs, right?
Beats, stomped, choked, spit on, humiliated, and they push him down the stairs.
And then he goes. He didn't get a ticket. He didn't get arrested. He didn't get a ticket.
Which makes sense too, right? Because then the cops got a process paperwork.
And they'd have to explain where they got called down to this comedy club.
And this dude looks like he just went three rounds with two police officers.
But what happened, again, this all ties back to the humiliation thing. According to him,
all of this stuff, because he's in a comedy club, right? He's in a comedy club.
There's cameras everywhere. You got 30 or 40 witnesses to all this stuff.
They got their cell phone cameras.
Apparently video of this, which I would easily pay money for.
I would love to see video footage of this.
But here's the thing. I don't even know if this happened.
Not that he made the story up. I'm wondering how much of this is just in his head.
That he actually went to the comedy club and just had a psychotic break.
But anyways, he said that this video footage of this event, this happened back in like 2021.
He goes, the video footage of this event was posted on his social media.
And he's afraid of vigilante attacks. He's afraid of vigilantes coming after him.
He posted this this year, back in June of 2022.
He's posting it because he was saying, my uncle's car recently got vandalized.
I think it's because of vigilante attacks. And here's why.
And then he just typed out this insane story, which he invites more vigilante attacks.
Right. Anyways, he posted this up and he's afraid that he's a target of vigilante attacks.
He's thinking of suing. I don't know if that's specifically the comedy club or the comedians or the police or everybody.
The Italians. I don't know exactly who he's thinking about suing, but he's thinking of suing.
Everyone's constantly thinking of suing in America. That means nothing.
He has met with a lawyer, which again, I would have paid money.
I would ask the lawyer, hey, how much do you charge an hour?
Okay, I will have to sit in this room while you talk to this new client.
He's like, what? Okay, I love money. That's why I'm a lawyer and you're sitting there and this Tony dude walks in and sits down and goes,
so let me tell you what happened the other night.
Just to watch the lawyer's face. The lawyer's like, oh man, I've seen some stuff in my life, but this is insane.
He's thinking about suing. He met a lawyer. He's currently back in therapy, which is good, right?
If you need therapy, it's good to be there and probably stay there because he went back.
So that means he stopped at some point and he's going into rehab, which is good too.
It's funny because rehab, I think of drug and alcohol stuff, but maybe it's even darker than that.
He obviously has some mental problems.
Allegedly, Tony, if you try to sue me, trust me, you don't want me on the stand test if I need to get to you.
It's a terrifying story. It's a fascinating story. It's a story of mental illness.
It's a story of people attacking a stranger in public, maybe.
It's a story of a psychotic break, possibly.
But either way, it's just fascinating, right? It's a look at the world that we don't have, that most people...
I mean, listen, I'll get lost in the dream world from time to time, but I don't think I've ever confused the dream world with reality.
Well, I guess I don't know if he has either, and you say that he did that, but I have no proof of that.
But I can see that happening, but it's fascinating because I think that all of us, even though we're not perfect,
even though we have our own challenges, like I said at the beginning, I'm dyslexic.
I have severe learning disorder when it comes to math.
Recently on an episode, I tried to do 60 minus 15, and I got it wrong.
I said it was 44. That wasn't a bit. I actually left that in, and I was laughing, and I go,
"I think people should know exactly how bad I am at math."
Like, that wasn't a bit. Originally, I was going to edit that out, and when I was listening back to it, I was laughing so hard.
I have a really hard time with math.
I have double vision. I have time dysmorphia.
I've had multiple concussions throughout my life. I'm probably somewhere on the spectrum.
I think pretty much everyone is on the spectrum other than a very few people.
I think most people are probably on the autism spectrum from one into another, but we all suffer from it.
I think no one's perfect, right? We all suffer from our own things, but even with all that added up,
even with all the stuff that I've gone through, I had a heart attack when I was a baby.
My mom denies that story. She goes, "No, you didn't."
And I go, "Well, that's what my medical report says. You guys didn't have a heart attack when you were a baby."
Anyways, we all have our issues, but when you meet someone who's truly, truly either having a psychotic break
or is in the real world interpreting events so differently, you can't tell if it's all made up or a little bit made up.
I don't know if this was a full psychotic break, which to me is scarier.
Imagine sitting next to someone and they're playing this whole thing out in their head, this whole scenario.
You're just sitting there and he blows a punchline and the comedian goes, "Up yours, buddy."
He comes to a couple of my shows, "I think you need to get a life."
And then the comedian goes on with the rest of his show and you're just sitting next to this guy and he's descending into a world of make-believe.
This whole story happens in his mind. None of it's real.
But he's sitting there in the nightclub and he's imagining standing up and hurling out these words and he's imagining about going,
"And I'll shoot all the police. Send them all down."
And what's even weird about that is if that's the case, if this wasn't real story, if it was all in his mind, even in his own dream world,
he's humiliated, he's mocked, he's beat up by the police, even in this psychotic break, he's still the victim.
Which I guess not to say it. I don't think many psychotic breaks are relaxing.
I think they're called psychotic for a reason.
I honestly don't know what's scarier.
We know as people how to deal with perverts and weirdos and sickos and stuff like that.
We know how to deal with them. Generally it's just to avoid them.
But if it's made up, if it's all in his head, it's just fascinating to see the world through their eyes.
And again, you have that perfect balance like a Max Kramer type character where you have someone who's crazy enough that it lets you see the world through the eyes of a crazy person,
but also sane enough to be able to spell words correctly and write out sentences that are comprehensible.
Like sometimes you don't have that second part, it's just the ramblings of a madman.
This you could understand.
So just a fascinating look at mental illness and psychosis and comedy clubs.
Comedy clubs, I guess the moral of the story is don't jump on your favorite comedian's punchlines,
because they may find a not-child porn on your phone.
I guess that's the moral that Tony learned.
But yeah, this guy's still out there and who knows how the story's going to end. He hasn't posted anymore.
I'm pretty sure his account is deleted, so we'll never know if anyone else starts posting is him again.
You know, is it just a fake?
We don't know if he ever stayed in therapy and got the help that he needed.
We don't know if he left therapy because he left it already, right?
He said I went back to therapy. He might have left therapy and started taking more screen shots from YouTube.
And again, that's a band-aid.
If your brain is so warped that you think that's okay,
then the only reason why you're not looking at child porn is because it is illegal at that point.
You're still using it for the same purpose.
So we don't know. Maybe he got rid of all that stuff.
He's like he's giving that phone away. He's like hey, you want a free phone?
Some hobo's like yeah, sure. And he's like oh, this is horrible.
We don't know if he got rid of all that stuff. We don't know if he kept descending down that dark road.
We don't know if he got the help that he needed or we don't know if he had a shootout with the police.
Like we don't know. We'll never really know how this story ends.
If he's still alive and he's still going through these delusions,
he's in this world where vigilantes are around every corner.
And anything bad that happens to him, it's because of the vigilantes.
And that's just gangstalking at that point.
Like this is just one of those crazy stories. It was one night in this guy's life, the worst night of his life.
And I agree. If this story is even halfway through, it is the worst night of his life.
And it will continue to impact him for years and years because every bad thing that happens to him,
he's going to chalk up to these vigilantes who watched clips on social media of people rummaging through his phone.
Which I don't even know if that exists. It's so bizarre.
It's so weird. Imagine if that video footage doesn't even exist if it's all made up.
But he's imagining anything bad happening to him is because of video footage that doesn't exist.
It really kind of boggles the mind. I love this story.
The content's a little rough, especially for this close to the end of the season,
but it's such a fascinating look at mental illness. Such a fascinating look at psychosis.
And we're still left wondering how much of it was real and what happens next.
How does this story end? And those are questions that will never be answered.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also go to set up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
TikTok is @deadrabberadio. DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great day.
[Music]
(upbeat music)