A bizarre, controversy rocks.
Australia's parliament.
And then we go back in time to take a look at the story of Captain Jason Seabury.
Historical reports say that his ship mysteriously vanished off the coast of Alaska.
But when you dig deeper into the reports, his death may have not been mysterious after all.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
I don't know if I'm a big gal, actually I'm a rock big gal.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hey, I'm recording
this in a totally new location. You know what, before I go into that, I want to get your
feedback on the sound quality. But before I go into that, let's introduce our Patreon
supporter, our legacy Patreon supporter, coming into Dead Rabbit Command floating around.
He's a ghost. He's a piece of toast. Hopefully, oh my god that's in bad taste. Hopefully, he's
still alive. But for this introduction, give a round of applause to Joel Gonzalez. He's
like, has a little Casper. Casper has regular legs. He has a little slimer legs. Like they
just come a little wiggle at the bottom. He's floating around. He's alive in real life.
Hopefully, but right now he's a ghost. Joel, you're going to be our captain, our pilot's
episode. If you guys can't support the Patreon, or if you are still alive, again hopefully,
that's fine too. That's actually amazing if you're still alive. Just helps spread the
word about the show. Really, really helps out a lot.
So the reason why Joel is a ghost, and the reason why I might sound differently, is
man, yesterday's episode took forever to record. I had it start taking a lot of breaks because
it's getting so noisy in the neighborhood. It's spring. People are out talking to their
friends, building bonds with fellow humans and things like that. I'm not going to rain
on their parade. I have no right to anyways. But it was getting too noisy to record, and
I've noticed that trend coming on for a while. So thanks to Patreons like Joel, I've actually
started to invest in some acoustic sound dampening foam for the microphone. I'm really going
to really pimp out this studio. And right now I have moved the studio out of my living
room into my haunted closet. I am recording this in my haunted closet. It actually is
dead quiet in here. The second I go in my living room, I hear a bunch of people laughing.
So we're going to see, you guys let me know, email me, because we don't have the YouTube
thing anymore. Email me and let me know how the sound quality is here. Is it better? Is
it noticeably better? Do you not notice a difference? Anything like that. But Joel is
a ghost in case, I'm pretty sure the ghost in my closet is chill at this point. I say
as I've invaded his home to yell for 35, 40 minutes about random stuff. But Joel, let's
go ahead, take a corporeal form, and I'm going to hand you the hair hang glider. Let's get
our journey started. We're leaving behind Jason's haunted closet. I'm stuck here. You
guys are leaving the closet. I'm there with you in spirit. We're leaving behind my haunted
closet and Dead Ravac Man. We're headed out to Australia. Joel is so used to flying in
his ghost form. He gets us there in no time. Specifically, we're headed to Capitol Hill.
That's in Canberra in Australia. And most of this information, I just saw this article
the other day. Most of this information I got from an article written for the Daily Beast
by Jamie Ross. So thank you, Jamie, for putting this all together. We walk into the House of
Parliament in Australia. And we go and we sit down. We're disguised as Australians. We're
just kind of sitting there. And we all look like the sniper from Team Fortress 2. And
we're watching this investigation unfold. These police are walking up to a desk and
they're like dusting it. And then they're like, mmm. And then they put on gloves and
then they're still like, hmm, hmm. And they're like, you're the rookie, right? And the rookie's
like, uh, yeah. And they go, you, you do this, you touch the desk, you do all the investigative
stuff. The rookie's like, dang it. So he puts on like three pairs of gloves and he's like
touching the desk and he's like, crikey, mate. The legends are true. So that's a really long
introduction to basically say people, people in Australia. Sorry, wait, wait, wait, before
I go any further, if you have any kids listening to this podcast, usher them out, put them
in their own haunted closets for the first segment. It turns out that what is going on,
that long introduction was leading to this, a bunch of dudes have been jacking off on women's
desks at the House of Parliament. So I know there was kind of a rush of information. So
let me break that down for you again. Men are videotaping themselves, masturbating and ejaculating,
not just pretending to like hump the desk. Me like, look at me ejaculating on members
of parliament's desks who are women. Because they want to do a man's desk, right? That's
a little gay. It's all grow. Let me start breaking this down here. A desk is a desk,
right? A man's desk is a woman's desk. The fact that they're targeting the women's desk,
it's almost like sexual revenge, you know what I mean? If they were just masturbating
on everyone's desk, they'd be like, okay, they have a problem. They just left a masturbate
they're doing it in public, which that's not a problem, it's a crime. That's one thing,
but the fact that they're specifically targeting women's desks, it adds a little more malice
to it. You know what I mean? If you found out that someone jacked off in your drink,
you'd get really really upset. You'd probably get violently upset. But if you found out
that he ejaculated in everybody's drink, he'd be like, oh, Barry, he's all blushing.
Yeah, right. I mean, it's still disgusting, but it's less targeted. So this has been going
on for a while. But luckily we have a whistleblower going by the name of Tom. Whistleblower Tom
has come forward and his job is to expose the pervert parties of parliament. Like I
said, there is a video of a man, he's all pixelated. There was a horrible birth defect.
He was born pixelated, but he's pixelated and he's masturbating at a female parliament
member's desk. So we have that. And then Tom has this quote in this Daily Beast article,
quote, "The fact that it is a female MP, a minister of parliament, only adds to the
disgrace that it is." Unquote. I fully, fully agree with you, Tom. Like again, if you're
doing it to everyone's desk, that's gross, but the fact that they're targeting a particular
group. If they were just doing it on men's desks and not women's desks, I wouldn't be
like progressive. I would still be like they're obviously targeting for some reason. So Tom
has exposed this thing. Tom, I really want to thank you. And then I read the very next
sentence of the Daily Beast article, quote, "The whistleblower, who was identified only
as Tom in the report, admitted to taking part in some of the misconduct, but said he decided
that the time is right to expose what's been going on." Unquote. So Tom, Tom wasn't Batman's
sending in the rafters. He's like, "Ah, the day of justice will come. I just need more
evidence. I just need more evidence of these men masturbating other than this video footage."
He was doing it too. He's like standing next to two guys and they're all playing soggy
cracker with people's desks. And then he feels guilty and he's like, "Oh, I must expose
these villains. I must expose these villains now that I'm done. I'm not going to wait five
minutes for everyone else to finish." No, I must expose them. And so on the one hand,
it's good that he's exposing them, but on the other hand, he was doing it too. He was
jacking off on these people's desks. He said there's a little room in the parliament building
that people go to for prayer or meditation. And Tom's like, "You won't believe what happens
in there. You won't believe the one time I went in there." He's shifting from side
to side. He goes, "Listen, people have sex in there. People go in that room and have
sex in there." So it's not just that they're masturbating on desks. They're also having
sex in the prayer room. If I had a choice between walking by a room and I heard two
people having sex or sitting down on my desk and going to get a post-it note and noticing
they're a little more sticky than normal, I would much rather walk by. Much rather walk
by the door with the "Ah, ooh, ah." Make sure your kids are still in the haunted closet.
This segment's not done yet. We got another quote from Tom. Quote, "Now is the time to
speak up. Now is the time to put it on the record. It is a culture of men thinking that
they can do whatever they want." I like to imagine that Tom, after saying that quote,
continued, "Including me. Including me. I belong to a culture of men given all the
do-types, given the male reporter a high-five because I don't want to touch your hand."
He's like, "Yeah, up until five minutes ago, I thought that I could do whatever I want.
But now, I was totally wrong. I was totally wrong the multiple times I masturbated on
women's desks. No more! I'm gonna rat everyone else out." And again, I want to say I'm glad
that he's ratting people out. I'm glad that he exposed this. But I don't think we can
whitewash this guy. There's no pun intended. I don't think we can whitewash this dude's
involvement. He was part of it and we'll get to why, not why he was doing it. That's just
being a pervert, but why he exposed it at the end, which I think is very, very telling.
It wasn't... He saw a culture of men thinking whatever they could do. There's a little...
I don't know what the libel laws are in Australia. But my hypothesis, my theory, I can imagine
Tom coming into my haunted closet right now and he goes, "You know what, Jason? I had
the courage to stand up and expose myself. I mean, expose the truth. Why are you making
fun of me?" Well, Tom, let's take a closer look at this article. It does say in the
article that Tom is afraid that he may be fired for leaking the story, not leaking on
people's desks, but now he's afraid that because he leaked the truth about himself and other
people committing inappropriate acts in a government building, that that's why he'll
be fired. Not because they'll dig up something or find his DNA all over the place. Here we
have this... This is a powerful quote. Quote. "It needs to start with the removal of this
toxic, powerful, privileged boys club that does what it wants, when it wants, where it
wants." To which I imagine Tom added onto that quote. And again, that's what I was doing
five minutes ago. I did what I wanted, when I wanted, and where I wanted was on that desk.
That chair you're sitting on, reporter. You might want to take pregnancy tests when you
get home. Reporters are like, "I'm a dude." He's like, "My jizz is that powerful." So
what prompted this? Did he really have a change of heart? I think this is really interesting.
And this is where the joke's in. This is also where the joke's in. Just recently, there
was a young woman, Brittany Higgins, 26-year-old worker at the House of Parliament. She filed
a report that she had been raped by a co-worker. And the federal police have started investigating
this. They're coming down to the House of Parliament. They're interviewing people. And
the idea was that this rape, this... No joke, not funny part. This rape of this young woman
was sparking conversations about the whole culture of the House of Parliament and the
way that sex was viewed in this place, these very powerful people, preying on vulnerable
people. You have powerful senior politicians preying on interns. The oldest story in the
book. And now this story gets exposed. This isn't the oldest story in the book. This normally
doesn't happen. But I'm wondering, put on our conspiracy caps, we're in Australia, so
put them on upside down. My theory is, and I have nothing to back this up. My theory
is, and I won't even say Tom was doing it just for illegal reasons, but my theory is
certain people may have been scared knowing that there is now federal police investigation
looking into sex crimes in the building and somebody said, "We're all gonna get caught,
so I'm gonna be the hero you guys can get caught." The difference is, and this is always
the thing about snitches and rats and stuff like that, I think the easiest way to kind...
If you view a horrible crime and you're not a participant in it, you should say something.
I have a little asterisk, if it involves gangs you have to really weigh your family safety
if it involves a street gang or something like that. But for the most part, if you see
a crime and you have nothing to do with it, I think you have a moral right to say... I
think you have a moral duty to say something about it. But if you're a participant in said
crime and you feel like everyone's gonna get wrapped up super fast, so you start spilling
the beans, that's when you're basically a snitch. Now you can be a snitch and do good,
do a net good for society like exposing this perversion. I'm not saying that you should
have kept his mouth shut. Snitches get stitches, or in this case snitches get sticky, but...
Because they're masturbating on him. The haunted closet, I don't know if my jokes are landing
in the haunted closet. My point is that it was a net good for society to expose these
people, but the article made it seem like Tom was this noble figure and maybe he is.
It doesn't say exactly what he was doing, it just said he participated in the activities.
I can't imagine a time I'd be hanging out with my friends, my coworkers and they're
like "hey man what's up?" I was like "hey dude what's going on man, did you guys watch
Justice League, Zack Snyder Cut?" They're like "yeah, it took me two days to watch
it, it was pretty good, yeah I really really enjoyed it. Flash is my favorite character
out of the movie, yeah it's pretty cool. Hey uh do you want to masturbate on this desk?"
What? What did you just say? Hey man you want to come over here and masturbate on this
desk? We all have. I look over, I'm like "oh dang it." Like I don't know, that was my
desk, that was my desk getting ready to clock in to work. I can't imagine myself getting
talked into that. And again there's so many layers to that, I can't imagine myself getting
talked into that. I definitely couldn't imagine myself targeting people like as a prank. I'm
not saying I would do it, but I could see people just randomly jacking off on desks,
that is, I'm digging myself into a hole. That is more, that's a little more, I don't want
to say tasteful because that's what we're talking about. You know what I mean, it's
a difference between, imagine if I was walking down the street and I was bashing people,
this is something I can do, it's something I can relate to. I'm walking on the street
bashing in car windows with a baseball bat and I'm just doing it randomly. Versus me
going "I don't like that type of person and I'm targeting the cars that have bumper stickers
that make me think it's that person." That's the difference to me, that's the difference
to me. You may not care when you're, you may not care when you're windows busted, but
you know if you look down the street and you saw people of all religions and colors and
creeds and ethnicities and all their windows are busted, you will say "whoever did this,
whoever did this, may be a jerk." But he is not a racist, he is definitely not a racist,
he just loves smashing windows. That's the difference between people like me and people
like the members of parliament, the masturbating ones, not the other politicians.
After that incredibly uncomfortable story, let's talk about a movie called Happily, new
today on Digital and On Demand. Joel McCaill and Carrie Bache lead an all-star cast in
a dark romantic comedy, Happily. The film centers around a couple who, after 14 years
of marriage, discover their friends are resentful of their constant public displays of affection.
When a visit from a mysterious stranger leads to a dead body, they begin to question the
loyalty of their so-called friends. Buy or rent Happily today on Digital and On Demand,
rated R, from Paramount Pictures. Dude, I really want to watch this movie. I actually went
to go get it loaded up, but my internet was acting kinda goofy. I'll probably watch it
tonight. I really want to watch it. Joel Gonzalez. Here comes the tickle monster. He's
like "what?" Where'd this come from? I'm tickling Joel Gonzalez, I don't know. Just popped
in my head. I'm tickling, tickling, everyone get a good tickle on Joel Gonzalez. Joel,
let's put you in the Carbinder copter. He's like "this is humiliating man. This is totally
humiliating. You haven't tickled any of your other Patreon supporters, so then you should
feel special." Joel, let's put you in the Carbinder copter. We are leaving behind all
of Australia and we are headed on out to the Pacific Ocean. And hit that little button
right there. We're going back in time to January 18th, 1852. Carbinder copter's flying over
an empty Pacific Ocean. This wind is still, we're just cruising baby. We're just cruising
over the ocean. We hear Joel go "man why are the controls for the Carbinder copters so
sticky?" Jason and I'm all "ooh" and I'm all blushing. Joel Gonzalez takes me, wash
off the controls and fly us on out through the middle of the Pacific Ocean. I love this
story. This is part two of our Sea Monster Week Sea Serpent Week. You guys know long
time listeners of the show know I really don't like Sea Monsters Sea Serpents because
it's the same thing over and over again, but this story. This story is actually reported
in the Maritime Heritage Project. You can tell from the name, it's a pretty snooty
organization. They talk about ropes and coils and what type of wood was on what type of
boat. It's basically a cumulation of all sorts of historical facts that if it did
not involve the subject of this story, I would be super bored. There are also documents
if you look at the Wailing Museum in New Bedford. They have the papers of the family
of the main character of this story. So this is not some flight of fancy. Or is it? Let's
take a look at it. Let's take a look at the story. I love the story. It's January 18th,
1852. And Captain Jason Seabury is on the deck of the Manga Hela. Manga Hela. Splash!
The boat is moving over the waves. We're dressed up like old time pirates. We're walking around.
We all look like Snead or whatever his name was from Peter Pan. Captain Jason Seabury
turns around and goes, "How do these pirates get on my ship?" Immediately we change clothes.
Now we're wearing American naval clothes or whatever. Just American clothes, Swabby clothes,
whatever. Probably going to research it, but I'm stuck in a haunted closet. So I can't.
The Manga Hela, Captain by Jason Seabury, I'm going to keep saying his first name because
it's the best name ever, is floating alongside the Rebecca Sims. Now they're both wailing
vessels and the Rebecca Sims is Captain by Captain Gavit. The Rebecca Sims is actually
coming back from its wailing journey and the Manga Hela is just getting started. Their
headquarters is New Bedford and where they're headed is Alaska. Get some whales, chop them
up. I don't know what they do with them. Cook them. I don't think they cook them on the boat.
They're like the whole boat is super smoky. They're trying to throw two tons of meat into
the boiler. But you know they get whale and whale fat and whale skin and whale eyeballs
for witches and stuff like that. These boats though are kind of stuck in the Pacific Ocean
at this point because there's no wind. There's just a little bit of wind, but not a lot.
But you know what are you going to do? You're just kind of hanging out and boats are just
kind of sitting there just going with the motion of the ocean. It's all you can do.
And then we hear "Captain! Captain!" and we look up and there's a dude in the little
crow's nest and he has like a telescope and he's like "Captain! That thing! There's something
over there! Look! Look!" and the captain pulls out his own telescope and he looks and he
sees this large shape in the water and he's like "Hmm, interesting. It must be a whale
that was hit with a harpoon but it didn't die. So, men, let's go put it out of its
misery. Let the feast begin! Let's eat this whale right now!" He orders three long boats
to approach the wounded whale and put it out of its misery. So Captain Gavitt's on his
boat, he's a bit farther off, and then Captain Jason Seabury's on his boat and they're watching
these three long boats go towards this shape. Now they're not really expecting anything.
They just expect like to see a bunch of blood. They're super blood thirsty captains. They're
all blood, blood, blood. They're never really expecting anything. They're just keeping an
eye on what's going on. The long boats get to the shape and they get a harpoon ready
and they launch it into the water and the second the harpoon pierces the skin of this
lump, it rises up out of the water. Now these three long boats are very, very close to this
thing and all they see is a giant head up here. It's about ten feet long and it looks
like a crocodile's head. And it thrashes the water so much two of the long boats get instantly
capsized. "Overboard! Oh, matey! Look out! A land ho! Other pirate stuff! Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
capsized. The guys on the long boat that hasn't been tipped over, they're like "We're not pirates
you idiots quitsane pirate stuff." But the creature is still there, a fresh harpoon in
its body. The Rebecca Sims and the Manga Hela start moving to the long boats. They gotta
rescue these guys. They don't know what it is, but remember there's not a lot of wind
so it's a slow journey but they're able to muster just enough wind to get to the long
boats, they rescue all the sailors. The boats pull alongside each other and Captain Jason
Seabaring and Captain Gavid are talking about what was that. They didn't get a great look
at it but it didn't look like a whale and the men were like "That was no whale sir."
But there's no wind, they're still stuck on there, they can't make any formatable change
of movement. By the next morning they look and the creature is now dead.
When they stuck with the harpoon it thrashed about and went underwater but now it has risen
to the top. And it is huge. It's 100 feet long and 10 feet of that is just its head.
From nose to the tip of the tail it's 100 feet long. It's a brownish grey color with
a white stripe 3 feet thick running along its side. You're like "Crap the stripe is
3 feet thick, how big is the thing?" It's 100 feet long, how thick is it? It's 50 feet
in diameter. So what's that like 5 stories of a building? That's how thick it is. Captain
Jason Seabaring is looking down at this thing and he goes "I..." He's got the pirate infection
as well. He got bit by a pirate in the middle of the night. He's looking at this thing and
he goes "I've heard the stories." We've all heard the stories of sea monsters. And people
come back to port. And they're laughed, they're ridiculed. But we have proof ladies and gent...
There's no ladies here, we have proof gentlemen. Now obviously they can't carry a 100 foot
long creature that's 50 feet in diameter. It won't fit on the ship. And then they're
thinking "Well we can't drag it." Actually that's not the story I'm adding that part.
But I was thinking they can't drag it because it would start to decompose and little fishies
would be eating it and eventually they'd be like "Here's our prize!" And it's just
like "Well that's still a giant skeleton but you couldn't drag it." So he orders its head
chopped off. He goes "If anything we can keep this head." So they chop the head off, they
bring that on board. That's only 10 feet long. And like I said it was in the shape of a crocodile's
head. It had teeth like a serpent where they were like angled. Like that sound effect doesn't
help. You know what I mean? Like a snake's teeth how it's like the hook. It has the hook
teeth. Each tooth is 3 inches long. There's 94 of them. Captain Jason Seabury goes "Good
we got this head. We got this head. Now we gotta preserve it so they pickle it." They
put in a giant jar of pickles. They're like "Okay everyone eat all the pickles today
because we need this giant jar, this giant jar of plastic pickles that my mom sent us
with." Let's empty it out. They put the head and they pickle it to preserve it. And he
goes "We're gonna bring this back." But he also writes up a very detailed report about
what happened. Now remember the Rebecca Sims is headed back to New Bedford in Massachusetts.
And that is where the Manga Hela launched from. Captain Jason Seabury he wants this as proof
that sea monsters exist. But also I think part of him wanted the glory of bringing it back.
And at the end of the day this was a commercial fishing vessel. They needed to get these whales.
So he told Captain Gavity says "I'm gonna give you this detailed report all these findings
that we have. You take this back to New Bedford and then I will return to New Bedford in a
couple months after we're done whaling and the world will finally have proof that sea
monsters really do exist." Now obviously we know in the future, in the year 2021, this
head doesn't exist. It's not in a museum anywhere. There was never any papers written
about this head showing up and what a huge psychological thing it was when the world
realized that there be monsters is actually true. It was actually a true warning. The
Rebecca Sims came back to New Bedford and they turned in the paperwork and people were
excited to see this head. It was reported in newspapers all around the world that this
head was going to show up, that this sea monster had actually been captured. But the ship,
the Manga Hela, captained by Jason Seabury, never returned to New Bedford. Years later.
On Umnock Island off the coast of Alaska, a piece of debris is found washed up on the
beach. It is weathered by the waves. It is weathered by time. But it is still quite clear
what name is written on this name board from a boat. Manga Hela. Manga Hela. Or the correct
pronunciation of that word. So the boat was never found. The name plate was found off
the coast of Alaska. And at that point that kind of solved the mystery. The boat never
showed up. You assumed it was lost at sea but when the name plate shows up washed up
on a beach in the location that it would have been going to, it definitely seals the deal.
They didn't go to Bahama and become pirates because they all got bit by pirates, caught
the pirate disease and eventually succumbed to it. This is really interesting story because
what we know is real is. The captain is real. The story is supposedly real. Supposedly there
are documents based on this. Based on this story. You have to want, this is where you
start to get fishy, no pun intended. Was it a story Captain Jason Seabury made up? Or
a story that Captain Gavitt made up for whatever reason. He goes, "Ah, that Captain, Captain
Jason Seabury is totally going to wreck that ship in Alaska. I'm going to write this crazy
tale and he'll never be around to expose it anyway." So the names are real. The boat
names are real. The Manga Hela was lost at sea in 1853. It was considered, it was never
seen again. All these details are real. The only thing we can't verify is because everyone
who witnessed it is dead is the monster's head. But these documents do exist. And again
if I was reading this on a French website, no offense. I love ThinkAboutDocs.com, Mysterious
Universe, Anom, Alien, all this stuff. I love this. But if this story appeared on those
sites, I would be a little more suspicious due to the documents actually exist, that
those boats actually exist. But because this is coming from the MaritimeHeritage.org
website and the Wadley Museum.org website, to be fair the Wadley Museum.org website only
verifies that Captain Jason Seabury is real and that he has papers in the New Bedford
Wailing Museum. They don't specifically say there's the monster head as part of those
papers. But they do confirm basic facts about the story. Is the story actually real we don't
know and we never know with these type of stories because they're so long ago. But
let's put on our conspiracy caps here and say that it's real because that's the world
we want to live in where ghosts and ghouls and haunted closets actually exist. And I
think for a huge portion of it, it is real. I think for a huge portion of it, it is real.
I... conspiracy caps fully on. What if Captain Jason Seabury's boat wasn't lost at sea,
it wasn't a storm, they didn't run out of provisions, the boat just didn't take on
too much water. What if they traveled with the head of a nearly extinct species? But
for a species to live that long to get that big to continue to exist, it would have to
have a mate. Was it the last of its kind or was there a second one or a family of them?
In the ocean as well. And while the first creature was sick or wounded in some way, they
saw it get finished off and chopped up by this Captain. And so they followed it. They didn't
understand what these giant wooden monsters that barely floated on the surface of their
environment were. They couldn't make sense of all the noises that they heard as they
swam silently underneath it, stalking this vessel. They didn't know what they were following
other than the murderer of one of their family. And so these creatures silently stalked
this boat. And while the men on board slept, when the men on board worked, when the men
on board played their accordions with parrots on their shoulders, these creatures simply
watched them. Until eventually, it was time to strike. I would like to hope that Captain
Jason Seabury and the good crew of the Manga Hela fought valiantly as a hundred foot serpent
wrapped itself around the boat and began to coil itself tight, smashing timber and destroying
the vessel. I like to think that swords were drawn, serpent flesh was cut, harpoons were
closed, torches were lit and held against its scaly skin. And in the darkness of night,
they saw two more serpents rise from the water surrounding the Manga Hela. I like to think
they fought valiantly that night. I like to think they died bravely. But whether they
did or not, we don't know. We just know the only piece of that entire boat left was its
nameplate. Man still builds bigger and stronger and faster boats and claims the globe is their
own. Land, water and air are the dominion of humanity. But is it really? We don't know
what lurks in the depths of the ocean, but the depths of the ocean knows what sails on
their waters. We only exist on the ocean because they allow us that right. Because at any point
they could decide to rise up and take back the waters. They could turn the beautiful
blue oceans blood red.
[Music]
[MUSIC]