Is there truly a conspiracy theory to make you look stupid whenever you're using the
internet?
Then we traveled to Arkansas to meet a middle class family living their best life.
But when a 13 year old boy is woken up in the middle of the night and sees a ghastly
specter in his living room, he has no idea his entire life is about to change.
It's a day on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing.
We got a ton of stuff to cover today so first off walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one
of our Thanksgiving live stream contributors.
Get on your feet and give it up for Rico and Aucopulco.
I know it's a country.
I know Rico is in Aucopulco.
Aucopulco?
That's how you say it.
Rico and Aucopulco.
You're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially I totally understand.
I really do.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
Really really helps out a lot.
Rico I'm going to go ahead and toss you a shovel and a little conductor's cap.
Let's hop on board the Carpenter Caboose.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Chug chug chug us all the way out to a government facility.
Chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug chug
Rico was taking us to the secret government facility and we're wearing our government
clothes.
We're in black suits, black shades, black shoes.
Walking around this military base and they're like saluting us and stuff.
They're like oh it's the men in black.
I don't know you guys are going to be here.
I love that song Will Smith.
We're walking around this government facility and we walk past the secret weapon experiments
where they're injecting people with growth hormones.
They're like they're beating up the scientists and stuff like that.
That's not what we're here for.
And then we pass the cloning facility where they're cloning a guy and there's like two
of them and the scientists inject them both in growth hormones and they're beating up
each other.
Yeah maybe next time we'll check them out.
The reason why we're going to this government facility is we're going to the information
warfare room.
Sounds dope right?
Sounds really cool.
You're like no I want to go back to the clone fights.
We're going to this information warfare room and we walk in and we expect to see a bunch
of like cyber warriors, people wearing computer graphic armor, hitting each other with computer
graphic swords.
No.
It's a guy sitting in front of a computer and he's like tickity-tack-tack-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick-tick.
He's typing into his keyboard and we're like hey bro what's up?
And he goes I have the most important job in this facility.
The nuclear people, the people who have nuclear powers and other people who work on nuclear
missiles, they swear that they're the most important but it's me who is constantly saving
the day.
And we go what are you doing man?
Tickity-tack-tack-tickity-tack-tack-tack.
And we see he's sitting there on Reddit and he's changing people's posts.
But not in any sort of meaningful way.
We look and someone has written everything you need to know about the fake moon landing.
And all the guy does is delete the letter E from the word fake.
Everything you need to know about the fact moon landing.
The man leans back in his chair and goes yep my job is done for the day.
This is a real interesting conspiracy theory.
I saw this pop up on Reddit and it's funny at first glance you go that's kind of goofy
but I spend a lot of time for the show.
I'm constantly looking for stuff because I'm trying to find stuff nobody else is talking
about.
That's kind of like the big selling point for the show.
I cover stuff no one else is covering.
I'm constantly reading all sorts of different accounts all spread across all these websites
some on popular websites some on just personal blogs.
Well I'm on Reddit the other day and there is this guy going by the name Rainbow Armadillo
Time.
Joey says you type something out you proofread it.
You're proofreading it as you're typing it out like you're clearly seeing what you're
writing down is what you want to say you submit it and when it comes through there's a spelling
error even though you can verify once twice three times that you've spelled it correctly
it's not spelled once you post it.
And Joey says really the reasoning behind this that he's putting forth is it's to make
you look dumb.
There seems to be a hidden hand editing posts.
But not in the sense like let's say you dropped some truth bombs right you are finally able
to show ten reasons that the color orange is satanic.
Which is an actual conspiracy theory but you finally have managed to get ten ways out.
It's not like they'll make super noticeable changes they change it to only eight and people
are like what were the other two.
He says Joey's argument is that they'll change the spelling of words.
They'll let the post stand they'll let the information stay but if you misspell a word
especially in the headline so in Reddit you can't edit your headlines I've never understood
that the technology is obviously there they won't let you edit the headlines websites
like the xboard you can't edit it at all.
It's just there the post is there you can't change anything about it and so if you're typing
out something you're trying to expose the truth about something they'll just misspell
a word this whether it's AI or human director or what have you it will misspell a simple
word so anyone coming across information for the first time will go well this guy's an
idiot this guy's an idiot he's saying that he can prove the science behind Kimtrails
but he can't even spell the word plain correctly right.
He forgot the P he forgot the P it's not a lane what is this it doesn't make any sense
you totally discard the entire argument.
And Joey says that this is an issue and it really really does work and it does because
like I said I read a ton of stuff online I read more online articles and online posts
than I do physical meat it's not even comparable I'm constantly reading to find stuff for the
show and I see a ton of spelling errors and you just have to accept it I don't generally
think that simple spelling errors are a sign of low intelligence in general I know that
you can be typing quickly I make spelling errors I make pronunciation errors but there
are a lot of people who do like there are a lot of people who don't like my show because
of the pronunciation errors and I'm not even sure I'm pronouncing the word pronunciation
correctly because they say well he's saying all this other stuff but if he can't pronounce
aquapoco then I'm gonna discard all of it I've never been that type of person but also
at the same time there might be like a subconscious thing like even if I go well no I'll still
read it even if it's misspelled even it has these grammar issues because I just come across
it all the time I'm sure subconsciously it affects me and it might make me think the
work is a little less well less thought out than if everything was spelled correctly and
Joey saying like this is happening you can and people did reply and they say yeah I've
seen that too and then people were joking around and misspelling stuff on purpose at
least I think they were joking around but it's an interesting conspiracy theory and
it actually makes a lot of sense I don't know how widespread it would be though I don't
know how widespread it would be I don't know if it was like every time you talked about
flat earth or something like that it would misspell words like that I don't know how
widespread because I do see a lot of misspellings but I couldn't say like oh all people who believe
in this conspiracy theory misspell things or anything like that but it's definitely possible
you know we've been talking we talked a lot about AI yesterday we've talked a lot about
bots in the past on the shelf but some of those episodes on the show notes it would be it would
be super easy to implement and once it's there like once that reddit headlines there you
can't edit it it's that misspelling is going to stay and everyone I should say everyone
but a lot of people who come across that information especially for the first time they're going
to disregard all of it because you can't spell earth you had a couple people you had a couple
people mention that when they use their phones to watch videos of just normal everyday things
on YouTube totally fine but when they start watching conspiracy theory content their phone
dies very quickly that's an interesting comparison that's a pretty interesting thing if that
was provable and they actually you could test it yourself I guess I could have tested it
but that's an interesting theory and that was actually put forth by someone online going
by the name morningstar360 and this morningstar dude he also said and again again an interesting
comparison I can be on Amazon I can be on Walmart shopping forever right it's not an
issue but once I start posting stuff about posting stuff that counteracts what the mainstream
media wants you to know my phone gets hot and my battery dies pretty quickly these actually
would be easy things to implement it would not shock me in the least if any of this stuff
was true you could you could test you could test the cell phone thing by watching some
rumble videos versus watching just some regular YouTube videos and you could also argue I
would also argue with that you could say websites like rumble or band.video or whatever Alex
Jones website they may not be as optimized as YouTube so you could say well that it is
actually consuming more energy to consuming more battery power to keep those videos going
that's definitely possible that's definitely possible rumble is definitely not as optimized
as YouTube but it would be interesting to test that theory the the on the fly editing
thing would be harder to test because it doesn't happen every single time but it wouldn't have
to it could happen just enough to discredit the person writing the post because people
openly mock you no matter what your point of view I get it right and it doesn't bug me
I get it where people go I really like your video but you mispronounce this word so the
whole thing is just throwing out the whole thing is just there's my chant chantix video
about the smoking cessation drug that may cause you to kill yourself was a really good
episode but I called it chantrix the whole time and mispronounce the whole time that's
a fair that's a totally fair argument you mispronounce you mispronounce the main thing
in it so every it was hard to even listen to because that was such an obvious error and
so I could see people running into that online and if that was me making a mistake I didn't
I didn't check how to pronounce the word I thought maybe it was maybe it was a Mandela
effect I don't know but super interesting you could easily program it in that if certain
posts are put up 10% of them will have a misspelling in them and it'll just disregard the argument
it will disregard the theory and if it was your very first time coming across that theory
you'd be like I don't even know how to spell I'm just going to disregard all of it in the
videos I don't know how true that is but that would be easy to program in as well you just
put it in an update on the phone and make it hard to go you know it's so funny a lot
of people we've talked about my explosive growth on YouTube due to my shorts my YouTube
shorts I'm going to start doing the YouTube shorts again I never really talked about
this on the back end I was having pretty explosive growth on tiktok where I was getting like
10,000 views 100,000 views on videos on these one minute long true crime videos the YouTube
one lasted longer like I was getting that that spike was there longer tiktok it was
growing and growing and growing and growing and then I did a video a one minute long video
about a guy we talked about it on the show a guy trying to kill another guy so he could
join the Illuminati and it was like someone just turned off a spigot on tiktok like I
it was day after day of growth on tiktok and it was still a true crime story but it mentioned
the word Illuminati once or twice and then it dropped it went I was going from 10,000
to 20,000 to 100,000 views and then it was 300 not 300,000 300 views 400 views 300 views
on my videos it was like someone just put the spigot over there very interesting it's their
platform right they're going to do what they're going to do I still am going to be producing
tiktoks and YouTube shorts because for me it's just more content that I get to do that
I love and it's free advertising for the show but yeah it was just interesting like that
was it that totally shut that spigot off and I don't think there was a human there who
did it I think the AI had if you talk about these topics we're going to shut you down
interesting interesting the way it's all set up Rico and Aucalpulco let's go ahead and
talk to the keys the world famous carboner copter we are leaving behind this government
facility take us all the way out to Arkansas this is a story of a family young family living
out in Arkansas they live out by the Ozark Mountains they're not actual they're not actually
like people from the wrong turn movies they're normal they're normal people who live near
the Ozark Mountains I'm sure there are normal people that live in the Ozark Mountains but
they're they're near enough to them that they can often go fishing and hunting and hiking but then
they come back to normal modern society when they don't have to worry about being caught by wrong
turn in bread mutants it's a good family it's a family of four you got a mother and a father
older son and a younger daughter this story was posted online we don't know what this guy's real
name is we're going to go ahead and call him Sam and Sam's just enjoying life it's the year 2007
everything seems to be going great and Sam is one of those kids who never really believed in the
paranormal nothing believe it he would hear stories about it obviously he's 13 years old in 2007
so he's heard ghost stories and seen spooky movies and stuff like that and he's heard of people and
he's met people who 100% believe the paranormal is real he always figured they were either
making up the story making it up is a scary story or they were mentally ill they thought that he
thought that these people actually were sick mentally sick and I might need some medical attention
and it's interesting one thing I like to do when I get the opportunity when I
find these types of stories online is I try to look at their past posting history this was posted
by someone going by the name opaque obscurity everything else that I could find that this
person posted was video game related counter strike global offensive modern warfare fallout type
stuff so that tends to make these types of stories more believable this totally could be made up
but the other day I found someone who had two encounters with the black eyed children and I
go okay I think I think you're making it up I think you're making it up the last two posts were
two separate stories about black eyed children and one of them gave you a special amulet and I was
like okay yeah totally made up but generally when someone tells it once in a lifetime paranormal
story and the rest of the time they're talking about pretty mundane things it does make you think
well no maybe this is legit Sam is a member of this very normal family living in the shadows of
the Ozark mountains well one night Sam's in his bedroom and I don't recommend this I think this
is one of the creepiest things you can do he sleeps with his bedroom door open apparently
I'd never do that never do that you have a baby in the other room you're like ah
I should be keeping an ear out for this baby but Jason told me to sleep with the door closed I just
think I honestly think there's something bad about it so like I do think it's not spiritually safe
I'll say that but anyways I've no I've nothing to back that up I also find it extremely terrifying
you'd have as many boundaries between yourself and the unknown as possible he sleeps with his
bedroom door open and his bedroom looks out into the living room of the house well this particular
night he's in his bed he's fast asleep and he begins to have this dream that he's being watched
there's an unseen presence around him staring at him and in the dream he feels himself
overcome with panic it just completely washes over him and he's trapped and he can't figure out
where this thing is at but he can feel its oppressive gaze upon him and in the dream he begins
screaming out for his mother he's crying out for his mother to come and save him and while he's
doing that he begins to hear this laughter this laughter again coming from nowhere something
is relishing in his torment his terror his pain well sam wakes up sam wakes up and he's laying in bed
and the first thing he sees when he wakes up is the living room his bedroom door is wide open
so when he wakes up the first thing he's looking at is out into the living room
and in the darkness of the living room he sees a shape laying on the couch
now there are some specifics here that he doesn't really lay out i don't know if the couch is facing
him or facing away or facing sideways we don't as far as like building a picture i don't know
which way it was laid out but i guess that's a minor detail because on the couch is a demon
whether whatever direction the couch was facing sam can look on the couch and he sees a demon and
the way he describes it is as a shadow man-esque figure so it had the body of a human shadow
but there also seemed to be a weird flowing movement to the the shadowy form almost if it was
also enveloped in some sort of dark energy that was kind of undulating and where the face would be
on this shadowy figure the face was skeletal sam's sitting in his bed and he's looking at the living
room and he sees this shadowy figure laying on the couch with a skeletal face its eyes were bulging
out of the bony sockets surprisingly crystal blue eyes shockingly blue staring through the darkness
staring at sam and somehow impossibly i mean obviously we're talking about a demon here
but somehow the skeleton's mouth was smiling at sam
now skeleton itself could not smile that's all facial muscles right it's a demon it's some sort
of demonic figure it's able to do the impossible i mean it is this shadowy figure moving around
on the couch i'm like what skeletons can't smile you had this rictus grin bloodshot eyes with piercing
blue irises a moment passes and then another and another and suddenly the skeletal figure darts down
darts out of view behind the couch and that's when sam finally snaps out of it right this obviously
was a huge shock for him he sees this figure move out of view sam jumps out of bed begins screaming
bust through his parents bedroom door completely freaking out tells his mom and dad what he saw
what's interesting is he says my dad
being a devout christian took it seriously
because i didn't believe in the paranormal right i was never one to ever really talk about the
stuff i thought it was fake so when i'm coming into the bedroom saying i saw something in the
living room saw some sort of entity in the living room father takes it seriously him and the mother
go and they wake up their daughter wake up their younger daughter and they all go into the living
room and the father opens the bible up and begins reading a verse sam goes i don't know what the
verse was but it had something to do with demons and my father was reading this and then
my father shouts out in the name of jesus christ i command you to leave my family alone if you want
one of us take me leave my family alone sam said that the family stayed up together that night and
we're just kind of talking about things and then his dawn grew closer they went to bed whether it
was a dream a nightmare that sam had had or whether it was some sort of real entity who knew sam
thought i mean in the end he didn't really believe in any of this stuff fast forward a couple months
and his father gets sick
he gets sick and he's not getting any better
so he goes to the doctor and the doctor diagnoses him he has cancer
now sam doesn't actually name the type of cancer that he has but i think i was able to find it i
think i was able to figure it out because what it seems to be that his father had osteosarcoma
and the reason why i think that's what it is is because sam said my father got a type of cancer
that is extremely rare and it's something that is almost 100 seen in adolescence osteosarcoma
is that it's basically a cancer that strikes kids and teenagers
and it happens when you're going through a growth spurt as your bones are rapidly growing during
adolescence there is a very very very rare chance that this cancer can happen but for a grown adult
a father of two kids to get a form of cancer that tends to only happen when bone growth is going on
it's odd to say the least
sam's father says okay let's do the treatments let's do whatever it takes i want to be here with
my family he starts chemotherapy he changes his eating habits he begins working out he is trying
to live the healthiest life he can to counteract the negative health effects of not just the
chemotherapy but the cancer itself he's making these huge changes to his life he wants to stay with
his family but sam starts to kind of put things together here and obviously you can chalk this up
to depression and and really trying to figure out things and trying to make sense of the chaos of the
the universe but he's like i had a vision of the skeletal creature in the living room
and before that i had the nightmare that i was being watched by something i couldn't see
and i see the skeletal creature in the darkness smiling at me
and then my father says if you want one of us take me leave my family alone and then my father
comes down with a form of cancer that affects people in my age group and sam kind of is kind of
seeing this parallel he doesn't really want to say it out loud he doesn't really want to give it any
power but he does acknowledge in his mind that maybe there is a connection between those it was
there for him but his father said if you want one of us take me
now the doctors they estimated that sam's dad had a year to live despite their best efforts and
despite his best efforts as well remember he's eating healthy he's working out and all this stuff
they say you probably have a year left but it's year three at this point it's year three and he's
been fighting at the father's been fighting at this whole time and the family is staying together
they're with him on this journey they want him to pull through but year three is the turning
point for this at this point the father has had his leg amputated but at this stage the cancer
has spread and he doesn't want to be a bother right he doesn't want to be a bother but he
does want to be around his family as he spends his last months weeks days on planet earth
but he doesn't want to bother anybody he decides to not sleep in the bed with his wife he thinks
that he's just too distracting he needs needs his own place so he can rest and he can make sure
that his wife has a good night's rest as well so he begins spending a bulk of his time on the couch
in the living room that's where he sleeps that's where he hangs out during the day
and sam sam and his sister and the mom they do what they can for dad but at this stage it's obvious
that he is in a steep decline and sam he can't say when he first realized it
he can't say the moment that he knew but at a certain point it began happening
every time he looked at his father as his father had laid on the couch and had lost so much weight
as his dad who he'd always looked up to as being the strongest man he'd ever known
as he became weaker as his body features became more skeletal when he would look over and glance
at his father laying on the couch and his father would look back at his son and weakly smile
sam realized that he never really noticed how how shockingly blue his father's eyes
were until he saw them nearly bulging out of his near skeletal sockets
it's an interesting story there's a couple different ways you could look at it the father did end up
passing away shortly you know he lived for the three years after the diagnosis he passed away
shortly after sam and made this realization that his father now living on the couch for all
intensive purposes looked very similar to the demon he had seen in the living room that night
now unfortunately wasn't the end of the story when the father passed away the
family the mother fell into a deep depression the family fell into crisis bills weren't getting
paid and they lost the house and sam said it took me a couple of years i'm an adult now i mean
obviously the story took place back in 2007 so what would that be 15 years ago right he's 28 he's
around 28 29 he goes i took me a couple years to kind of get myself back on track so i mean the
family did continue to go through crisis from this it's such an interesting story if it's true
right sam insisted that this story was 100 true it could be fake could totally be made up
but it's an interesting story and you would have we talked about this a little bit last week and i
kind of mentioned i kind of did a teaser for this episode where we look at the idea of illnesses
caused by spirits that's what people used to believe for hundreds if not thousands of years right
and the medicine men weren't necessarily saying here take this it'll cure your gout it was take
this it'll keep the angry spirits away from your kneecap like even the medicine even the herbs
that were used were done in a spiritual sense for thousands of years i would argue that medicine is
far i i think i think china may have had a different view of their form of medicine but i'm talking
mostly like in the western world at least that's what it seems to be it wouldn't have been until we
got into maybe the enlightenment right 17 1800s and that's when we started seeing medicine as a
thing i take an aspirin to reduce inflammation that helps the inflammation in my back so that's
like a scientific thing and i'm not arguing that oh well they believe that for thousands of years
therefore that's true but like i said on friday's episode what if some of it is again i'm not saying
that your back hurts because of a ghost but what if and you know that's funny that i say that because
i did a whole episode about that about solar plexus clown gliders where i did encounter a
you might just just listen to that episode but i encountered something and then i had like this
unbearably bad back pain from such a minor injury it shouldn't even registered i'm sitting in an
uncomfortable chair in a courtroom for like an hour or two and i do think that there is a combination
i do i do i don't think that everyone who suffers from a pain or a sickness it's related to the spirit
world but i think some of it and i think even if the sum of it is one or two percent that's a huge
amount if you took one or two percent of people who suffer from back pain was caused by some sort of
spiritual force and i'm not saying don't take medicine for it because the medicine probably
will work but also look at the whole picture i think that's why it's called holistic medicine
isn't it because you're looking at the whole picture i could be wrong i don't think everyone
who's a gambling addict or a porn addict has a demon attached to him but i think some do
right one or two percent people you're an alcoholic you have these vices you're trying
to get rid of i don't think everyone who's an alcoholic it's somehow attached to the world of
the demonic but some of them do right and i think the problem is i think 99% of the time
you could handle it just in one way but there is a portion of the population i would believe that
they do also have to look at the spiritual answer i think the problem is before they only looked at
the spiritual answer and they're like oh you have a toothache that means a leprechaun's living in your
mouth here eat these cloves it'll go away and it wouldn't because there wasn't there wasn't a
leprechaun in your mouth and the cloves are ineffective but i think to say it's only medicinal
and you're not looking at that so i i think the story is interesting in that fashion
where you had what was in this house was coming for sam and the father took the brunt of it really
took the whole thing right and got this rare form of cancer there's also the other option that i was
thinking that it's not necessarily a demon he saw but the future right i mean the connection to the
dream having the bad nightmare may have been completely unrelated that he was really glimpsing
the future and what he saw that chaotic energy surrounding that couch was just
the turmoil of all of the emotions that he was eventually going to be facing and it became
he saw the future so there was no way to avoid it his father was going to become that skeletal
figure laying on the couch not as some sort of demonic thing but he was looking basically
three years forward and seeing that thing and in this case i think it would make more sense that
he was seeing the future i honestly think when i say stuff like i think demons are connected to
illness i think that i i don't have youtube i don't have youtube comments anymore unfortunately
so we don't get that tit for tat we don't get to talk about the episodes after they're done and i do
miss that but youtube is just such a beast when it comes to the censorship stuff i i think that
people are more reticent is that the word people are more cautious or people would call me out more
when i say things like i think some illnesses are caused by spirits i think there's a lot of people
who would disagree with that theory just on its head and that's totally fine obviously you can
disagree with me but where are you gonna do it where are you gonna do it you can't do it on youtube
anymore um i think people i think i'd get pushback from that i honestly think people would be more
willing to accept that he was looking into the future or that this if you believe the story
that this particular story may have had a demon causing the cancer but it's super rare it would
never happen ever ever again but i think by making the statement that i think some illnesses
or vices right are caused by demonic influences that i think i would get pushback on that and
fair enough right it does sound insane it's it sounds backwards is what it does when i say that
i think the fair argument goes no that's what we used to think we're better than that now but
maybe i'm wrong maybe there are a lot of people out there who could say no i do think there are
certain illnesses especially illnesses that just seem to devastate not just the person who has it
but the whole family around them eating disorders is one of those things right eating disorders
gambling addictions cancer where it's such a slow burn for the most part it can really really
devastate everyone around them that there's something particularly dangerous about that as
opposed to your appendix explodes it's so sudden it's so painful hopefully you make it you probably
will you get to the hospital or diverticulitis right where you get a little piece of food stuck
in a fold of an intestine and it festers and it's super painful and stuff like that i've had friends
who have gone through that that doesn't seem to have the same oomph as your loved ones addicted to
pornography you know what i mean if you've had diverticulitis i'm sure you're like jason it's
a hundred times worse i wouldn't i wouldn't mind if my entire family was addicted to porn as long
as i don't have to go through that again pornography addiction and gambling addiction they just are
like such family devastators they were just reading the story the other day about a former
police officer who got caught he his house got raided because he was watching child porn
and his he was like 70 years old and his wife goes i thought she i thought he was just playing
solitaire he was that was her actual quote he was on the computer all day long and she thought he
was just playing solitaire all the time like talk about a nuclear bomb going off in that family
because now the wife the screw him but now the wife is like what do what do i do like do i defend
him do i just take his pension and run like what happens now like imagine living your entire life
you're a 70 year old woman and the fbi kicks down your door what no no he's just playing solitaire
the next few years of her life are going to be like court dates and stuff like that she didn't
sign up for any of that i don't know i don't know again i think people could push back on that
but in this particular case i think it's one of the two things and it's it's one of the two things
it's either time travel or a demon caused cancer they're both fantastical right they're both pretty
fantastical but in the end it's just a tragic story because it could have just been a coincidence
it could have been a waking nightmare that sam had there could have been nothing paranormal
about it whatsoever and it could have been a giant coincidence but sam a man who never believed that
the paranormal was even possible now does he now 100 believes that demons are real it's just a tragic
story really any way you look at it because what we're looking at here is a son who lost his father
right a son who lost his father in such a horrific way that it changed the way he looks at the world
sam's father sacrificed himself to save his son and sam had to watch sam had to watch firsthand
the effects of this demonic influence like at the end of the day sam goes i didn't believe in the
paranormal now i believe demons are real and i watched my father give up his own life to save me
and i watched my father day by day by day look more and more and more like the demon that came to
claim my life so now i know that demons are real i saw the effects of one on the strongest man i
ever knew i saw what it could do to a human being it broke him down so completely by the end of his
life my father looked like that demon and no matter how much i hope no matter how much i pray
the last time i saw my dad he looked like that skeletal figure smiling at me from the couch
it even took that from me it didn't just take my father's life it took the memories of the strong
man i knew growing up and turned him into this thing not only took his life but it took the memories
too i try my best to remember my father as the man who would lead us on hikes
and taught me how to cast a fishing rod and showed me how to hunt through the forests
in the Ozark mountains i try my best to remember that version of my father
but in the end the only way i can remember him
is as the skeletal figure smiling at me from the couch
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also
do this up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio tiktok is at dead rabbit radio
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't
have to listen to it every day but i'm glad you listened to it today have a great one guys
you
(upbeat music)