Today, we take a look at three American cities.
One is known as the most haunted town in America.
The other one is known to have the 8th gateway to hell.
And the third one has been plagued with legends of monstrous beasts running through the forest.
Are any of these stories true?
We'll find out today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
We have a lot to cover today because we're doing three stories on three different towns.
So I want to jump right into it.
Now this is related to an episode I did recently.
Ariana Grande and the 7 gateways to hell.
Now when I released the episode, I had a lot of fun recording that episode.
I have a lot of fun recording all of them, but that one was particularly entertaining to me.
When I posted it up on YouTube, I had a YouTube commenter named Rising Vapor hit me up and says,
"Hey, there's actually, I know of a couple other towns that are similar to the town of Stoll, Kansas."
And so he sent me some resources.
He basically said, "Here's a couple of information for town enough for me to track them down."
And so we are going to take a tour of these towns in America
that may or may not be haunted.
We will discuss that as we get into it now.
Normally we take the carpenter copter, but I figure we're in America.
There's no point to have to get in.
Oh, and the helicopter is a Boeing 347.
I looked it up.
That's a helicopter with the wings.
So if you're ever curious of what the carpenter copter looks like,
it is a Boeing 347.
All two of you out there who are like, "What's it look like?"
And I'm one of them.
It's a Boeing 347.
But anyways, carpenter copter, we're going to just leave grounded for today.
And I know a lot of people are disappointed.
Now we have the carpenter copter for our air travel international.
Can helicopters fly over oceans?
I guess we should have checked that out.
So we have the carpenter copter for international travel.
We have the rabbit rowboat that if we're going from to islands or again over oceans.
And I was like, "I need a car.
I need a car."
And I was, I came up with a couple of different ones.
So I needed a land vehicle to, you know, we're just driving around town.
So that is why I want all of you to hop on board the Jason Jalopy.
I want you to picture it looking like a steam powered old timey car,
all a chitty-chitty bing-bing, but probably less cool.
So let's all hop into the Jason Jalopy and makes all sorts of weird noises.
It sounds like it's going to die at any moment.
And it might, but it's still a reliable vehicle.
Now Rising Vapor has sent us on this quest to check out these three towns.
So, so the first place we're taking the Jason Jalopy to is a little town called Dudley Town.
Now Dudley Town is in the state of Connecticut, the beautiful state of Connecticut, I'm assuming.
I've never been there.
I just imagine there's like leaves and people named William and Buffy and Stella and
Stewart.
They're drinking tea and they see a car of like hooligans show up and they're like,
"Show us your ghosts.
Show us your ghosts."
And they're like, "Oh my, oh my, I don't know what to do."
Call the authorities, Martha.
And then the authorities come out and they like, "What are you looking for?"
And they're like, "I'm looking for ghosts."
Now Dudley Town was called, okay, so let me back up.
Dudley Town brief overview.
It was founded in the 1700s.
By the 1800s, it was abandoned.
The forest grew up around it.
It used to be farmland and it just wasn't great farmland.
So people move away that that tends to happen.
In the 1920s, this dude writes a book called The History of Cornwall.
And he says, "You know, Dudley Town has had a string of bad luck.
This guy went insane and this guy killed his family and a bunch of Indians came in
and killed these kids and a bunch of people disappeared."
The end, like it was just like an anecdote in a book.
And he didn't say anything supernatural was going on.
He just said, "This is a string of bad luck."
Rumors started to swirl.
One of the rumors was that Dudley Town was founded by a guy who betrayed King Henry VII or whatever.
And the curse was brought over because English kings are known for putting curses on people.
But that was a rumor that started.
The rumor started that just the land was cursed and then it became that the land was haunted.
The area itself was haunted.
Dan Akroyd, a literal ghostbuster.
And he's actually really big into paranormal research.
But Dan Akroyd's an actual ghostbuster.
He said, "Dudley Town is the most haunted place on earth."
Quite the boast.
I think even in the intro I said the most haunted place in America.
Dan Akroyd, I was selling it short.
Dan Akroyd said it was the most haunted place on earth.
Now, before the history of Cornwall was written,
long before Dan Akroyd was talking about being the most haunted place on earth,
after the town of Dudley Town was abandoned,
the town was bought by basically the people who still lived there.
And they was bought in the name of this group that is one of the most ominously named groups
that I can think of outside of Cobra or Umbrella Corporation.
Actually, those names aren't as scary as this one.
The Dark Entry Forest Association.
What?
Now, their name comes from a forest near Dudley Town.
It's part of it called the Dark Entry Forest.
Because apparently the way that the mountains are situated,
the forest is always dark because of the shade or something.
Maybe they're lit up during the noon,
but I mean for the most part they're in the dark.
Why don't you just call yourself the DEFA, the DEFA?
Why the Dark Entry Forest Association?
They bought this land up in the 1920s, so the whole area is private land.
You can't visit it, you can't take your ghost crew there,
you can't traipse through with your EMF or your spirit box or none of that stuff.
They shut it down to the point that if you're driving down the road,
people have reported this,
that if they're driving down the road and they stop or they slow down, cops show up.
People in the area are constantly watching for ghost hunters or teenagers or whatever
and calling up the Connecticut State Police.
Like they have nothing better to do than patrol this area, catching the ghost crew or whatever.
Dark Entry Forest Association guards this area so zealously
that to me that actually raises more questions.
If I had just seen this place and it was like,
"Oh, this place Connecticut had a string of bad luck."
Dan Alcord said it was the most haunted place on earth.
I'd be like, "Oh, that's kind of interesting."
But the fact that there's a group that's actively like suppressing people
from investigating it, it just seems odd.
Now, there was a report that there was a Christian based movie production company
that wanted to do a movie on Dudley Town.
And for whatever reason, it sounds so bizarre,
but the director, the producers, got six screenwriters,
put them in a house in Dudley Town and they're like,
"Write a script."
What?
But it sounds like a mix-up of a bad reality show and a horror movie,
but anyways, the six writers were sitting in there trying to write on the script.
A bunch of behind the scenes stuff happened with the movie producers arguing and things like that.
One of the things, according to this article, was that the Dark Entry Force Association
threatened to sue the filmmakers for defamation
if they made this horror movie based on their town.
That is aggressive debunking.
They've come out, I mean, if you go and you look up Dark Entry Forest or Dudley Town,
most of the first links are, "Our town is in haunted, our town is in haunted,
our town is in haunted, please stay away."
And one of the things said, "How would you feel if you were sitting in your house
and you saw a bunch of teenagers walk outside throwing beer cans and setting fires?"
Well, I wouldn't feel too good, but if I knew they were there,
because they thought it was the most haunted place on earth,
I wouldn't mind because I would charge them five bucks.
I would charge, I would open it up and say,
"Five bucks, ten bucks, I mean, it's the most haunted place on earth."
And again, we talked about this with the Ariana Grande thing.
Stole Kansas is like, "Do not come here, there's no ghosts."
Roswell says, "Please come here, there's aliens."
And Roswell is a booming economy, tourist economy,
and Stole Kansas is just this little town in the middle of nowhere.
Now, I'm going to stereotype Connecticutans,
people who live in Connecticut, Connecticutis, I'm going to stereotype Connecticutis,
and I'm going to assume they're all just wealthy, so they don't care.
They don't need the extra money, and they don't need the money.
Again, they're just sipping drink and tea.
Teenagers are kind of like Archie and Jughead
are like running around in the backyard, and they're like, "Ugh."
But the pushback is what makes the story suspicious.
The pushback actually is what makes the story interesting,
because there's hundreds of supposed cursed towns
and ghost towns and stuff like that across America and over the globe.
But the fact that you have a group that's so aggressively trying to debunk it
actually makes me more suspicious that something actually happened there
or is happening here today.
Who knows?
I mean, it could just be that they got tired of teenagers
like knocking over their crumpets and like driving motorcycles over their doilies and stuff like that.
That's the most logical answer.
But again, sometimes it's not the story itself can be fairly bland.
It's the little meta details behind the story that make it more suspicious.
So, we'll rate these.
On a scale of 1 to 10, how much would I want to visit Dudley Town?
I don't know.
It sounds kind of pompous.
It doesn't sound like there's a lot of meat to the story.
On a scale of 1 to 10, I'd say probably 4.
I wouldn't even waste my gas drive into Dudley Town.
So Dudley Town, a bit of a wash.
I look over at Rising Vapor who's in the Jason Jalopy next to me
and I'm like, "Dude, didn't she tell me to go to this town?"
And he's like, "Well, I mean, I heard of it.
I didn't technically tell you to drive to here in this really slow car."
And I'm like, "Okay, now we are going very slowly to Masa..."
I can't say the...
I can't pronounce the state's name.
I don't think I can at least.
We're going to Massachusetts.
So, Massachusetts is a couple states over, I think.
It's still the East Coast.
And we're going to a place called Leichester.
Or Leichester.
I think it's Leichester.
There's no H.
So, we're going to Leichester and we're going to visit a place called
the Friends Cemetery.
Or, also known as the Quaker Cemetery,
which I wrote in my notes is Quarker Cemetery.
Just to let you know the level of detail and precision I have with my notes.
So, the Quaker Cemetery.
Or, it's most commonly known as the Spider Gates Cemetery,
a.k.a. the Eighth Gateway to Hell.
Not one of the official Seven Gateways to Hell.
No.
This is the Eighth Gateway to Hell.
This is the King Kong of Gateways to Hell.
It was founded in 1740.
That's my first note I have written down.
The second note that I've written down.
This website is fucking nuts.
So, that should let you know where we're going.
I found General Information Website on the history of Spider Gates Place.
The next website I found seemed to be where most people got their information
about the Spider Gates Cemetery.
I'm going to read you some detail.
So, this website is proposing that these things are true about the Spider Gates Cemetery.
Number one.
Spider Gates Cemetery is one of the most visited spots in the state.
Let me tell you a little bit about the state of Massachusetts.
Benjamin Franklin's birthplace.
Martha's Vineyard.
The Battle of Lexington.
The place where the Revolutionary War started.
The shot heard around the world, also in Massachusetts.
Cape Cod.
Any of these places ring a bell?
But this website proports that Spider Gates Cemetery
is one of the most visited places in the state.
The Quakers apparently believed that this cemetery, their cemetery, was sacred.
And it is where they did their incantations.
What?
I don't...
Okay, I'm not too far up on my Quaker information,
but this website makes them out to be borderline
Satan worshipers.
And at one point, actually straight out accuses them of building an altar to worship Satan.
Now, like I said, my information on Quakers is fairly limited,
but they're...
From what I understand, they are a breakaway denomination from Christianity.
They're not like crazy hard workers like the Amish,
but they're not like super lazy like every other Christian on the planet.
They're like in between.
But I don't think I would ever classify the Quaker Oats Guy in the box
where I get my oatmeal as a Satan worshiper.
But anyways, this website does.
Story goes, in 1984, a young boy hung himself in the cemetery.
The family of the boy goes, "Oh, that sucks."
So we're going to give you gates for your cemetery.
What?
I mean...
They say we're going to give you gates for your cemetery,
and they're going to look like spider webs.
Because the boy was Greek, and we are Greek as well,
and the spider webs represent the story of a Rakhne who weaved webs.
Okay, so anyways, they have these gates that if you squint really hard,
they may look like spider webs.
Other accounts say they actually are supposed to look like sunbeams.
They kind of look like boobs with wrinkles, to me.
But anyways, Spider Gate Cemetery.
Apparently, if you go through the gates at midnight,
the devil appears and takes your soul,
that would be a very easy thing to test.
Just do it.
Just walk through the gates at midnight and see what happens.
There's also a...
There's a bunch of dead grass where a house used to be,
which is where the Saint and Worshiping Quakers went.
But the house is gone, but the grass...
The grass is still dead.
Can you...
Can you Laffyne podcast host explain that?
Well, I mean, I don't...
Not a soil expert,
but I think if you build any stone structure on something
and leave it there for a while,
grass might have a hard time growing back there.
There is a grave for a dude, real name...
Earl Marmaduke.
Even back in the day, that fool got picked on at school.
Earl Marmaduke is grave.
If you walk around it 10 times at midnight
and say "Marmaduke, talk to me,"
then put your head on his grave.
He talks to you or moans or something.
He does...
He makes some sort of noise.
There's two things...
There's two things that I have a problem with that.
One, if it's a ghost,
like I can walk into my bathroom and see like the ghost
of like an old man hiding underneath my
kitchen cabinet.
I don't know why I have a kitchen cabinet in my bathroom,
but you understand, like...
Ghosts are things that you walk through the force,
you see a ghost,
you get in your car,
you look in the rear of your mirror,
there's a ghost in your back seat,
you're sleeping and you see your bedsheets start to rise
and there's a ghost crawling through your bed, all that stuff.
Why is it that some ghosts can just appear anywhere,
but other ghosts need these ridiculous
incantations and rituals to appear?
It's never explained,
and this comes...
I see this stuff a lot.
But they're like,
if you do this ritual,
if you hold up three thumbs,
you have to borrow one from somebody else,
light two matches,
and then blow them out all at the same time at 444 a.m.,
a ghost appears,
but then I could literally just like walk outside
and see like a ghost jogger,
like it doesn't make sense.
I never get the incantation stuff.
My second thing,
my second problem with it,
as you walk around 10 times in midnight,
say Marma, do talk to me,
and you put your head on the grave,
and he says something to you.
Who, who, who did that?
Who was the first person to do that?
Did someone walk around eight times and go,
I give up, nothing's happening?
And then another guy walked around nine times,
and he's like, oh man, I,
this doesn't work.
And then a guy walked around 10 times,
but it was three in the afternoon,
and he's like,
I mean, like,
how did you get to that evolution of this stupid,
this stupid ritual,
and you can actually go and see pictures of Earl Marmaduke's tomb?
There's a bunch of grass worn out
because people are walking around it.
Does that mean that Quakers were also satanically murdering people on that grave?
Like, you can't have it both ways.
You can't show me a picture of dead grass
and go saying worshiping,
and then show me another picture of dead grass
and go, I just, people are walking around a lot.
You can't have it both ways.
And then this website ends with this quote.
No joke, this is the last phrase on this page for
Spider, Spider Gate Cemetery.
I love this,
I'm gonna read this whole quote without trying to laugh.
The last legend surrounding the cemetery
speaks of a hidden cave
where the body of a young girl was found.
You're like Jason, that's not funny, but it gets funny, okay.
Most attempts to find this cave end in disappointment
as there really are no caves,
at least not once big enough to hide a body, how does he?
Someone's like, oh no, I know my body hiding caves and that.
Back to the quote.
Furthermore, there is no proof that a girl was ever found.
However, about a mile from the cemetery is a small cave,
once used as a root cellar,
where a six-year-old boy was beaten and dumped into the river.
This occurred in the early 1980s.
Spider Gate Cemetery is a good day trip to explore a few legends
and get close with some nature and local spirits.
What? I don't want to go there.
You just told me that a little kid got beaten and dumped in the river
in the 1980s, that's in my lifetime.
I was watching Transformers,
this kid's getting his brains beaten,
and then the next sentence you told me to go there for a fun trip.
They don't even say if this guy ever got caught.
They should say the kid was beaten and dumped in the river,
and it happened if this guy's still alive.
Not the boy, but I mean the killer.
I don't want to go there.
But the funny thing is, is that other people have.
So there's another website where a guy's like,
hey, I'm doing a day trip to Spider Gate Cemetery.
And it's so funny because this guy, he's really,
he's like me, he seems, he's really into the stuff,
but he got his information from a book called like,
Weird Massachusetts.
And I am pretty sure the website that I was reading
got their info from that book,
because what he was talking about on his journey
is totally matches the book.
He's like, yeah, I went to where the gates were
and I looked for the hanging tree,
but I didn't really see it.
They said the tree that the boy was hung from was like an elm,
but I only saw like a sycamore.
He goes, I saw the place with the dead, dead grass.
I saw the Marmaduke, there's a picture of him by the Earl of Mar-
not Earl, there's a picture of him standing by Earl Marmaduke's grave.
And so I think it matched up, he was reading the same story.
The funniest thing is, is his story starts off being like,
I couldn't find the place.
It's super hard to find.
He goes, I think I passed it a couple of times,
I had a really hard time finding it.
But apparently this is one of the most visited places
in the state of Massachusetts.
This graveyard gets a zero stars.
I would not go to this graveyard if you paid me to.
What a crock.
What a, what a waste.
I was like reading this, what was in a waste because it was highly entertaining,
but to think that people think that this story has any validity whatsoever,
it is almost 100% made up.
I'm hoping the boy who got his head caved in is also made up.
But none of it's, none of it's true.
Other than the fact that there's a place called Spider Gate Cemetery.
So this place gets a big fat goose egg on a one to 10 scale.
It is one of the most ridiculous fake hauntings I've ever covered on this show.
And the people who wrote that description,
they either have to start writing fiction or they should be ashamed of themselves
because there is no reason why people should be wasting gas or time or brain cells
investigating Spider Gate Cemetery.
Where we're going to now, we're staying in Massachusetts.
So if you're tired of me mispronouncing that,
which again, I think I might actually be pronouncing that right.
There's a lot of T's in it, but I don't, I think they're all silent.
So anyways, now we're going to a place called Dogtown.
Dogtown, Massachusetts was founded in 1693.
Lot of weird coincidences, lot of weird events.
The early settlers in the area reported that there was a,
there was a tribe of Indians called the Agawam Indians.
And when the early settlers got there,
they noticed there was a lot of wolf activity in the area.
And the story that they heard from the natives was that the Agawam Indians ancestors,
they have the ability to gain their heads would turn into the heads of dogs.
You're like, okay, you know, shamanistic and stuff like that.
But the Indians also said there is a herb in this area that anyone can take,
turn you into a dog, shape shift into a dog.
You didn't have to have any sort of high level ritual training or anything like that.
You could turn into a dog if you could find this herb.
Early settlers probably like whatever did.
See you next Thanksgiving.
The reason why the town's called Dogtown has a couple of different origins.
One is that there was a bunch of dogs in the area, like wolves in the area.
Another possibility, which this was another fact.
So they just, these are all facts.
They just don't know which one contributed to the name of Dogtown.
Was during the American Revolution.
So the town was founded in 1693.
It was actually very well situated because it was close to
water.
It was close to the water.
So you could do fishing and stuff like that.
But it was protected, it had natural barriers to protect it from both pirates,
which was a big issue back then, and native raiding groups.
So they kind of had protection from both, you know, sea adversaries and land adversaries.
It wasn't the best for farming, but they were able to do other things there.
So it was a bustling town to a certain point.
It was not like a Boston level town, but they were, it had a population.
During the American Revolution, when all the men left to fight the British,
women started taking dogs on in disproportionate amounts.
So it got to the point where pretty much every woman had a pet dog.
Now that sounds creepy too, and it kind of makes you think like this area has some sort of like canine
presence.
But it was almost like all the women in town to have company, don't be dirty,
you're going to be anyways, but to have company, they got dogs.
But what happened was American Revolution, spoiler alert, America won,
and the town was still there.
But during the war of 1812, when those dastardly British showed back up,
I think it was against the British.
I might have been the French, I'm not for sure, but the war of 1812,
that particular town, Dogtown, was now susceptible to naval bombardment.
And people were like, you know, we can go to a place that has, you know,
better economic factors, better farmland and stuff like that.
And as the townspeople left, you basically had three groups of people that stayed in
the town.
You had widows, you had independent women, which back then was basically codeword for
witch, and vagrants moved into towns because they had all these houses and no one living in them.
Got a lot of accusations of witchcraft in the area at this time.
Now, and this is past, we're in the war of 1812, so this is past the Salem witch trials.
This isn't during witch mania, but this town had such a unique creepy vibe that it got the
reputation of housing multiple witches.
One of them was known as Tammy Younger, and her nickname was Queen of the Witches,
and she would sit on on her patio.
And when people had to travel by her house to get, you know, they're going from point
A to point B in Dogtown's in the middle, as they drove by her, she would curse their oxen,
and the oxen would stop and she'd be like, give me some potatoes.
And then she would let them on through.
Now, that obviously could just be legend, but the person apparently did exist.
And people would give her food.
Now, whether or not she had the magical power to stop Beast of Burden, I'm not for sure.
I mean, obviously, logically, probably not.
But for whatever reason, people were stopping and giving her food.
And maybe she's a prostitute.
I don't know how to think about it, but there were stories of in the woods, like booming sounds,
you'd see like flickers of light in the forest.
Sometimes figures would just be standing there by the tree line.
It was not a fun place to be.
Imagine like Blair Witch USA.
It was not a cool place to be.
A practical problem.
So whether or not Tammy Younger was actually a practicing witch,
or she may have been practicing witch, but whether or not she actually had any sort of powers,
that's up to debate, whether you're a skeptic or a believer or things like that.
And I always kind of fall in the middle.
What's not mystical, what's not, you know, like, ooh, might be spooky is what is spooky,
but not paranormal is the third theory of how Dogtown got its name.
Now, some people believe that the town didn't get the official name of Dogtown,
or it didn't really get known as Dogtown until far later in its life cycle.
Because after the American Revolution, after where everyone got their dogs,
after 18, War of 1812, where people were leaving, people just left their dogs there.
And the dogs went feral.
You just had wild packs of dogs roaming the town attacking people.
And they think that that's the reason how it really got the name of Dogtown,
is that people from out of town would be like, I'm not going there.
There's a bunch of dogs running around.
And, and if we're lucky, they won't eat our oxen while Tammy Younger has them frozen in fear.
In 1845, the last building was raised.
Like, they're like, get rid of the town, it's gone.
And to make things even creepier, this town, apparently dog-headed Indians are running around it.
People have an incredible fascination with dogs.
There's a witch, there's a bunch of dogs, crazy dogs running around.
You knock down all the buildings and a spooky forest appears instead.
Not just flatland.
So you have all these trees, the forestry, not the next day,
but I mean, you know, the forestry appears and Dogtown, when they tore all the buildings down,
they left the basements.
Because what are you going to do, the cellars and stuff like that?
So you can literally be walking through this forest and fall into a spooky basement from the 1600s.
And no one will ever know you're there.
And it's probably full of feral dogs.
A lot of the cellars now have been marked with rocks.
But not all of them.
There's still quite a chance as you're walking through this spooky forest that you're going to fall into a cellar.
A spooky, spooky cellar.
So now we're in the present day.
Well, not the present day, we're in 1984.
Present for me when I was a kid.
Now, I, another boy just got his brains bashed out in Spiderwebs, Spider Gates, sorry.
I've already forgotten what that place is called.
This is 1984.
Return of the Jedi just came out a year earlier.
Transformers, I think, came out this year.
I was quite chubby.
While I was in California watching Transformers, what was going on in this abandoned city/spooky forest of Dogtown?
1984, March 17th.
There was a report of a giant animal.
I don't know why I made that noise.
I guess I should have went.
Anyway, whatever.
It sounded like a circus song.
There's a giant monster.
There's a giant animal that's roaming the cliffs near Dogtown on March 17th.
March 24th, a deer, it's carcass, is found ripped in half, not eaten, but torn in half.
That night, two people in the area say that they saw a giant dog monster roaming through the forest.
So those are all reports that they had seen this monster moving through the forest.
Actual news event, actual provable news event on June 24th of that same year.
So just what is that?
March, April, May, June, at five months later, four months later.
Ann Natty was an avid jogger and she loved the Dogtown area.
She just thought it was a beautiful forest.
And there's a man out there named Peter Hodgkins.
Ann, he ended up telling the police so you can tell where this story is going.
I didn't plan it.
I didn't really think about it.
I just saw her and I had an overwhelming desire to murder her.
So in these dark forests full of so many legends,
Peter Hodgkins comes up behind her with a rock, smashes her head and just completely
out of the blue.
He just saw her and knew that he needed to kill her.
Is there a connection between that murder and the monster that was roaming the woods?
Was this town infested by some sort of spirit animal?
Is there really a plant in that area that if you ate it you could become a shapeshifter?
Was it possible that Peter Hodgkins was the beast that was sighted just five months earlier?
No memory of it, just a wild, murderous beast?
This area definitely seems sinister.
Could be completely made up.
All the information that I've presented to you, it could just be myths and legends that are
sewn together to tell a compelling story.
I, on a scale of one to ten, out of all the places, I would put Dogtown at a ten.
This place sounds absolutely fascinating to me.
Dogtown, I think, has a dark secret.
And the only way you'll ever be able to really prove it, right or wrong,
is to walk around at ten times.
No, no, the only way you're ever able to really like prove it would be to go out there.
But if Peter Hodgkins wasn't the beast, where's the beast now?
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @JasonOParpenter.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.