Today we travel to the town of Ong's Hat.
Did it exist?
And what happened there?
And we cover one of the most requested stories.
Even a story I have been so curious to find the truth out about.
Ageless Travel.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
Hope you're having a great day.
We're recording this one a little early.
I always wanted to get an episode out on Sunday nights, and so I have episodes coming out
Monday through Friday, so I'm hoping that we can keep the schedule going.
I think that works out for most people, because if they're working Monday through Friday,
how who works Monday through Friday anymore, actually?
Who has a job like that?
I don't know.
I haven't worked a job Monday through Friday in 15, 20 years.
But I guess they still exist.
I guess they still exist.
So let's just go ahead and jump in.
Because this is kind of a weird, both of these stories are related.
It's kind of a little two-parter.
I'm going to try to get it into our normal time allotment.
I like to hear these episodes between 20 and 30 minutes.
30 minutes max.
Normally, until an interesting, quote-unquote, interesting story right now, we're going
to jump right in, because I think this story is interesting.
It was originally spread out over two days.
I'm going to be able to fit it into one, though.
And Ong's Hat is a story that I was looking into originally when we started the podcast.
It's only been like-- we're at episode 33.
It seems like we've been doing this forever.
But it's only been maybe three or four weeks.
But I looked into Ong's Hat, and I was like, yeah, I don't really know if that fits.
We've kind of covered it with the Bellray Surge and Dublin, Wisconsin.
I wanted to do an episode on ageless travel, though.
That was always something that popped up.
You always laugh.
What does ageless travel mean?
You just think it's word soup.
It's one of those things you think people threw it up on the conspiracy iceberg chart
and was having a laugh.
But both Ong's Hat and ageless travel were on there.
And boy, boy are the interesting stories, and they're connected.
So I want to get them both in the same episode here.
Now Ong's Hat, just Ong's Hat story alone, now that I've looked into it more, is very
interesting.
So first off, we have to go, what is actually verifiable?
So yes, there is a town called Ong's Hat.
Ong's Hat is an unincorporated little town in New Jersey that has just kind of, the
people have just kind of moved out of it, moved out of the area.
It's mostly just rubble now.
The buildings are pretty much rubble now.
Basic small town.
The story that I came across was that it was some sort of dimensional portal.
First off, I just heard that the town was abandoned.
But the conspiracy theory was that a portal was opened up and a bunch of people walked
through it or disappeared.
And I was like, I've already covered that with Dublin, Wisconsin.
I knew I was going to do Bell Ray Surge, so I kind of left Ong's Hat on the table.
However, I've gotten some more information.
So Ong's Hat supposedly is what happened was there was a group of scientists who believed
in what's basically chaos science.
They believed that we should embrace the chaos of the universe.
And if we do that, if we take it full to the metaphysical extreme and incorporate drugs
into science and expanding the mind, we can find new ways of energy, new ways of using
technology.
All of these advancements can come from embracing the chaos instead of trying to find order
in it.
Now, they were these groups of scientists, obviously it was controversial.
So this happened pretty much in, say, the 70s, the 80s around there.
They went to the small town of Ong's Hat.
One of them had purchased a bunch of the land and basically was a commune for scientists
to do whatever they needed to do.
They could run wild with the technology, whatever they could think of, they could make.
There was going to be no academic review board.
There was going to be no government interference.
They were going to do what they wanted to in this fairly, I think at this point it was
abandoned as well, town.
So now this group of scientists basically has carte blanche in this small town of Ong's
Hat.
What happens when a bunch of scientists who have all of the intelligence in the world
and no restrictions, it generally doesn't end well.
We've seen that in Nazi death camps or the Japanese death camps where they're running
all those horrible experiments.
If no one's there to tell them to stop, the scientists will just fulfill their curiosity.
Well these scientists kept pushing and pushing and pushing the boundaries of reality, the
boundaries of science.
And what they discovered was a device called the gate.
Now the gate was actually a series of other devices and these things would allow, they'd
get into these machines and they could transport themselves to another dimension.
Now not a dimension of sight and sound, but of mind.
I'm going to copyright that, that's great.
They'd go to these dimensions and the dimensions would either have two defining factors to
them.
One, they'd go to a dimension that was exactly like ours, but there was no humans.
It was completely empty.
Who built the buildings?
I don't know, but the buildings would be there.
I think.
Well it doesn't specifically say the buildings were there.
It would make more sense if they traveled to Earth and there were no buildings there,
but you know they're inter-dimensionally traveling so I think the rules are kind of out the window.
They'd go to a planet, they'd go to a similar Earth without buildings, but there would definitely
be no people there.
The second dimensions they would go into is they'd go into dimensions with these amazing
structures, these amazing fortresses and then ruins of fortresses with glyphs that nobody
can understand and in these dimensions they were creatures, aliens, no one is the lemurs.
They're called lemurs because they had big eyes.
I know what you're thinking.
Jason, aren't those called gray aliens?
Well kind of, but these ones are different because apparently gray aliens have the big
eyes, but they can only drink water and the water comes out of their skin.
That's how they relieve themselves, which is kind of terrifying because if you think
if you ever like surprise an alien and he starts to get slippery he's probably pissing
all over you and their genitals are in the inside of their body and they don't exist.
With lemurs they're actually more mammalian so that you can see their junk and they eat
food and drink water like humans.
But anyway so you could go to these dimensions full of these lemur creatures is what they
call them.
They're constantly traveling to these dimensions.
They were scientists so they were going there, they were taking information and trying to
communicate with the lemurs and trying to understand their glyphs.
Then the government finally figured out what was going on there.
So what would the government do?
We've seen them do this with all sorts of inventions.
They went in, they decimated the town.
Now the theory, there's a couple theories there.
One, the government went in, took all their information and destroyed the population.
Secondly is that by the time the government got there everyone had disappeared.
They're in an alternate dimension in Ong's hut where there's no humans.
They're the only ones there and who knows what type of scientific technology they're
coming up with.
Third one is that the government took the technology, took them and that's just it.
Now they're working for the government maybe against their will, I don't know.
So that's the story, that's the basic story of Ong's hut.
I'm going to give you a ton of resources on this because there has been a lot written
about Ong's hut.
Some of it is historical and some of it talks about this group of chaos scientists that have
basically broken reality.
Now the way that they would travel has been lost to science.
The way that they travel to these alternate realities, we can't replicate because whoever
came up with the information, they're gone now.
But do we need that technology to travel to those dimensions?
You see what that technology was called was the egg.
It was an egg-shaped ship that you would crawl into, hook all the electrodes up to your body,
power it up, I'm ready to go chief.
Five, four, I don't know if to count it down.
I guess if you're going to alternate dimensions you probably don't need to count down because
time doesn't matter.
Anyways, it was called the egg.
I backtracked this because first I was looking for Ong's hut thing and I dismissed it, but
as I was looking for Ong's eggless travel I was looking for it for a while.
I've been looking for that probably about as long as I've been looking for sexual assault
missiles.
Again, if you know anything about sexual assault missiles please email me, deadrabberradi@gmail.com
because I'm losing my mind over that one.
Eggless travel, I found this quote in a book.
"The travel cults are quite real, let me assure you."
A certain pagan group in Northern California has been working on things like eggless travel
and dimensional doorways for some time.
One such test of eggless travel, sort of like one of Michael G. Comey's invisible spaceships,
occurred at a major Midwestern pagan gathering in 1988.
That was the first lead I had found on even the term eggless travel.
I typed in eggless travel, I've been looking all over for eggless travel.
You know what kept popping up?
Little tips for vegans.
Is that a concern?
Are vegans constantly afraid that when they're traveling there will be an egg next to them?
That someone will sneak an egg into their bag?
Type in eggless travel, you'll get a ton of vegan travel tips.
I didn't know that there was like a constant war between the omnivores and the vegans,
but apparently there is.
And remember, if you see a vegan with tattoos, don't say anything, they might chop their arms
off.
Little tip from Jason Carpenter.
So I found this and I was ecstatic.
And I was like, yes, here we go.
This is my first hint that somebody out there has some information about eggless travel and
what eggless travel is.
Then I had to backtrack it to the Ong's Hat Story and I found out their device they used
to travel to other dimensions was the egg.
I finally had something.
Now here is the key.
I had to look for those invisible spaceships in that guy's book.
And I found the guy's book and read a little bit and I couldn't make so much sense of it.
His book, it's called The Sack.
Who wants to write in something called The Sack?
Get in the sack, guys.
Let's go on an adventure.
That's gross.
But it basically was an invisible ship, so you would fly around, but it would just look
like you were sitting down like invisible, Wonder Woman's invisible jet.
But it's called The Sack.
So I was like, this is a dead end.
Looked all over.
I kept looking because I needed to find out more about eggless travel.
I had been so curious about this since I first saw this phrase.
And then I decided, maybe, maybe someone was at that pagan convention and witnessed pagan
travel and I got something better.
Here's a quote I found.
At least they showed me theirs, which is more than I've ever gotten from the travel cults.
Eggless has definitely been around since at least the mid-80s.
I ran into it in 1988 at a pagan gathering, some sort of large, approximately 12-couple
double yulking that opened the gateway into a higher dimensional space.
I was in a high spin singlet state and accidentally got sucked up into the startup of the drive
field they were building.
The yulks merged, blah blah blah, everything merged.
There was a wall of white at some sort of higher dim space open.
Anyway, they went somewhere.
I got yanked along, though I was bounced around and lost in the slipstream.
I ended up briefly where some Philadelphia experiment folks must have went because I periodically
have experienced similar phenomena on psychically, the overload damn near killed me.
That's it.
Eggless travel is the ability to travel from a dimension with no technology or to a dimension.
Well from a dimension is relieving our spirit.
It's the ability to travel, to leave our dimension into another dimension, lemur or not, without
the egg, even though we don't have the science.
Maybe what they did opened those gateways.
Another source I have that says, "Eggless travel has become standard operating procedure
for advanced travelers."
There have even been permanent doorways that have been constructed that even work for people
who aren't initiates into these cults, into these travel cults is what they're called.
The groups of people who, Ong's hat scientists are gone, these people still are taking up
the work in a more mystical, holistic way.
Ong's hat, eggless travel, totally connected.
Ong's hat is considered the first ARG.
If you're not familiar with what an ARG is, it's an alternate reality game.
It's basically a, it's like a proto myth.
It's something that people get together to kind of add on and then other people can join
this game and become part of the story.
Sometimes they help shape the narrative.
Sometimes they just have to unravel clues to find out the next step to it.
So you'll see ARGs, a lot of times are used for marketing purposes.
A new movie comes out and there'll be some cryptic numbers on the web.
And a good example of it was Cloverfield.
Cloverfield had a lot of ARGs with a slush-o, I think was their drink.
You could follow the links because at first nobody knew what Cloverfield was and you could
follow these clues and you'd have to figure it out.
And usually like the whole Reddit community will come together and try to figure out like
these clues to, you know, oh, what's under the ocean?
Oh, slush-o owns an oil rig and they were drilling.
Oh, what were they drilling for?
Oh, and then the rig got shut down.
Maybe this is some sort of monster movie.
So a lot of times it's used to drum up support.
Ong's hat, the story of Ong's hat is considered the first ARG.
It was created on a bulletin board.
It's a community created myth.
And what's interesting about it?
There's two interesting things about it.
Well, three, there's a ton of interesting things about it.
But one, it perfectly weaves true events, true groups, I guess I should say, true locations
and groups along with well-known conspiracies tying into the Ong's hat myth.
Ong's hat is a real town.
It really is abandoned.
They refer to real groups like the Church of the Subgenius, which was a crazy like,
I don't want to say anti-religion, but I mean, it was again came out of the 80s.
I used to have a ball reading about it because it was just, I forgot what the guy's name
was, Joe Bob or something.
But Church of the Subgenius was just like this really weird religion that kind of made
fun of organized religions.
Think of the precursor to the flying spaghetti monster, but a little more advanced.
You'd have links to real groups and real locations.
And then it would talk about print, they'd talk about like UFO sightings and then cite
like actual recorded UFO sightings.
And then in the middle of it, it would start talking about this series of chaos scientists.
When I was reading this was interesting because one of the articles I read said the interesting
thing about, I know I keep saying interesting, but let me come up with another word.
The fascinating thing about this story, Ong's Hat story, is that if you come from a conspiracy
website to the story of Ong's Hat, you will believe that it's an actual conspiracy.
If you come from a website that talks about ARGs and they list it as the first ARG and
they're talking about it, you will believe it's an ARG.
Where you first find out about it from is will determine how you feel about it.
Now there's one of the guys who started it, Joseph Methany.
He wrote a book called Ong's Hat in the beginning and it tells the story in detail about the
scientists and going there and their experiments and everything.
It's basically a novel, but he won't say whether or not it's real or not.
He says, well, some people think it's real and some people think it's false and maybe
it's a little real and maybe it's a little false.
He's very coy about it.
So that just feeds the flame.
People who believe in the conspiracy theory believe, oh no, no, no, this is real and the
only way he could tell this story without the government killing him is to position
it as a novel.
And then other people who don't believe it's real go, no, no, it's just a novel and he's
really coy on it, which again, that's a marketing technique.
If he came out and said, no, it's just a novel, I wrote, it kind of ruins the mystique.
This is how legends are born.
This is how myths are created.
A little bit of real, a little bit of false.
It's gotten to the point where these resources, the book, a lot of the books and the stuff
I'm sourcing was very hard to find.
The main book, talk, his book is available online, but again, that is, it is basically
written as fact.
He just says, well, maybe it's true, maybe it's not.
It's written as that it is real.
It's not listed as a novel in so much.
The main book that really goes into this theory and talks about how online myths are created
and how it was called legend tripping is the name of the book and I'll put a link in it
in the description, but it talks about how these stories by taking real life myths, real
life legends that everyone knows about and weaving them into this complex story, you
can create a, you can create a more grounded myth and say the most ridiculous stuff, but
people go, well, I don't bigfoot.
And I know UFOs and I don't know about Ong's hat, but maybe you give it legitimacy within
the conspiracy corner by having the people in Ong's hat talk about those issues and
talk about real life people who exist.
That book is out of print.
It's like 55 to $100.
So as that book fades farther and farther out of the consciousness and gets harder and
harder to find, the only things that we're going to find are the sources that position
it as a real conspiracy theory.
There was maybe two websites that said no, this was fake and one website that was kind
of on the fence about it.
Again, that's interesting.
The way that they structured it.
Now to Aiglis travel, if Ong's hat is fake, then Aiglis travel is also fake.
So Ong's hat was just a narrative.
It was just a story.
It was just an ARG.
So where does that leave us with Aiglis travel?
If the initial source of it was an ARG, let's assume that it was an ARG and it wasn't a
way to get around government censorship because that's kind of where most of the evidence
lies.
Where does that leave us with Aiglis travel?
Well, unfortunately, Aiglis travel falls into that same route.
I think it's simply part of the myth being carried on.
It's a fascinating story and it's one of the stories that I'm really glad I researched.
Like as you're researching these type of stories, every time you find a piece of information
that kind of unlocks the puzzle, you get that little endorphin rush.
Because you realize that I've seen people ask about this for months and months and
months.
What's Aiglis travel?
And when you're able to go in and you find that, find those phrases and it starts to
make sense, you're just ready to go.
You feel great.
That's one of the things that I love about researching.
And what is even a weirder coincidence?
What is it?
Yeah, I mean, it's, it was one of those things.
This was kind of the last bit of research I did.
So I looked into Aiglis travel, backtracked it to Ong's hat, researched that, came back
to Aiglis travel.
And the very end of my research to wrap everything up, it turns out that there was a kid show,
or you know, like a young adult, you know, like, I don't know, 13 year old kid show called
Gallador about a young boy who travels to the outer dimension to save the people there.
And in it, he uses an egg.
It's called the egg.
It's this obviously egg shaped device, not the sack, which would have been, hey, 13 year
old boy, climb in my sack.
Hurry up, they're shooting the sack.
It's going to leak.
It's called the egg.
And it's taken from this ARG, the story, this egg allows him to go to these other dimensions.
That was interesting enough.
But then, to surround it all the way back, the first time I saw the iceberg was on 4chan,
which I go for a lot of my paranormal news.
Actually also go to the fitness board a lot too.
They have a lot of great exercise tips, but actually got to the fitness board because
I was trying to get to the paranormal board and accidentally clicked on fitness.
And that happened so many times, I just, I'm just going to look at the fitness board.
And I've talked about my weight loss.
I've lost 75 pounds in the past year.
And a huge part of that is thanks to fit.
So thanks fit.
But anyways, found it on 4chan.
Found out about Gallador.
The main bad guy in Gallador comes from a planet full of evil, like an evil empire planet,
called Keck, K-E-K.
Keck is the name of the ancient Egyptian deity that members of 4chan worship and worship
its current avatar, Pepe the Frog.
Does it mean anything?
No.
But I thought it was just, again, it was one of those interesting endorphin rush moments.
You know, what are the chances?
What are the chances out of all the words?
But you know, again, I just thought it was an interesting moment for me to find that
connection there.
So it's just weird how the universe works.
It's weird how these stories all kind of came together in a per, I found this on 4chan
and the last piece of evidence for me to find was that kids show with planet Keck, where
all the evil, evil comes from.
Fascinating.
I like the little, a nice little bow tie on my egg.
I actually hate eggs.
I've never eaten an egg in my life.
I might have had eggs when I was a kid, but I don't like them.
Oh, I don't know if I don't like them.
I've never eaten them, but they look disgusting.
And I heard sometimes you crack them open and a baby chicken comes out.
Not in a form, but like when you go to crack one to make eggs like to put them in a pan
or whatever, you'll crack it and there'll be a dead baby chicken.
And people tell me that's impossible, but if there's one thing I've learned, nothing's
impossible.