Ho ho ho! Merry Christmas! Today, today Santa's the host, but he changes his voice to sound
just like Jason. I'm not gonna do that for long. First off, we got all heartwarming stories
today. A man commits the ultimate Christmas crime, then we find out about a real life hero
who became a fictional legend. Kind of weird, but it's heartwarming. And then we delve into the life
of the real Saint Nicholas. I always knew Santa Claus was inspired by a real person,
but I did not know that that real person fought demons today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to the Christmas special of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host,
Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Just a quick note, I'm gonna take Christmas. You're listening to this episode on Christmas,
unless you don't listen to it daily, unless you're listening to it a week from now, that's
totally fine. But I'm not gonna record an episode tomorrow, because I had a short vacation and I
said I'd sprinkle out some days off throughout the season. So I'm gonna use one of those days right
now. So I will return with an episode for Friday. Tomorrow I'm gonna take it off, I'm gonna sit,
I'm gonna catch up on the Mandalorian. I'm behind on that, probably catch up on It's Always Sending
Philadelphia. I'd say catch up on the Simpsons, but I might have 10 seasons behind on that. I'm up
to season 20. Love that show, love that show. Now, yesterday I complained most of my stories are
really sad. Yesterday's episodes were kind of sad and I said, you know what, I'm gonna find some happy
stories. And I did. Heartwarming stories to warm the cockles of your heart. Remember when we heard
that when we were kids, we thought it was so funny. Now that's not funny at all. Like poop jokes are
still funny. People getting like kicked in the nuts is still funny. I mean, depends on who's
getting kicked if it's me, it's not that funny. If it's you, it's hilarious. And, but you know,
like people go, "Hey, look at my my weenus." That's not funny. I never actually thought it was funny
or as long your epidermis is showing. So it's funny how some jokes are universally funny. Somebody
pooping their pants will always be funny. But what was the, oh, warm the cockles of your heart.
Like when you were eight, that was kind of funny, but or maybe 12. I don't remember.
That's not funny now. So that's our first story about jokes that aren't funny. Now let's go ahead
and move on to our first topic of the day. So let's hop on board the Carbentercopter. We are headed
out to Colorado Springs, Colorado. Also, and I guess I should address this now because I'm sure
some of you guys are aware of this. As I'm flying the helicopter to Colorado Springs, we're leaving
behind Hood River. And I'm going to say, "Hey, so I know there was a bigfoot sighting in Hood River.
It's been, oh, it's been slowly seeping into the news. There's actually footage from a highway
security cam and ODOT cam, Oregon Department of Transportation of a bigfoot. Now, I don't know
what it is, but we're going to cover that in depth. You're like, "No, no, no, cover now, cover now."
"Is we're flying away from Hood River? We want to hear the local bigfoot story." "No, we're going
to cover that tomorrow." "Wait, we're not having an episode tomorrow." You're like, "No, no, come on, Jason,
why'd you tease us with that?" As I'm, now I'm hitting the gas for flying even faster away from
Hood River. I'm going to cover that on a later episode. I kind of want to like go out and like
poke around with a stick because it's within walking distance of where I'm at right now.
Bigfoot was sighted. But let's go to Colorado Springs. I look, everyone's all sulking in the
back. You're like, "Oh, man, I really want to hear about Bigfoot." And maybe Jason was like,
"Restling Bigfoot or something." I'm like, "Yeah, yeah, we'll talk about that later. It's Christmas
episode." So unless Bigfoot's walking around the Santa Hat, we're not going to cover it. So just deal
with it. You're like, "Ah, complaining the rest of the way." No, we'll cover it. I just wanted to
get that out there because I'm surprised no one sent me that link yet. It seems like it's slowly
filtering out. Veronica sent it to me. Veronica, friend of the show, she sent it to me. But it's
weird because there's actually a picture of Bigfoot, tiny little, like faraway picture Bigfoot,
but it's not hitting mainstream, which makes me think it might be true. The Bigfoot industrial
complex may be trying to shut down the truth. But anyways, we'll talk about that later.
Helicopter's landing in Colorado Springs, Colorado. So we're jumping out and you're like,
"We're not getting out of the helicopter until we talk about Bigfoot." I'm like, "Come on,
dude. I shouldn't even brought it up. Come on. Here, I'll swaddle you. Pick you up and carry
me through Colorado Springs." And a little like, you're on my back like a little baby.
You have a little bow and arrow. So we're walking through Colorado Springs, Colorado,
and you feel better now. You know we'll talk about it later. Now, it's 12.27 PM. It's December 23rd,
2019. So I'm recording this on... You guys actually should be proud of me too. I've actually
remembered this time to record the Christmas episode the day before Christmas. So there's that.
So you can actually listen to it on Christmas. It's 12.27. It's Monday. It's December 23rd,
2019. And a man, an old man, 65-year-old man, runs out of the bank, white beard and all. We're like,
"Ooh, Santa Claus?" Well, kind of. He's allegedly holding a weapon. He runs out of the bank, stops,
and then goes, "Merry Christmas!" and throws up thousands of dollars into the air, and then walks
through a Starbucks, sits down at the patio, and just hangs out. Now, we'll go into the bank and
we walk into the bank and it's just been robbed. Our suspicions are correct. That was my suspicion.
I'm assuming that was your suspicion too? Just from the clues available, the old man, the weapon,
the thousands of dollars in the air. And we talked to the tellers and they did get robbed. This guy,
again, I'm gonna have to say allegedly, David... Or sorry, okay, either his name is David Oliver,
or I misspelled it and it's... I'm pretty sure I misspelled it. Daviled. Daviled Oliver. Let me
double check and see what his name actually is. Good old Daviled. Yeah, his name's David. His name's
David. Good thing I double checked. But anyways, maybe if I call him Daviled, I won't have to keep
saying it allegedly the rest of this time. Daviled does sound like an elf name. Anyways,
then Daviled did rob this bank and when the cops showed up, they saw him sitting at the Starbucks.
They were like, "Hmm, a 65 year old man robbed this bank through a bunch of money. There's a 65 year
old man white beard sitting there." It's probably him. They walked up. He had an order to drink,
which was a weird detail the newspaper put into the article. I was like, "So? Like, really? That's
breaking news. Thanks for not... Thanks for letting me know he didn't do something." Anyways, the cops
came. They arrested him. Christmas miracle, you might say. Old man robbing a bank. The story's
a mystery on a couple different levels. One, why would you do that? There's always that thing,
like, if you're ever on the verge of homelessness, just commit a crime. I do not agree with this tactic,
but it's kind of a philosophy. If you're homeless or on the verge of homelessness,
just commit a crime where no one really gets hurt and you'll be taken care of for like
seven to ten years. It's real dicey. It's real dicey. I mean, I guess if you were... If things
were worse for you on the streets than they think they would be in prison, you know, I've also heard
that thing, like, you know, people always go, "Oh, you're in prison. You're gonna get raped."
Apparently it doesn't... I have a lot of friends and family members who have served a long time in
prison. Seven years, ten years. I have a... My cousin serving 17th of life in prison right now.
Apparently, like, people do get raped in prison, but a lot of times it's prison-specific.
And you can go your entire stay without, like, binging a dude or getting raped yourself, and
you're like, "Jason, this was supposed to be your heartwarming Christmas episode." That's true. So
we're gonna leave behind... Well, that's heartwarming to know it's not as brutal as you think it is,
but anyways, that could be why I did it. There's real... This story is so recent,
we don't know why he did this. And to make it even more Christmassy than it already is,
man with a white beard throwing money around, giving out presents. Most of the money, people
walking down the street, they saw this, they ran, they scooped up handfuls of money, they're like,
"Yes! Now I can return this to the bank." And they went into the bank and they gave it back to the
tellers. Some of the money is missing. They said a couple thousand dollars were missing, but they
said a good amount of it, people actually scooped up and took it back to the bank. It's Christmas
miracle. People saw that this guy robbed the bank, threw the money up in the air trying to give them
some Christmas cheer, and they gave themselves Christmas cheer by returning the money. A very
heartwarming story. So many Christmas true crime stories are family massacres. I made that comment
last year as well. So let's go ahead though. We're leaving behind the Christmas miracle
of Colorado Springs, Colorado. It'll always be remembered. Little kids are going to be like,
"Oh, I remember! I wish I was there! I could have bought like so many Pokemon and Beyblades and
stuff like that." Like that honestly will be a Christmas story. They'll make a movie of that
someday. A Hallmark Channel movie. The old man who reigned money. It'll be in parentheses,
but not in a strip club. Speaking of movies, speaking of movies, there's the best thing
way I could think of. I edited out 10 minutes of other garbage. Let's go to Charlotte, North
Carolina. Now I'm going to tell you this one. This story I just read about today. You might want
to grab a little hanky. You might want to grab some tissue. I don't know if hanky is an American
term. In some other country, it's probably something super obscene. Hankerchief. Hand.
Kerchief. Whatever you want to pronounce it. Hanky. Tissue. Something. Maybe I'm building it up too
much, but this is a rough one. But it's truly a Christmas story. April 30th, 2019. Some total
piece of trash. Every good Christmas story starts off with that language. And I hate humans like
this. April 30th, 2019. Some just human debris. Garbage. Piece of filth. Walks into
University of North Carolina, Charlotte, and opens fire. Just starts shooting people. Now while
this is going on, it's like five in the afternoon. People are getting ready to show these video
presentations they've been working on for class. He walks in, he starts opening fire. The teacher
opens its side door and is letting kids escape. The guy's just like pop, pop, pop, pop, shooting.
And there's a young man there named Riley Howell. He's 21 years old. He sees what's going on.
He jumps up. He rushes the shooter. Pop! Gets shot once. Heaps running. Pop! Gets shot again.
And then hits the guy. Hits the piece of trash so hard. Actually, after the guy ends up getting
arrested, he suffers internal injuries from being rammed. But at that final moment when he
smashes into this dude, Riley gets shot in the head and killed there. And the shooter lays on the
ground and someone says, "Quit shooting!" And he goes, "I'm done! I'm a big piece of trash, garbage human."
He doesn't say that last part, but he does say, "I'm done." It wouldn't have been a lie if he did.
The shooter was a guy named Tristan Andrew Terrell. 22 years old. The shooter gets taken to jail.
They've never been able to find out a motive for it. He played guilty. He ended up killing two people
and injuring five. One of the people was Riley. And the police said, "Absolutely Riley helped end this
shooting." Now, some dude in Florida is reading newspaper articles about this incident, about
this heroic act and this just piece of trash human. And I know I might be repeating piece of trash over
and over again. There's more choice words I would like to use, but again, I try not to cuss so much
on this show. There's this guy in Florida named James Wes Karen. And he's reading all these newspaper
articles about this shooting up in North Carolina. And he notices there's a trend in these articles.
All the articles about Riley Howard mention what a Star Wars fan he is. How much he loves Star Wars.
So he writes to Lucasfilm and he goes, "Hey guys, you don't really know me. I don't really even know
this kid." He had no connection with Riley Howard. But he writes to Lucasfilm, emails him, says,
"You might want to check this out because every single article I've read about this guy talks about
what a Star Wars fan he is." And I'm not saying like, make him a major character in a movie, but
you know, maybe throw him something in a comic book or something like that. Even his profile,
I think it was on CNN, said that his favorite thing was Star Wars, something else, and then
his girlfriend. Like, Star Wars was listed as his main thing. New York Times mentioned that he had
a big Star Wars collection. His little brother was doing, his little brother, Teddy, was saying,
"He's the only, let me find the actual quote." This was the quote that little brother said,
"The only 20 year old, 21 year old who would willingly fight his lightsaber with me." His
little brother saying that. That is passed away brother. So it was on May 4th when James emailed
Lucasfilm. So May 4th is the holiday of May the 4th be with you. It's like Star Wars day. May the
4th be with you. That's when he sends this email out. So 16 days later, May 28th, Lucasfilm reaches
out to the family of the Howells. They send him this letter. To the Howell family. In the wake of
your recent tragedy, everyone here at Lucasfilm wishes to express our deepest condolences.
Riley's courage and selflessness brings out the Jedi in all of us. We hope you may rejoice in his
memory and we join you in honoring his life and example. As a small tribute. Our story group has
incorporated a reimagining of Riley's name as a character in the Star Wars galaxy. We can't reveal
the specific details at this time, but the character's name will appear in a forthcoming
book publication later this year. Please keep this confidential until the book is released,
at which time we'll share it with you. Again, all of us here extend our deepest condolences.
The Force will be with Riley and all of you always.
So that is released. That's sent out on May 20th is when they give that email and they've kept it
under wraps. The family hasn't revealed any of this information. Not even close friends knew
about this. And what happened? This is where the story has come out now. What's funny? I know there's
a lot of divisiveness over the Star Wars fandom. I'm a huge Star Wars fan. I've been in love with it
since I was a little kid. I saw Return of the Jedi in the theater. I remember watching the Cyskolan
Evert review for Return of the Jedi on television. Like, it was a you were at home that day just to
watch the review to see a couple minutes of the clips. Huge Star Wars fan. Didn't like the prequels
when they came out. They didn't like... I turned... I started liking the Clone Wars when that was out
or what was it? Attack of the Clones or whatever. And then I haven't really watched the... I haven't
seen any of the new movies. I've seen the first half of Rogue One, watched the Mandalorian, but I
haven't seen The Last Jedi, Forged Awakens, none of that stuff. And I remember The Last Jedi came out.
I would get in low arguments about how dumb that movie was. And you could say, "Jace, you didn't even
see it." And I would be like, "Well, I read the synopsis. I don't have to pay money or spend time. I
know every plot detail..." Because I took it as you're totally messing up this fandom, this stuff
that I loved. But it's funny because between The Last Jedi and now, I just don't care anymore. Like,
I have... I choose what I want to like in a universe. I'm no longer like, "Oh, no, that's canon and it's
totally ruined." I just don't care anymore. Like, I really love the original trilogy. I think it's
great. The prequel trilogy is okay. It's pretty good. And I don't want to watch the sequel trilogy.
And maybe I will someday. I don't know, but I don't take it personally, one, when other people like
stuff. Well, I do kind of take that personally. That's a different thing. But I've sometimes
I find it irritating that nerd culture has gotten so popular because I used to get beat up
and get in fistfights over this stuff and now just anyone can like it. So that kind of irritates me.
But that's not really my point. My point is that... What was my point? My point is this. My point is
this. It's like, now I didn't like in-game. I thought it was stupid. It was boring. It took the story
nowhere. But it didn't ruin Iron Man for me. It didn't ruin Civil... I don't like Civil War. It didn't
ruin Winter Soldier for me. It was just dumb. It was boring. They did nothing in the whole movie.
It was stupid. I didn't like in-game. The end. I mean, like, you know what I mean? I didn't get
offended by how terrible it was. It was a shoddy movie. And... But the fact that I saw it didn't ruin
Infinity War for me. Anyways, that being said, I think definitely the new Star Wars movie, there's
a lot of divisiveness going on. There's a huge conspiracy theory involving Rise of Skywalker
right now. We'll get into that in our next episode as well. But right now, I kind of wanted to focus
on the positive. And I think this is a positive story because I'm sure as I was reading that
letter, there are some of you who are like, "Yeah, but the new Star Wars sucks. So who wants to be
involved in those?" Well, Riley would. Riley would. And even if you don't like new Star Wars movies,
if you even if you think that Luke, the Jedi warrior kind of dying on a rock after trying to kill
his nephew is stupid, and it was a bad story choice, Riley liked it. So sometimes we don't,
just because somebody else likes something that we don't like, or because the universe goes in
a different direction. When I say universe, I don't mean the actual physical universe. I mean,
the canon universe of these stories. Riley liked it. And sometimes we have to remember that when
we're in these internet arguments about how stupid, how stupid it was that Leia flies through space
now or whatever. So let's go back here. We get the letter out. And then about a week ago, one of
Riley's friends calls up his girlfriend and says, "Hey, you want to, this is weird. This is really weird.
I was reading the Rise of Skywalker, the visual dictionary. And I came across this
passage and the girlfriend's like, "Nerd, why are you calling me on this?" He's like, "No, no, no. Wait,
wait. Hold on. Let me find it. I've dogged this section." It says, here's the section in the book,
the Ionica, it's a sci-fi word, the Ionimaka, whatever. Jedi master and historian, Riley Howell,
collected many of the earliest accounts of explorations and codifications of the Force
in the Ionica, a two-volume combination of codex, correspondence, and scrapbook.
Though much of its contents would later be stored in holocrons, which have since been lost,
the physical books have passages written in the hands of the original sages, carefully preserved by Howell.
And the girlfriend basically starts bawling because she realizes this is it, this is his
memory. Now, Riley, it's apt that he was a historian character because
one of the people quoted in this article was saying that he was into the lore. He was going
through the Wikipedia, Wookiepedia is actually the name of it, but Wookiepedia pages read all of the
books, was really into the lore and the history of the Star Wars universe. He wasn't just a fan who
collected toys, he was into the obscure information. A historian would be a good character for him.
And then his mother will end it with this quote from his mother, Natalie Henry Howell,
is her name. And this is what she says, quote, "And I like the way they actually left his last name."
I think he would really be appreciative of that because, you know, they could have just said,
"Riley, Jedi, Riley." And we'd be guessing the whole time about whether or not it was really him.
But they put his last name in there just to really honor him. And that really made me cry when I
heard about it. Here's the rest of this article. "She also wept last Thursday when the whole family
went to see the new movie on opening night. They brought his ashes and left a seat open for him."
I think Henry Howell says he would have liked the way it ended.
So that's the story of Riley Howell, now Jedi Master Riley Howell, a real life hero who became
a legend in the universe he loved so much. It would be really cool if someone made a fan fiction,
made a short film or something about Riley Howell and explored that character more.
Who knows, maybe, I guess they were planning on doing Knights of the Old Republic.
Maybe. Long shot, probably not. But yeah, an uplifting story. A man who gave up his life to
save others gets to live on forever in the Star Wars universe. Let's go ahead and move on to the
next story. You might have to fly the helicopter. I got something in my eye right now. I gotta get
it out. So go ahead. Go ahead, take the controls. It's Christmas time. I trust you. So as you are
piloting the Carbenter copter and I'm sitting in the back thinking, feeling bad about all the
times you talked trash about last night, even just a couple minutes ago when I was talking trash
about last night, flying. I'm just kind of hanging my feet out of the helicopter looking down a
landscape. That is a sad story. It's a sad story no matter what you cut it. But it's truly a story
of giving. It's a story of giving. You're like, Jason, shut up. I'm trying to fly the helicopter
and now I'm getting stuff in my eyes too. I was like, sorry, sorry. Sorry. Okay. So you're like,
where are we going? And I'm like, we are going to Turkey and we're going back to 300 AD. So go ahead
and hit that button right there. We're flying over Turkey now, 380. We're looking for a man. A man.
I can't really build up the suspense because I already told you in the intro who it is. We're
looking for St. Nicholas. We're looking for Nicholas of Bari. Sometimes known as Nicholas of Myra.
But anyways, we're looking for a dude named Nick. So we're landing. We're flying over like
little Pueblo dirt houses and stuff like that. Flying over. I don't know what the houses were
built of back then. I barely know what houses are built out of now. I think it's mostly wood
still, right? Anyways, we land in the middle of Turkey. Maybe they had wooden houses back then.
I don't think they were still like living in caves. I mean, there was obviously like established
shitties, but I just assumed everything looked like, you know, Bible times, even though it was 300
years afterwards. So we land and we're walking around and we're going to meet a guy named Saint
Nick. It's the dude. His name, he's not Saint yet. He's like, whoa, spoiler alert. I'm a Saint? Apparently
he's also Rodney Dangerfield. Oh, I get no respect. I got three miracles and all I do is walk around
with a stick. These other people got two and people are praying to their bones. I get no respect. So
Nicholas, it's Nicholas of Bari to the two people who listen to this show who know who Rodney Dangerfield
is. Nicholas of Bari is this dude. I keep wanting to call him tall. He's actually like five foot six,
which may be back then was tall, but I'm guessing we're all taller than this guy or at least equal
to him. So we're giants in this time period. So we're walking around with Nicholas and we're like,
so yes, spoiler alert, we're from the future. Nice to meet you. He was like, oh, I get no respect.
I'm stuck in the present. We're like, that's okay. The joke's over. It's like, okay, we're here to
explore your life. He's like, yo, okay, so let's do this. Now he's a monster. I just have to differentiate
the voices. So Nicholas is like, first off, what I'm going to do here is there's this house down the
street. Now let me say this too here. I'm going to push him aside, push Nicholas aside to stand in
front of the camera. All the stories we're about to talk about, I know there's going to be someone
out there, multiple people actually, who say that story is not true. That story is actually about
this person and that person. Because this guy is so old, and there was no written records of him
until 600 AD, people know he exists because there were like a church named after him that was before
600 AD. And he was listed in documents, people know he existed. He's not a mythological figure,
but he wasn't being written about until 600 AD. The stuff he wrote had been destroyed and the
stuff other people wrote about him had been destroyed. Because he was in Turkey for the most part,
it was getting conquered by the Muslims at a certain point. Things were just being demolished.
It wasn't the best environment. Paper was frail. So I'm going to tell these stories and people go,
well, actually, that is part of this old pagan myth. Maybe, maybe they got assigned to him, maybe.
But these are all just fun stories about Nicholas. Nicholas, Saint Nicholas. So get off my back.
Saying here, all of these stories have been attributed to Nicholas in one way or the other.
However, you could easily say that didn't happen. I think you can probably say that about most of
the stories I'm about to say, but historically, they've been attributed to Nicholas. So I'm going
to step away from the camera now. Come here, Nick. Get back in front of the camera. He's like,
what's a camera? What was that? He goes on to say, like, listen, you see that house down the street
there? There's this dude. He used to be really, really rich, right? And he's not rich no more.
You got no money because the envy of Satan took it from him. That's an actual quote. That's what
people were calling it. How much you imagine Satan has a lot of money. You imagine that he's
probably pretty well off, dude. You know, he's the corruptor of the universe. How much money do
you have to have for Satan is jealous of you? I imagine an awful lot. But anyways, he's, he has
too much money. Satan got jealous, he ended up losing his money and now he's poor. Now that sucks,
but he also has three daughters in 300 AD, which is not good because you have to pay dowries
to marry them off. If you can't pay the dowries, they got to go. The women got to work. You can't
raise them their entire life. It's not like they could go get a job at the local market or something
like that. And if they can't get married off, the only real option for them is to become freeloaders
living off the dad. He didn't got no money. Satan took it all and or, or they become prostitutes.
And Nicholas hears about this. Now, Nicholas, what we do know about him is he came from a very wealthy
Greek family and his parents passed away. So he's basically like Batman. But instead of fighting
crime, he was a devout Christian. I wonder if Batman is religious. I know Daredevil is.
You know, I remember once when they were talking about Miss Marvel, she's the,
she's a Marvel superhero character. They mentioned that she was the first Muslim
superhero. And it's funny because I never thought about it. I go, I never really considered what
religion Spider-Man was. He could have been Muslim for all I know. Like it was weird. Like once you
start saying this, like you knew Daredevil was Catholic, he was kind of built into his character
because he was like this Irish dude from Hell's Kitchen. But like I never really, I've, once they
pointed out and said this character is Muslim, then I had to sit down and go, well, I'm sure Tony
Stark's an atheist and I guess Captain America's probably like Lutheran or something like that.
Like I never really considered any of them having a religion outside of Daredevil until they somewhat,
until you explicitly pointed somebody out and said this is the first Muslim character.
And I go, oh, that's weird. Anyways, what was I talking about? Oh yeah, St. Francis,
not St. Francis, St. Nicholas is not Batman. He's a Christian. I wonder what religion Batman is
not just showing, I'm just showing. So anyway, I'm sure Batman's atheist as well. I don't know.
Like what would Batman be? It would be, I honestly think if anything, the most religious character
in comic books, I don't know why I think this, but it would be Superman. And yeah, Superman like
punches like dark side in the face and he like fights like sons that eat planets. But I still
think Superman would believe in God. Like I don't know why I think that like Superman seems like
the character who would probably be the most religious dude out there. I don't know why. I mean,
I'm sure someone could point me to a comic book where he's like God doesn't exist, only me and he
like evaporates a bunch of bad guys. But maybe because he's so powerful, I think he would have to
assume there was someone more powerful than him. I don't know. I don't know. I think Batman probably,
Batman probably doesn't really care much about religion. It's funny because Batman,
you're like chasing this supposed to be episode about St. Nicholas. You haven't even gotten the
good stuff yet. I think Batman only thinks about beating up criminals. I think he would,
I think he would probably be super shallow to talk to. Like I honestly don't think he, I love
Batman. He's one of my favorite comic book characters. He's honestly one of like my favorite
fictional characters. But I'm sure he's super boring to hang out with. When he's Bruce Wayne,
he's pretending he's a shallow idiot. So no one catches on that he's the world's greatest detective.
He would just basically talk about partying and stuff like that. Surface level sociology
conversations with Bruce Wayne. Not an idiot, just shallow. But just somebody that when you talk to
you're like, okay, we've talked for about an hour. That's probably, this is probably the most in-depth
conversation we're gonna have. And as Batman, I don't think he, he would, he would talk to him
much. And then he would just, I think that's all he talks about is beating up criminals. I think
he's probably super shallow. I think Superman, you could have long conversations about stuff. I think
he'd really be willing to, because he's so powerful that you're, everyone's an idiot to him. So he
has to talk down to everybody. And he's seen things in the universe that humans can't even
comprehend. It'd be like Doctor Strange. But again, I think Doctor Strange would be kind of,
he wouldn't care. Like he's super smart and you're like a waste of his time. He talked to you a
little bit and then say, I gotta go somewhere. Then he would just teleport into another room in his
house and be really quiet until you left. I think Superman would actually take the time out to have
a conversation with you. Batman, it would probably take the time out to have a conversation with you,
but he would only talk about choke holds and arm bars if you're lucky. Otherwise, he's just gonna
sit and flex on you all day long and talk about how, how nice his car is and how nice his house is.
Just so you leave. So then he can go, it's Sulk in his Batcave and try to find, not just Sulk,
you know, also try to solve murders and stuff like that. But I don't think it would be kind of
dope to talk to, but none of this he's anything to do with St. Nicholas. As we're going off in
that rat in St. Nicholas, he's just standing there. He, he's invented a watch. He invented a little
sundial watch. So like, are you done? Are you done? Are we gonna talk about me? Yes, we're gonna talk
about you. He's like, thank you. Let me finish telling you about my miracles, not your stupid
fictional characters, Jason. He says, listen, Batman's not real. This story's real. My parents died
and they left me a bunch of money and I'm standing outside this house with three potential prostitutes
living in it. These dudes, he's super mad at us. He's a saint. He's a Catholic saint. I just spent
10 minutes talking about Spider-Man and talking to Batman and we're in the presence of a man.
When I get done telling this story, you're gonna realize how this whole segment, this dude is so
dope. St. Nicholas is so awesome. And the fact that I was talking about all these dumb two-dimensional
drawings for however long that took, you're gonna be mad at me. I'm kind of mad at me because this
guy does some crazy stuff. He's like, listen, okay, I'm standing outside this house. There's three
potential prostitutes in there. I have money. So what I'm gonna do is he puts these gold coins
in a bag and he throws it through the dude's window for the first daughter and bounces out.
The dad the next day wakes up and he's like, what? Look it, here's enough money to pay for the dowry
for one of my daughters. Marrys the daughter off. The other daughter, she meets a man. She's gonna
get married. A bag of gold magically appears on the dude's floor. He's like, what? That's so weird.
Like, this happened last time. I wanted to get this daughter married off. A bunch of gold showed up.
Now his third daughter's marriage is coming up as well. And he goes, you know what? I'm gonna stay
up tonight. I'm gonna stay up tonight. And I'm gonna see what happens. Because you would assume
it's magic. A bag of gold appearing in your house before your daughter's wedding. Because if she
didn't have the money, the wedding would be called off. Girl has to turn tricks. So he stays up and
he sees a bag of gold, fly through a window, and he runs outside. He sees Nicholas standing out there.
Nicholas goes, hey, hey, listen, don't tell anyone about this. Like, the reason why he was doing
secretly, because he goes, this is the theories. This is the theories that was written about.
He didn't know if the guy would accept the money because it was charity. This guy was a formally
very wealthy man. Then he would basically be taking handouts. And he didn't know if his pride
would get in the way of it. And then, too, he didn't want any credit for it. So he tells the dad,
don't tell anyone about this. I'm just paying this off. And the dad ends up getting the third
daughter married out. Now that story does eventually. That story is actually probably the one of the most
historical stories involving Nicholas. Because really what they do is when they start to look at
stories, because Nicholas actually starts his, oh, after his death, he becomes such a main player in
the saints. He becomes such a big figure in the saints, in the world of Catholicism, that we see
stories being attributed to him in the year like 1400. So they have to go back to stories that
they could find in the 600, 700, 800. They think those are more likely to be true. And this is one
of the earliest stories involving Nicholas. And it really, so as his legend grows, basically, well,
let's take this one. Because this one, I think, really is the Santa Claus that we know of.
Then you go, Santa Claus, it's funny. I took for granted that everyone knows that Saint Nicholas
is another name for Santa Claus. You're like, what? I thought you were just talking about some
dude throwing money around. And you know what's funny now that I say that? That was the first story
we did. Guy starts throwing money around. Who knows? Maybe there were some potential prostitutes
walking down the street that day, and he was able to make it. That's an interesting, weird story.
Did not even plan that. What if he felt that cops interrogate him? They're like, what'd you do? And
he's like, I don't know. I just felt compelled to do it. And at that time, there was this girl who
was really like, I might have to become a prostitute. Wait, money. And then she scoops it out. I know
this world works. But maybe, maybe. Anyways, so this is the story. This is kind of the overview.
That's one of the main stories involving Saint Nicholas. He's giving, he's doing it in secret.
One version of the story is he was throwing it through the chimney. And that probably wasn't true.
I don't know how many chimneys they had in Turkey, but they basically, the story travels out of Turkey.
He becomes a venerated figure in Catholicism. And he becomes like the patron saint of children
and sailors and all sorts of stuff. And the story of him giving gifts is one of the reasons why Saint
Nicholas morphed into the story of Santa Claus or Sinter Claus. And it's one of the versions that
we have today. Now, that is all cool. That's all an interesting story. That's not what I want to
talk about, even though I just did. That was kind of the intro. Because I always knew Saint Nicholas,
the story of Santa Claus, was loosely based on somebody real. But I didn't know he was such a
dope figure. I didn't know. So we have that. Very generous man. But let's look at some other feats
of Saint Nicholas. See, to be a saint in the Catholic Church, you have to have three miracles.
You have to have three miracles attributed to you. They just don't say, "Ah, you are a good dude."
Like Mother Teresa, if they ever want to make Mother Teresa and have heard that they're trying
to go through, they have to find three miracles she did. There's this whole thing,
whole process you have to go through to be named a saint in the Catholic Church.
Now, I want you to think about this for a second, guys. So our version of Santa Claus,
the gift-giving thing, is based on that story. Imagine if our holidays were based on any of
these other stories here. Here's some of his other miracles he had. He was at sea, he was at a boat,
big storm came, he calmed the storm. Lame, boo, could you, that's nothing. Every year you get
like a bowl of water, he stayed around the bowl of water and someone shakes it. And the other
person's like, "No, don't, don't." And then go, "That's it." That would be a lame holiday to have.
That'd be a lame miracle to build a holiday around. Here's another one. It saved three
innocent soldiers from execution. So people were about to be executed for a crime they didn't commit.
And he shows up. It's so funny. So this dude was a priest. His uncle was like a mayor of the town,
and he knew that Nicholas wanted to be a priest. So he goes, "Aye, you're a priest." He was super
devout, a little bit of nepotism, but it was his calling. And so he's this priest for a while. And
then like there was this thing where like the uncle died and a couple other town officials died,
and the priests were like, "Oh, dude, we need a new bishop. Who should we elect as bishop?" And
someone goes, "Tell you what, whoever is the first priest to walk through that door is the new
bishop." And Nicholas just walks into the church and they're like, "Congratulations, Nicholas. You're
a bishop. What? That's how they picked officials back then?" That is ripe for an Adam Sandler movie
where it's basically just this dude, this shlubby guy who's down on his luck. And then there's like
this diocese and they're like, "We don't know what to do. Bishop, archbishop, died. The first person
who walked through that door is our new bishop." And he's like, "What?" And then like some old
like third eye blind song starts playing and he's like training to be a priest. Make that movie,
Adam Sandler. I think he's Jewish actually. Actually, no, I don't think he's Jewish. I know
he's Jewish because he did the Hanukkah song. But still, make that movie, Adam Sandler.
What was it? Oh, so anyways, he, um, not Adam Sandler. Nicholas walked through the door of the
church and they go, "Hey, it's a new bishop." And he's like, "Hey, I'm a new bishop." And they lift
him up on the shoulders. They dump a gatorade bucket of holy water on him. He's like, "Yeah." So,
anyways, so as bishop, these three dudes are about to be executed and he's like, "Hey, stop it."
And like put his hand on the sword and lowered it and let him go. That would be kind of cool. You'd
be able to like carry swords around at Christmas time. That would be kind of cool. Any holiday that
involves swords would be cool. But I don't think it would catch on and be kind of old after a while.
Instead of the nativity scene, you just had three dudes standing, a guy with a sword walking around.
So here's some cool versions though. I also should say this as well. The Council of Nicaea,
right? This is how dope this dude was. So the Council of Nicaea was this thing where a bunch of
bunch of priests, a bunch of dudes get together to figure out what should actually be in the Bible.
Probably one of the biggest events to happen post the death and resurrection of Christ regarding
Christianity easily, easily was a bunch of people getting together and saying, "What are we going
to do with all of these stories? We're going to keep some of these. We're going to put some of these
away." Like the Book of Enoch, that's when they removed it. They're like, "This is way too weird to
be in the Bible. Let's put this book in." And it basically created Christianity and it wasn't
just books. They were going into individual passages and editing them for clarity. Anyways,
Nicholas was there. Saint Nicholas was at the Council of Nicaea. He was in one of the roll
call sheets, but didn't appear in any other roll call sheet at all. Now some people say that he
just kind of showed up and then bounced. Like he's like, "Ah, see you later nerds. You guys are just
sitting around reading a book. I'm doing, I'm going to go pray and I'm going to talk to God. You guys
can keep reading them dumb old scrolls." But some people say not that he said that, but there's another
version of that. He goes to a Council of Nicaea and there's a debate over whether or not Jesus,
God, and the Holy Spirit are one, the Holy Trinity, or that Jesus was a separate person from God.
I guess you can guess which side one, because everyone talks about the Holy Trinity nowadays.
But some people said, "No, no, no. Jesus was like a separate dude. He had God as one being and Jesus
was a separate dude." So Nicholas believed in the Holy Trinity and this other guy believed in that it
was just that Jesus and God were two separate people. And during the debate, Nicholas is listening
to him and he's like, "Yeah, yeah, I understand that, but no, it's all like Jesus is God and God is
Jesus, the Holy Spirit is the Holy Trinity." The other guy's like, "No, no, no, that doesn't make
sense. Like, that's the two separate people." And at the Council of Nicaea, while they're debating
what to put in the Bible, Nicholas punches the dude in the face, just socks this guy. And so
that's the other version, is that he basically beat this dude up at a religious conference
and they kicked him out. And that's why he's only in one roll called Sheep for the Council of Nicaea.
So if he had stayed, there probably would have been way more fistfights in the Bible. They're
like, "Hey, you know, this part about numbers is really cool where they're like counting all the
sheep, but can we just insert the story where I go back in time and I'm beating up sheep?"
They're like, "No, Nicholas, you can't keep putting yourself in the Bible." Anyways, so he was just
beating people up at a religious conference, which is hilarious. Imagine a Christmas based on this
story. Imagine a Christmas based on this story. This, what happened was when Nicholas was around,
Christians were still getting tortured and murdered. And then, who was it? Constantine came into town
and basically came into power and changed it into the Holy Roman Empire and all that stuff.
And I know a bunch of historians just pulled their hair out of their head because I know I got some
details wrong, but basically Christianity began to take off. It became the new thing. It became the
meme that would eventually conquer entire swathes of the planet. So he was in that perfect time where
he did get beat up a lot, which isn't part of the perfect time, but he suffered religious persecution
and his beliefs stood up against that persecution. And then he got to get some of that sweet, sweet
love from the people where people are no longer beating him up, but actually saying, "Hey, let's
listen to what this guy has to say." So he began this thing where he was walking around and he would
go to these pagan temples. He would leave the city, wouldn't just be sitting in his vestments, wouldn't
be sitting all high and pretty. He would leave the city to go talk to the common folk, and he would
come across these pagan structures that were built in the middle of nowhere, and he would walk up to
them and he would begin to pray in front of them, because he would sense the demons inhabiting these
buildings, and he would just sit down and he would begin to pray. In towns people are like, "What?
Is he praying to our God? Is he praying to Hermes or Zeus or whoever is in that house?"
And he'd be like, "Shh, praying in the house would fall apart." His prayers were so proud. You're
like, "Jason, that story is probably the most unbelievable story you've told yet. Call me in a
storm. Could just be good timing. Praying till the house blows up is probably, maybe that was also
good timing. Maybe he happened to go, "Hmm, that's weird. I see termites. He's Batman. He is the old
timey Batman. Maybe he was the world's greatest detective and he would walk around till he found
a house that had a bunch of termites in it and go, "This house is also a shrine, isn't it?" And
they're like, "Yeah, you're right. We worship termites." And he prays and the house falls apart.
Or could just be a miracle. Like the place wasn't happening. You're like, "Jason, Jason, Jason."
As skeptical as you are, are you really trying to say that maybe this dude prayed in front of a house
until it fell apart? Well, hey man, it's a weird world. You know, that's the funny thing about
being a skeptic. I think you can either be a skeptic or you just believe in everything. And
that's not fun. That to me seems very dour existence where you don't believe in anything at all. Or
you can be a skeptic like me. You can be sin-chooses and will totally mock certain beliefs and then go,
"Well, maybe a dude prayed in front of a house, but at least I'm honest about it. At least I'm
honest about it. It is ridiculous to think that a guy could pray in front of a house and it falls
apart. That's some sort of miracle. And I embrace the ridiculousness of it. So at least I'm honest
about it. At least I'm honest about my hypocrisy because I will trash-talk other weird beliefs and
then be like, "Well, maybe there's one happening. Maybe a guy just was praying in it, Philip."
But anyways, so even that's not the best part of the story. At one point he's walking, he sees the
house, right? And he sees a bunch of demons floating around in it and he's like, "Oh,
break out my praying hands!" He's getting down on his knees. And the demons start to talk to him,
and this is what they say. "Do us no wrong!" Wrong, wrong. There's an echo. It's a really big
house. It's a really big house. "Though we have committed no offense against thee, yet thou douse
drive us from our home. It is here where we have long dwelt and led astray the people who worshiped
us. And now where are we to go? To go? To go?" I love the fact that they admit they're like,
"Yeah, dude. We were leading these dudes down the wrong path, but don't we weren't doing nothing to
you? You? You?" Even in their summary they echo. And here's a response. So he's sitting there.
So as he's sitting there, he's kind of like dusting off the ground. He's getting ready to kneel.
And they're like, "Why are you coming after us, bro? Come on, man." So they
ask, "So where are we to go?" And then he goes, he looks at him, dead pan and goes, "Go to the fire,
the everlasting one, which has been prepared for the devil and his angels." Starts praying.
No, no, the house blows up. Now, I think the quote's funny, one, because the demons do speak
pretty proper Greek or whatever this is translated from, or whatever this is translated from.
Also, I love the fact that he has to clarify where he goes, "Go to the fire." And then I imagine
there's a long pause, the demons are like, "Huh? Which fire?" And he's like, "The everlasting one."
And they're like, "Oh, he means hell. Oh, no, we didn't get that." Like, he has to be specific.
I don't think you have to be specific when you're dealing with a horde of demons. Because there's
not, if you say you're going to the fire, I don't think they're like, "Hmm, does he mean the fire
sale? Does he mean Fire Island?" It's obvious hell. They're obviously adding that in for the reader.
Someone reading this book back then, and they're like, "Go to the fire." They have to turn the page.
"Oh, the everlasting one." The one, they're like, "Oh, he means hell." So anyways, he prays. Now, he also,
eventually, there was a demon-possessed tree that apparently had Artemis in it. The people,
it was super weird. So, these stories make it seem like they weren't these demons were impersonating
Greek gods, which is an interesting thing. It's not that the demons were, it's not like he would,
I was reading this on a Christian website, and it wasn't like they were saying that the Greek gods
themselves were demons, but the demons were impersonating Greek gods. And I'm not saying that
the Christian website I was getting from them believes that Artemis and Hermes and Zeus,
but it also wasn't going so far to say the pagan gods were demons themselves. Apparently, the legend
is, those gods don't exist at all, like the Christian version of the story is. There are no
Greek gods, which I think is not a controversial statement to say in Christianity that there are
no Greek gods, but it's not like Zeus was a demon. It's that these gods didn't exist at all, and
these demons were inhabiting these buildings, these shrines that were built to these false idols.
They would normally be built, there'd be nothing in them, and then a demon would find it in
hide inside the building. And the same thing, there was just happened to be a tree that people
were worshiping as Artemis, the goddess of the hunt. Now he's already been praying and making
houses explode. This one, he finds out there's a demon in the tree, and he's just like done. He's
so done with praying. People in town are like, "Hey, yeah, we prayed to that tree," and he looks over
at it, and he sees a demon in it, and he's like, "Well, listen, prayer time's over. Wait, no, it's not.
Pray to God, he still gets to pray. Prayer time's not over, but I'm going to chop that tree down." He
picks the axe up, starts walking a tree. The demon just leaves the tree. He's like, "Oh, that was
easy. Why didn't I have to pray all this time and blow houses up? I could have just carried an axe
around and they would have left." And then he goes to another town. There's another tree, a demon
possessed tree, and he goes, "I wonder if this will work again." Just walks up, grabs an axe,
demon leaves. So, I think at that point, he probably realized there was a way easier way to do this.
I didn't have to sit and pray and pray and pray until house exploded. I could have just carried
an axe around the whole time, and the demons would have run away. However, the demons that ran away
from the trees, did they end up in the everlasting fire? I'm assuming when he was praying, the houses
exploded, and the demons went somewhere. So, maybe he was just getting lazy in the end, and he's like,
"Ah, whatever. I don't care if this demon keeps hopping from tree to tree. I just don't want him
in this town, not in my neighborhood." Now, imagine a Christmas based on that. Every year,
your family gets together, just like carving a pumpkin, but you guys build a giant gingerbread
house together. And then, you get a little like gross goo, and you throw it on it and be like,
"These are demons." And then you put firecrackers in it and blow it up. Every year, instead of
decorating your house for Christmas, you would build a smaller house in your front yard and blow
it up. That would be way better, or maybe just if you were lazy, just carrying axe around in your
front yard. And then you'd be like, "Oh, there's a demon in the tree and it left." If you couldn't
afford to blow up a small house every year, that is how you would celebrate Christmas. But,
that is not even his best miracle. That is not even his best miracle. Ladies and gentlemen,
let me introduce you to the brine babies. Let me introduce you to why you've been
staring perplexed at the image that has been linked on this podcast. Because as you have noticed,
I'm sure that is not the standard Dead Rabbit logo for today's episode. For the past, what, 30,
40 minutes you've been looking at it and going, "Get to this part of the story! I don't know what
this image is!" And if you're not looking at the image, it is a medieval painting of St. Nicholas,
a suspicious man lurking in the back hallway. And you're like, "That's not the most notable part
of that picture. The man in the back hallway is not the most notable part of the picture." You have
St. Nicholas, you have a creepy man in the hallway, and then you have three naked dudes hopping out
of a barrel. You're like, "Jason, please tell us why this has anything to do with what the story is."
I will, but first, let me talk about my Minecraft server. So, this is the deal. Minecraft server
is in the show notes, but his most notable miracle is this. There was a famine coming
through Turkey. People were starving. Now, generally when famines happen, first you eat.
You're like, "Jason, just tell us what's in the picture. Don't do it. Show you a famine."
I can just imagine people for the whole episode being like, "What is this? What is this picture?
Why am I looking at it?" So, when famines strike, you're like, "Damn, Jason's really going to do
this. Yes, I am." When famines strike, there's usually what happens is they eat all their food
that they have available. Then they begin to eat their livestock, normally stuff that they provide.
Like cows, if you drink the milk or chickens, you would eat the egg, but you're basically running
out of food, so you just eat the chicken. Then you begin to eat your clothing. In modern times,
you'd eat leather shoes or drywall. People eat drywall a lot during famines. Then you begin to
eat each other. Now, this famine, they were in phase eating human meat. Now, it wasn't super open
when this famine was going on. People were eating people, but you had to do it on the slide. You
didn't want to sit down. I'm like, "The mailman's walking by and you're like, 'Oh, I'm not eating
them in the bushes.'" But this butcher needed to make some money, needed to sell some food,
and wanted to eat himself. So he grabs three boys and kills them and pickles them in a barrel of
brine, and he's going to sell them as pork. Now, Nicholas is passing through town. This wasn't
happening in his neighborhood because he came from a wealthy area. Like I said, he was traveling
the countryside. He comes into town. He is Batman. He investigates this crime. He starts to realize,
"Hmm, something's not up with these evil doers. I believe he's the saint. He should be the saint
of rooftops." He's like standing on the rooftop all night long. He's like somewhere out there.
Somebody's eating kids and I will find them. Could it be the Joker? He has to solve it. He comes into
town and he's investigating the famine and trying to do what he can to feed people.
And something clues him off because he's Batman. He is the world's greatest detective of
the 300 AD. He's walking through town and he starts to become suspicious of a local butcher.
And he goes to the butcher shop and he's like, "He puts on his infrared goggles." And he's like,
"Interesting. I see someone's been here recently judging by the footprint." And then there's three
little pairs of footprints added towards this bloody table. Okay, that's a little, that's a little
dark. Even for me. He shuts off his infrared goggles. Butchers behind him with a knife. They're
wrestling. Throws him over his back. Does it like a... Do you know in the new Batman movie,
I thought this was so awesome. They're training Robert Pattinson on Brazilian Jiu Jitsu. So
you're gonna... I'm basically learning the same fighting skill as Batman does. Anyways, throwing
around arm bars, rear naked chokes, anaconda chokes. He's doing all the moves, all the moves that I
know. And finally, St. Nicholas gets on top of the butcher and goes, "Now it's time to butcher you."
He doesn't do that. That's stupid. He goes, he finally gets on top of the butcher, chokes him out
completely. Falsely. Butcher's all tapping. He doesn't care. This guy's a criminal. Puts him out.
Nicholas gets up and... Okay, I don't know if they actually got in a physical fight because in the
drawing, the butcher is just walking in the background. I think most likely Nicholas broke
into this place and the butcher walked by and goes, "Hey, what are you doing in my shop?"
But it doesn't matter because at this point Nicholas opens up the barrel and sees the little
dead boys in the... You're like, "Jayson, this is supposed to be a Christmas episode. Shame on you."
Yes, this part's dark, but that's not the miracle. The miracle is that he found three corpses. That's
not a miracle. The miracle is this. He then brings the three boys back to life. So they're coming
out of the brine. He resurrects them. That is the biggest miracle that he ever did. Now,
a couple different takeaways from this one. One, you have a man who can resurrect the dead,
which is probably one of the biggest things you can do really ever. I mean, if that's in your
skill set, if you can resurrect the dead in your skill set, you are God. So that's a big miracle.
I don't know how many other saints can put that on their belt, but he resurrected the dead. Two,
that would be a dope haul. That would be a dope Christmas tradition. Every year, like if you're
bad, you have to drink brine instead of coal and you're stuck in there like, "Oh man, even bad this
year. Here, drink some brine." And remember all the murdered pork babies. Remember the brine babies
before you go and go, "I don't want to be a brine baby. Well, then you should be better next year."
If you're bad, you're a brine baby. That would be awesome. And the fact that you would have,
like, imagine having your Christmas story involve cannibalism and children being pickled and turned
into pork and then having to sit down at a table eating meat with your family. Maybe we
would have vegetarian holidays. I don't know. I'd like to imagine this. Listen, you're a kid,
you get murdered by a butcher, you get pickled, you get brought back to life. And my first,
my first, when I read this story, I thought this would be my first thing. I'd pop out of the barrel
and I'd be like, "Awesome. Thanks. But can you unpickle me? Like, here's the thing. You imagine
these kids were pickles at that point. Like, when you're brought back to life, are you restored to
your point the moment before you die? Like, or are they, were they permanently pickled? Weren't
these poor boys permanently pickle boys? Brine babies? Were they walking around town? They're
super green. They're all wrinkly. How did that work? I would assume, because see, now we're asking
a whole bunch of questions. Like, if your head got chopped off and a saint put your head back on and
brought you back to life, you would assume that now you, your head's not going to roll off every time
you turn to your body too quickly. But, it's like being stabbed and having your wound healed and come
back to life is one thing. Having leprosy and not losing any body parts or having like a disease
where you're internally damaged and then having that disease cured and coming back to life,
that's, but you, they were killed, they weren't killed in brine. They were killed and then put
in pickle juice and then brought back to life. So, their injuries were healed. Were they still
pickled? Is my question. And you're like, Jason, you're really nitpicking this one because these
kids came back from the afterlife. It wouldn't matter how wrinkly their skin were or the fact
that they smelled like vinegar up until their late 80s when they finally died. I'm still curious,
though, because I would have been like, hey, thanks a lot, dude, for bringing me back to life.
First off, you could have been here, you could have been here about a day earlier. Stop the whole
thing. But I appreciate you bringing me back to life. But also, please unpickle me. Like,
what's that part of the process? Secondly, you know, no case of the kids come back to life. They
jump out of the brine. They may be pickled. They may be not. They're immediately starving to death
because they're still a massive famine hitting the area. But I'm assuming, I'm assuming that the
kids were real fed. I'm assuming there's some other minor miracles. At one point, he made a
bunch of wheat. They took a boat and they unloaded like a ton of wheat off the boat. And then the
boat went to its main destination and still had all the wheat on it. So he could multiply food and
stuff like that as well. He ends up having all these miracles about him. He passes away. He becomes
such a major religious figure that he becomes one of the only non-warrior saints that was worshiped
during the Crusades. People were stopping by his church. Now, we still got one more super bizarre
story to talk about Saint Nicholas, because at this point, he is Saint Nicholas. In the year
1,000, I think it was 48. So when he died, people knew this dude was legit. He has all these magical
powers. These three little brine babies show up at his funeral. They're like, "Yeah, it was us. It was
us." People are like, "Yeah, we know it was you." He smelled like vinegar and they're like, "Ah,
shut up. He brought us back to life." So people knew this guy was legit. They start the saint process
pretty early on for him. But when you're a saint, your bones become like holy relics. Now, his bones,
when we look back, there was this story that they secreted a rose water smelling liquid
that people attributed to being mana or myrrh. And by drinking the liquid, you could get super
power, not super powers so much, but like supernatural abilities. Very, very vague stuff.
And you're like Jason, old, timey superstitions, whatever. The Muslims ends up invading the
area that his bones are interred in. And these dudes are like, "Dude, we can't let
them get these bones." They don't have enough time to take the whole skeleton, so they take his
major bones. So I'm assuming ribcage, skull, shoulder blades, stuff like that. They couldn't get
all of them though. So they take as much of his body as they can, take it out of the country,
bring it back to myrrh, which is why he's also known as Saint Nicholas of Myrrh or Nicholas of Myrrh.
They bring his bones out there, and the legend continues. People go, "It's so weird,
like when they bring the bones to the church, they're like, why are your hands so wet?" And they're
like, "Dude, this is totally trippy. His bones keep shooting out water. It's almost like a super
choker, but a skeleton." And so they begin bottling his, they said, "Every year you can get like a
flask of his liquid that's coming out of his bones." And they would mix it with a little bit of holy
water and they'd sell it. They'd have these little glass vials, a little picture, little tiny
Saint Nicholas on it. And if you flipped it over, there's three little tiny brain babies on the back.
And people were like, as time went on, people go, "Oh, that story's just completely ridiculous. There
has to be a logical reason for that." Because it is true. There is a liquid coming out of his bones.
And so in the 1950s, the 1950s, they had to do a reconstruction on his, and at this point,
they've gotten the rest of his bones out of Turkey. There was some naval fleet going through
during the Crusades and they're like, "Stop. We got to go to this church and get the rest of this
dude's bones." And they've done all sorts of tests on the bones over the years, because he's one of
the biggest saints out there. And when they test the bones, they go, "These bones definitely came
from the same person. It looks like the skeleton was about 70 years old, 73 years old, which is when
we know around the time that Saint Nicholas died. Looks like his nose got broken while he was still
alive. We think that could have been while he was being tortured." So they really do believe that
this is the skeleton of Saint Nicholas. And it has pretty good, what's that thing called, when you
kind of have like a chain of command or a chain of custody? It has pretty good chain of custody.
No one's really disputing that these aren't the bones of Saint Nicholas. What people were wondering
is, why are they leaking water after all these centuries? And so when they pop the tomb open,
they're going to do a reconstruction on it. They see that there's water in the tomb. And people go,
"Oh, that makes sense." Like the old stories are probably fake, but there was probably some ground
water in his actual tomb. And the water that's been leaking out is, you know, like kind of gross
spring water kind of mixed with corpse. People have been drinking it for a couple hundred years.
It's not going to kill you. It's just a little tiny drop that solves that. And so they put the
bones on this like linen cloth while they're working doing the reconstruction on the tomb. And then
when they come back, the cloth is wet and they're like, "Oh, that just must be residual water from
the tomb." But while the bones were out of the tomb that was being reconstructed, the bones kept
leaking water. And they've done tests on it and they say it appears to be water. It appears to be
water. But they can't explain why it's coming out of the bones. And to this day, apparently, I tried
buying this online, but I don't think you can. Apparently, to this day, you can go to visit
his bones and then there's like a gift shop to the left where you can buy a little vial that has
a drop of the liquid that comes out of his bones. So still a miracle. Now here's my thing. Would you,
if someone says, "Hey man, I got this little toe bone and it's from a saint." And if you chew on it
or you turn it into a powder and drink it like a tea, you'll get superpowers. I would probably do
that. I'd probably do that. If someone goes, "Here's a liquid that's leaked out of a toe bone."
Drink it. I don't know if I would drink it. I mean, I'd be like, "First off, what are the superpowers?"
The toe bone, I would do that just for bragging rights. Be like, "Oh dude, I read about a saint
in a history book." I'm like, "Haha, totally ate that dude's toe bone." Like I would totally be down for
powdered toe bone. But if it wasn't powdered, I don't know why I have...
I don't know why. It's grosser that it's a liquid. This is what I'm saying. If someone was like,
"Here, you take this toe bone, you just hold it up and you shake it and a bunch of liquid comes out
of it and you drink it." You'll get superpowers. I don't know if I could do that. I actually,
okay, let me phrase it. I couldn't do that, but I don't know if I would enjoy it. My first question
would be like, "What superpowers?" And they're like, "Well, you can astral travel." I'd be like,
"Nope." It would have to be something good like flight or invisibility or something. Something,
super strength, the ability to turn myself as strong as a toe bone. I'm like, "Ugh."
Whenever someone punches me, I'd just become a toe bone, a giant toe bone. And then I'm like, "Haha,
you thought you defeated me?" And then I beat him up. My fists turn into giant toe bones. If I could do
that, I would drink the liquid, but otherwise probably not. And let's end this story like this.
Because every good thing has a dark side. That's not true. There's a lot of things that are just
good, like puppies or cats or pancakes. But sometimes good things have bad things. So with
that vague answer, we are going to leave behind the bones of St. Nicholas. And we are going to travel
one more time back in time to the 1700s. Because, see, people really, really loved St. Nicholas.
They really loved those little vials. They believed if you take a drink of that bone juice mixed with
some holy water, good things would happen for you. And so for one woman, it became a weapon of mass
destruction. In the 1700s, there was a woman named Teofania di Adamo. And she is credited for creating
a drink known as aqua tofano. It was a little tiny vial. Had a little picture of St. Nicholas on it.
Filled with water and a drop of the juice of Nicholas's bones. However, she just had a bottle
of water. And instead of the Nicholas juice, just a tiny bit of arsenic or any other flavorless poison.
And she would give it out to women who were having trouble with their husbands,
businessmen who were having trouble with their partners. Anyone for any reason who could afford
some aqua tofano would come to her. She would hand them a little tiny vial decorated with one of the
most venerated saints in Catholicism. And they would give it to someone as a gift. Here, drink and
be merry. Have some bone juice. 600 people are believed to have died because of aqua tofano.
Including Mozart. So remember, dear listeners, as you're opening your presents this year for
Christmas, that the person giving you those presents may not be a jolly man from the North Pole.
May not be a figure based on a real life saint who performed some amazing miracles.
It may be from a human, a human who hates you, a human who wants nothing more than to poison you
and end your existence on planet Earth. So if you happen to get a vial of liquid as a present,
even though you asked for one, exactly what I wanted, mom, you say as you hold up the tiny vial
of liquid filled with bone juice and holy water, be careful before you drink it. Because even though
this is Christmas, a time of joy and cheer, it can also be a time of murder, a time of darkness,
a time of paranormal conspiracy and true crime. And who knows, if you fall into one of those categories,
you may end up being covered next year on Dead Rabbit Radio's Christmas Special.
MWAH! It's basically that ending is more fitting for a Halloween special,
we're just gonna roll with it. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is gonna be your email address. You can also
hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye!