A man from the future uses TikTok to warn the world of incoming disasters.
Then we travel to Palm Springs to take a look at an old story of a man who was just minding
his own business until his body got invaded by an impossibly strong foe today on Dead
Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I'm your host Jason
Carpenter I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
I really do we're getting close to the weekend.
Hope you guys are going to do something fun.
Let's go ahead and start off by saying thank you to our latest Patreon, Revren Samuel.
Revren Samuel thank you so much for supporting the show.
Hope you guys are clapping along unless you're driving.
No clapping if you're driving.
Just a salute thank you so much Revren Samuel.
If you can't support the Patreon that's fine too.
Just hope to get the word out about the show that really really helps out a lot.
We also have the merch store and the Minecraft server.
Hopefully by the time that you're hearing this that I'll have the new update for the
Minecraft server the new Nether update.
A lot of you guys are just shaking your head.
You sure like it there's no way I'm playing Minecraft.
It's fun.
If you do play Minecraft top on the server it's in the show notes.
If you don't play Minecraft just give Minecraft a little salute.
Little salute to Steve and Alex.
Revren Samuel let's hop in that Jason Jalopy.
We are leaving behind Sunny Sunny Oregon and headed out too to Houston Texas.
You're driving along we're leaving behind Oregon we're driving out to Sunny Sunny Texas.
Now as we're driving there we're gonna go into the future but just a little bit.
Just a little bit into the future.
About a month or two from now that's where we're headed.
It's August 10th 2020.
We're in the middle of Houston Texas and a massive hurricane we watch it start to wrap
around the buildings.
It's like hugging them with high powered winds big alarms but instead of like a hug of love
it's a hug of whirling debris.
There's cows smashing through high rise buildings glass shattering all that stuff 30 floors of
that sound effect just have it keep going over put it on repeat and then like a bunch
of stuff it's raining and we're like ahhh we're like holding on to trees and we're almost
getting blown away.
Now you're wondering why I took you to this death zone this possible death zone.
Blame it on Beatrice Leyva she recommended we do this story thinking she's also holding
on to a tree wait oh no she got blown away sorry Beatrice we're waving to her with one
arm the other arm we're holding on to the tree she's fine she fell into a mattress factory
but she wanted us to do this story so thank you for this recommendation it's now August
11th and the hurricane is done and now we're walking through the rubble that was previously
Houston and I'm gonna sit down on this pile of human bodies and I'm gonna tell you this
story why we're here so obviously this is in the future this hasn't happened August 10th
2020 hasn't happened yet but according to one man it's going to unless little asterix
let's go back and take a look at this so I'm a sitting on this pile of bodies and it's
pretty comfortable the residents of Houston make really comfortable seats let's take a
look at why what brought us here let's take a look at what brought us here so what brought
us here is a man known as 2028 man he's a man from the future who the first thing he
does when he gets back to our timeline is set up a tick tock account which I'm sure
would be the first thing we like if you went back in time to like save Kennedy's life the
first thing you're gonna do is put a personal ad in the newspaper announcing you're there
to save Kennedy's life but that's what this guy does by the way your mission failed if
that's why you went back in time to 1963 this guy comes down he sets up a tick tock account
called 2028 man he weaves the story about the great collapse there's an incoming civil
war Trump loses the election but he won't stop being president Biden wins but dies like
a month later the thing is is that he weaves his tail and then he also says there's gonna
be a major hurricane hurricane Kyle on August 10th 2020 that's going to destroy Houston
there's gonna be a massive civil war currency is going to fail crypto currency is going to
fail everything's gonna fall apart but there's hope we have to be kind to each other he keeps
saying because I don't know what being kind to each other how that prevents a hurricane
the hurricane's getting ready to beat up Houston he sees everyone hugging and hurricane Kyle's
like oh and then like goes goes and destroys a meaner city I don't know but that's his
whole shtick but it's a nice message right kind of falls apart because he starts hardcore
trolling people it's whole thing gets weird Beatrice thank you so much for sending this
over because it's a very weird thing he sets this thing up it it blows up it goes viral
like he has like 150,000 followers it it got big very very quickly so we have like we basically
have dual storylines one is this weird thing about him in the future and the other thing
is just this weird thing about him as a person so the future thing he says that he makes
these bizarre claims yes more bizarre than hurricane destroy in Houston one in every
thousand people right now is from the future that's huge I don't know if this guy understands
percentages but that's a massive amount that means if you go to like a baseball game there's
going to be at least 500 time travelers there and that at that point we're almost being replaced
by people from the future that's a lot that's a huge percentage but all of it's only men
only men are sent back in time because women are too valuable they have to be breeding
they're like apparently some sort of breeding pit in the future which is just that's grim
that's grim and that's one of those details that he kind of added in to build the mythology
or he doesn't mention that early on I don't think he would have gotten 150,000 followers
if he was breaking into a car and being like oh by the way we keep women in cages they're
far too valuable to be sent back in time he also says he's back in time because he's a
criminal or he did okay he did quote something wrong or something bad he says that people
are like well wait a second if the great collapse has happened and there's this horrible civil
war 90% of the population is dead and all the women are kept in breeding pits why would
it be a punishment to get sent back to 2020 when it's none of those things are happening
right and he goes oh because that way we're gonna have to live through them like this
is the worst point in human history from now until the election and all that stuff this
is the worst point in human history so they sent us back they sent us back to this sunny
place where we can buy sprite and eat roundtable pizza underneath the summer sun no how dare
you future okay so then he does the normal thing where he again a surprise this is so
popular he does this normal thing where after probably about 10 videos he goes I did it
guys I met this person who's going to help change the future so now everything's in flux
none of this stuff may even happen now you're welcome and that's really typical of this
type of myth someone comes back someone makes these bizarre claims and then they don't they're
not they were never meant to come true in the first place the person making them up knew
they were making them up because they were literally making them up and then they go
oh we avoided it there's a thing called the godlike productions effect or the GLP effect
it's from the website godlike productions happen all the time someone would make a claim
the Illuminati are going to strike on March 13th 2015 they're going to do this big exercise
because there's this military exercise that's planned for Houston Texas they're going to
do with some so that's the day that the Illuminati is going to make and then it doesn't happen
and and then they go we averted it because we were talking about it the Illuminati overlords
went we're also on godlike productions they go our plans have been exposed godlike productions
knows we can't do it now it's called the GLP effect you make up a claim it doesn't happen
and you say it didn't happen because you exposed the claim that's the same thing he's doing
here an odd detail though when he because I was watching all these videos thank you
Beatrice I had to lose several days and I still get alerts from this guy by the way right
I'm just sitting there doing my thing and it did loop and it's like you have a new video
oh cute now I gotta watch it right because I gotta see how the story evolves I'm unsubscribing
right after this episode because it's super irritating but he doxes himself which was
very odd he showed photos of his wife but he also shows his kids and then he takes that
video down and he goes yeah I probably shouldn't have shown my kids yeah probably or your wife
and then someone's they I just the video that just popped up today someone was like that
woman's too hot to be married to you so you start showing photos of his women his wife
again it's all bizarre and that's where that's a good segue to get away from the prophecy
stuff and just to kind of this man as an individual now I don't know him I don't know his real
name but I have some ideas about what's going on here I definitely don't think he's a time
traveler right I think we're pretty clear on that I don't think he's a time traveler but
I don't think even he imagined it would blow up as much as it did can you imagine putting
I mean I obviously put out material I've been putting material out for two years I have about
I'd say 1500 1700 follower daily followers and that's a good I started off with 14 that's
a good ramp up right if I had put out my first episode on I had 135,000 people listening
from episode one it would definitely I think the show I think that would have went to my
head obviously like I think most people most of those bands they were we were talking about
Motley Crue last week you work you perfect your craft you make an album it's a hit and
then it grows from there it's not like you play one song and they have 135,000 fans that's
what happened to this guy and it's just at that I think is kind of affecting him in an
odd way because now he's running for president now he's running for president in the year
you guessed it 2028 and he's turned his tick-tock platform away from time travel he still talks
about it from time to time but now he's talking about how he's going to become president of
the United States and I wouldn't be shocked this could be part of the jokes narrative
or something like that but I wouldn't be shocked if he actually thinks because he developed
a following so quickly that he has a chance of becoming president in 2028 to be fair he
is a time traveler so maybe he knows more than I do but that's weird that's weird right
though the first when Beatrice sent this to me she goes there's this guy on tick-tock
who's claiming to know the future the first video I pulled up of his his latest video
at the time was he was selling merch so I immediately was like this is this is ridiculous
time traveler coming back in time getting his message across maybe I mean most likely not
but selling t-shirts he's like I just got to make money bro and that was see that was
the kickoff for me if you were a time traveler and you needed to make money what would you
do like obviously you're headed back into the past you know you're headed back in the past
lottery lottery right lottery so that was the first kickoff for me was that he comes
back to the past and now he's selling t-shirts because he needs to make money when any time
traveler worth their salt would bring back lottery ticket numbers but anyways that also
the fact that time travel most likely doesn't exist but anyways so now he's thinking he's
going to run for president there's some guy going around called 2029 man who's just taking
his videos and repeating them word for word which is kind of funny and 2028 man is now
making videos against 2029 man and fabricating evidence from the future and then he goes
oh I'm just joking people are like if you're a time traveler and trying to convince people
that you're from the future you probably shouldn't photoshop articles and but now he's kind of
on this presidential kick someone was complaining about him and he goes I gave $110 to a girl
with stage 4 cancer so if you complain about me you're complaining about her and people
are like what and he did apparently give money to a $110 to a girl with stage 4 cancer but
I mean that doesn't mean I can't analyze this behavior as far as I know the whole thing's
an act and he's a totally nice guy and he's doing some sort of OVENT guard performance
art hopefully he doesn't turn around and turn it into this was just a social experiment
I wanted to see how gola people were because that's always kind of a cop out thing I think
the easiest thing would have been for him to make the predictions and then say it's
time for me to go back home and delete everything and that the myth would have lived on right
what happened was the August 10th would have come around and there would have been no hurricane
or would have hit Houston and people would be like oh he almost saved us or he saved us
and stuff like that but now that he's trying to run for president in 2020 it's just basically
the mythology is going to go on and on so I find it fascinating on the level of one
just the time travel element two he see it seems to be going to his head and then three
because it that easy to get successful on tiktok he's not dancing there's no booty
shaking it's him sitting in a car that he hot wired which is most likely his own car
that he hot wired but again I think there's a short shelf life to that but we'll find
out I'll if on August 10th a hurricane destroys Houston I will give 2028 man $110 there we
go I will pay him back that $110 but I really don't think that's going to happen so Reverend
Samuel let's go ahead we're going to wave goodbye Houston is being repaired I'm giving
2028 man $110 we're waving goodbye to Beatrice she just has her arm in a sling she's going
to be fine but I was wrong the city was destroyed and we're not going to assist in the relief
efforts though they're like we could really use that helicopter we're flying away we're
headed out to Palm Springs recently I did a story about the giant shrimp living in the
wall or walking around in the wall in Seattle and I got that from a magazine called Strange
Magazine and in that same issue there was this story as well Strange Magazine issue
6 very kind of bizarre story let's take a look at this there's no time period for this
and it was written anonymously so you know take take what you will from it but it's it's
one of those stories that sounds realistic enough definitely more realistic than what
we just covered Reverend Samuel bring that carbonic hopper nice and low we're going to
fly over the desert landscape a man from Santa Barbara let's call him Timothy Timothy was
living in Santa Barbara and he bought a house in Palm Springs Palm Springs a really nice
area I grew up down there in Riverside County Palm Springs was farther away but is where
all the rich people either lived or vacationed is kind of a nice temperature away from all
the pollution so Timothy's leaving behind Santa Barbara and he's talking to his UPS
man he's like yeah you know you're gonna start having to drive hundreds of miles away to
start delivering packages and the UPS man goes that's not how it works like there's other
drivers we drive all over the country what I thought it was just one no I thought your
name was UPS no he tells Mr. UPS yeah I'm moving down to Palm Springs and the guy's like what
Palm Springs sucks bro you don't want to go there and what do you mean it's like there's
like big old mosquitoes and there's like giant bugs and then there's like the the the mushrooms
dude the mushrooms that stick to your skin Timothy's what Cthulhu level horror are you talking
about this is Palm Springs is where all the rich people go Mr. Ups is like it's your funeral
bro like I would not live there I would not live there Timothy moves out he doesn't really
think anything of it he moves out he goes out to Palm Springs and sure enough dude giant
cockroaches are all flying around he said there's five different kinds of fire ants
and then there's the Podex is is terrillus also known as the desert inky cap mushroom
and he was actually into mushrooms like this was a hobby of his so he's like who yeah he's
like sees a little inky thing he's like yes I'm gonna take a picture of this because my
life is completely devoid of meaning click and he would read books on mushrooms and stuff
like okay I don't think he had a mushroom fetish he might just had a passing interest
but he was intrigued by this mushroom he had heard about it he read about it in a book
and it's a mushroom that's like a puffball mushroom so it has a little stalk and there's
a little ball on top and then it goes when it blows up and the spores will just flow
it all around to plant other mushrooms in the book that he had read years earlier he
remember coming across a weird sentence in it it said it was quote implicated in attacks
on living tissue and quote and they at the time he's like that's kind of weird like does
it is like a triphid is it walking around breaking into people's houses they wake up
they're half mushroom it also said no matter what you should never eat one of these no
matter how hungry you are don't eat a mushroom that that attacks living tissue so Timothy
reads that has horrible nightmare that night about inky caps but then kind of goes on with
his life so then when he's in Palm Springs and he sees one of these he's like that's
fascinating I've heard about these Palm Springs it's in the desert and these mushrooms ought
everywhere but they're there and they only puff in 110 degree heat so the chances of
you ever coming across one of these things and it exploding near you is very very small
usually they're out in the middle of the desert they're puff if it's 110 degrees you're not
out on a nature hike probably have more serious things to worry about that a mushroom puffing
all over you but Timothy he's living there for a while he starts because he's a mushroom
dude he's a mushroom man he starts to hear stories from people people know him he's
interested in mushrooms so whenever they come across an interesting mushroom anecdote they
tell him he said that there are stories of hunters duck hunters in the area rabbit hunters
in the area tracking their prey down getting that gun ready killing the rabbit walking
up cutting it open full of mushrooms not like it eating them not in stomach it's not all
like it would didn't die having a good last meal like fungus in the skin on the skin little
mushrooms growing on a up until a few minutes ago living creature I swear Timothy that's
what I saw you're the mushroom man I figured I'd tell you that story thank you thank you
really appreciate it would you like to have a drink no because I know you're gonna give
me some sort of mushroom concoction and I'm I think mushrooms are gross myself Timothy
I just wanted to tell you that story have a good day he would hear these stories from
multiple people he couldn't get he never got him to drink mushroom juice but he'd hear
these stories from multiple people one day Timothy is gardening and he sees one of these
mushrooms in his garden he's like oh it's interesting I mean Palm Springs again is a desert so
it's not like he's living on a patch of dirt but they explode and they spore everywhere
it's not 110 degrees outside he's just looking at this and it's fascinating it's this mushroom
he's looking at it puffs and he watches the black spores just flying cover him now he gets
it pretty bad he gets it on his neck gets it all over him but he mostly gets it on his
left arm and his left leg his left foot but he gets it on his neck gets it on his shirt
and he's just looking I mean there's a ton of spores and he's kind of laughing about
it oh oh good ol' linky's at it again can't wait to talk about this on my mushroom newsletter
because they didn't have blogs back then I'm sure he'd have one if they existed he just
goes in and washes it off he just goes in and he washes it off but then we have this
quote I rinse myself off with a hose but the spores stayed in my pores and in every scratch
and small wound on my arms neck and feet about a month later I got my first indication that
something was wrong a series of small black growths began to emerge from my left arm I
thought they might be spots of road tar that had somehow splashed on me so I scrubbed them
with no results just got the weirdest case of deja vu this is bizarre he started washing
them off with bleach these little bumps these little growths and after a while they started
crumble away then we have this quote I was relieved until I noticed that the skin around
them felt strange I touched my arm into my amazed horror a circular area about four inches
across was numb and cold absolutely cold it stayed cold too and began to harden and then
disintegrate he said goo started leaking out of this little growth hole in his arm and
he started seeing more spores pop up where his body was exposed to this now he's going
to doctors he's going to doctors in the Palm Springs area he's saying hey I got sprayed
with one of these inky camp mushrooms and this I don't know what's going on like I feel
like I'm turning into my I'm turning into what I love most and all the doctors are like
that's impossible and he's like these things exist in this area like these are real things
but none of the doctors are like this that's not true like mushrooms don't grow on people
like this so maybe something is maybe it's this fungus well I mean the mushroom is the
fungus but they didn't believe it was the inky cap could have been anything else but
that what he ended up doing was using athletes foot medication which deals with fungus he's
put an athlete's foot medication and eventually that kills off all the spores but he still
has scar tissue in his arms it was eating his flesh as he's trying to figure out what's
going on and treat it and to prevent himself from turning into a full-on mushroom man he
begins to talk to other people in town and he knew three other people that this happened
to one of them use agricultural grade fungicide to take it out he's like I really should have
tried that athlete's foot medicine I didn't I just dipped my arm in a straight up Agent
Orange brought it out of his just a skeleton arm one woman got him and she just could she
had him on her legs and she could not get rid of him and Timothy said it sucks because
when I figured out kind of how to deal with it with the athletes foot nothing not the
agricultural grade liquid he can never find her she moved out of the area so he kind of
that story kind of ends with him kind of shrugging his shoulders and going I hope she's okay
it was a bad thing it was eating through his skin he ends up this experience was so awful
for him he ends up poisoning the plant he goes back to where the mushroom was and poisons
the soil and moves out of the area because he knows these things are out there he had
seen them around he knew they existed in Palm Springs but he never had a close encounter
with one and he wrote a letter to the editor of the newspaper and said hey you guys got
to be careful about these puffball mushrooms this is what happened to me like I was injured
by these things the newspaper never published his letter to the editor he began writing
several letters to them saying hey guys you know this is a serious problem but the newspaper
didn't want to have anything to do with it the newspaper never talked about it and the
doctors had no idea what was going on and what he believes at this time is that it's
a cover-up because Palm Springs is a tourist town he ends the story by saying that these
things can heavily damage a human body imagine if you got one of these in your eyes or a
kid ate one he believes it was a town-wide cover-up and he says sure they grow in the
desert and it has to be in 110 heat for them to explode but it's not always the case because
the one blew up on him and he goes as Palm Springs expands as the city gets bigger the
chances of these mushrooms landing in residential neighborhoods they're like living landmines
the more houses that are built the bigger the town gets the more likely that these things
are going to be popping up in this area all over the place a dog in the backyard comes
down with a mysterious illness a child has a horrible coughing fit and the doctors just
don't know what to do a gardener gets his hand covered in black spores and ignores it
until he feels growths underneath his skin and the whole time the city of Palm Springs
know this is an issue but it's one they can't control they're the invasive species the mushroom
had already been there it would be almost impossible for them to eradicate this thing
it's just messing with one of them just make it explode and now you got possibly thousands
of more in the area so he moved away it wasn't worth the risk to have this happen to him
again this may be happening a lot in that area a lot not like not like the entire town
singing over by mushrooms but even once I mean he met three other people that this happened
to so even if it only happened to three or four people a year that's still a lot when
you're talking about being eaten alive by mushrooms right is it possible that the city
of Palm Springs is covering up this event because they can't stop it who wants to move
who wants to buy a million dollar home in a posh neighborhood if you can't even leave
your house safely who wants to visit this place if while you're taking photos of your
family step on a little mushroom it spores on your leg it's a creepy story because it
sounds true sounds true it's one of those small town conspiracies that you could see
the city government covering up it could be that the doctors were in on it as well it's
possible that at least one of those doctors knew exactly what it was but he's not going
to risk his job you know doctors like I don't know I don't know what it could be I don't
know what it could be and then Timothy leaves and doctors goes home and his wife is like
what's happened again like I don't my hands are tied though I can't tell him what it is
he says it's the inky cat mushroom he's right but just got to keep my mouth shut this is
how small town conspiracies work in which I think are far more easy to contain because
you only need to control a certain group of people and everyone else just lives unaware
if you're listening to this in your mom Springs right now you're like oh I was supposed to
go to the mushroom festival tomorrow don't by the way don't know how much you love mushrooms
but yeah a creepy story it sounds it sounds realistic it just sounds creepy has all the
elements you have a conspiracy a town-wide conspiracy of silence like the steppford wives
you have an innocent looking thing that can ruin your body imagine again if he'd gotten
this in his eye good luck putting athletes foot stuff in your eyeball and if you did
get it in your eye you take your nine-year-old son to the doctor his face is covered in black
spores I don't know what happened I don't know what happened he's just freaking out
take him into the doctor and the doctor looks at that boy and the doctor knows he can say
nothing it'll be fine I don't know what it is but it'll be fine the creepiest conspiracies
are the ones we don't know about and if it wasn't for this small article in a strange
magazine number six no one would know about this except for the people who fight to keep
the story silent allegedly allegedly dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email
address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is @dead rabbit radio
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't
have to listen to it every day and I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys.
you
you you
you you you
you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you