A deadly event in...let me double check where it's at.
Let me check my notes here real quick.
A fun filled event in Pakistan that is also known for its grisly deaths.
We look at a book that predicted the tragedy of the Titanic and then we discuss homonculus
recipes.
Yes, I pronounced that right.
I know you're shocked.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
Actually, I wasn't going to record tonight.
They'll sleep in my chair and I thought, "Yeah."
But then I was like, "You know what?"
I actually have about 400, 500 listeners who listen to the show day of or the next day.
And then the episode downloads on both YouTube and the podcast go up over time.
And I was like, "You know what?
I got that sizable amount of people between YouTube and the podcast that expect an episode
on schedule."
So I fell asleep in my chair and then I woke up and I was like, "Okay, I'm going to take
a shower.
I'm really tired.
I'm going to take a shower and wake up."
And I'm going to record this episode.
For you guys.
So we did it.
We made it through Hell Week, the first week of doing the three jobs.
And it worked.
We got an episode out every day, which is good.
That's very good for the show.
I think I'm going to start recording earlier in the day.
I might even record extra episodes on the weekends, so kind of make the recording schedule
a little smaller.
But we'll see.
Because I really like the process of recording and editing and things like that.
Just when I get started late, it's like eight o'clock at night, I know I'm going to be
up until at least 11 by the time I start uploading these to YouTube.
Anyways, so that's all extra stuff.
You guys don't care about that.
Maybe you do.
But let's go ahead and move on to our first story.
So our first story is part of our new news stories from the year 2004.
Now this particular story, I wasn't able to find the original article, but I wasn't
shocked to learn that it's still going on today.
Because when I read the article in 2004, I was like, "That's ridiculous.
Why would they have such a horrible event annually?"
And when I started looking for the original article, I found an article from 2015, 11
years later, documented the exact same incidents.
It is...
In 2015, there's this thing called the Spring...
No, every year, every year, it's an annual thing.
But this happened in 2015.
There's a Spring Festival in Pakistan.
And everyone comes out.
It's like everyone kind of like, I guess, leaves their house or something, and they
go to like one big field.
I guess there's like one giant field in Pakistan.
And it's a kite festival.
So everyone's like, "Yeah, I got my kite."
You know, thousands, tens of thousands of...
I don't know the exact amount, but let's say thousands of kites.
They would have to be for the casualties that are about to come.
Thousands of kites lining the sky.
And you're thinking, "How does a festival of kites lead to a bunch of people getting
killed?"
Well, in this particular event, they actually...
So the year before, they said, "No more kites.
No more kites.
You can't bring your kite to the Spring Festival anymore.
So many people are getting killed and injured."
And they had just lifted the ban.
They said, "Okay, this year you can bring your kites back."
And you're like, "Jason, just get to the kites killing people.
Just get to the kites killing people."
But let me lay this down.
So just this year, just in 2015, they said, "Okay, we'll lift the ban.
You can bring your kites back."
In 2015, 11 people killed.
Over 100 injured.
And you're like, "Why are these kites like eating people?"
Well, some of them were killed and got injured because of people shooting into the air.
And you're thinking, "Okay, that's fine."
You know, people are like, "Yeah, it's Spring.
Oh yeah, this is so awesome.
Only happened once a year."
I don't know why they even have a Spring Festival, but shooting guns in the air.
But what they, the problem is, is that part of their kite festival, and this is pretty
rad honestly, but part of their kite festival is they have kite duels.
So we have a rivalry all year long.
And I'm like, "You know what, dude?
Oh, I can't wait until the Spring Festival.
Only three more seasons than me, you, and our kites."
And what they do is they build kites and they have kite battles.
So they take kites and they build spikes on them and they crash them into their rivals'
kites and destroy their kite.
But that's not the only thing they do.
The other thing they do is they, oh, and I think a couple of people got pierced by the
spikes on the kites, but the big problem they had was they would take the kite string.
Someone at one point during this weapon war, during this arms race of the kites, decided,
"Oh, you know what would be great?
If I took my kite string, coated it in glue and then rolled it around in broken glass."
So their kite string, their kite's like, "Meow."
It's making, you know, the noises Snoopy's doghouse makes when it flies around, just
really like, "Meow."
And the string would hit the other guy's kite string and cut it in half.
And you'd be like, "Oh, no, my kite string and his kite would fly away."
And then the arms race evolved to some people would take, like I said, the glue, just put
glue and broken glass on their kite strings.
But the more industrious ones would say, "Oh, I'm actually, I'm going to make my kite string
bulletproof.
So I'm going to use metal wire for my kite string, thin metal wire."
Now you can start to see how this kite festival can become quite deadly.
Because you have kids running around, you have people just sitting there at their picnic,
enjoying eating apples or whatever, just having a good old time.
And a metal kite string wraps around their neck.
And the kite is like just getting like tons of like air flow, whatever the thing is that
lift.
And you're like, "Ahh!"
And your family's watching.
And you're like slowly being suffocated.
People have just gotten their throat slashed by these super sharp wires.
People have been electrocuted because they're flying their kites.
And they, I mean, because again, you have this huge mass of people and the people who
show up late, they're like, "Oh man, I don't have anywhere to fly my kite."
But except by these power lines, they get electrocuted.
People were falling off buildings trying to get their kites that had crashed.
11 dead, 100 wounded.
The article that I read back in 2004, because I had remembered it when I saw the headline,
was that a young girl bled out because a kite string coated in glass wrapped around
her neck and sliced her throat open.
Because the thrust of the lift, I don't even know the technical terms, but the like
lift of the kite just tightened the string enough that it just cut her throat open.
And I was like, "Ugh!"
And so they're still doing it.
And now they have a band again.
They'll probably be lifted in a while, but it's just such a bizarre, I mean, I get that
there's like weird festivals and traditions around the world, but most of them don't involve
groting, nor just people who are like eating a picnic.
Not eating a picnic, but having a picnic.
You know, there'll be guys, some people are having a picnic and another guy eats their
picnic.
I don't know that.
Okay, okay, we're done with that.
We're done with that story.
The next one we're going to look at is the story of the man who predicted, in a way,
the sinking of the Titanic.
And you may go, "Ah, Jason, I've heard this story before."
And maybe you have.
I'd actually heard it a couple times.
But anyway, so this is the story of the man who predicted the Titanic.
And there's a lot, you know, the thing is, is like conspiracy theories a lot of times
hinge on coincidences.
And like my good friend, Garrick, said, "I believe in coincidences.
Coincidences happen all the time, but I don't trust coincidences."
Now, when you put out so much media as we have as a world, you're going to get stuff
that eventually does line up to real life events.
And it's weird.
Sometimes there's so many coincidences, you really have to like step back and go, "That's
eerie."
To be fair, when I read about this guy, they said he also predicted the Pearl Harbor attack.
And I was like, "What?"
And I was like, "That's like two for two."
And I looked it up and he just predicted that the Imperial Japanese Air Force would attack
the US Navy.
And I'm like, "Oh, that's kind of just, that's not really Pearl Harbor."
And it was like out in the middle of the ocean.
So he's not two for two.
But anyway, so Morgan Robertson was the author and he wrote a book called The Wreck of the
Titan or Fertility, Fertility, Fertility, The Wreck of the Titan.
Anyways, that was the name of the book.
And he wrote in 1898 and this is the plot of the book.
The plot of the book is worthy enough to talk about.
I think it's pretty funny.
There's, the plot is there's a disgraced naval officer named John Rowland.
And he gets, I don't know why he was disgraced.
Maybe he was, I don't know, stealing sea water.
But anyway, so he gets a job, like a low down dirty job on the Titan.
He's like, "Oh, this sucks."
But he has to like make money.
So he's like, "Oh, this sucks.
I'm just shoveling coal into this engine."
The Titan in the book hits an iceberg.
So what happens is the boat, it's a thriller.
The boat hits the iceberg and it's starting to sink.
And John Rowland is trying to make his way off of the ship.
And he comes across the daughter of his ex.
I don't know where the ex is at.
I was just reading the plot.
But anyways, he finds the daughter of his ex and he's like, "Oh, I have to save you.
Maybe that'll, maybe it'll get me out of the friend zone."
So he like saves the girl.
He saves the kid by jumping onto the iceberg.
So the boat hit the iceberg and he jumps onto the iceberg with the kid.
A polar bear shows up.
He fights the polar bear.
I mean, come on, dude.
That should have been in the movie.
Instead of Jack just floating to the bottom of the earth.
They should have had a polar bear fight scene.
John Rowland fights the polar bear.
Then after having saving this kid, he gives it back to his ex and goes here.
I've saved her.
And the ex has him arrested for kidnapping.
Even though he was kidnapped, he was kidnapped and he was off of a sinking boat.
Eventually he's found innocent and because then it becomes a court drama.
The trial is not taking place on the iceberg.
They're like, "Is there a judge on here?"
Anyways, so they all get saved.
He goes to court for kidnapping.
He's found innocent and the ex is castigated for being lame.
Like, "You shouldn't have done this."
They're like, "Listen, dude, you're lame."
This guy obviously was simply trying to save her.
He wasn't doing anything wrong.
And John, then the happy ending, he becomes homeless.
He slowly works his way up and he gets a good government job.
So basically he's kind of just like a cog and a machine at the end, but that's happier
than where he was at.
This is actually the end of the book.
Spoiler alert for a hundred year old book.
This is the last part.
So it says he finally gets a civil service exam, and this is the quote, "to a lucrative
position under the government, and as he seated himself at his desk in his office, could
have been heard to remark, 'Now John Rowland, your future is your own.'
You have merely suffered in the past from a mistaken estimate of the importance of women
and whiskey."
What?
So basically it was the migthal version of the Titanic.
But this book came out 14 years before the Titanic sank.
It actually was written before they even started building the Titanic.
So you're like, "Okay, Jason Iceberg, Boat hits Iceberg, the name's similar."
They both sank in April in the Atlantic.
They both came from England.
The Titan was 800 feet long.
Titanic was 182 feet long.
Both had similar tonnage.
Both called unsinkable.
Both had a shortage of lifeboats.
Both hit Icebergs.
Both on star sites.
Both 400 nautical miles from Newfoundland.
What's interesting was that, so he wrote the book and it was a pretty good seller.
People had read it, and then people still were like, "Hey man, remember that book you
read?
That was awesome.
Hey, you want to go on this boat called the Titanic?"
Oh yeah, totally.
Where is it leaving from?
England?
Oh cool.
How big is it?
So on and so forth.
For years, Pester the author about being a clairvoyant.
And he goes, "Listen, everything that I came up with was because I know nautical stuff.
I know boats and I know how they move.
I know how they go through, not go through the water, but I know what routes they'll
take and things like that and the chances of them running to an iceberg in April and
all this stuff."
So he denies it.
He denies that he's a clairvoyant.
And that he's probably right.
It is, even given all of the saying, you know, I know a lot of stuff about nautical stuff,
it is still weird about things like the name and the idea of it being built as an unsinkable
ship.
I don't know.
It's just the shortest of lifeboats.
It's a lot of stuff.
Now obviously, no one jumped off on the iceberg.
Actually, I wonder why nobody jumped off on the iceberg.
Probably because they saw too many polar bears over there, but that probably would have been
fine.
I guess you probably can't hold onto an iceberg or you just freeze quicker because it's ice
ice.
I wonder if the iceberg got damaged.
Dude, I wonder if the iceberg is still out there.
That sunk Titanic because it must have been a big iceberg, right?
Just floating around.
They don't...
Icebergs break off of stuff and then just float around, right?
I wonder how long icebergs live.
Okay, so our next story is an interesting one.
It is on the conspiracy iceberg, which you know what?
We don't see much conspiracy iceberg around anymore.
Not just on this podcast, but in...
We do it once a week on this podcast, but on 4chan they'd always discuss the conspiracy
iceberg.
It's kind of died out.
I guess that meme's over there.
But homunculus.
Trust me, I'm pronouncing that right.
It's not homunculus.
Hom...
Homunculus.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm pronouncing it wrong.
But anyways, homunculus.
What homunculus is?
It's a tiny human.
It's a human that's a little, little dude.
He's like the size of the palm of your hand.
So let's measure him in centimeters.
Let's say he's probably like, if I'm 136 centimeters tall, he would be like 13 centimeters tall.
So he's a tiny little guy.
And they're not made by normal reproductive practices.
I.e. you don't bang a woman in a homunculus comes out.
It's a really old belief.
We actually have references to homunculi type creatures going back as far as 3a.d.
But the earliest mention of the word is from the 1500s.
So this is a longstanding tradition.
Tiny little guy.
A little tiny guy.
Now, it was a big thing in the alchemist circles.
They're like, now, when I say, let's get down to brass tacks here.
The goal is to make a tiny person out of, without banging a woman.
And they have special powers.
And we'll get into that in a second.
But really, I think these alchemists just really wanted to have a reason to masturbate
all day long.
You'd think that was most likely the scenario.
They're like, Sir Edmund, Sir Edmund, what are you doing?
He's standing in the corner.
He keeps moving his beard out of the way.
And they're like, what are you doing?
He's like, I'm working on a spell.
What type of spell?
Tiny human.
They're like, oh, OK.
And he's like, leave me alone.
Leave me alone.
Leave those wood carvings.
Leave those sexy wood carvings.
And I'll be out in a bit.
That's mostly, I mean, let's be honest.
But anyway, so they thought back then, back in the olden times, that you didn't need an
egg, like a little woman egg, you know, the little tiny egg that comes out of a woman.
They didn't think you needed that to reproduce.
You just needed this.
The semen was where all the life was.
You just needed a warm place for it to grow.
You just needed to give it some food and some like just like a little bed.
And it would turn into a tiny human.
You know, so they came up with all sorts of crazy schemes.
The question is, is will any do any of these work?
And we'll get to that in a second, because that's an actually interesting question.
So first off, you could take a homunculi and they had special powers.
These are their special powers they have listed, other than being a tiny human that didn't
require a mother, which is pretty special.
They have the ability to control the motion and appearance of the moon.
What?
Who?
Okay, first off, that's not a good power to have.
People are like, "Ah, like giant tidal waves are coming after them."
They're like, "Look at moons closer.
The gravity pull is getting all messed up.
Cows don't know where to jump."
Like it's, that's not a good power to have.
That's so overpowered for a tiny person to have.
They've given them the ability to send the moon far away into the solar system.
They also, speaking of cows, to allow humans to transform themselves into sheeps and cows.
Why would any human ever want to transform into a sheep or a cow?
The two most easily killable animals on the planet, next to a caterpillar.
Why at what point in your life as an alchemist do you go, "You know what I've always wanted
to do?
I've wanted to be delicious meat.
I've wanted to be something that is known to be eaten or melt."
Okay, there's probably some perverts out there who would be into that.
But for the most part, I think most of humanity wouldn't say, wouldn't take, what do you want
to be, a were-cow?
It doesn't work that way.
These powers are dumb, which makes me think that these things might be real.
Because if you were making it up, you'd be like, "Oh, you turned into this big badass
wolf with like a metal chain collar and there's like old-timey heavy metal music."
Like, you know, like with leers, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down