A woman finds out that nothing in life is truly free, but she didn't expect it to be that expensive.
And then we travel to the Solomon Islands, where a massive island sits uninhabited to this day.
Stories of villagers being chased off by a spirit is one thing, but why did an entire company shut
down? Where they also afraid of the monsters of Titi Pear Island today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter,
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a lot of stuff to cover,
so we're gonna slide right into this like it's a big old slip and slide. First off, I want to give
a shout out to one of our legacy Patreons, Ash Knotts. Not astronauts, although that would be cool.
If they supported the show, Ash Knotts, actually a good friend of mine and a patron of the show,
really, really appreciate it. You're gonna be our captain, our pilot, you're gonna do all sorts of
cool stuff today. You can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. Just help get the word out about
the show. That really, really helps out a lot. So Ash, let's go ahead and get suited up here.
First off, I don't know why we're wearing suits, you can wear your normal clothes, you don't need to
get suited up. First off, let's hop inside the Jason Jalopy. We are leaving behind Oregon,
and we're just taking a little drive up north. We're headed to Spanaway, Washington.
That's the sound the car makes. We're in Beverly Hill, Billy's car. Oddly enough, that's the theme song
for Green Acres, but it doesn't matter, because most of you have never seen either of those shows.
We're driving up to Spanaway, Washington. This story's pretty recent. This story happened on
February 5th, 2020. We're gonna park outside this house, this little house. Looks like a normal house,
as opposed to those floating houses in other cities, the orbs. This is a normal house in
Spanaway, Washington, and inside we hear a little mommy going, "Hush little baby, don't say a word.
Mom is gonna buy you a more given." And we're like, "Oh, that's kind of sweet." We're gonna knock on the
door and see what was up, but we're just like mesmerized by this mama song. She has a little baby.
She has a newborn baby, and she's like, "Man, this baby's so awesome. If only I could get photos of
this baby, but I don't have a way to take pictures. It's not like I don't have a cell phone or access
to webcams or anything like that. No. I want to invite a stranger into my house to take photos
of my newborn baby." So little mommy's holding her baby. She's like, "Okay, hit this button to send
strangers to my house now." So Juliet Parker, she's 38 years old. She'd been posting ads on
Facebook saying, "I will take free photos of your baby. I'm trying to build up my portfolio."
Then when you read her comment, there's a little emoticon of eyes shifting from side to side.
She shows up to this woman's house and she rings her 16-year-old daughter along as well.
So we're gonna sneak in the house as well, so we're kind of sitting in the back watching this
stuff. So Juliet Parker comes over and she's like, "Hey, new mom. Yeah, I'm the person who's
gonna take free photos of your baby and not only am I doing it for free, I brought you a present.
Here is a glass of wine and a cupcake." Now that should be suspicious right off the bat,
because not only is she doing it for free, now she's in the tank. Like now she's basically like
out money doing this thing. But the mom's not thinking it. She puts her baby down.
Woman's taking a bunch of pictures of the baby and every so often, allegedly, this is all allegedly,
every so often Juliet allegedly looks over at the mom. She sees the glass of wine, she's the cupcake.
"Hey, are you gonna drink that and eat that? That's how consumables normally work." And the
mom's like, "Yeah, yeah, sorry, I forgot." She goes to take a drink of the wine. "Oh, maybe you should
take a picture of the baby like this." And Juliet's like, "Just drink the wine." Click, click, taking
pictures of the baby. Eventually, she does start drinking the wine. The mom's like, "Mm-mm-mm-mm."
"Oh, yummy. Oh, I got this cupcake too. You gave me this, right?" And Juliet's like, "Yeah, yeah."
So the mom starts eating the cupcake. They're taking baby pictures. Everything seems relatively
normal other than the fact that a stranger is in her house taking photos of her baby. But she
starts to notice something. Whenever Juliet touches something, she's like, "Oh, here, let me move this
for this shot." And she'd move something on the coffee table. She'd then wipe down where she
previously touched. This is before coronavirus, okay? This would not be abnormal now. Actually,
bringing a stranger in her home would be the worst part of the story. This is before coronavirus
really took off. February 5th. She would touch stuff and she's like, "Oh, look at this. You,
look at this award you won for tennis." And then she'd set it down and she'd wipe it off.
At this point, the mom's getting a little drowsy. Oh, what? What's going on? She starts getting a
little drowsy, starting to get a little weak. She throws up where she throws up while they're
taking a picture of the baby. The baby's like, "What? The mom is throwing up in the background."
I don't feel good. And Juliet's like, "Oh, no, no, no, no. You look great, honey. You're just losing
weight." You have that new mom glow. This is what all new moms go through. She's continuing taking
pictures of this baby. And as the mom's throwing up, she's realizing something else through the haze
of misery that Juliet is taking now selfies with her holding the baby. You don't get a photographer
to come over to photo bomb the photos you're in. She's taking photos of herself holding the baby.
At that point, she kicks her out. She's like, "Okay, listen, something's wrong. I drink your wine.
I ate your cupcake. I'm throwing up. That's not what cupcakes normally do. Now you're taking a picture
of my baby and you're wiping it on your fingerprints. Get out. Get out. Get out." She rushes them out.
And then she's like, "Well, that was an afternoon. I invited strangers over to my house and who would
have thought they would act like total weirdos and drug me?" She realizes her house keys are missing.
So she calls the cops. And the cops come out and they start investigating Juliet Parker.
It turns out that she had contacted other women with newborns saying, "Hey, I'd like to take pictures
of your babies." Now, that's not super suspicious because she was saying she's trying to build
portfolio and all that stuff. But all the photos she took were of babies five weeks or younger.
And she was talking to her ex-boyfriend once and she's like, "Hey, so how things go? And you
know, you moved on, stuff like that. So, hey, do you know how I can get some GHB? What? What? Yeah,
yeah, you know, the old date rape drug. Do you know how I can get some? You know, used to be my
boyfriend. So I kind of know you're into some crazy stuff." Ex is like, "Okay." And she would say
the ex would say, "Yeah, that was a red flag, right?" She's always talking about how I can get
her GHB. But then I remember one time we were hanging out and she's like, "Honey, you know what would
be great? You know what would be awesome? If we found a homeless person, a homeless person who had a
little homeless baby, and we took that baby from that homeless person and we raised that little
homeless baby, that little homeless baby in a home, wouldn't that be awesome?" Boyfriend, I imagine was
basically fliming through the stations and halfway through her speech kind of paused.
And my first thought was, how many homeless babies are there? Now, don't get me wrong, they exist.
But I imagine they would be relatively hard to find. Like a five-week-old homeless baby. Maybe,
hopefully, I'm right on that. Hopefully, it's very, very hard to find a homeless baby. Hopefully,
it's hard to find, right? And I'm trying really hard to avoid making jokes about a baby carrying a
spindle, but it has a diaper on the end of the stick. Because that would be a bad taste if I made a
joke about a baby being homeless. But I know like they would most likely end up in foster care and
stuff like that. It would probably be pretty hard. It's not like, you know, homeless people are sitting
out there with their dog, spare change, or they're sitting out there and they have a box. There's
like three or four infants walking around in the box. Is that joke? I'm sorry if that joke was tasteless.
But anyways, I don't imagine, I think most of the time, I think most of the time they just end
up in the foster care system, right? I can imagine when the cop has came to talk to the ex-boyfriend,
he's like, let me guess, baby stuff. And the cops are like, what? Let me guess, my ex-girlfriend was
doing something weird trying to take a baby because here's all the stuff she told me that was baby
related during the course of her investigation. So she is under arrest now. She's currently facing
charges for trying to steal that baby. She's basically charged with kidnapping. What they figured
was she was going to get the mom to pass out and take the baby or with the house keys, let herself
back in. Moral of the story. Don't trust anyone on Facebook. It's bad enough when people are posting
stupid stuff on Facebook and I have to just mute people all day long. I stop even going to Facebook.
So Facebook is not only a place for political discussions or for people to
air their views on society in a very civil way. No, it's also a cesspool of baby kidnappers.
So if you have a baby out there, you're like, oh my goodness, I do when you look over and there's
a baby sitting right next to you. I forgot I had you. Hey, what's up, Jimmy? If you have a baby out
there, be on the lookout for anyone giving you wine and cupcakes unless it's your birthday and
you're an alcoholic and they are your friend and they hate babies, then it is allowed. That's the
only time that you're allowed to have that. Ash, let's go in and fire up that fabled carpenter
copter. We're leaving behind Washington. We're waving goodbye to little baby. Little baby's waving.
We're waving goodbye to the mom. Ash is flying the copter. I see her drinking wine and eating a
cupcake. Where'd you get that at? She's like, what? No, I'm hungry. She's flying away. The helicopter
is starting to dip. Luckily, we get her stomach pumped. We land in a local hospital. We get her
stomach pumped. She's ready to actually fly the carpenter copter. Now, check her. Make sure she
doesn't have any more cupcakes or wine. We are headed out to an island I'm almost for sure I'm
mispronouncing, but it's a daily podcast and I don't have time to check. We are headed out
to TT Pear. The helicopter is flying over the Pacific Ocean. This is in the Solomon Islands.
Technically, Solomon Islands is then a geographical location called Oceana,
which I thought honestly was just made up for 1984, but apparently it's a real place. It's like a
nation, not even a nation. It's just like a continent of water, maybe would be a good way to put it.
We're flying over there. I found out about this island from a Reddit user named Murderber.
Murderber. It was very, very fascinating. Murderber actually has some stories from this island
themselves. So we're going to fly over to this island now. This island is near, just to give you
a geographical area. This island is near Papua New Guinea and the Solomon Islands include Guadalcanal.
So if you've played Battlefield 1942, it's that map. That map is real and it's here. So we're flying
over Guadalcanal. It looks like PS2 era graphics, but it's still a fun game. Battlefield 2 was amazing.
Flying over that, I'm looking and longing. I wish we could land there. No, we're going to TT Pear.
So Ash, let's land on the beach here. Now there's a lodge here that people will use because there's
a lot of research teams come and check this place out. This island has what they call biodiversity.
There's just tons of different species. There's animals that have seemingly gone extinct in other
places around this island. It's full of boars and pigs and all sorts of stuff. Reptiles and all
sorts of animals you can think of. You have this little lodge there that people will stay at.
And it's beautiful. It's beautiful. Lush green jungle, sandy beaches, fresh water. The soil is
perfect for planting crops. But no people are on this island. It was abandoned almost a hundred
years ago. So we started walking around the island. Parrot lands on our shoulders, feeding it little
crackers, feeding it cupcakes. They're like, "We'll eat that parrot later." We're walking through this
island. It's interesting because the Solomon Islands have, the Solomon Islands in total,
have long had stories of giants. And we've talked about giants a lot on this show. Apparently there's
giants on the island. To the point that the native population, it's kind of like, yeah,
yeah, there's giants. Like whenever ected researchers go over there, they're like, "Oh,
yeah, yeah, I know there's giants." There was one researcher who married into the culture and he
goes, "How come you guys are just kind of like sitting on this giant information? It would be
big news to the rest of the world." And we just kind of look at him and they're like, "Well, it's
he said he goes, it's weird because to them, the giant stories are so normal that over the years
as whalers were stopping by and other cultures were stopping by, they never really talked about it.
It would be the equivalent of someone came and visited you in your hometown and you're like,
dude, let me tell you about squirrels. You wouldn't even think about it. I mean,
unless that was your weird fetish. But you wouldn't even think about it. To them, it was just this
thing that, "Oh, yeah, look out for that guy. He's 20 feet tall." But other than that, they have a story
of one of their own, one of the islanders goes missing for 25 years. Everyone just assumes she's
dead, which I think he would. I mean, after 25 days, you're kind of like, "Oh, this probably isn't
going to end well." 25 years later, this woman comes running through the jungle and a bunch of
villagers like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down." And she does because she falls to the ground and they
notice she's slimy. She's super slick. Go to pick her up. They're trying to carry it. She's
squippin' out of their arms. It's not a word, but you understand what's going on.
She's like, "You're trying to grab a banana and your hands are covered in Vaseline."
So eventually, the villagers are like, "Okay, this is getting annoying." So they make a bed out of
giant leaves and they carry the leaves and carry her back into the village. Now, they notice something.
One, she's completely incoherent. She's babbling. They can't figure out what it was. They don't
really ever say what the slime is. Secondly, she's pregnant. And she does give birth. I forgot the
shoe baby stories in this one. She gives birth to this little baby. Now, she's again incoherent,
but they decide to name the baby Mango. Maybe she cried out the name Mango in the middle of her
incoherent ramblings. And he's super furry. And they're like, "Uh, yes, one of them giants, one of
them giant babies." Luckily, she survived childbirth. She gives birth to Mango. He's a hairy baby monster
boy. And eventually, by the time the kid reached age five, the villagers just killed him. They're
just like, "Nope, this is creepy." And we know that at best, this kid's going to be like eight feet
tall. Like, even if he's just half human, half giant, he's going to be a big old kid. Okay,
that is not, I'm not, Ted Rabbit Radio is not endorsing. Well, if your kid's a giant, oh, it's
okay. I'm not obviously endorsing that. That was them. Do not, do not say, "Well, you know, I heard
Jason say the other day on his show that if the kid's big, you better dig a big grave." I didn't
say that. So, it was just well known that there was giants wandering around in the jungle, but
we're not here for the giants. We're not here for the giants. Also, you had a ship visit the Solomon
Islands. Well, you had a bunch of ships, but one ship in particular visited the Solomon Islands in
1593. And there was a guy who was doing an almanac. He was making maps. He'd have the normal thing.
Here's a real duck. Here's a real bird. It's said underneath it, real bird. No, he was doing all the
stuff, but one of the creatures he profiled was a dragon. What's known locally as the Solomon Island
Dragon Snake. And from 1593 and before to today, there's still sightings of this beast that flies
above the jungle. And it has a unique ability. It shoots out fireballs. It's not like a stream of
fire, which you could kind of imagine maybe they're pushing out methane and their tongue is like flint.
I saw that on some show when I was a kid, but they're lighting methane in their bellies,
dragging the rope. So, it shoots out fireballs and you'd have villagers be like,
"You won't believe the day I just had. Yeah, I was at the supermarket. I was behind stuff. And
what do you know? A dragon snake's flying around and that's why I'm late." So, you'd still have
sightings like that, but we're not even here for the dragon snakes. We're here because specifically
at Tete Par Island, it's empty. So, let's take a look at this island. Back in the 19th century,
you had people slowly start filtering off the island, which again, the island is an untouched
jewel. It wasn't because of lack of food. It wasn't because of lack of water. It was because people
started to feel uneasy on the island. People started to leave the island, go into neighboring
islands in the area. Scientists, historians look back and go, "We think dysentery hit. There was a
disease that started killing people off. We think it may have come from some of the wailing ships in
the area. We don't know presumably, but it could have been something else, but these natives were
getting dysentery. So, people were leaving the island. Then you started to have wars. Now,
all the islands were constantly attacking each other, sometimes it was almost done as sport,
but you started to see different tribes or inter-tribal warfare even. Tribes split in half,
going to war with each other. That was weird in and of itself, even though you would have
people fighting. It was generally island versus island. To have people fight on the same island
was odd in and of itself. Rendova is the closest island to Tete Par, and that is where our source
murder bur is from. This was the story that he had heard. He goes, "The official story is
people started getting sick. There was conflict on the island, and over time people started spreading
out." But he goes, "In our culture, there's another answer for this." Rendova at one point said,
"You know what? It would be fun. It's Saturday, right? You guys want to do something cool?" And
then he was like, "Yeah, let's go over to Tete Par and just mess them up. Sick them with a couple
spears, give them a couple noogies. It'll be a fun afternoon." So they get a war party together.
They take their canoes across to Tete Par, and right when they get to shore, something feels off.
All the large canoes are gone. That's weird. They start thinking, "Did they have the same idea?
They got bored on a Saturday? There's a war party in our part of the land?" They're walking around,
they get to a village, and it's just dead people. Unburied dead people. This is back in the 19th
century, so it's not like they could just pick up a phone and be like, "Hey, so is anything suspicious
happening back home because it's pretty scary here?" A bunch of unburied dead people, which was
totally not acceptable in that culture. In most cultures, it's not acceptable. They continue to
look around the island. There's no one alive in the portion where they're at. So they just
pack up, get on their canoes, and head back home. That was the start of the legend of what was going
on on the island. The people who had left the island before, they had no idea what happened,
but they were getting a weird vibe. You've had researchers today go there, like I said,
there's a lodge that people go to and from, but it is an abandoned island. It is a desert island.
I didn't know this, but I always thought it was a deserted island. A desert island means
an island with no people on it. You said it doesn't actually have to be a sandy island. It's just an
island with no humans. People go there, researchers go there, hunters will go there, a great hunting.
People will come from Rendova to that island to hunt, but you have to be careful where you go
because people get lost. Like anywhere, right? You can get lost in Manhattan. You can get lost
in Idaho, but you usually find your way back. The problem is that it seems to not happen to people
who go too far into the jungle. They just disappear. And since the locals don't really like the island,
they will go there to hunt and to fish. They don't like being in the jungle after nightfall. And
what's interesting is if you have to get from point A to point B on the island, let's say you
want to go to another part of the island, you don't cut right through it. You will take the
long way. You will go back to the beach and walk along the coastline to get where you're going.
You do not cut through the middle of the island. Murtuber has a story that when they were a little
kid, they spoke relatively good English and there was a researcher who wanted to see some
things on the island. So Murtuber goes, "Yeah, I'll do it." They're walking around the island.
It starts to get dark. And Murtuber is like, "I don't want to do this anymore. Like this is super
spooky. It's dark and we definitely don't want to be in the jungle after night." Researchers
researcher. They're not thinking about spirits or evil legends or things like that. But whatever,
their guide, their 10-year-old kid wants to go back, whatever. We can always reconfine tomorrow.
So the researcher has some sort of navigational device. Murtuber goes, "I don't even know what
it was. I was 10, but it was some sort of device that would show directions, most like a GPS device."
And so researchers looking at it and being like, "Okay, so we want to get to the coastline. We go
this way." So they start walking and Murtuber goes, "No, no, no, no, no. No. Do the coast. I mean,
it's an island, so the coast is in any direction, but the coast that part we want to go to is this way."
The researcher's like, "No, no, no. According to this GPS, we go this way."
He starts walking again and the kid's like, "No, no, no. I'm glad your fancy device tells
you to go that way, but I'm going to tell you right now. The way it's pointing is away from
or supposed to go, and not only is it away from it's supposed to go, it's pointing us to the
densest part of the jungle. I'm not going that way. And I'm especially not going that way
with the sunsetting." And they actually got an argument. They were arguing back and forth,
and eventually, I think it comes down to this, the researcher goes, again, assuming this story is
true. All of this historical stuff is true. This story is a first-person account. The researcher
at a certain point has to go, "Okay, here's my choice. I can either follow my device, which I know
works, or I can ab- because the murder ber wasn't going that way." It's like, "Okay, I can- if I've
trust the kid and we're wrong, then we're wrong, but if I- if the kid doesn't go with me, I can't
abandon a 10-year-old. What do you think? I am some sort of woman in Washington who's trying to drug
moms and take their babies, allegedly?" "No, I'm a better human than that." So eventually, the researcher
goes, "Fine, we'll go the direction you want to go on, but it's probably going to lead us in the
wrong way. We'll end up spending the night in the jungle anyways, but your funeral." He didn't
actually say that, but fine, we'll go your way. They end up- the kid was right. Takes them right
to the coastline. The GPS unit was directing them to go deeper into the jungle, and at that point,
the researcher, when they see the coast, the researcher's puzzled. "Hmm, I must research this.
Someone's doing my job." And begins fiddling with the machine, and the machine now, when it says,
"Where's the coast?" or where their direction is, it's right where they're headed, because you can
see it now. But when they're in the middle of the jungle, couldn't see anything, and it was telling
them to go deeper, deeper in where people go missing. All of these things are superstitious
stories, right? Tales of disappearing tribes in the 1900s, giants, dragons flying around. All of this
stuff can be chalked up to superstition. There's an interesting footnote to the story, and actually
what made me want to cover it. I mean, I think the island itself is pretty fascinating, because it
still stands today. It's completely uninhabited. There's one thing you can easily spook off a person.
You can even spook off a town or a city. You can spook people out of living in places, but the hardest
thing to scare is money, is human greed. A lot of times, people will do insane things, scary
things for money. There was a coconut farm that was operating on Titi Par in the 19- I think they
opened in the 1930s. Extremely successful coconut farm. They were moving 250 to 330 tons of coconuts
a year. It was the largest exporter of coconuts in this region. Not just on that island, but in
that archipelago or oceanic. 250 to 330 tons of coconuts a year. Then World War II started.
Guadalcanal was a major battle point between the allies and the Axis powers. They abandoned the
factory during World War II, which is what you would want to do. There's a difference between
being like, "I'm not afraid of a ghost and be a businessman as ghosts are possessing all your
employees." It's another thing to have bombs dropping around you. Honestly, they probably
stayed in operation a little bit longer than they were supposed to, but they did abandon it during
the war because there were a lot of violent battles over there. Because I played a lot of
Battlefield 1942. I know those Japanese spawn points are very hard to take. After World War II,
though, they opened the farm back up. They're pushing out those coconuts 250 to 330 tons of
coconuts and they're hollow, dude. Do you know how many coconuts that must be? It's gone. The factory's
gone. The factory is closed. It's abandoned. They just shut down. That's odd. That would be like an
oil... Think about how many stories we hear about haunted mines. And a lot of times they're like,
"People refuse to work in there." And then eventually, 10 years later, they shut it down.
Because this doesn't exist anymore. It's just decaying buildings. The official reason is labor
unrest. Labor unrest. But you can import it. If it's just the labor and we've seen it in so many
other countries. If people want to unionize, they just shut down the union. If it gets really bad,
we've seen it in other countries. They start violently putting down labor. You can. I mean,
those coconuts are just ready for... If you own a coconut farm and you're looking to expand,
here's... You sponsor this podcast and also go to Titi Pear Island. All of the stuff is still there
to do it. They left. What type of labor unrest could there be where you couldn't import more labor
and build cheap camps for them to stay in? Like every other migrant factory and farm in the world.
Something must be really bad there if someone's looking at that brown gold, which is what the
coconuts are known as. But you didn't know that. That brown gold. And saying, "No, I don't want that."
Thing about every episode of Scooby-Doo is some sort of businessman or some sort of like swindler
pretending to be a ghost to scare people out. This island is so spooky, people don't want to operate
a business on that island. Not a hotel. Not a coconut farm. Not a fishing village. Nothing.
Pristine, untouched land. Just sitting there. A place has to be exceptionally terrifying to turn away
a human's motivation for money. And when it's as simple as plucking a coconut off of a tree
and shipping it off in a box, it must be really bad when it gets dark at that place.
How scary does a place have to be for even a business to say, "Nope, I'm good." I never thought
anything could be so scary that could actually cancel out a human's motivation to make money.
Something could be so mysterious in that jungle that I would rather not sell coconuts.
I'd rather go somewhere else and leave all those coconuts untouched than to open my business
back on that island. I didn't know anything could be that scary. But I've never spent the night
on Ttpar Island.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio. DeadRabbitradio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true fan
podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]