When a band was hired to play at a Russian nightclub, they thought they were just going
to have an easy gig.
Instead, they came face to face with a bizarre mystery.
Then we take a look at a cult in modern day America that local authorities blame for almost
100 deaths.
They're still in operation today, and one of my listeners used to be a member.
You'll hear her story today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a ton of stuff to cover, so we're going to get started right away first off.
Let's go ahead and introduce our Patreon supporter for the day coming into Dead Rabbit Command
right now.
Hi, I'm Jason Carpenter.
I'm
Jason Carpenter.
So let me give some shout outs to you before we start the story.
First off, Ira Onok is the one who sent me the story, so thank you so much.
I hadn't heard of this story before.
Really appreciate it.
I got most of my information from a YouTube channel called All Things Creepy.
If you like this channel, I'm sure you'll like All Things Creepy.
We talk about a bunch of creepy stuff, but it's just not the name of the show.
But there's this, so check them out.
Also I needed some translation on this because it's in Russian.
There's English subtitles, but we've been tricked before in stories from other languages.
People put fake subtitles.
So I reached out to a listener who I knew could speak Russian.
Spiritual Abortion.
Spiritual Abortion did a secondary translation just to make sure that's what they said.
I want to give another shout out to Spiritual Abortion.
Due to the first 90 days challenge, he just released his first EP.
So that's what the 90 day challenge can do for you.
It's nothing I'm selling, it's no gimmick.
Try to make these next 90 days really count in your growth.
It was the kick in the pants he needed.
He said to get his EP done, I'll put a link in the show notes to one of his music videos.
It's not safe for work, it's sludge metal.
So I can't understand it anyways for all I know.
Maybe it is safe for work.
Maybe it's about work.
Check out his channel.
It's amazing that he got that album done and just think about what you can do for these
next 90 days to be a better you as well.
Garrett, go ahead and stop right here.
We're standing outside this Russian nightclub.
Now what happened was back in 2013, there's video footage of this.
A band is playing some music.
The power goes out.
And this video footage you're seeing of the audience, the power goes out and yet there's
like a split second.
All of a sudden you can see three pairs of glowing eyes.
Everything else is pitch black.
The headline of this YouTube video, glowing eyes caught on tape at Russian nightclub.
I'm like okay, I appreciate it.
I don't want to be super dismissive, no one's going to send me stuff.
I resend me this, I watch the video and I go okay, glitch.
You guys don't understand how much stupid reptilian footage I have to watch because
of this job.
I watch every time somebody glitches in a video, I have to watch it.
This one might be the real reptilian.
Did you know Barack Obama was a hologram?
Barack Obama's a hologram now.
Which I love the idea that we have the capability of creating AI perfect holograms and reptilians
can perfectly disguise themselves but the camera at MSNBC can foil this entire plot.
Like they've perfected this alien technology.
It's lasted throughout the millennia across the galaxy.
But somehow some cameraman can butterfinger a button and all of a sudden shhh.
Anyways, so you know what, I actually want to do something.
I would like to meet somebody who believes that this is real, that this phenomenon in
the video digital.
What it is, it's like artifacts.
It's artifacting in the movement in the face.
It's totally explainable.
I would love to meet someone who believes that and I can replicate that on them.
Would they think they are a reptilian?
You could replicate that effect and would they be like oh no there's claw on their face
off you're like ahhh.
The joke's over, the joke's over, it's just a prank.
They're like all reptilians die.
But anyways, I watched the video.
I saw the people's eyes glow.
I go it's artifacting, it's something like that.
But as the video continues, because I don't just poo poo it, I mean I poo pooed it then
but then I kept watching the video.
There's a clip of a guy in the band, the lead singer in the band and he's like we saw it
too.
We were standing there, we were playing the music, the power went out and I looked out
into the crowd and I saw a bunch of glowing eyes.
So it was more than just the three and it wasn't a video artifact thing, it was live.
People standing there, no video cameras, just their eyeballs, just nature's video cameras
aka the eyeball.
They're seeing it.
This is the whole band panicked.
They left, they left the show.
Now the interviewer goes who was at the party and the guy's like yeah right.
Because these were the richest of the rich.
This was a private elite party.
There was also a testimony from a supermodel named Natalia Boydanova and the band guy was
named Sergei Shernov.
He's actually a really big like ska musician.
This wasn't just some hobo who showed up with this ragtime band of animated bears.
This was like a really well known ska musician in Russia.
He's been around for years and years and years.
This is like a blip in his career.
Like when you look him up and you type in his name, you have to type in like his name
and then glowing eyes.
Because normally it's just like articles about his musical career and his different
bands and stuff like that.
So this wasn't his claim to fame.
So that does make the story more valid that you have this high profile guy and then you
have this high profile supermodel who was in the crowd as well and she said yeah I was
standing there.
She said a totally different angle and she turns and she can see people's glowing eyes
in the pitch black room.
So we have three different witnesses.
It's really important when you look at this stuff.
We have three different witnesses all from different angles.
One witness is the band.
So there's like actually five witnesses there but they're all viewing it from the same angle.
They see it.
Then you have someone in the crowd turn and look from her angle and sees it.
And then we have the video footage which shows it.
So there's a lot of conspiracy theories about this and you would have all things creepy
went over these.
So I'm kind of cribbing on his notes but it's a really cool channel.
You should check it out.
I'm sure you guys are already familiar with it.
And it's the same thing that you would guess.
As I'm telling this story you probably came up with these theories as well.
Aliens that these are some sort of hybrid alien creatures.
Androids that's not the first thing that would pop in my head right.
I think androids are pretty low on the list of Russian C-3PO.
There's a gold robot wearing a gold chain unbuttoned shirt and dress shirt made of silk.
I don't know I would really want to think of androids.
That would be way down on my list.
But aliens androids are demons.
Would be one that would pop up.
Like demonically possess people making their eyes glow.
But then we get into something that's a little more likely.
I mean I believe in demons and I believe in aliens and I guess I believe in androids.
I mean there's no reason for me.
They'll be here eventually.
But I don't think there's automatons walking around right now.
But Natalia she said that someone else in the crowd after this had gone on.
Someone else in the crowd gave their opinion that it was stem cells.
It was stem cell therapy.
And what's funny because this video I'm surprised they didn't touch on adrenochrome.
Because that is instead of androids I would have gone with the other a conspiracy theory.
Adrenochrome.
That's what I would have gone with.
Not saying it's true but if someone said pick conspiracy theories what make people's
eyes glow.
It's like well supposedly you get injected with adrenochrome in the eyeball or something
like that.
Stem cells which is far more realistic than adrenochrome because we did a whole episode
on that and it doesn't work the way the conspiracy theorist think it does.
But stem cells.
It's basically like gene spicing gene editing stem cells and things like that.
And I looked into it and there actually is the ability to make your eyes glow in the
dark.
It is possible to do that.
They just take the stem cells and they take a couple of glow sticks from the dollar store
and they're like mixing it up.
Apparently you can do that.
The question is is this their eyes glowing in the dark is it the bug or the feature?
Like it could be something that these incredibly wealthy dudes are doing this because it's
cool to make your eyes glow in the dark or it could be they are receiving some sort of
life enhancing or super super strong super strong Russian soldiers and the side effect
is your eyes glowing.
And it's funny because a stem cells is one of those things that like I was vaguely aware
of back when the early 2000s when George Bush was like we're not going to allow stem cell
therapy in the United States and I remember thinking is the president of the United States
really talking about like cloning technology like he was who was saying like we can't have
clones and I was like what sci-fi world do we live in?
The coolest one it turned out because this place is pretty cool.
I didn't know in advance to the point I always thought it was still theoretical and they
were still kind of goofing off stuff nerds in a laboratory throwing stem cells pouring
them down each other's backs.
I saw this article the other day this woman had some macular degeneration what they'll
do is they'll take belly fat out of your stomach and they injected into your eyeballs.
They actually there's a couple there's a couple steps in between that they have to like remove
stuff they just don't go like I hope you ate a bunch of Taco Bell last night we need all
the fat cells we can get they have to like separate it they get out the stem cells they
injected into her eyes and she went blind but apparently people do that that's an actual
therapy that people do for macular degeneration oh gross like all of it's gross getting
the stuff taken out of your stomach then having having some guy with a little ladle going
hmm just right stem cells are just ready to get injected in your eyeball and then she
got injected into her eyeballs and then the retinas peeled away.
This happened multiple times you think after the first time people would go maybe this
isn't a good therapy for people who are losing their vision to make them go even more blind
it's unlicensed so stem cells have that's the thing when I watch this video it's like
yeah but stem cells are still like theoretical no no they're actively being used they're
being injected into people's eyes as we speak so it's possible that these guys just thought
it'd be really cool to have glowing eyes so they could have other things going on and
this is the side effect or could be a bunch of androids it could be proof that the C3
POs are about to take over the very polite world order is about to begin.
Garrett let's go ahead and leave behind Russia I'm gonna tashi the keys of the Carbenter
Copter we are headed back to an undisclosed location in the United States.
As we're flying out there I gotta give a Dead Rabbit Recommends I can't tell you anything
about the movie I'm just gonna tell you to watch it you're gonna enjoy it.
I actually was recommended this movie by a Dead Rabbit radio listener named Christopher
Padmos he sent me this movie he has watched everything on the Dead Rabbit Recommends list
he goes I'd either seen it or when I was watching it being like oh do this this movie's nuts
so I have a movie to give to you it's called Freaks it's not the old 1930s Freaks one
of us one of us with the circus freaks it's a new movie it's 2018 it's called Freaks
it's on Netflix it starts email Hirsch and Brewster don't look at the trailer poke your
eyes get stem cells in your eyes if you even come close to look don't watch the trailer
don't look at the movie poster don't read the synopsis just watch the movie there's
a magic to the storytelling in the movie which is incredibly hard to replicate it doesn't
have a twist it's just a very unique way to tell a story like you start that movie you
don't know the genre you don't you if you don't know the genre all conventions are
gone because if it's a romantic comedy you know certain things are gonna happen if it's
a drama certain things are gonna happen you go in you start the movie and here's a little
fun game because after I finished it I go that's fascinating you watch that first scene
and then you just pause it for 20 seconds a minute and imagine what the last scene of
that movie is going to be and then start the movie up again again it's not a twist it's
a really interesting thing it's not a twist but you have no idea where things are going
and it's one of those rare movies and I've only seen like this done two or three times
each scene basically informs what happened in the scene before it you watch a scene and
you don't really understand what's going on it's not an art house film either it's a
it's so amazing it's each scene of the movie you watch it and you go very interesting the
acting is great all this cinematography is great everything like that but I don't know
what's going on and the next scene gives you a little bit of information that makes that
first scene makes sense and then that third scene gives you a little bit of information
that makes that second scene make sense it's so dope dude I'm I normally include the trailer
in the show notes because people sometimes have a hard time finding the movie I'm not
doing that I'm including a clip from IMDB of one scene near the beginning of the movie
if you're on the fence watch that scene it gives nothing away it basically it's just
that scene I showed it to Sabine and she goes the first thing she goes she goes that that
acting I was like I know just in that two minute scene you're like these people know
their roles it's brilliant freaks Christopher thank you so much for sending it over I'm
recommending all of you this weekend to watch freaks 2018 it's on Netflix I'm sure you can
find it other places but if it's white and shows much of circus freaks that's not the
movie I'm recommending that movie's okay too but check out freaks
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
11 children, no postnatal care. She's just suffering. The pain is constant. No pain medication. No treatment. She is just withering away in her home. She has eight surviving children.
One is less than a year old. She has to take care of all these kids. She has to homeschool them. And she is in physical agony because of Hobart Freeman's teachings.
By May 2007, she couldn't deal with it anymore. She broke one of the most important rules laid forth by Hobart Freeman. You have to have faith.
God will take care of you. She called up her mother-in-law. They took her to the hospital. Here's a quote from the email that I received.
"It didn't take long for them to find out the source of her agonizing pain. A tumor of cervical cancer the size of a four month old baby inside of her with limbs wrapping around her organs shutting down her system.
They got her one treatment before she decided that she was to come back home and to trust God." That was in May of 2007, by August of 2007.
Bella said she could smell her mother's body rotting. Nothing helped. And there really weren't giving her anything. Pray the pain away. She would scream constantly.
One night, Bella's older brother was woken up when he heard the back door slam. And he ran out of the house, followed his mother, and got to her just in time. She had taken a knife outside with her and was ready to end her life.
After that, she was put into a hospice, separated from her husband, separated from her kids. Just a few days later, she passed away.
After she died, her husband, Bella's father, had the body cremated, went home, and burned all the possessions of his wife. The memory was gone.
He ended up becoming an alcoholic after it. The children, Bella said, "We are all basically illiterate." And by May 2008, so half a year after all of these events, child services come, and they remove the children from the house.
Bella's doing great now. She's doing perfectly fine now, but this was her upbringing. It's fascinating to look at a cult in this perspective.
The email that she wrote, it's different than, because it was to me. She's a listener of the show, so it was a message to me.
It was interesting to read it like that. I've read accounts from cults, and I've watched YouTube videos from people who have escaped cults. There's something different about it when someone who was involved in a cult, born into it, she had no choice.
And writing to me, and she had written to me before as well, just talking casually, so it was an interesting thing for this to come out.
To read this account from somebody that you had been talking to, and then they feel comfortable sharing a story with you. And you can imagine this story played out at least 100 times in the Faith Assembly.
100 families went through this. Hey, how's Uncle Joey doing? I heard he had really bad diabetes. I get the worst. He had diabetes 3.
And someone going, "He stopped taking his diabetes medicine." What? Yeah, he threw it off a cliff and a bunch of ants showed up. I didn't even know they liked insulin.
Why? Well, because he is following Hobart, Hobart freeman. His Faith Assembly has been tied to at least 100 deaths. You have to wonder about all these families.
The mother goes out to the barn. They're ready for their new little baby brother. They're going to have so much fun playing with the baby brother.
And then a couple hours later, the mom comes back. There is no baby brother. That happened. That story happened. And it happened over and over and over again, at least 100 times.
Those are the ones they could calculate. Those are the ones they knew of. In some ranch out in the middle of nowhere, far away from Indiana, where they're not paying attention, that no one knows about this cult outside of the people in it, none of the local authorities.
And you have people suffering and dying and nobody knows why. It's tragic.
Hobart freeman, his legacy is one of death. There are still people who follow the Faith Assembly and they could probably say, "Well, you know, we have these good beliefs and stuff like that. We do this community service for the Lord and all that stuff."
It's fine. That's awesome. But it's still a legacy of death. It's still a legacy of death. And not only a legacy of death, a legacy of preventable death, Hobart freeman's teachings convinced a woman that she could rot in front of her family for months on end and it was all okay.
Tomorrow, God will cure that. I believe God gave us medicine and gave us the intelligence to figure these things out to prevent this.
I think both can be applicable. You can have faith and have faith in that your doctor is going to heal you. To Hobart, that would be heresy.
He doomed Bella's mom to not only die, but to suffer for months and die. To bury her children and then die. And to convince her husband that her memory was worth nothing after she died.
Hobart freeman's legacy is a legacy of death and the terrifying thing is he's not the only one out there. There are many other people who believe they have the answer and there are even more people who are lost and looking for any answer.
When these two groups of people meet, tragedy and chaos are the only result.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also do this up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day.
We're glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
[Music]