was a conspiracy theorist killed
before he could reveal his secrets
and the fascinating story of the medical, edible mummy.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
(upbeat music)
Hey everyone, thanks for coming back to Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day.
Little sore, back's a little sore.
I don't want you to always think
things are going super perfect for me.
I've got a little heating pad on me.
I know I always sound kind of upbeat
unless I'm talking about a story
that really kind of irritates me,
but you know, everything's not always perfect.
Things are generally very good though.
And I hope everything's going good for you guys as well.
Now we have a lot to cover today.
We did something unusual where we actually had a part two.
This is a part two.
The first, just a brief rundown,
so you don't have to go and listen to yesterday's episode.
And again, I don't think everyone listens to every episode.
Just listen to the episodes that are interesting to you
or the most current episode.
That's fine with me.
If you want to go back and binge, totally awesome.
But don't ever feel like you have an obligation
to listen to all 55 episodes that we're at.
So a quick recap.
Yesterday I talked about the Super Soldier Program
and John Storm in particular.
So the Super Soldier Program is a program run,
okay, it's not true,
but anyways, I was talking like it was factual.
Super Soldier Program was allegedly a program run
by the US government where they kidnap children.
They do all sorts of testing on them
and break their bones to make their bones stronger
and make them into the Super Soldiers.
Then they release them back into the world
with little to no memory of all of the training.
And then through hypnosis or psychic techniques,
all of your memories are unlocked
where you are actually a soldier fighting for the government.
Sometimes they fight against aliens
and sometimes they fight against humans.
John Storm at least, and he was who we profiled yesterday,
his whole Super Soldier story
and just the insanity that is involved in it.
Just the delusion.
He's kept it pretty basic
where he says he was created by the US government
and he fought in Vietnam.
And he realized it was like just an unnecessary war.
So he broke the programming
and now he's on our side as homo sapiens, as normals.
He's going to save us.
And he was the perfect fighting specimen,
but now he looks like he's 80 years old.
He has back problems and narcolepsy
and needs insulin shots.
And his narcolepsy is so bad,
he sleeps through his insulin shots.
That's the story of John Storm in a nutshell.
Insanity, insanity.
Oh, and he also knows Peter Parker, the Spider-Man.
He completely is like, "Oh yeah, I know Peter Parker.
"He's a black guy and he has the powers of Spider-Man."
Okay, anyway, he's just so bizarre.
So if any of that interests you, that was the last episode.
But I wanted to cover that
because a big part of the super soldier community
is paranoia.
So these people were created by the government.
And like I said, some of them believe
that they were created by the government to fight aliens.
One guy was talking about how he remembers
psychically sniping aliens in Afghanistan.
Other ones say that they float around in the astral realm
and they meet aliens and they're like,
"We are one of the 151 races that live on your planet."
And blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I almost kind of have to gloss over that insanity
'cause it gets even weirder.
So the problem is that they believe
the government created them.
So they're incredibly hostile and paranoid
towards the government.
And by extension, any authority figures,
mostly like psychologists and psychiatry, obviously,
the medical profession.
So you had John Storm yesterday I was talking
where he was saying that his pharmacist and doctor
were trying to kill him.
And then when he left the pharmacist, a car hit him.
And this was all proof that the government was after him,
even though they pay him disability checks.
Somehow the government also hates his guts
and wants to stop John Storm.
No update on Spider-Man though.
No update on whether or not the government's after Spider-Man.
But anyways, let's get into today's story.
Okay, so let's talk about Max Spears.
Now Max Spears was a conspiracy theorist
who in 2016 died.
It's really the only details that we can confirm.
Everything else seems to be up for grabs.
He was in Poland to be at a conference
to speak about him being a super soldier.
And he was a big conspiracy theorist,
he believed in the Fourth Reich.
He believed there was a secret city underneath London in LA
that controlled people's minds.
He believed that the Bushes were reptiles
and the reptilian overlords
and all these crazy conspiracies and things like that.
And he was a super soldier created by the US government.
Or British government maybe, I don't know.
Reptiles, it's reptiles all the way down.
Anyways, he goes to Poland to be in this conference.
He dies.
Original report, he had black liquid on his lips.
That report later became,
he had two liters of black liquid.
He was soaked in this mysterious black liquid.
There are reports that he was kidnapped by a satanic cult drug
to put in a coma for two days, allowed to go home,
died later.
There are reports that at the scene of his death,
when the police and the coroner
were still investigating his death,
the police and the coroner left.
And a satanic cult came in, called up his mother
and performed rituals over his body.
If some of these details are sounding a little far-fetched,
it's probably because they're completely made up.
I don't think he was kidnapped by a cult.
Let's take it apart one by one.
Let's do this relatively quickly,
'cause it's an irritating story for me on multiple levels.
But we'll get to the key point of it.
But anyway, so let's say that you're the evil Illuminati
and this guy has information you want.
You're able to kidnap him to a cult compound
in the middle of Poland.
You put him in a coma for two days, you take him home.
But Jason, they wanted us to find the body
'cause they would send a message to other conspiracy theorists.
No, it wouldn't.
Him disappearing would be far more terrifying
to anyone investigating conspiracies
than finding him and his buddy's couch in Poland.
Far more terrifying because then your imagination would run,
is he like some sex slave in Saudi Arabia?
Is he in a red room somewhere?
They found his body.
Apparently the satanic cult kidnapped him,
was successful in that, drugged him, was successful in that,
took him home, dropped him off on a couch,
died a couple of days later.
That's according to the girlfriend.
The mother says that as the police were still investigating
his murder at the house,
cult members were in the house
and they were saying satanic, horrible rituals.
I mean, I'm gonna read these to you
and you're going to be shocked,
shocked that the media could even report
such satanic phrases.
Check these out.
Put milk by his side.
Get garlic and put flowers and put vinegar.
Oh my God, I can't believe I just read those out loud.
This house is now haunted 100%.
According to his mother, those are satanic phrases.
She said it sounded like rituals going on,
some sort of satanic rituals.
I don't mean to mock a mother who lost her child,
but I think there's two things going on.
One, she's just as delusional as her son was
and she believed he was a super soldier,
sent, created by the aliens
and yet will destroy the aliens.
Or it's all about money, book deals, pay pals, go fund me's.
Because even today, even today,
the story is that the British government
took his cell phone and his laptop
and when they gave it back to the lawyer
and her, the mother, they were wiped.
They were wiped clean.
What does that mean?
That's not a legal term.
It's not even a technical term.
Is the desktop wiped clean?
Is the hard drive reformatted?
You know, if I gave my, if someone took out
my mom's laptop and she turned it on and it said,
"Would you like to install Windows 10?"
She's going to know immediately
that the computer was actually reformatted.
She's gonna be like, "There was nothing on it at all.
"Nothing on it at all."
If they gave it back to her and it had a fault
that had the folder that said,
"Dead Rabbit Radio is missing," she would never know.
She would never know.
If you are the secret Illuminati reptilian overlords
and you take, I feel really heartless
talking trash about this dead kid,
but I think it's important.
If we take, if they have control of that laptop
and it has information on it,
that will be completely detrimental
to the reptilian overlord alien plan,
they're going to either conveniently lose the laptop,
conveniently destroy the laptop,
and they'll just tell the mother,
"Well, we accidentally lost an evidence locker,"
or remove the files they need removed.
I don't see the point of simply wiping it clean
and then handing it back to somebody
who's obviously going to know it's wiped clean.
I think she's making these details up.
I think that they're making these details up.
And I actually have something that leans in that direction.
The original report that the friend made
that I found online was that Max Spears
did not have two liters of liquid covering his body.
He had a black liquid coming out of his mouth.
The story evolved to be covered in two liters
of black liquid.
If you walked into someone's house
and they had a little bit of black liquid on their mouth,
you would not mistake that for two liters.
And the same thing, you would not mistake two liters
for a little bit of black liquid on your mouth.
The stories are changing, the stories are morphine,
they're becoming more and more dire.
There are reports, I'll include the link,
and people say, "Well, maybe it wasn't the mother
posting this, you never know online."
But there are reports that the mother
initially never even reported the tweet,
the text message, I should say,
where he tweeted her and says,
"Mom, if something happens, you know, investigate."
And the early reports, that wasn't even reported,
that got reported later.
So it seems like the story has become
more overly dramatic as time has gone on.
What is most likely in this situation?
Now, this is where it ties back to John Storm
and it ties back to the Super Soldier program.
Is that he had medical problems,
he had an opioid addiction that had become
a heroin addiction.
At the time, it is believed he was clean of heroin.
However, he says that he was kidnapped and taken to a cult
and he was given drugs and he was asleep for two days.
And truth be told, if I had a history of cheating on my wife
and my story was I got kidnapped and taken to a brothel
and I banged like 50 women, but it was totally
against my will and I only came twice.
If someone who has problems with heroin addiction
says they are kidnapped, taken to the middle of nowhere,
given drugs and slept for two days,
it's a little suspicious.
I'm sorry, my girlfriend, I didn't call you.
I was kidnapped by St. Worshipers and they drugged me.
But I have no proof of that.
That's just a, it's probably not what happened.
He probably went to a flop house.
God, I'm really shitting on this dude.
I think the problem with this story is what makes me mad
about the story in general.
I feel really bad just talking trash about a dead kid
and talking trash about his mom.
I honestly do, but I think that they're using his death,
his natural death.
I think he had an ulcer.
I think he had a peptic ulcer
and he believed in all that super soldier nonsense
that the doctors were out to get him
and the medical establishment was out to get him
and the government was out to get him
and he had stomach pain and he wasn't taking care of it
because they're all evil reptilians
and he died of a completely preventable disease.
That's what I think.
I think when they say it's natural causes,
that would cause the black blood to be on your lips
because he's coughing up blood, not two liters.
But you know what I mean?
I think he, I think that's what irritates me about this.
I think we had a young man
who had some mental health issues obviously
and it was related to either self-medication
of the heroin use or just the heroin use in general.
He had a mom that obviously seems to promote that.
She encourages that lifestyle, that super soldier stuff.
Dude, if I was walking around talking
that I was a super soldier,
my mom would slap the shit out of me.
And especially if I died, she wouldn't say,
oh no, he was really a super soldier.
The mom, I think, kept that delusion going.
She obviously has a similar delusion
that the world is out to get these people
for seeking out the truth.
All of the stuff that he was talking about,
Fourth Reich and secret cities
underneath LA and Los Angeles
were controlling your brain.
Bush and their royal families, they were reptilians.
This is all common knowledge in the conspiracy field.
And the fact that the son,
the son British newspaper is publishing this stuff
should tell you it's nonsense because if it was true,
the son would never publish it.
Oh no, no, he was working on another story,
connecting the Illuminati and powerful people
and celebrities.
There's a thousand websites about that.
He was exposing nothing that can't be found anywhere.
He dies a natural death and it is being exploited
and turned into a myth for either money
or to further your own delusion.
I think it's a little bit of both honestly.
I think people who already believe
in this super soldier nonsense,
they bought into it right away.
You can read the forums of the day he died.
And at first they're like, no, he's just in a coma, it's okay.
And then John Storm's like, ah yeah,
we gotta be extra paranoid now.
They're taking us super soldiers out one by one.
And that's why I had to do that whole John Storm episode.
He ran in this crew.
I think people are delusional.
And the day Max Spear died,
they're already exploiting it for their delusion.
And I'd be shocked,
shocked if the mother's not trying to get a book deal
or a movie deal.
I don't feel good talking trash about dead people
and dead people's relatives.
That might be, this might be the episode,
not the one where I said
that I would not record street gangs for crimes.
This might be the episode where you say,
damn, Jason, you're kind of scummy.
But I hope it gets through where my scuminess is coming from.
I'm not trying to mock the dead.
I'm trying to mock the beliefs
that I believe led to his demise.
And they're just still ongoing.
If the mother is still saying,
oh no, the government wiped the laptop,
which again, give me specifics.
Tell me that there was no operating system on it.
What does wipe the computer mean?
The desktop was clean?
Tell me specifically what it was.
I'd be more likely to believe you, maybe,
because I've seen the story shift so much.
So I'm not trying to mock the grief the mother went through.
And the mom may be trying to make sense of her son's death
by believing in the delusion.
It may be the only way for her to deal with it
is to believe that her son was murdered
by the reptilian Illuminati overlords.
Does she believe her son was a super soldier
who was kidnapped by Alene's Winoose Kid?
I don't know.
I'm sure, like I said, I'm sure there's a book deal
or a movie deal or something coming down the pipe.
I believe it feeds into the delusion.
I believe people are making money off of it.
I think it's scummy.
I think it's only going to lead
to more disasters in the future
where we have more young men and women who now have proof,
proof that the Illuminati is out to get them
and they're not going to seek the help that they need,
either physically or mentally.
Because I'll admit, when I heard this story back in 2016,
it was very alarming.
My first inclination was, oh man,
maybe he did know something we weren't supposed to know
and they killed him for it.
But Illuminati reptilian aliens do not exist.
So looking into that, and of course, again,
if they did exist, they control everything.
So these stories shouldn't exist.
He dies to cover up these stories.
He dies because he's exposing these stories.
But in his death, these stories are exposed.
It doesn't make any sense.
So yes, people do get killed for discovering stuff.
Generally, they get run off the road
or they get a bullet in the back of the head.
They don't spit up alien goo.
They don't get kidnapped
and then return to their place from where they were kidnapped.
And their murderers are not reptilian alien overlords.
You know what, I honestly, this story is so irritating to me.
This is gonna sound kind of cheap,
but I'm gonna end the episode now
because the other story I wanted to do
was actually kind of lighthearted.
But this story really pisses me off.
And here's a little secret.
I've recorded this episode.
This single story, this is the fourth
or fifth time I've recorded it.
And it pisses me off every single time I do
because it makes me mad
and it makes me kind of, makes me scummy
that I have to take this position
and I'm kind of pissing all over this family.
But again, I think it's dangerous.
I talk about cults like sun gazing and we laugh,
but I think this stuff is dangerous
because it feeds into a delusion
that makes people not seek mental health or physical health.
If you believed your doctor, you know what?
I'm done.
We're gonna go ahead and end this episode.
I hope you guys had a good time.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Our Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
I will be back tomorrow with some fun stories.
And at the end of the day,
I have no remorse about releasing this episode
because again, I think it's dangerous belief.
It has serious consequences.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it.
I have great ideas.
(upbeat music)