It's the beginning of Insanity Week. It's the craziest stories that I could find. I didn't actually want to find them
They found me were covering some of the craziest stuff this week on Dead Rabbit Radio
first off a time traveler appears in a city in Wyoming his mission
Warn us of the massive alien invasion coming in the year 2018
and then we meet a group of people who have pierced the veil between reality and
fantasy
using methamphetamines and
They've started their own religion their gods the shadow people today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter or I'm having a great day
I hope you guys had a great day, too
Hope you guys had a great weekend
It was a calm one because this week this week we're gonna cover some of the craziest stories
We've come across on Dead Rabbit Radio
It didn't go out of my way to find them
They just somehow dog piled on me no matter what I researched this week
Turned into just a super bizarre rabbit hole so to start off Insanity Week coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now
It's our newest patreon supporter. He's dressed up as one of those old-timey mental people
Not the guys in the asylum. He's not walking around a straight jacket. You know what old-timey people they used to carry around the nets
They had like the funny wagon
They didn't actually have his people Jesse everyone give a round of applause to Jesse he runs in he's he's drawn like an old
Bugs Bunny cartoon character. He's running in with his net. Did they used to do that?
They used to like drag you off nowadays. They're like police come to the hospital
But I guess in the old I saw this documentary once about Bugs Bunny and Debbie Duck
Didn't they used to throw a net over you Jesse's like no that didn't exist that didn't exist
There was a cartoon Jesse you're gonna be captain our pilot this episode. He's shaking his head. Oh, you think this is bad
I feel really bad for the patreon supporter on Thursday's episode
But Jesse you're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon work
You have a job that actually exists. That's fine, too
Just help spread the word about the show really really helps out a lot
Jesse I'm gonna go ahead and touch the keys of the Jason Jalopy. We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command
We are headed out to
Casper
Wyoming
Old Jason Jalopy is driving down the road. It's October 2nd
2017 it's 10 30 p.m
a
Man appears in the middle of the street. He's like what where am I?
And someone goes you're in Casper, Wyoming and he goes no I mean the date
Yes, where you were and today's like no the date the date and they said it's October 2nd
2017 and he goes
They've sent me back too far and he's running through the street of Casper, Wyoming
I have to warn somebody have to warn anybody. He's running around this man's name is Bryant Johnson. This is true story. Well
The true part is there's a man named Brian Johnson in Casper, Wyoming. He says he's from the year
2048 he's running around he starts saying he has to talk to the president of town
Who's the president of the town and people are like what are you talking about?
Then he'd like run away and then he'd run into someplace else and he'd be like
What year is it? He knows the year that's just the best way to start the conversation
He wants people to know he's a time traveler. He's doing this the police are called out
They come out and they see this man. He's running around. I
Was kind of making the story more exciting
It was more like he was stumbling around town going where's the president of town people are like what the alien invasion is coming
He wasn't this super active Kyle Reese character. The reason why I had to add that disclaimer
Was one because it's the truth. I wanted to make sure it's telling the truth
But two what's coming next when the police show up this man who I previously said was running all over town
The police walk up to him and they can obviously tell he's incredibly drunk
They give him a breathalyzer test. He blows a point one three six
Which a point zero eight is
Illegally drunk or at least illegally drunk to drive
So this guy is off the sauce or on the sauce or off his rocker or all sorts of stuff, right?
This guy's super drunk. That's an illegal term the guy was super drunk your honor
So the police question them they're like listen
You're drunk. There's not really a question. It's a statement
We're gonna say that you're drunk and he goes that's funny that you say that it's funny that you say that because you're right
I am drunk. I am drunk officer, but not by my own accord
You see in the future
This is the greatest excuse. This is the greatest excuse I've ever heard in the future
The only way you can time travel is to be incredibly drunk
You're like Jason
Excuse at all. That's the worst excuse. I think it's a creative excuse
He says listen, so what happened was in the year 2048
I was put on this giant
Transportation pad and to make it so I could actually time travel. I was force fed liquor is his favorite liquor
Honestly, he's like and I object Daniels, please go go go go go go. They don't give him like gin or something disgusting
They force fed him liquor and the liquor is the body has to be saturated with alcohol to travel back in time
The police are looking at each other and they're like that
We don't know how time travel physics are going to work near 2048. All we know is that you're drunk here now
and
You're running around you're asking you're not
He's adding that detail. You have laser blasters. You're shooting everyone. You're stumbling around town. You're harassing people
You're publicly intoxicated. We're bringing you in and he is like no no you can't do that because he does have this mission
He was sent back in time to warn about this alien invasion that's coming in the year 2018
He was supposed to return to the year 2018, but he was sent back to the year 2017 instead
So Jason, why are you covering the story? It seems like just a local weirdo got a little drunk hallucinating whatever
I mean, it's not outside the realm of what I cover on this show doesn't involve aliens
But there's a specific reason why I'm covering this story
It's funny. It is funny and it does give us an idea of what time travel may be like
What I thought was really interesting was that he was sent back in time to warn us of an alien invasion of the year 2018
Now obviously it's the year 2021 it never happened
But the people who sent him back now, this could just be his alcohol-addled brain
But the people who sent him back were aliens
Aliens
Time traveled him back to the year 2017 to warn about an upcoming alien invasion
That's been under conspiracy caps here for a second when I read that I go
Why would aliens send back somebody to warn about them invading?
What if aliens in the few let's let's say this in 2018 aliens invaded the planet
It was a blowout the aliens spaceships flying around
Dropping drop and bottles of Jack Daniels and people are like what this is the best weapon ever and they're drinking it
And everyone's just taking big naps and the aliens are just kind of like walking into Congress and they're like
I guess we won we didn't know humans we didn't know humans would react so poorly to our biological weapons
We thought it well we thought it would kill them, but instead it just put them to sleep
So it's now that you're 2048 and the aliens who've invaded Earth hate it here
So they decide to send the most sober human back. They're like this man only has a blood alcohol content of point one three six
They send him back in time. He runs around Casper, Wyoming. He's saying aliens are gonna invade and
Aliens
Also read the local newspaper of Casper, Wyoming. You didn't know that that's the only newspaper aliens read the aliens get all their information
From the Casper Gazette some little newspaper and they can read this report and everyone laughs at this guy
I'm not laughing at you Brian Johnson. You're a hero. You saved us
But Brian Johnson comes back and he's like oh no don't invade the aliens send me back and the alcohol pad and all this stuff and
Everyone laughs at him and throws him in jail, but up somewhere in recticuli seven the aliens are like
Oh my god, did you read today's issue of the Casper Gazette?
Of course, I did that's the only newspaper we read and they saw this and that's why the aliens didn't invade
So thank you Brian Johnson. Thank you for saving the planet
All you had to do is sacrifice your own liver and 48 hours in jail. You were able to
Keep us from being taken over by aliens as we all laid around in alcoholic stupors a true
Hellish future
Jesse I'm gonna go ahead and touch you the keys of the carboner copter. We're leaving behind Casper Wyoming. We are headed out to
the school of shadows
This is where the insanity starts this is where the insanity of insanity week starts
We're gonna take a look at a group of people
Who have formed a new religion and I got to give a shout out to Fabio
Nurbon he actually recommended the story he's recommended a lot of good stuff really really appreciate it
Jesse you see that school down there and that's spooky spooky swamp. There's no roads connecting it to anything
It's all like dark and moldy and everything like that. That's where we're going
So hope you guys me and Jesse have on our gas masks on our PPE
Hope you guys brought those and you came to listen to a podcast
We're walking through the swamp we open up the school doors
I
Don't know why they sounded like that either don't need to I imagine they are like moldy they make a weird sound
We're walking into the school of shadows
This school was set up by a man on reddit
No one is thought bought 100 and I'm I couldn't verify it, but I think we've covered him before
We've done a lot of meth stories on this podcast
Even starting early on if you have a so before had a meth story
So I think I've covered him before but he created a subreddit back in February 2021 has a hundred and eighty five members
Which is a hundred and eighty five members more than it should have
And I'll explain why I'm not jealous. I'm not jealous, but I'll explain why
But let's take a look at the theories here. So we walk into the school of shadows and
We sit down in the desk. We all sit down on the same desk. It's a quantum desk
You can hold all of us. Let's take a look at what thought bought 100 is teaching
He has a philosophy known as the life addition theory
Where life is about adding things life is constantly about growing as a person
Fascinating really if you think about it, and it's quite simple
You gain experiences. You don't really lose experiences
You gain knowledge. I mean you can forget things, but it's not really that you forget it
It's that you just don't have access to it anymore every life is always about addition
So you constantly need to be adding observations to your life adding information to your life adding
Experiences that is what the universe wants
life is
perception
perception is thought thought is reality
So
What you perceive is reality that is the secret that is the science to getting rich that is an old
Philosophy you can warp reality
Through your own thoughts and if you get a bunch of people together and they agree on reality
That is what constructs the universe. This isn't groundbreaking stuff. It's interesting. It's not groundbreaking stuff
I hadn't heard of the life addition theory before but the idea that thoughts and reality is and we've all decided
That's wood. We've all decided that my hand won't go through oak
That'd be awesome if everyone on the planet just goes Jason's hand can go through oak like if everyone just believed that
I'm just like sticking my hand pulling squirrels out of trees all day long. I'm like thanks world
But those are all I remember hearing that type of stuff in high school. That was like high school philosophy
So that's all well and good and I can understand where that logic is coming from
This is where it starts to get darker. This is why it's the school of shadows and not the school of intro to philosophy
If thought is reality and everyone's combined thoughts is what makes up the reality of the universe the shared reality
psychosis
bends the rules of the universe
quote
We believe psychosis has contributed to dismantling reality and making it more simulation
unquote
Which we hear a lot about in conspiracy theory today
That we're moving to a reality that's so
cartoonish
That you can look at and go how are things playing out the way they are it feels like we're in a simulation
It feels too dynamic to action-packed too full of mystery
Like constructed mysteries. It seems like we're in a simulation rather than a random chaotic universe and
You could say predictive programming isn't the Illuminati putting stuff in television shows to predict what they have to do because some sort of
weird cosmic rule
It's the opposite the universe is so bizarre now
That it's replicating what is in the popular culture that it is a natural phenomenon
And that's kind of what's going on here
The psychosis is actually bending the universe and making it less real and more simulation
So the goal of the school of shadow is to continue this process and the best way to continue this process is
with the deities of the universe on your side
aka the shadow people
We've talked about shadow people a lot on this show shadow people I've had personal experiences with shadow people
I'll put those up cut all put those episodes in the show notes
There's a whole bunch of theories whether they're interdimensional whether they're gin
Whether they're alien whether they're the original
Inhabitants of hell who were pushed out when demons came down. There's a ton of different theories on these guys
Are they ghosts are they more malevolent ghosts?
But the shadow people you can see them when you are
In an area where shadow people normally inhabit a haunted house a normal house
The shadow person wants to pay you a visit another way that you can actually see shadow people anywhere
You can be at the mayor's office. You can be talking about the upcoming alien invasion
smoking meth and staying up
Will allow you to see the shadow people
I don't really think just staying up on its own will allow you to see shadow people
But definitely a site a very well known side effect of smoking meth of meth psychosis is seeing the shadow people
I used to follow the subreddit the meth subreddit and I
Had a hard time telling because I also cover
I also follow a bunch of paranormal subreddits and I would see shadow people pop up all the time in
My reddit thread and I would have to look to see if it was a meth subreddit or if it was the truth is here or
Ghosts or some other subreddit they talk about shadow people all the time in the meth subreddit
But thought bot 100 has an idea here. We should worship the shadow people. They're the closest we have to real
Gods real angels real demons are the shadow people
That's an interesting thought because I guess I guess I should add this in now thought bot 100 smokes a lot of meth
He does a lot of meth
He's on a lot of the meth boards as well, and I might have mentioned that earlier
I think I did in passing but to be specific he does smoke a lot of meth and he's very open about that
How many people can say they've actually seen God? I can say I've seen the work of God in my life
But I've never seen him. I mean my eyeballs are still intact. I'm not a pillar of salt
So but I've never seen God, but you can see you can see the shadow people
Tomorrow if you start or maybe tonight depending on how quickly you can get it if you I'm not I'm not recommending this
But if you did start using meth and had meth psychosis, you could see shadow people don't do it. It's not worth it
But if you had questions about faith do angels exist do demons exist you can see shadow people with the right amount of chemicals
I'm sure with the right amount of any drug or lack of sleep you might be able to have other spiritual experiences
But it's almost guaranteed with meth. So when you have a religion geared towards meth users
They've all seen the shadow people. There is no faith. They've seen them. They've interacted with them
The shadow people thought about explains that they want to be worshiped, but it's not like the traditional build a shrine kill a calf
bow before it
They clone you
The shadow people clone you for two reasons
One the first one is
Incredibly disturbing
I mean anyone cloning you for any reasons probably creepy, but when I read this I go that's creepy
They clone you for two reasons one the shadow people clone you and they keep this clone
So when and I'm gonna keep using this term over and over again. It's thought-bought 100s term. It's a catch-all term
I'm not saying that everyone who suffers from this does this but just because I'm gonna be quoting a lot because he says it's schizophrenic
He's constantly talking about people who are schizophrenic hear voices and I know not everyone who hears voices schizophrenic and vice versa
But he says when a schizophrenic hears a voice in their head
That's somebody else's clone
So think about that for a second extrapolate that for a second was really creepy that means that somebody who is hearing a voice in their head
Could be your voice
Could be you
Isn't that's creepy
Some dude who's dealing with some sort of mental issue
And he hears a voice telling him to do horrible things that could be your voice
Now I'm not saying this is true. I'm not saying it's true
But that's a creepy theory
That's one reason the other reason is that they
feed off of this clone
Emotionally and this clone of you is called the ego
And so this is how you worship the shadow people you have to go in front of a mirror and you remember good memories about yourself
You think good thoughts about yourself you build up your ego
And you look in the mirror and you talk yourself up you make this cloned version of you a
shining star a
Dazzling light in a world of darkness and it has a two-fold effect one the shadow people get more energy to eat from this clone to
absorb from this clone and
You start to become more like your ego
You start to become the superior clone the superior version and the shadow people reward you with this
Because you're giving them more energy. They will help you in your reality
Bending quest
Another interesting thing that thought bot points out is that almost every religion
reveres the prophet
But we are all prophets we all predict things every single day in our dreams
Second rule of the school of shadows well first one is it helps to smoke meth right it helps to smoke meth
So you can see the shadow people
- every day look in the mirror do this multiple times a day
Give yourself a big ego like literally talk about how great you are remember great things that you did
Imagine yourself being great. That's giving the shadow people more energy to feed off of
Three keep a dream journal
Because the more you write down the more dreams you remember and the more you write down you can start to make
connections between your dreams and
Reality you're actually seeing the future
Thought bot goes on to proclaim that all schizophrenics could be a prophet
The voices that they're hearing since they're us since their actual voices their egos that are spread out across the planet
They could be telling them your dreams that you had and it's their job to make sense of them
Just like any prophet it is their job to make sense of the vision
one of the quotes in
This is quote we believe in the voices
This is
Deeply unsettling stuff honestly you notice I'm cracking a bunch of jokes. I find this very very unsettling for a couple reasons
but
We'll get into this
I want to get into a little bit more, but yeah, I find this deep deep stuff deeply unsettling
I think you can tell my tone has changed a bit. I definitely can tell as well
But let's let's talk about this real quick a thought bot 100 himself is currently creating a new heaven for us a new
Afterlife I guess I'm using the word heaven. He uses the word afterlife
He also proclaims that he slammed meth for two years slamming is where you're injecting it so that'll be interesting
It's always nice to know that the person in charge of our afterlife is a hardcore meth addict
This is highly dangerous stuff that he's messing with
It's highly dangerous and he's uncontested in this space
This is the equivalent of
One nation having a nuclear bomb. No, it's not even that this is the equivalent of
One drug addict having a nuclear bomb. I
Have never come across
Somebody trying somebody organizing a religion around worshiping shadow people
shadow people are
The X factor in this whole paranormal game
Like we can say maybe they're aliens. Maybe they're interdimensional. Maybe they're demons. Maybe they're
Ambivalent towards the whole thing. We don't know
They're the only X factor in the paranormal game
We know what the alien factions want. We know what the angels want. We know what the demons want
We know what the ghosts want. We know what the cryptids want
But we don't know what the shadow people want
They're like the mercenaries, you know what I mean like we don't know what their intent is
So that means that whoever figures it out first has an edge
And while everyone else is just kind of dismissing them or not not dismissing them
But as everyone else is just saying maybe they're this maybe they're that we have a meth addict a a
Self-proclaimed meth addict trying to disparage this guy. He says it himself
Worshiping these things and building a cult around worshiping these things
185 members now let's say 30% of them are in it for the lulz
They just thought it was a funny thing to add on to their subreddit. That's still over a hundred people
Who may be doing this and nobody else is
No one else is experimenting with this they're
Afterthoughts they're not part of the lore the mainstream. This is extrude. I am not joking
I think this is one of the most dangerous cults we've covered on this show and we've covered cults like the Leopard Society
That actually murders people
still
Deeply unsettling story deeply disturbing story when I talk about insanity week
This is the type of thing I'm talking about like the stories are more lighthearted than this
But this is insane and this is insanity that can actually affect us all building a new afterlife
From a guy who's been slamming meth for two years and you're like Jason
You don't really think he can do that
We don't know what the limitations are of the shadow people. We don't know we know nothing about them
We can't even agree what they are
You hear but you're knock on the wall you can go maybe that's a ghost maybe that's the plumbing
Da-da-da-da-da you can debate that but ghost in and of themselves we we for the most part you go they
Are trapped here. They didn't go under the light
They have something that they didn't finish those are small variations whether whether or not you go know they have to do this
Those are small variations, but we know that ghosts are human
We know that they're human spirits. We know that demons are fallen angels
Angels are messengers of God
These are all things that the lore
Says we know that Bigfoot is a cryptid that lives in these particular parts of the world
You can debate whether or not these things exist all day long, but they have an alignment
Shadow people don't and we've covered them so many times on this show
They are a loose cannon
They are a mercenary group and it is extremely dangerous that the people who are communicating with these things the most are the most
unstable of society and
If they succeed in this goal
If these things do work
It's bad for everybody
Outside of the realm of talking like outside of paranormal stuff
Does any of this stuff make sense? No, I'm not gonna be running through the streets of Casper, Wyoming
Getting people to shut down the school of shadows like outside of the realm of the paranormal
It's a group of a hundred plus people who are worshiping a what they perceive to be their God or their ruler
But when we talk about in paranormal when we're talking about this type of stuff
This is one of the most dangerous groups. I've ever come across
Because if they can actually alter reality they can get enough of them together and
Use group psychosis to bend the rules of the universe
Would we even know that it happened?
Because it's the rules of the universe
99.9% of us just kind of wake up each day and we know what the world was like before and we expect the world to continue like it was
And I'm not talking about geopolitical events. I'm talking about stuff like gravity or the fact that care bears aren't real
But if there was a shift like this
It wouldn't be like the Mandela effect where people go
I remember there was a cornucopia on fruit of the loom you'd wake up
Your doctor would be a care bear and you wouldn't even think twice about it
You'd be like dr. Hugs a lot sure is good with my carpal tunnel syndrome
But even that would be nothing compared to an afterlife
crafted
by a man who suffers from meth psychosis and
afterlife the rest of eternity
Trapped in a reality made by a man who injects toxins into his bloodstream
for fun
We may wake up tomorrow in a new reality a new dimension
Ruled over by mad men who have now ascended to become insane gods a
World inhabited by shadow people. We are simply food sources for them
They feed off of our light
They feed off of our hope and
When those are gone they feed off of our fear our
anger or
sorrow
This is the new reality this is the world that the school of shadows prophesied
It is the one they crafted it is the one they made it is the one we all now exist in
And it is one that we can never escape from
We called them crazy
We laughed at them
But in the end
They succeeded where we failed
Their gods came and showed themselves to the world and while the rest of humanity
ignored them
The school of shadows worshipped them
Their reward was total power our
Punishment was unending pain
I
Did a radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also do this up at facebook.com/deadravoradio
Twitter is @deadravoradio
Dead rapper radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
*Music*