Hey Ghouls and guys, do you like to get spooky and stay spooky?
Then check out our podcast, The Golden Ghouls.
Each week we talk about our favorite things, ghosts and the paranormal.
Sound like a good time?
Then give us a listen on iTunes, Spotify, Stitcher or wherever you get your podcasts.
Goodbye.
Is Ted Bundy's ghost still haunting us today?
And they thought he was an urban legend until he asked to feel their muscles.
Today on Dead Rapper Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rapper Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
This is the official start of season two.
We're back.
Took a little week long break.
It was weird coming back.
You know, I've really only done this show for about two months, but it became such a
routine for me.
So for me not to record for a week, it was odd.
It was, it took me a while to get back on the mic, but I'm glad that I'm back here.
Back on my keto diet, that'll actually play a little bit into our next story.
But first off, our first story is going to be...
Okay, so this story, it took me down some rabbit holes and it made me realize something
a lot about just paranormal research in general and the way that we approach these things.
And this story is going to be, is Ted Bundy's ghost still haunting us?
Now I came across this because I was looking for stuff on killer ghosts.
And of course, when you type in killer ghosts, I got results for ghosts of serial killers.
Oh, that's great.
That's actually probably more interesting than ghosts you kill people.
I came across an article in a website, psychology today is the website.
It's a very reputable website.
It's not a fringe website.
It's not a goofy news website like the Daily Star or anything like that.
Had an interesting article about the ghost of Ted Bundy and it profiles these different
stories.
Now the author of this article wrote a book also called "Blooding Ghosts".
It's about supernatural events or ghosts, paranormal events at crime scenes.
Sounds very fascinating.
I've always wondered how much police officers and EMTs and things like that encounter a
ghost.
It's probably not a lot, but you figure, these are people who are constantly dealing with
tragic situations.
They're out in remote areas late at night.
I've been watching a lot of Twin Peaks lately, but even before Twin Peaks, actually, no,
maybe the first Twin Peaks when it was being aired on CBS, it may have given me that idea.
But how often do the police and the FBI and EMTs and stuff?
What if you were a fireman and you ran into a haunted house?
That actually is a pretty good idea for a movie.
Fire ghost.
Fahrenheit 450 ghost?
I don't know.
I'll figure that one out.
But anyways, so, okay, so I'm off traffic.
Okay, Ted Bundy's ghost.
So the Psychology Today article, it's an interesting article and it talks about sightings of Ted
Bundy's ghost.
Now the first thing is, they talk about, so at the prison where Ted Bundy was executed,
there's guard, he's anonymous, he didn't want his name revealed because obviously the guards
are going to feel that they are going to be harassed and made fun of and stuff like that.
But anyways, as guard said that other guards at the prison have seen Ted Bundy's ghost
sitting in the electric chair.
This is about 2001 when this story was told.
But anyways, so, which sounds terrifying, an execution room isn't the most calm place
anyways.
It's not a place like, oh, I just need to get away from the guys, I want to eat my
break on by myself and I want to be bugged.
I'm going to go in the execution room, eat a sandwich.
So he says that in the execution chamber where, I keep wanting to say Bill Cosby, where the
execution chamber where Ted Bundy was electrocuted to death, the guards have stated that they
have seen his ghost sitting in the electric chair, terrifying.
And then he turns to them with what is known as a knowing smile.
And then he would say, oh no, no, he would say anything then, he would just turn and
smile and then disappear.
But he was also seen in other parts of his, of the prison, specifically his holding cell
on death row.
And he would say, well, I beat all of you, didn't I?
And then he fade away.
You know, the terrifying things, I personally think serial killers are very gauche.
I think it's tacky.
I think it's one of the tackiest crimes possible.
I'll do another episode on that.
But anyways, so this guy is the serial killer, blah, blah, blah.
His ghost is popping around.
And it got to the point where the guard said, the warden of the prison said, if anyone ever
repeats this story, you're fired.
I'm tired of hearing about Ted Bundy's ghost.
The Psychology Today article goes on to say that mediums have said that they've channeled
him, mediums have said, or he's been spotted on the porch of a home that he rented out
in Tallahassee.
The Psychology Today actually had a really, even more creepy segment about Ted Bundy's
ghost.
And he went to University of Puget Sound.
Puget, Puget, Puget, Puget.
I think it's Puget.
University of, I don't remember how I said it, University of Puget Sound.
Anyways, the school newspaper there, the Puget Sound Trail, did an article saying that students
there have seen his ghost so regularly, they actually gave him a nickname, Teddy the Friendly
Ghost.
And the reason why they call him Teddy the Friendly Ghost is because apparently he's
quite friendly.
He will walk young co-eds across campus, which is terrifying, but he can't do anything to
him.
And the co-eds are saying, "Oh, you know, it's just kind of a pleasing presence to have
somebody there with me."
And he's been spotted at parties, like dancing along to parties.
I'm just quoting the article.
And they ended up doing a Ouija board thing, Ouija ceremony, a Ouija board reading.
I don't know the exact terminology.
But anyways, and the message that came across was, "I cannot touch them, so many to kill,
and I cannot touch them.
It is my hell."
That's really creepy.
And actually that would be hell for a serial killer to be trapped in a form where all of
your pert, new bile, young, tasty victims can just walk by you and go, "Oh, Teddy,"
and you can't touch him, you can't interact with him.
That's how he exhibited his power.
Now he also had a huge obsession with pornography, and he figured being a ghost would actually
help that, because you could just fly to pornographic sets or just, I guess, hang out in girls'
rooms really if you're a horny ghost.
Here's the thing.
Everything in this article is complete nonsense.
Absolutely.
And I read this article and I thought, "Wow, this is really, really creepy."
And I had the story ready to go.
I was ready to move on it.
And something inside of me said, "You know what?
Double check this.
Double check this story."
Because something didn't sit right with it.
And what it was specifically was seeing where Bundy was partying with the kids at the school.
That's really what clued me in that this was a fake story.
Okay, so this was the actual quote.
This is really what's -- and I read this quote multiple times and I thought it was weird,
but because it was sourced in the psychology today article, I just let it pass and then
I decided to finally look into it a little bit more.
I'm going to read you the quote first.
The quote is, "And this is from the Puget Sound Trail article."
Bundy's ghost is not just popular with girls, but with guys as well.
"He's a crazy guy to party with, especially if there are girls dancing," said junior
Kyle Verklin at an off-campus party that was shut down for noise complaints and paranormal
activity.
"T Bundy can tear the dance floor up.
Something about seeing those girls bump and grind made him go crazy.
Things down the best thing I've ever seen at a UPS party."
I read it the first time.
I thought it was weird that the party was shut down for paranormal activity.
The fact that he was called T Bundy.
The fact that there was this ghost that said Bundy -- but I let it go.
I continued to prep this story.
I came across it again.
I read that it was reading the article again.
I still let it go.
Before I decided to start recording this, I just needed to check something out.
It is in the Puget Sound Trail school newspaper in a section called Combat Zone, which is
surprise surprise, a parody/comedy part of the student newspaper.
This is completely made up.
This is the part that contained the Ouija board.
It never happened.
They never called him Ted the Friendly Ghost.
He never walks girls across campus.
He definitely was never bumping and grinding with girls as T Bundy and a party was not
shut down due to paranormal activity.
Once I eliminated half the article, I went back to the story of the guard in the prison
prison.
I researched that.
We never know the name of the guard, which is fine.
I understand people want to be anonymous, but we never know the name of the reporter
who initially told the story to.
We never know the name of the newspaper that published the article.
We never know the name of the warden who said you can't talk about Ted Bundy's ghost.
There is no sourcing for this.
And every time I found a reference to the story of the warden, they all linked back
to the Psychology Today website.
It's an urban legend that somebody told and the Psychology Today reported it.
The reason why this is important, the reason why I still wanted to go ahead with the story
was that as fans of paranormal stuff, I want to believe in this stuff.
And I do believe in this stuff.
I've had personal experiences.
I've seen stuff that makes me believe in this stuff.
So when I come across these articles, and I think when most people who are fans of this
stuff come across these articles, our willingness to believe overrides our logic sometimes.
And I think it's important for us to then step back and go, "Let's get a little more
info on this."
Just because a legitimate website reports it, doesn't mean it's legitimate.
But you'll notice this a lot.
You'll hear an interesting story, and if you start to look into it, you realize that there's
nothing behind it.
Typical thing, regular rule in journalism, who, what, when, where, why, how.
Now I know in paranormal stories, you're never going to get the how or the why unless it's
provably fake.
The why is usually money or attention, and the how is wires and a sheet and a flashlight.
A lot of times people want to rename anonymous, and I get that.
But we need to have when, we need to have where, we need to have more details.
I understand the person want to stay anonymous, but who wrote the article initially about
this?
This was a paper in Florida, a newspaper in Florida, a journalist in Florida, who, it's
made up, and it's frustrating because I want to read these stories, and I want them to
have some credibility because I want to believe in this stuff.
I did find an interesting story related to this, and this kind of shows the other side
of this argument that I'm making.
There is a contractor who says that he worked on the house that Ted Money grew up in and
it's haunted.
This is this contractor.
This article is in the News Tribune.
It's a Washington paper.
This contractor is saying, "I went to this house.
My name is Casey Clopton.
I was the contractor.
This started in September of the year 2017, fairly recent.
We're seeing things like drawers being opened, when they shouldn't have been open.
Electronic devices failing, finding messages like leave and help me written in the sawdust
on the ground.
This is a young girl over, and she doesn't want to be there.
Other people have stopped by.
They didn't want to be there."
He didn't know it was Ted Money's home.
He got two priests to come in to bless the place, and he wrote Bible verses on the walls,
and then he just finished his job as quickly as he could.
He said it was both scary and neat, and that's the story.
Now it's possible, obviously, he's making it up, and it's also possible that he could
not be making it up, but things like going into a house and your phone dying.
Sex do die.
Kids don't want to be places they don't want to be in general.
Some places just have a creepy vibe, and you could heighten the otherwise normally mundane
things because they kind of stack on top of each other, and it doesn't mean that it's
haunted.
So there's the possibility it's haunted, the possibility he's making it up, or the possibility
that it's not haunted, he's not making it up.
There's just a series of odd coincidences that were happening in order.
Leave and help me, someone could have wrote that, a ghost could have wrote that, he could
be making it up.
I don't know, but you see the difference in these two articles.
One has far more facts about it.
It's less compelling and less scary.
It's just the guy saying, "I worked in a haunted house for a couple months, and it was creepy."
The creepiest thing was I saw Leave written in the sawdust.
The other one has direct communication with Ted Bundy, and the prison guards interacting
with Ted Bundy.
Generally as listeners, as readers, we give more weight to people in official positions.
So a contractor saying he saw a ghost, we weigh differently than if a prison guard said
that he saw a ghost.
Same thing if someone sees a UFO versus a pilot sees a UFO, we weigh those things different.
I'm more apt to believe the Casey Clopton story, the contractor story.
Actually, no, let's rephrase it.
I'm a thousand times more likely to believe that story from that guy that I've never
met than I am to believe the Psychology Today article because it's provably false.
But it's funny because I was ready to believe both of them equally, and actually I think
I was ready to believe the Psychology Today article more because it was a reputable website.
So you know, the key thing here is that we as fans of this, as researchers of this, really
need to do our due diligence.
We need to be willing to call out things that are fake or we believe are fake.
There's nothing wrong with that.
There may be less fun.
There's always that old saying, you'll never sell a million books about UFOs if you say
UFOs are fake, and that's true.
But I think there's enough real UFO stories out there and enough real ghost stories out.
There are enough real conspiracy stories out there and they might not be as sexy as the
made up ones, but because they are real and because they have enough to go on that someone
can research them years later, they are far more fascinating than Ted Bundy's ghost dancing
at a party.
The next story we're going to do is fascinating to me.
I've said this multiple times.
I'm a big fan of urban legends.
I'm a big fan of local legends.
This is a story of an urban legend, a man that people in the area thought was fake until
they met him.
And more importantly, until he appeared in court.
So this story takes place in Northwest England in the early 2000s.
Now when I was growing up, not in Northwest England, but just for an aside, when I was
growing up, there was an Alameda, which is in the Bay Area, there was a homeless man named
Joe Trombone.
And Joe Trombone was this crazy homeless man who all the teenagers saw.
I was too young.
I was around 11 or 12 at the time.
They all saw him and what made Joe Trombone interesting is that when you saw him, if
you said, "Hey, Joe Trombone, bust a rhyme," he would start rapping on the spot, freestyling
the most insane lyrics possible about all sorts of stuff.
Now, being able to make rhymes, like disorganize rhyming is a sign, is a side effect of schizophrenia
because you're just the way your brain is wired.
So if you saw him on the bus, you just say, "Yo, Joe Trombone, you know, drop a flow,"
and he would just go.
He would just start rapping.
Now, I always wanted to meet him, never did.
He's a local legend.
So I've always liked those stories of those people in certain areas because you're never
going to meet him.
You're across the globe.
And sometimes you never even meet him when you're in this city.
So in Northwest England, which is a big geographical area, obviously, in the early 2000s, there
was a guy known in the area as Purple Aki.
So let's get the meaning of the name out of the way right now.
Purple Aki came about because he was considered so black, he was purple.
He was a black dude, and they considered him so black, he was purple.
His real name was Aukenwale Arobike, people in town called him Purple Aki.
Yes, that's a very, very racist term.
He's actually not like, when they said that, I was like, "Oh dude, this guy must be like
super black."
He looks like Coach from Left 4 Dead 2.
But I guess in that area where they weren't used to seeing black people, he seemed super
black.
And when I'm first reading about him, I'm like, "This guy's kind of a tragic figure.
He's this big, giant black dude.
He's six foot five and three hundred and ten pounds.
He's living in England."
People are referring to him as Purple Aki.
As his legend grows, a restaurant started a Purple Teriyaki burger.
His name, Purple Aki, was used in court documents.
Nowadays, he's like, "I just want to be left alone, mate.
Why you guys?"
Because people will follow him around with YouTube cameras and be like, "Hey, Purple
Aki, Purple Aki."
He's like, "Hey, I just want to be left alone."
So your heart kind of goes out for this guy.
People are saying racist things right to his face.
People are stalking him.
Then you just slightly, slightly look into the story, just a little bit more.
This guy is, all sympathy goes out the window.
All sympathy for this guy goes out the window.
No, you shouldn't be calling him that.
For the rest of the episode, we're going to refer to him as Aki unless I'm specifically
quoting something.
So you shouldn't be referring him as that name, especially in court documents, and that
comes into play later.
But anyway, so Aki, his claim to fame was, like I said, he was six foot five.
He was three hundred and ten pounds.
He was a bodybuilder.
What he would do, what he was known for, and what he admits doing is walk
in up to young fit men, young muscular men, many took care of their bodies and things
like that.
And he would ask, "Oh man, oh mate, look at your muscles, mate.
Can I feel them?
Can I feel your muscles?"
And you'd be like, "Uh..."
And this guy was so big and so imposing, they'd be like, "Yeah, sure, feel my muscles.
All right, mate, let me feel them.
Oi, strong."
You then take out measuring tape and measure your muscles.
And you're like, "Okay, that guy seems a little mentally ill."
But sometimes he would walk up to someone and go, "All right, mate, can I feel your
muscles?"
And there would be like, "Uh..."
And he'd be like, "How's your cousin doing?
I know he goes to that school across the street and I know where you live.
Can I feel your muscles?"
He was stalking these guys too.
He kept detailed records of these men, where they lived, where family members lived, their
father's place of work, and he would write down the measurements of the guys.
He had a stalking guide.
He was in this poor, sad sap who was walking around England.
You know, just, he was a stalker.
He was a through and through stalker who used his size and his, first, wait, I just realized
this, how does a six foot five guy stalk you?
Does he dress like a bush?
How hard would it be to spot this giant walking through your front yard?
But anyways, he stalked people, he threatened people, one family had to go into witness
protection.
He actually caught a manslaughter charge because this young man, I think it was like 15 or
16, was petrified of Aki.
He had to run with him before, get a run with this guy before, where he felt intimidated
to let Aki touch his muscles.
A time later, he was at the train station, Aki showed up.
The kid terrified of what was going to happen because there was also urban legends that
he would cut you open or rape you and stuff like that.
None of that's ever been proven, but he was definitely an intimidating person who stalked
people.
Anyways, this young kid is terrified of Aki.
He runs across the railroad tracks, steps on a live-walt line, you know, like the third
rail, electrocuted, dies.
They arrested Aki for manslaughter.
He was found guilty.
The one on appeal for two reasons.
One was he said, he usually defended himself in court.
I'm not for sure if he defended himself on this account, but he said all I was doing
was standing there.
There was no one else to dispute that.
All I was doing was standing there.
And in the court documents, they refer to him as purple Aki.
So he goes, "This is obviously racism against me."
They were using a racist slang word.
The police are using a racist slang word.
That's why they're coming down on me so much.
He actually won on appeal, did not get the manslaughter charged, and won 35,000 pounds
or dollars or 35,000 of some currency for that.
That aside, he was in and out of jail.
He was constantly being arrested for harassment, for grabbing people's muscles, for basically
like stuff like intimidation.
So a quick tip about crime in general.
I'm walking down the street and there is somebody who's much smaller than me and I say, "Nice
shoes, can I have them?"
I can be charged with intimidation or theft.
Because the implication isn't, "Nice shoes, can I buy them off you?"
The implication is, "Nice shoes, give them to me or I will beat you up."
That is generally what happens when you're in jail or prison.
They just go, "Hey, nice shoes, can I have them?
Hey, do you mind if I eat the rest of your food?"
You have the option of saying no, but you understand the implications if you say no.
But your defense would be like, "All I told him is he had nice shoes and he gave them
to me."
That doesn't fly.
So he could say, "Well, I just walked up and said, 'Can I feel your muscles?'
And he let me feel his muscles."
But the other person, the victim, is going to say, "Yeah, because he was a giant and
I knew his reputation and I knew he was stalking people."
So anyways, he's in and out of jail.
He eventually gets because the court believes that all of this stuff about feeling, "Oh,
I haven't even gotten to the upside down squat thing."
So just when you're like, "Oh, he's just feeling muscles.
He's just measuring muscles.
Oh, he's just hiding in people's bushes and finding out where their nephew lives."
There's no big deal, Jason.
The physical, let's put this, I want you to imagine yourself in this position.
Whatever physical fitness level you're at.
Let's put yourself in the streets of Northwest England.
Aki comes up to you and says, "Hey, I love your muscles.
Do you want to do an upside down squat?"
You're like, "What's that?"
Never heard of that before.
So normally a squat is you just squat.
You stand up straight and you sit down in the air.
That's probably the best way to explain it on a podcast.
You sit down so your thighs are horizontal to the ground and then you stand back up.
Squat basic.
Everyone does them.
Then you have the squats where someone hangs off your back.
So you get some young hot chick at the gym to wrap her arms and legs around you and you
do a squat.
It adds another 110 pounds to your lift.
An upside down squat is where Aki climbs on your back.
So now you have 310 pounds and a six foot five guy on your back, but he's doing it upside
down.
So his face is in your butt and his dick is pressed against your neck and you're squatting.
Whether or not you say, "Ah, these victims, you know, they should just deal with it."
Some guy feels their muscles, it's no crime.
Even having a dude's giant dick on the back of your neck as you're squatting in public
because he knows where your nephew lives.
Anyways, the courts could never prove that he was doing this for sexual gratification,
which he probably was, but they hit him with a SOPA order.
SOPA is a sexual offender protection order and they said, "It's basically like a thing.
You know, we have them in America where we're like, you can't live within 100 yards of a
school or you can't interact with children."
This order was a judge said, "You can never, ever touch another man's muscles.
You can't ask for it and you can't do it."
And he violated that order multiple times.
He was going other places, he had the order on him.
He would feel someone's muscles, they would call the cops, the cops, that's all they need
to know.
They'd pick him up, throw him in jail.
Happened multiple times.
He didn't care.
And then all of it got removed because his defense that this was a racist witch hunt was
eventually believed the lifetime ban is removed.
He no longer is able to be arrested on the spot for feeling someone's muscles unless the
person is truly saying, "No, I was victimized" and stuff like that because the police had
to use that stupid nickname in the police report.
He shouldn't have done that.
They hadn't.
He probably would have been in jail for the manslaughter charge.
He would definitely still have a SOPA order.
As of today if you are a fit young man walking the streets in Northwest England, there is
a chance that you will run into Aki and he will ask to feel your muscles.
And as much as I would like to run into a urban legend, I don't think I could do an
upside down squat.
Even with all my keto, I don't think I'm in shape enough for him.
But however, maybe someday, maybe some, I don't, I'm glad that it's like I'm looking
forward to that.
But no, no.
So Aki, I don't want to meet you.
I don't care how fit I am.
You need to stop doing this stuff.
Nowadays, there's a lot of YouTube videos of people stalking him and him being like,
"Go away, mate, go away.
I just want to live my life."
And part of you, like the initial part of you goes, "Wow, they're picking on that guy."
But then when you remember all of the stuff he's done to other people, you realize this
is just dessert.
You can't really stalk people when you're famous in an entire region.
And he's not going to be left alone.
He is a meme.
He went from being an urban legend because people didn't believe he existed.
The story was so absurd.
One bodybuilder would tell another bodybuilder and they'd be like, "That's absurd."
And then they would run into Aki and the legend grew.
And then eventually when he got arrested, it was proven that this guy actually existed.
And now people hold up signs at soccer games.
And like I said, the restaurant has the Purple Teriyaki burger.
And he's well known.
He seeded a documentary on him and he flipped out about that as well.
So you got your just desserts, bro.
You got your just desserts and they're loaded for a little carbs and it's totally going
to ruin your cut.
But this is what happens when you stalk people and ask to feel their muscles.
I wonder what would happen if someone who was like not super muscular but was like working
really hard doing go mad, drinking a gallon of milk a day, is walking with their super
fit buddy and Aki is like, "I just talked to your buddy."
I wonder if that would make you like go to the gym and want to hit it more because you
know what he's doing or would you just be like, "I think I'm good here.
I think this is the body that I want.
The body that makes me invisible to a six foot five giant."
Well, everyone, that is basically season two, the first episode of season two of Dead Rabbit
Radio.
We're going to keep doing this.
I'm having a lot of fun doing it and I'm getting a lot of great feedback from you guys as well.
I featured your promo for another podcast at the beginning.
We're going to keep doing stuff like that because I like celebrating other podcasts
that kind of have the same vibe as us.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadratveradio.
You can hit us up on Twitter @jasonocarpenter.
We also have our YouTube channel, which is Dead Rabbit Radio.
We have, it's basically the same thing as the podcast.
We're going to be rolling out some new stuff there though soon.
I'm going to let you know what's going on with that.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it to have Red
Blue Dice.
[Music]