Hey everyone, this is Jason Carpenter, the host of Dead Rabbit Radio, and the episode you're about to listen to is
our Thanksgiving live stream episode. It is a full episode. It has three really cool stories.
It is a full episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. The reason why it's so long is afterwards we did a
about an hour and a half long answer and question, or is it a question and answer session?
No, I give the answers and then you're like, "Whoa, how did you know what my question was gonna be?"
So this is a full episode of Dead Rabbit Radio with a bunch of bonus content.
I hope you guys enjoy and I hope you guys had an awesome Thanksgiving.
A contest in the Philippines is supposed to bring joy to the country and instead it brings deadly riots.
A man driving his car down the road
has a close encounter of the
turned kind, because like the cars are turning, stuff like that.
And then
we travel
to the world of sci-fi.
Is it possible that there really is a pair of glasses out there
that will allow you to see aliens on Earth today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day, too.
I hope you guys are having an awesome Thanksgiving.
The way I think we're gonna do this segment is I'm going to go over the story, then
maybe take a little break and look at your comments and things like that. Hey Peter.
And we will go from there. We'll just kind of be flexible with it. But first off,
let us go ahead. I didn't have someone picked out to fly anything in this. Hey, Fehu.
So we're just all gonna hop on board. We got no pilot. It's totally autopilot. This time should have installed this.
Let's hop on board the
Dead Rabbit Rowboat. We are headed out to the Philippines.
We're rowing. We're rowing and stuff like that. My back's all hurting. So I'm assuming you guys are actually rowing.
I'm just gonna sit back drinking some sparkly and ice caffeine.
Mmm. That's one thing that gets edited out of the podcast is my constant drinking of stuff.
Constant drinking of stuff. Hey, comfy.
So
We're going to the Philippines. The year is 1992.
And PepsiCo in the Philippines has a problem. They're looking at their spreadsheets. They're looking at all of their stuff.
And they go,
This is shocking actually. I didn't know a major company could be this sucky.
Pepsi only covered
4% of the market share in the Philippines, which is nothing.
I probably have 4% of the market share in the Philippines and I don't even make soft drinks.
So
they were like, okay, this guy in Oregon makes more money than we do in the Philippines.
Let's decide to have a lottery. They did this in South America and it was a huge hit.
So they go, let's do it in the Philippines, you know, we're over there.
So they have this thing that if you bought a Pepsi
a 7up or a Miranda drink, I'm assuming that's some sort of drink, not just a person named Miranda who works at PepsiCo.
On the caps, they had a three-digit number from 001 to 999.
And it's a lottery basically. We've all done this. I mean, uh, Coca-Cola. I remember I used to have this
scam. Don't tell anyone. It's probably past the statute limit. It's probably not even a crime now that I think of it.
I used to
live off of free Coca-Cola's. What's up, Stuart? I used to fall off of clean free Coca-Cola's
and they had a thing where now they have QR codes and see what things you got to enter into the computer.
Thank you, Rampart. Really, really appreciate that. That is awesome.
Um,
I used to they had a little thing that was a free Coca-Cola and I was super poor at the time
and I would
Go to the store and I would just look I tilt them. I tilt them somehow I evolved like they were designed not to do that
Thank you, Wesley. They were designed not to do that
You should just have to be able to see but somehow is able to figure it out
Um, so basically this is what is going on there except without all the rampant fraud
except without me trying to break the system
Now in the Philippines
They use the peso and you could win anywhere from 100 pesos. So you buy us Miranda
which historical hiker just said is like an orange drink
You can buy a Miranda drink
And you could win 100 pesos which is about four dollars
Now the average daily wage in the Philippines at the time was about four dollars. There was 118 pesos
so imagine if you could buy a drink and
You'd earn a day's wage. That's huge, right?
But that was just one of the lower in prices
The number the number one prize was one million pesos
And there'd be a 40 000 in us cash at the time
Which was the equivalent to 23 years of work
so of course
Everyone was buying these drinks. Could you imagine buying a drink? I mean even just get one
One day off basically but to get 23 years worth of days off for buying a Pepsi
And if you lose you still have a delicious Pepsi
Their market share went from 4 to 25 percent
They didn't corner the market, but they had a corner of the market. Which is just as good, right? It's not as great, but it's pretty good
May 2nd 1992
Wait, let me back up. This is where I would do a cut
So the way that the way that the price was done
Was that they had them made it a factory. It was super secure. They had them made it a factory
And you had a three digit code and then a security confirmation code to keep counterfeiting down
You would be able to match up that bottle with that security code
May 2nd 1992 the daily number is announced. It is 349. So check your check your bottle caps guys
Check your Pepsi and your Miranda bottle caps if you have one
The number is 349 it's announced on the news. It's a huge deal in this country
but
There was a computer that number wasn't supposed to be
That well it was supposed to be 349, but what happened was there was a computer error at the factory
So more than two caps were listed with 349
A total of 800,000 caps
Were worth a million pesos
800,000 people were about to earn 23 years
Of never having to work never having to work for 23 years
But of course that's that's not what
It's not what was it was that happened Pepsi it set aside two million dollars for this competition because of this screw up
They were on the hook for 32 billion bucks
Now Pepsi is a big company. I don't think they can take a 32. I don't think they can I don't know many companies
That could take a 32 billion dollar hit
So they immediately were like
Hey guys, sorry, but so sorry about making you think that your life was changed
There's only actually two winners out there
We have the security codes. Nobody else can win this money
So
What do you expect would happen in this
situation
You figure people would be upset. That's true
You figure people first off they all rent to the Pepsi co-plants to redeem their caps and that's when they're like no
I'm sorry. Sorry, dude. We don't have any money here as trucks full of pepsis are constantly going out
They came to the plants. They weren't getting their paid the money. The Pepsi came out and said listen
We don't we're not gonna we're not gonna cover any of this stuff
Tell you what though. Tell you what to make it up for you. We will give you 18 dollars per cap
So that's still a good week's worth of labor
Half the people said that's fine. Like they got that. It was a total error. Half the group said we'll take the 18 bucks
We're not going to get anything else
The other half of the people
Form the 349 alliance, which actually sounds pretty badass honestly 349 alliance
Now they didn't take their 18 dollars. They think that they are deserved
One million pesos so they begin protesting. Oh pay so pay so they're walking through the street
They're walking through the street. They're walking into banks. They're all pay so they're like, yeah, we know that's our currency
Why do you keep yelling that they're walking on the street? They start protesting outside of pepsi factories pay so
They probably had a catchier slogan than that
And these people are like, what does that even mean? You're just saying what we use to buy stuff
They start protesting that doesn't work. They call for a boycott of pepsi
That doesn't work. So then it just it just remember this all started with with soda caps
They begin setting pepsi trucks on fire
So now they're hurting they're hurting what they truly love. I'm sure most of them were addicted to
Pepsi at this point pepsi trucks are driving down the street people are setting them on fire
they're breaking into parking lots they're destroying the trucks and then that's not even the top thing
And then one day a couple people were at a pepsi warehouse typing
Doing stuff
Selling pepsi out of the back of the warehouse. They're black market pepsi salesman a grenade comes through the window
kills three people
So now everyone's like, okay, let's we might want to rethink this 349 alliance thing
There were rumors that pepsi had actually hired
Agitators like pepsi there was a rumor that pepsi got some south american mercenaries to come and be like
Hey, we really need this protest to end. Would you mind setting our trucks on fire?
And lobbing grenades
Through our windows south american mercenaries like yeah, that's what we do. It's a wednesday. That's what we always do
Then to make matters even worse
There was a pepsi truck driving down the road one day
And someone came up alongside of it and threw grenade
into the pepsi truck
and the explosion
Killed a mother and her child nearby
So
That's
That's pretty rough at this point public tide was turning. I think probably the first grenade attack people were already like
I don't know about this whole 349 alliance thing that it killed us three guys at the pepsi warehouse
but at this point
Pretty much all the protests stopped all the attacks stopped
The court cases though continued and eventually
Pepsi goes listen, we're so sorry about that. We'll offer you
$380
And then most of the people said it will take the $380 way more than 18
It's way less than 40 000
But you know again, you probably threw a grenade at someone
You're just hoping to get some money to get out of the country
And then a couple of them hold out for even more money
Supreme court the supreme court of philippines had to step in and say
You don't deserve anything you you get zero money. You should have just taken the 18 dollars or the
380 bucks. There was no way you were going to get 40 000 dollars as far as I can tell
I mean again, this story just happened back in 1992. Thanks for the thanks for the support steward
This story just happened back in 1992 as far as I can tell no one was ever prosecuted, you know for like throwing throwing grenades into stuff
You know the big crimes. It's one thing. Listen setting Pepsi trucks on fire is still like a crime
It's still technically a crime, but when you're throwing grenades at trucks because you didn't get 40 000 dollars
You might want to reevaluate your life decisions
However, you also have to think that Pepsi probably should have done something more on the outset
To take care of this whole situation. So that is just another weird
Is this a thing now another this is one of those weird wacky stories that just kind of been lost to time
I had never heard about this before people's lives are actually affected
And i'm actually now that I say it I wonder what happened to the two people who had the winning lid
Did they ever get there? They were the ones throwing their grenades. They got their 40 000 dollars
And they're like the fire rises brothers. They use all their money to buy grenades
I thought that was a weird story. I just saw that the other day. I don't even remember how oh actually I do know how it came across it
I saw it on reddit. So I wanted to give a shout out to the real big jc 22
for posting that in uh reddit. So I really really appreciate that
And it is
Burn i'm gonna open a window real quick. Let me know if this changes the
um
The audio quality because i'm wearing this and I got my pajama pants on i'm wearing this shirt
Okay, i'm back
Take a little segue real quick if you don't mind I posted this on my twitter yesterday
It's something really weird was happening yesterday something really weird. Hey, nicole
Citrus Heights dudes citrus heights in the house
I I came across something weird yesterday. I was watching. I don't remember what I was watching on youtube something dumb
Probably I think I was just wasting time
I saw a commercial it kind of like struck me. I was like, uh, it was a commercial for the rise of skywalker
And it said coming soon this film has not yet been rated and I was like what didn't that movie come out last year
Now because I obviously am into like the paranormal
And so like that I immediately thought
I immediately checked my calendar. I was like
Did I travel back in time? Did I go back in time?
Now I didn't as
far as I know
But it popped up and first I was thinking because I think I was watching
Um read a letter media earlier. They were doing something about the force awakens
So I was like maybe that triggered some sort of algorithm
for the rest of the night
I got pretty much two ads
Playing back to back now to get ads for like I don't know. I this gets a friend a ad pops up
Still that's always weird
I would get ads for the rise of skywalker coming soon in uh christmas
Which again came out in 2019 last year and every time that commercial came on I looked down at my little digital clock on my computer
I was like
still 2020 right
I'd get commercials for that
The other commercial I got was
For a model car
A model no joke. No, this is so weird and again, I don't
Not a big believer in synchronicity and stuff like that, but
I get a commercial for the model car of the delorean
From back to the future. No, just the loren. I should have added that far as I go. It's the lorian. It was actually it was actually a
Like back to the future time machine and melk just said the blu ray release. That's what I thought as well
But that's been out for a while
and again, it said
Thank you, sk really really appreciate it again. It would say this movie has not yet been rated
It was they were running the ads that they ran
this time last year so
one
YouTube is ripping off disney. They're charging them. This could be happening all over the world
And they're charging disney to run ads that disney doesn't even knows running
So they're getting like an extra million dollars two
We're about to time travel basically like right now the
Was a thing
Was a thing going on the veil is getting thinner and thinner and we're all about to go back in time
Or or actually there's a thousand other rational explanations, but I remember thinking I remember when I first
That's that that's that I remember the first time I took more than one time the first time I thought did I go back in time?
And then it goes on and on and I kept doing it throughout the night
And then my first thing was like if I went back to the year 2019
My first thought was
I don't want to have to record all those episodes again
Like that would be super weird to have done all that work and then have to do more work on it
So different time zones collapsing the uh, that was bonkleman's comment. Yeah, I would
But then I figured you know what I would do obviously you would warn people about the whole covid situation
You'd be like just running around everyone's gonna get sick everyone's gonna get sick in a couple months
But not really everyone just some people but everyone's going to be afraid they're gonna get sick and you're not really gonna know
what to do for the first
Uh, first 100 days. Yeah, sure Eric
shout out to Eric
and then um
Yeah, I would just be I I could probably save a bunch of lives
But then I'd have to like rerecord episodes. So that would be rough. That would be rough. So
rerecord episodes
rerecord episodes or
save
200,000 lives
Uh, I was hoping maybe I could go back in time and keep my files on my computer. That's how lazy I am
I don't mind going back in time, but do I get to keep the files on my computer?
So let's go ahead and move on to our next topic here. This one's a shorty
I haven't done a lot of stories from think about it docs.com lately
I've been doing a lot of stuff and I kind of want I really like that website
I hope you guys aren't getting tired of it. I think
subconsciously I knew I needed to take a break
but
um, yeah, I've
I really like that website
I like them because they're just kind of these short creepy stories
That we can look at
Um
And then to ask answer ryan's question real quick because he has to go take a shower
What's the hottest cryptid? I was thinking about that the other day that big booty reptilian that I covered
Last year. I was honestly sitting and I was thinking about
That you guys I don't remember the episode but there's an episode where I talk about falling in love with a big booty
Reptilian alien so that would be that one and thank you again steward for keeping the spirits up in the chat
Let's go ahead and hop in the dead rabbit durgable
We are going to head on out. We're leaving behind the Philippines. We're saying goodbye
We're drinking a bunch of coca-cola because they didn't honor their sweets
And I'm have a bunch of bottle caps in my hands of 349 on them
I'm throwing them out into the people below everyone get rich but no grenades no grenades
We're flying away in the dead rabbit durgable
Durgable is flying over the pacific ocean
I think I think that's easy's way to get back
We're headed out to seattle washington
The year is 1997 wait
The year is 1972 had a little
Little brain. It's the time travel. It's it's the veil getting smaller the year is 1972. We're in seattle washington
We are walking down the street
I don't all know why I always put myself into these scenarios and then I have to like go. Oh never mind never mind
We're not walking on the street
Hold on a second
Gonna take another drink
We're walking on the street and we see a car
There's a bunch of car. We're not straight. There's a bunch of cars. There's a bunch of cars. This isn't a norm
This isn't no abnormal
Sorry, my god light headed there for a second. Hey, zapp zapp
I think I have a problem because I stare at myself while i'm talking
And it actually hurts my eyeballs
It like makes you dizzy when you do that like I feel a little a little light headed. Okay
One second to recalibrate. I'm gonna do a little stretching
I'm gonna
Burp burp away from the my cave elvet
Sorry guys
Yeah, it was weird. I
I've had that sensation before doing the life's
I've had that sensation before doing the life's okay
We ready? Yeah, we're ready. Yeah, it's just weird. Okay
Hey cantilians
The year is 1972. We're in seattle washington. It's a sunny afternoon day
There's a man driving
Let's do it. Yeah, I'm fine. There's a man driving home to interview
And you know, he's probably a pretty good
Interview whether or not he got the job, but we'll just assume that he did
Can there it okay considering what's about to happen?
His car comes and it stops in an intersection
He's just sitting there cars idling listening to some 1972 music
He's waiting for
The light to change and then he says
He becomes aware of a sensation to his left
So he's sitting in this car
And he can sense something on the left hand side
Can tell something staring at him he can tell something is intently staring at him
He says he turns to his left and he sees what he calls an old junker car
a beat-up piece of garbage
If he wasn't that bad, maybe they weren't driving the jason jelapi, but it was a beat-up car
And he looks and he says what he sees
Is a woman
Sure enough staring at him
from that car
She said
He said
She had an exceptionally round head large round head
Not so much like great alien
But he almost said that it was like
super obese
Like just just
You're just saying like this big old chick was chair staring at him. Well, it's a little more than that, right?
Because that's not a story
But he said like he had like a she had like a big
Obese head not like a great alien that big obese head
And she's staring at him
And he's still waiting for that light to change but now his view is kind of locked on her
She said
He said
Her eyes were wide open
They were bright blue
You're like she's you just described you mean a normal woman. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I'm saving the best for life
He looks at this woman. She has big bright blue eyes
Pale skin super white skin with
red lipstick super bright red lipstick
And and hair she had hair on her big head her big dome head
What makes this scary because again, I've just described basically you driving down not you not you is her
But I'm saying everyone's seen this no
What is scary is as he's looking at her she looks relatively normal
She's a little pale could probably use some more iron in her system
She smiles at him
I just realized
Let me go ahead and finish it
She she smiles at him. Okay this woman this woman who may or may not be totally normal smiles at him
And he notices
He notices her teeth are made of wood
And then he
He drives away. Okay, so
When I first read this story, I thought whoa dude
That's like when I at that time I was driving on the road and I thought that I saw that alien
Not alien when I was driving on the road and I thought I saw that demon
Remember I told a couple stories like that where I thought I saw like no milks like the poor girl
I thought it was okay when I first read it and I read it a couple times. I thought
Oh, dude, it's like when I saw a demon in the car next to me or driving past me. Maybe this guy
She doesn't do anything spooky. She doesn't do anything spooky. She's just an obese woman
With a lot of lipstick on and wooden teeth
I totally thought it was creepier than that actually now that I think about it this poor woman was 1972
So she may not be alive anymore. She might be it's meant on how old she was depends on how much she took care of her teeth
but
sorry
That's just a story about a woman with wooden teeth
I thought it was going to be a story about a man who
Do you like even how I built that up? It was like super slow because I was like, oh, I can't wait till I get to the teeth part
This is going to be super spooky
And as I was reading I was like, wait a second. She's just an overweight woman with bad teeth
Now that I'm looking at these notes, let me show you
This is the actual sentence here
She stared at him and then fixed a very broad chest shire cat like grin
showing
Showing sorry. I had to do it
showing very square yellow brown teeth that looked
like they were made of wood
They weren't even made of wood. They just looked like it
Uh
Sorry, sorry guys
After I saying hey, how come I don't do think about a doc's doc on anymore that might be why so
Thank you team ad
Thank you really appreciate that and that woman looks like she might have wooden teeth. I yes
So that is not the case. Yeah, I know I know that
That was not to be fair to be fair. I didn't make the report
I didn't make the report if it was me
Making the report then I'm just reading
Just reading it, but I thought that was spookier. Oh man
That was a Thanksgiving episode. Okay, but we have
A really cool story to wrap this guy up
Really cool story to wrap this up and then I'm gonna stick around and we'll do some questions and answers
If you guys want to kick out kick around and stuff like that as well
Let's see. Oh and this owl painting we should talk about this real quick. Sorry for the podcast listeners
but this owl painting I got at artifacts bookstore
And it was like two bucks and it has a little hole. Oh guys here. Hold on
I think I might have shown you guys this before but I'm gonna show you some me
I'll take a quick break. Yeah, when you stare at yourself talking you actually get dizzy
It actually makes you dizzy. Check this out
I got this for free
I got this for free. It was actually Sabine helped me get it. Dude check that out
This is a watercolor bigfoot painting
I haven't figured out where to hang it up yet. I kind of want to hang it back here, but I'm afraid I'm going to bust it up with my
My chair rocking back and forth
And then while I'm up I got my bigfoot
Bigfoot lunchbox
So
I think that around town people always
Yeah, that should put I you know, I I always thought you know what to be a cool, um
logo, but I'm not an artist
Is the
You know how bigfoot's doing that walk that walk pose
If someone could put a book in one of his hands
And just write on it book of Mormon
That'd be a sticker
That'd be sticker
You could have book of Mormon bigfoot
People love that theory
Mormon bigfoot monkeys don't exist
Those are the two
Yeah, I thought about that you could just put a little tie on him a little tie on the bigfoot
Monkeys don't exist in Mormon bigfoot are my two like go-tos when I'm talking to people about the show that haven't
Uh
Haven't heard about it
It's like well, do you think monkeys exist? Yeah, of course. Well, I should listen to my episode
I've thought about going back and doing moron stuff. You got to be careful
You don't want to keep
One time I did a whole week about vampire lord kevin. I love that week
I absolutely love that week. I should just repeat that at some point
But he had so much material haunts has a ton of material as well
but um
He gets
His youtube channels keep getting shut down for a reason like I
Not a huge fan of people being censored and stuff like that. He doesn't he just
But anyways, so you got to be careful how much haunts how much haunt stuff you've covered
Again, I've said this before and I'll say it again. I wish him the best of luck
Wish him the best of luck. He's a young man. I don't agree with him
But I don't think he's a uh bad. I don't think he's a bad dude
I think he's probably I think at heart. He's a good person. I just think he's misinformed about a bunch of stuff
So I wish him the best
um
Doesn't mean that we don't have a laugh. I think
I don't know. I don't know. I kind of have you know, I guess I guess I've kind of adopted haunts
Adopted haunts as my conspiracy son. He will someday become the true mongo jr. I'd like to do something with him. But yeah, so
We are we've left behind the Philippines. We're now seeing good, but you know what we really should
Pull the guy from the last story. Let's pull him out of his car and make him apologize. Make him apologize to
This woman this poor woman who he put on a UFO
Paranormal website to talk about how spooky things are
We're basically just punching him in the stomach or like apologize. Apologize. He's like what I thought it was spooky
She had horrible teeth and as we're punching him as we're beating this guy up for being rude
We all feel someone looking at us from behind
They're like what?
We're slowly turning around and behind us. She's just still standing
There she's still standing there on her phone. She's like what guys? I just have that type of Bora
We're leaving behind Seattle, Washington. We are headed out to
Los angeles. Oh wait, what I have to say what vehicle we're in
Let's hop on board the carboner copter. Everyone get on board. Our hands are all sore from doing all the punching
Um, my elbows. I started a couple elbows there. Hey, robert
Let's all hop on the carboner copter and and nick just asked who's hawns
Um, that's a long story, but you can check out episode was it 151 152 somewhere around there
hawns is a man who believes monkeys don't exist and he's
He's he's a jewel. He truly is a jewel in the youtube crown
We are all hopping on board the carboner copter. William burdell says there's 50 of us
We're all getting in the car. We're not team at standing outside
We are leaving behind Seattle, Washington. We are headed out to Los Angeles, California
Helicopter is flying over the west coast now this story is partially a story mostly a story
But I want to say real quick
I want to say really quick that a quick dead rabbit recommends
There's a lot of movies that I saw that I assume
Other people saw who are into this stuff
So I'm going to assume almost all of you have seen they live at this point
They live is the story of a man
We're actually what I mean the plot is pretty basic
It's the story of a man who finds a
Box of glasses
What and he sells him at the sunglass hat makes a million dollars
It's the story of a man who basically lives in our society. He finds a set of glasses
Put some on because he's homeless almost people do they still glasses and they put them on
He begins to see that the world isn't really what they think it is
You guys have seen the iconography you've eaten if you've never seen the movie the old bay sticker
It's kind of like the weird alien face or just the word obey
He looks up at billboards and it says consume pro create obey magazine covers are all basically
everything is
subconscious
When he takes him off the world is colorful when he puts him on the world becomes black and white and he sees all these
messages everywhere and he sees maybe one in every
50 people maybe a little less than that
Are aliens so he takes up this cause the movie is actually really good. I saw it when I was a kid
My dad rented it. I remember watching the commercials for it
So I had have been like 11 or 12 when it came out. It's definitely a mind-bending movie when you're that young
To see all this stuff it is great sci-fi it's more of an action movie than a sci-fi
Thanks, Sean
Really really well done movie. So
It's one of those things like you want it to be true
You want it to not that you want aliens to be putting subliminal messages in all of our stuff and you want aliens flying
You know down to take us over and yes, uh, nick has pointed this out and so did david david the
line i'm here to
What was it? I've come here to chew bubblegum and kick ass
And i'm all out of bubblegum and then he starts a mass shooting. It's a really interesting movie because from his point of view
He's shooting aliens
But to everyone else in the movie. He's walk. He walks into a bank and massacres a bunch of people at random
So it was a really and yeah rowdy rowdy piper started. I think you steward
It's a really really interesting film because you it can really trip people out you imagine
Not saying this is true
But when you you could take that i'm actually surprised this doesn't play you more into mass shooting culture
I know there was the one guy who shot his minister
Like four times in the head because he thought he was a reptilian
And the minister survived and everyone said whoa, he must have really been a reptilian because he survived four shots of the head you
You can survive four shots of the head
The thing is is that
Not like right in your head
But remember if you get shot here or you get shot here
It's still considered people in the podcast can't see what i'm doing
But you get shot on the forehead right here or if you get a bullet that grazes the side you're there still considered shot in the head
So you can survive i'm not saying why the not the guy's an alien. He i doubt he's an alien
but um
Because aliens could also die from four shots in the head
Anyways, where was it going?
I'm surprised this isn't playing more in a mass shooting culture, which i'm kind of glad
I wish we didn't have a mass shooting culture but this idea that
I only killed the bad ones like not
I think basically that's a hitman or an assassin or a soldier
But you know somebody's saying I walked into that place and everyone I shot was an alien
So I don't know why i'm on trial i'm surprised it doesn't come out more often
But anyways, it's a great movie did rabbi recommends they live i'm surprised they haven't remade it yet
Was zack effron in the lead
Which actually now I say doesn't sound too bad. I always like movies when they get
Hot young not physically hot although he is cute
Not cute
Okay, I I think it's interesting when you take like robert patinson and put him in batman because you're going to get a whole new audience for the movie
So if they took uh zack effron and put him in they live you're going to get a bunch of people
Who've never watched they live to watch it so I don't have a problem with that. I think it remakes her fine
So here we go
Yeah stewart said he just knows someone who got shot twice
In the head i'm assuming but maybe not and they live so yeah, it can definitely have multiple shots can happen
Get shot on the head. Okay, so
The other recently on
The export
this
Paraglasses appeared so we're in los angeles and that's where they live takes place. We walk into a warehouse
Rowdy rowdy piper. He's standing there like a force goes. I miss rowdy piper
Not like I knew him like he was my neighbor
But his force goes to stand in the corner. He's not into us. We're walking through this warehouse
And there is a pair of goggles sitting on a table
And recently on the export there's been a kind of explosion of interest into these things
They're called killner screens or killner goggles
So we pick them up and we put them on you know
What?
Everything's blue now kind of purplish
Um, we're looking around I was about to make an iphone 65 joke, but I didn't so I should deserve some credit for my restraint
We're wearing these killner goggles and i'm looking around at all of you guys you guys all look totally cool
You're your auras. Let me actually explain what the goggles do first
Apparently they allow you to see auras and you can train yourself to see an aura
Or you can just look at them
and you can look at them
And you can put what was I said I was distracted by caggy key's comment
Um, who said the first time you ever heard about they live it was recommended to him by a neo nazi
when you
Put on these killner screens
You can look at people and see their auras. Hey scar you can see the energy around the person
Now you can train yourself to see auras
You can do that
And I I'll get into the aura thing in a second, but anyways so auras are the basically the life energy around you
Now you can go through years of training to see auras or with these killner screens
You can put these on you can actually look at people and see
Their auras but these killner screens did something else too
Every so often you'd be looking through a group of people. So i'm looking through all you dudes
You guys are all super cool and stuff
You guys are hopefully you guys are just standing there normally
But when I look at you with the glasses, you're making a cool b-boy pose spinning around on interdimensional cardboard
But then we go outside. We're wearing these killner goggles
We go outside in that Los Angeles proper and every show often we see someone with a
interesting aura
Did you see that guy the guy driving the bus? We see an obese woman with bad teeth. We're like, ah, but she has a normal aura so
But every so often you see you'd see people with different auras like an angry aura or like a super happy more happy than normal aura
But every so often you'd see something that could only be described
As an inhuman
aura
So these killner screens were banned by the government
Specifically the ingredient that was used to make them
Which i'm gonna try to pronounce
Dick, I don't think this is how you say it but dick yannan die
Dick yannan die was this
Die that was needed to make these killner screens
The government banned it. They said you can't use dick nan and die. Not only can you not use it? You can't pronounce it correctly ever again
Dick yannan die. You can't use it
And to this day dick yannan die is still illegal
And so the ability to make these glasses
Are also illegal is the government possibly keeping from us technology?
That will allow us to see
alien invaders
It's an interesting story and I had a lot of fun looking into it. Let's really dig into it. That's pretty much the bulk of the mythos
Dick yannan die apparently is what bonkelman is saying
Here's here's we here we go there apparently also there was an other version of these glasses
Made by a guy named tom bow camp arnold called the prana view goggles
But I couldn't find any proof that this guy like when I went looking for the information on that name
I couldn't really find anything prana view goggles do exist, but they're apparently the same thing
Basically, hey short circuit
So let's take a look at first off did these goggles exist is this just an internet myth that's going around?
Yes, the goggles existed. William killner was a real person. He wrote books on the human aura back in
1911 really wrote the first book about human auras or at the time as they were knowing
human atmospheres
So he's one of the pioneers of human auras and he did invent these glasses and they were made
with dick yannan
In between two sheets of glass dick yannan die is made from
Like burnt tar to die. That's made from tar
What's interesting about this
is that
Let me explain to you apparently the human auras were kind of like white light energy around them and these other people
Who knows what they were would show with like a blue oval there would be like an oh
It wouldn't be like this energy just kind of floating around the person
But an oval around them
And one guy said apparently he looked through them and he saw
Someone with slits for eyes
But we just had a guy who saw wooden teeth
Wooden teeth and reported it as an alien or monster
So I don't know maybe the guy just maybe the guy just got little ninja stars in his eyes and then pulled him out
And then he looked at him. He didn't notice there was a pledge to you now to his eyes. He had blue goggles on
So the the goggles did exist. They
Were made by William killner who is a real person who steadied human auras. So all that part of the story matches up
So then I started looking at it and I go
Okay, then my next question because this is how I approach these stories. I read it. I was like that's fascinating
Is it true?
I
Started looking into this. Is this dye actually illegal? Yes, it is. So now my interest is really peaked
Now my interest is really peaked because we having a lot of this story matched up
It was banned in the 1940s
There should be our first clue of where this could be going. It was banned in the 1940s
And in 2010 around 2010 it was briefly made legal again for some weird reason
I'm assuming it was a paperwork mess up
Because it was quickly made illegal again
Now when you read about these goggles
You'll always come across this
story
When you read about these goggles, you'll always hear this story
I hired a chemist
who could
Get anything he has security clearance to get acid he gets security clearance to buy as much heroin as he wants
He's a chemist. He can do science stuff with this
We asked if he could buy some dicky dicky ham and dye for us
And they told him his security clearance wasn't high enough for that stuff
So everyone's like, oh, it must be true the aliens must be working on this
They must be suppressing this technology
Because if this chemist can get lsd and heroin, how come he can't get this dye?
Interesting story interesting little tidbit because you sit there and you think yeah, that is interesting like heroin and lsd is super
You know, it's illegal. We know that why is this stuff illegal?
But then you got to start and this is where I started thinking differently and was able to kind of get to the bottom of this
If I'm a nuclear engineer, I'm a high level
scientist and I'm working on like nuclear chemistry. Do you think I could order unlimited amounts of heroin?
Just because you're a chemist doesn't mean you can get every possible chemical out of there
If you're a chemist in one field you can't be like, you know what I want to do
I know I've been doing like biology. I know I've been doing this chemistry of starfish
But I really want to see what happens when I inject him with heroin. So you order a bunch of heroin
You'd probably have to get some paperwork filled out for that
The reason why this stuff is illegal and this is kind of
Interesting because a lot of people lead this stuff out the ex post was posting what they knew
It's the articles that he was sourcing that leaves this information out. It's highly carcinogenic
Dicky M and I
Can cause cancer. It's toxic at the very least you can argue that. Oh, you know the cancer research may
May not be valid because we haven't had long-term studies on the very least
It's toxic. It can also be used as a way to and this is why it was made illegal in the 40s
Because if you had this stuff and you were able to see aliens from 1911, why would they make it illegal in the 40s?
Why would they spend 30 years when people walk around being like?
There's an alien. There's an alien
Why wouldn't you just make it illegal the next day? The reason why it was made illegal in the 40s is because this can be used to make
disannose
settling
Rocket fuel
Now before we were really making a ton of rockets and making jets
I actually think it's a jet fuel before we were like, oh, look at this stuff. It's blue. It's kind of cool
I can kind of tell if my boss is an alien
But once we start building jet fighters
We start to realize it's probably not a good idea to have this stuff two inches from your eyeballs or really anywhere around you
This stuff, where did I put in my notes? This stuff burns so hot
It burned not the glasses itself, but it can be converted to the dye cycle Eikoline or whatever
It can reach temperatures of
910 degrees Fahrenheit. That is the hottest possible fire in an oxygen atmosphere
Two inches from your eyeballs, right?
I mean that is as hot as it can possibly get on the planet earth and you got people like hey, Mal, look I can see a white line around you
Isn't it awesome in there like smoking a cigarette?
So that's the reason why it's illegal because it's super super dangerous, but of course
You could always push back that, you know, it's not toxic
Toxic levels and carcinogenic levels is easy to kind of say. Oh, it's just that it's just that stay away stay away
The thing is you can make these goggles yourself. They say if you take a purple sheet of glass or plastic
And a blue like because it's cobalt blue is really what you're looking through
This dye is this particular shade of blue
Take purple tape blue put them there stare through them
And you can see them you have to pretty much shut off. I got differing things on this you either have to shut off all visible light
Or you have to just get a little bit of light in the side
But people who have built these goggles using the plastic stuff not you can buy these online, but they're total ripoffs. They're basically like
Sunglasses you can buy at a gas station someone commented on x you can buy glasses that you buy at a gas station, but they cost you 90 bucks
Just
Oh look at these blue shades you can find them
But you know you can also build them yourself by taking the two proper colored lenses and put them together
But what's interesting there's this is the way we're going to wrap this up
You have some people saying
The reason why you do see a white outline around the person they said the reason why that is is because the way that the tint is
It's blocking all the light waves except for like a little bit around the person
So it's actually a natural way that light is reflected
You're seeing white lines around people and if you already believe in auras
Then you're going to believe that is an aura
So you have to think this is just another device another spooky invention that's supposed to let us
Pierce the veil and see what we know is true. I believe in auras
I totally believe in auras
I think it's I think it's one of those things
It's it's one of those weird things like if you don't believe in them or if you believe in them
It's not it's such a benign theory
But I do believe that we do when we're around other people we sense them
Like I think you can build we call it, you know gut feeling but I think really what we're doing is we're detecting their aura
The
Cal and aura is basically an energy field that we give out
It's basically like you can tell someone could be standing there totally normal
And you can go something and I've talked about this on shows too. I can walk into your house and tell you how healthy your marriage is
And I think they're just the walls are soaked with that emotional energy
You can be soaked with that emotional energy people can see you and you think you're doing just fine and someone walks up to you and go
You doing okay, man? Oh
You can even be someone you don't know being like are you feeling okay?
kind of just I feel like you're
Feel like you're kind of sad that you have those wooden teeth. You're like it's
So I do believe in auras. I do believe people can see them
I do believe it's something that you can train yourself to do
But that's something that these glasses can skip ahead
And I think a lot of people wanted there's two stories of these glasses
One is that it gives you the paranormal ability to see people's emotional energy
Which would give you a leg up and would make you feel special that you could see that the other one
Obviously is the effect that aliens are invading that might be more important than telling whether or not your neighbor is mad at you
but
Preventing an alien invasion by wearing these goggles and and being able to see what's going on
That's kind of the sci-fi story to it
And then we have the mystical one of you just being able to see people's auras
I think this story is important for another reason and I want to wrap this up like this and I want this to kind of be
Something that may be some of you and I I feel the same way. We'll take something away from this
This might sound contradictory coming from me, but why do you need to see the aura?
Why do we need to visibly see the aura if we know that we can feel it
Why do we need to see it because we want proof
We want proof it's this weirdest thing in this
Form of research we want proof
example
You walk into a house
You feel uncomfortable
You feel like you're not alone
When you're in your bedroom
So you tell someone hey man, I think my bedroom is haunted
What's the first question they're gonna ask
Would you see
Well, I didn't see anything. I just felt something. Oh, okay
You know that your house is haunted you feel it in your bones
But you still want proof
We believe
That scene is believing that scene itself is proof
But why our sense of sight deceives us all the time you can look at any sort of optical illusion
Or something off in the darkness
Our sense of sight deceives us all the time
Why is it important for you to be able to see auras when you can already see
Air quote auras you can already feel them you can feel that energy
We have a weird desire to need proof. I don't know if it's a human thing
I don't know if it's something that's mostly in the paranormal world
But you know what I mean
If someone tells you they think someone's haunted someplace is haunted you are going to ask
What did they see did you see something did you hear something?
Think about all the times I've done this many times or I'll be sitting in my living room
And I'll be thinking something's haunted. I'll be wondering about ghosts or anything like that
And I'll be thinking what would happen if I saw that bottle fly across the room
It's never happened to me. I've never seen anything levitate in front of me
But is that really
Let's not say the bottle flies across the room because that's a violent act
But let's say that you see your phone levitate an inch off the table and fall down
Is that any more proof that one moment than
months of
Being in your place feeling psychologically like there's something standing behind you
You never see anything you never feel anything you never hear anything
But every time you get up out of your chair. It's almost like someone else is getting up out of that chair with you
When you're standing in the shower
It's like there's someone right outside the shower curtain
watching you
You feel this so intently
That you're uncomfortable in your own place. You've actually been looking at moving
But you keep telling yourself no that's dumb. That's dumb for months that goes on versus one second of your phone going
This is just a inch off the why and I know the answer is the phone
But why
Why do we put so much emphasis on the scene?
Why would you want to build glasses made of a carcinogen that also turns into a jet fuel?
So you could physically see something even though you have 40
In my case 43 years of being able to sense people's auras
I think it's important for us to start looking at some of these
Events that we are investigating and the reason why I say it's contradictory for me because
I'm always about the proof. I'm always about the proof
But you'll notice with UFO stories ghost stories things like that. I'm not so much about the proof
Because it's usually just one person telling a story
Conspiracies is where I want proof because conspiracies have a weird tangle
You're trying to draw all these connections and I do that with alien stories as well
Sometimes and they're talking about like weird, you know, weird people making bizarre claims
But when it's one person driving down the road
Sees a beast woman with wooden teeth and this I didn't fact check that I probably should have read it a couple more times
But I didn't fact check that I think it's important for us and for you
dear listener
To follow the gut to not worry so much about what we see and what we hear because both of those can be
Just as easily deceived follow your gut
When you're investigating ghost stories when you're investigating the paranormal
Don't worry so much and again this super contradictory and it might come to bite me in the butt in later episodes
But don't worry so much about what you're visually seeing think about that feeling you have
because that feeling is
Your sixth sense that's probably the bad term you're feeling is your seventh sense
That feeling is just as important as sight as hearing and it's telling you that person has a bad aura
It's telling you that person
May not be a person
So don't worry about evp readers don't worry about
electronic devices unless you're a gamer then you know you probably worry about this
But don't worry about the goggles and the think about it those ghost hunters. They go in with the machine
They're like look at the temperature is lowered
That's doesn't prove that doesn't prove anything more than someone going in there and going
I sense a great spirit in here one's a measurement that anyone could go
Well, yeah, they're the blue the wind blue buyer
I wasn't there and that could be fake and stuff like that we put so much of reliance on science when we're talking about something
That's paranormal
To the point that we're building carcinogenic glasses made of jet fuel on our face
Let's we can do that stuff, but don't discount that gut feeling because if you're in that house
Could cut see this way because if you're at home you may have all the emf readers
You may have all the spirit boxes
You may have your kill-nir screens on your face ready to go
but
All of those can be equally deceived as well. The only thing you can trust is when the pit of your stomach opens up
Because that thing is standing behind you once again
If it can't be seen by our eyes if it can break the laws of the universe
Why wouldn't it be able to deceive the technology man has made to detect it
The only defense mechanism we have against this stuff is ourselves
So don't waste money on this junk
Just understand that when you feel uncomfortable
There is probably a good reason for it
Or
A woman with wooden teeth is staring at you right now
Dead rapper radio at gmail.com you guys know the drill you guys know the drill
You know it's funny those in the we'll wrap it up. I guess it should do proper wrap up
Dead rapper radio gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/ dead rapper radio twitter is at dead rapper radio
Dead rapper radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
This is normally the point where I immediately shut my mic off and I go
Those in so thank you rampart and thanks Austin Austin for jumping in and christian I see you're in there as well
Shane
I um
Normally with those this one I kind of knew how it's gonna end it because I remember the other day
I was taking a shower and I go why is it so important for us to see these things when I was looking at these glasses
I was like, why is it so important for us to see these things like isn't it enough for us to just know?
And I get it. It's uh, it's okay mug. I get it. It's a
Like you want to see you and I get that too like I would
It's it's an interesting dilemma and I was thinking about then I go that's kind of how I want to wrap this episode up
You want to see it? I get it
But it's how important is it to see it if you can feel it like I've seen
A few things I've seen a few things but I've
I've
Experienced more than I've seen now. Take that which episode that I did the other day imagine if
I um saw the witch walk into the salt and go
Like a blue lightning show up and stuff like that. I could be like I could tell you guys that would you guys believe it though?
Like even I was like guys, I swear to god
I saw blue lightning come down and stop the witch from walking in you be like what?
The story the fact that she doesn't walk in through the salt
I
Didn't see the physical reaction. I was sitting in the chair the whole time and this is a comfy chair by the way
Who mentioned that earlier?
Milk yeah, it is a comfy chair. Um, so yeah, we have this tendency to want to see
And then callum that's funny callum just posted. What does everyone think about this supposed december second alien invasion?
It's not gonna happen. I'm actually I would I have thought honestly about
doing
A podcast like a whole podcast
Weekly podcast that's just prophecies
Not old prophecies
You could do a week and you're like hey everyone december second it's coming up
Everyone's going everyone's going to get diced and then of course that would go by nobody's going to
Pay attention to it
And then you go on to the next one and the next one and the next one and all that stuff like these prophecies
They keep coming. They're always super close. They disappear. I remember aliens were supposed to invade the 2012
Olympics, I remember that aliens were supposed to invade the royal wedding
I'm not the kate middleton one
Um, what other world in civil war in the united states guys remember that just like a couple weeks ago
We were being told that the war world war three with america is going to go to war if i ran and all this stuff is going to happen
Everyone does this stuff. It's not just paranormal people
Everyone does this everyone does these prophecies
I'd say a late night tv show on sci-fi. That's what khaki kih was saying
I don't understand why the whole idea. I mean I again, I believe in aliens
I don't understand why we don't have a
I
Got to turn my fan on it's so hot
Yeah, why don't aliens just fully invade or if they have been taken over
These are the questions that I would like to ask someone who legitimately legitimately believes in
The I had a brother-in-law. I guess I still have a brother-in-law who believes that reptilians are taking over the world
They're queen of queen of england, you know, you guys know the theory
Queen of england's a reptilian world leaders are reptilian
I would love
He legitimately believed that stuff. He might still but I would love to
Sit down and talk with someone who actually believes that stuff because I just have a ton of questions. Yeah, david. Ike
When did the aliens start my big question is this when did the aliens start doing this and what's taken him so long?
Those are big questions. Um khaki cube. Have you ever heard the theory that earth is actually under alien sanction?
No aliens are allowed to make contact with earth. That's an old one. I've heard that before
It's a pretty convenient one as to why aliens don't make contact with us
Obviously, there's some leaps of logic in that and this is funny because like again if with with straight off alien encounter stories
I'm more
I want to say trusting but I give them more the benefit of the doubt but that is becomes a conspiracy theory
Why would the aliens have this convention put up? Oh, it's because humans are barbaric and then
They have to learn what what if humans done in the past when we've come across quote unquote barbaric people on this planet
Do we just sit there
There's basically a couple tribes left now that we don't do anything like on the island
We covered it in one of our stories about. Um, what was the name of that island?
paint paradise island a sanctuary island or something like that
Generally we we either enslave them destroy them
or um convert them
And usually it's a combination of the three
So why would the aliens be sitting outside this?
Planet the only planet with that has liquid water in it in a any sort of as far as we can tell
As far as we can tell within light years of us the only planet with liquid water with two thirds of it being liquid water
Why would you just sit back?
And just kind of see if they blow it up. It doesn't make sense. I can see there. It doesn't make sense
And yeah, the rampart says that's the star trek's prime directive a lot of
A lot of UFO conspiracies are pulled directly from science fiction. Sure. You could argue it's vice versa that the cia is trying to
put those theories into science fiction so people don't believe them when they come out but
You do see a lot of that as well
A bonkerman says that he's heard it's more advantageous for alien race to obtain the raw materials from asteroids
That's true
It would be more advantageous for us to get raw materials from asteroids
But you can't get tons of liquid water from asteroids and as far as we know
Liquid water is important. I mean assuming they're biological which a reptilian would be a biological and nordic would be biological
Even if they have massive water reserves in their home system, they're a far far from home
So why don't they come to take our water like well again?
Why are they just kind of hanging out and waiting to figure it out and you can imagine like the nordics of the table and he's like
I believe the humans deserve a chance and the gray aliens talking about hippie
Environmental nonsense the reptilians like let's eat them all like how's that a council?
Basically they all hate each other's guts
Aaa
Asked if I could talk to bigfoot, what would you ask or tell him?
That's an interesting question if I could talk to bigfoot
If I met bigfoot and he I could talk to him
I would probably ask him why
Like what is he doing here?
Not from some sort of metaphysical thing because that's a deep question. You're walking on the street and you're like, hey, buddy
What's up?
Why are you here? I like to get coffee. You're like no
Why are you I would wonder why he hangs out in the forest and stuff like what's his he may be like me bigfoot
Me this is me home
And I'm a leprechaun now. I'm saying me all the time. You could be like this is just where I hang out
But I would be I would be curious like did you used to be human do I have more than one question?
Did you used to be a human?
Are you from another dimension? What's like? What are you talking about weirdo?
I'm a giant ape that can talk for like five minutes. You're asking me if I used to be human to me
That's the scariest bigfoot theory every time I cover it on the show. It gives me the heebie-jeebies
People turning into bigfoot. So I've covered that twice and it's super spooky. Yes
Milk xm64 sentinel island. That's what I was talking about. Thank you
Bigfoot's watching the stream right now
yeah, you know, there's a lot of
belief that bigfoot and UFOs are tied together
Why is it that the states with the most cryptids
Also have lots of goth girls in it like florida, for example
I don't know if that's true because I'm assuming that new orleans has a ton of goth girls
I don't know how big their cryptid count is. I know I really haven't found many cryptids in
A lot of times they're lame cryptids. No fence. No fence southern southern dead rabbit radio listens
You have like swamp creeper dude. Yeah, it's basically bigfoot, but he smells even worse
Maybe a lizard man
That's it
I gotta say this man south america has it beat for cryptids like the stories that we've pulled out of south america
South america and eastern europe
But I don't think anyone's come close to south america's cryptid count. Absolutely insane. Absolutely insane down there
I will say this. I remember once reading something
You know why we get all the crazy articles about florida and florida man and all that stuff
It's not that florida has a higher population of crazy people. It's that their
Public records and their freedom of information is way more open than any other state
So if someone commits any sort of crime all the information is released almost immediately
So their name details of the crime stuff like that other states can take a while other states have more stringent rules on on who can know what
That's why florida has so many crazy cases. They just have much more open access
Much more open access
The documents how do we get talking about goth girls? I mean i'm not complaining necessarily, but i'm seeing goth girls pop up a lot
Um, which again not complaining. I think we talked about this before how come there's not goth the women
And I think it's because most of them start using heroin at some point
um
But yeah, is it if you are 30 years old and you're dressed goth and you're not a musician
You're not a heroin addict and you're not a vampire
Are you a goth girl or a goth woman? Is there another term for it? Is there a goth term?
Is historical hiker still on here? She may know she knows about old timey stuff. Um, she's like what no
I don't know if there's such a thing as a goth woman. I don't know if she's still on here though
I've been thinking about redoing the boo pill
That episode came out years ago or two years ago. I think it's an important episode
I think it's an important episode
Girls love the paranormal
so if you want
To find a good way to communicate with girls do paranormal people levitate girl levitating in the corner and they're like, hey ladies
How are you doing?
um, no join a ghost hunting group
Or a man that must suck with all pandemic stuff not being able to do ghost hunting
Or there's a bunch more ghosts running around. I actually miss ghost hunting. That's one of the things
That I really haven't done in years. I would love to do that
I would love to start doing that again x m 64 the boo pill is my theory
That if you want to meet women be interested get interested in paranormal because women love this stuff
so
Learn to do tarot cards learn to read palms do astrology ghost hunting
See women aren't so much in encrypted hunting. You're like, oh, we're gonna go hunt a squash. They're like, uh
But if you're like, oh, we're walking through a dark house with this device
Girls love that stuff girls love to be scared. So take the boo pill. Um, it's a good way
It's really is a good way to meet women
Yeah, we might do it as a rerun the problem is in that episode
I played audio from someone else's clip and I had to be I think I edited it out at this point
I had to be careful earlier on in the show. I was doing more stuff like that. See you later. Ross. Have a happy Thanksgiving
Um, yeah, but you got to be careful with copyright on the podcast side and the youtube side. So I think I took that out
What's going on in the afterlife that prevents ghosts from talking to us in a more obvious way
Why do they have to be so vague? I think that there's basically two answers to that one is
That they don't have the power to or they can only manifest in certain ways
I think which is interesting, you know, a lot of people who have ghost experiences
Especially when people have passed away loved ones have passed away. They come to them at night. They come to them in dreams
They'll smell
The smell where they're sitting in their dad's chair. They'll smell as old cigars and stuff like that
I think all that's touching and I'm not diminishing that at all
I think the thing is is like I think the most obvious answer is how come after your
Father or your mother or your brother passed away. They're not constantly hanging out with you helping you shoot hoops
Because after you die everything here seems so minimal
it would be the equivalent of
As an adult do you ever go back to your kindergarten playground?
Like I don't even know if that's a good example as an adult would you ever
pick up
a rattle
And if you did would you be amazed by it? I think when you died the and you don't forget the people here
But I also have a theory that there's no time in the afterlife. So let's say that I died right now
and
My mother dies 30 years from now
In heaven, thank you osu!mir or in the afterlife. I guess I should say
I died and instantly
Thank you, Ari appreciate that
I died and then instantly my mom standing next to me. There's no time there. It's not like I'm up there and I'm like 30 years
Oh, I'm so alone
There's no time. It's all instant. So to you
On earth it's 30 years and then you pass away and you see them to them. You're already standing right next to them. So
since time isn't of an issue
And you're in a realm where you realize all this stuff is inconsequential. Why would you be hanging out here?
Because as far as you're concerned, everyone's up there already. That's just my theory
It doesn't make sense that you would have people floating around in the afterlife
Time is something that really only exists in this dimension that we can measure it
Barfee man, I have a pop filter. This is my backup mic. This is my real mic over here
Tlm. Yeah, am I popping it pretty bad? That sucks
I'm gonna lean in really really close. Yeah, this is my blue yeti. This is my live stream mic
As mere asks do you believe in the law of attraction? Yeah, I've actually done a couple episodes on the law of attraction
Um, I 100 believe in it. I think you I think that you
I think people who don't believe in the law of attraction still use the law of attraction
Which is a kind of an interesting thing
You'll see any bodybuilder any bodybuilder you talk to
They'll say when I started bodybuilding I visualized this body
Before I started
Lifting I visualized what I'm gonna look like today and as I was working out over the years
I would visualize my legs getting bigger my thighs getting bigger. That's a lot of attraction
A businessman doesn't go into his shop
Five times or seven days a week. It's a small business owner
Goes in there seven days a week works eight hours a day and then it's a success
You have to visualize that success and and I am he pointed out nevel Goddard. I believe
I recommend going to Wallace waddles. They really the guy who invented it. He preceded nevel by about 30 years
I believe he wrote the science of getting rich
And that book changed my life it changed definitely changed the way I look at life
I don't really read a lot of books. I read monthly articles, but that book's amazing and the law of attraction totally works
I do not work on this show. There are times where I don't use the law of attraction on this show
And I noticed that my my views go down and my I don't gain new listeners
But when I focus on people finding the podcast enjoying the podcast my numbers go up. It's 100 true. You create your reality
Yeah cocky cute cocky cube said I I heard a theory once that ghosts exist in all forms at once time past present future
Yeah, that would make sense
It would make sense. You'd be chilling up there with you know, vlog tepe is
Hopefully not but you know, maybe he's gone over his whole impaling thing into him
He's only been up there for a minute. You wouldn't even notice you're like, hey, vlog. What's up?
You're all covering your butthole as you're walking by and he's like, yeah, it's a horrible stereotype
Yeah
Denzo says that skateboarding is a lot of law of attraction. I think any sport
Where you're thinking you visualize that ball going out of the stadium. It's super powerful
It's a super powerful thing to visualize and the sport is interesting because you have everyone's visualizations working against each other
but
The universe gives you what you ask of it now. Obviously the pushback is you always hear
What about some kid in the Sudan?
His family was killed by raiders and he's on the run and he hasn't eaten in four days where his law of attraction
Do I think he brought those raiders to his village? No
No, I don't think the law of attraction in my personal experience
Because I'll be walking on the street and I'll be like, dude
I hope like some ninjas jump out of the bushes right now and then Leonardo comes and he helps me
We fight off the foot clan. I'm constantly thinking about like getting in fights
I'm constantly thinking about like what happens if someone kicked in my door right now
I'm always thinking about all of this stuff and never happens. It never happens. I'm just always on edge
I don't think the law of attraction works on a negative aspect. It probably would if that's all you did
I also have positive thoughts
But if you think positively
I don't basically what I'm saying is the kid in the Sudan that was really unlucky that he was born in that place in that time
in that village
It sucks
but if we could get that kid out of that village get him into a
like a society
Move him to Egypt or something like that move him anywhere
Give him some books give him some people who care about him
And apply the law of attraction that kid's going to be a success without law of attraction
The kid will still be have a much better life than he had before
Because you know, he was not under constant threat of getting killed
But I think a lot of attraction can't help but it doesn't I mean if you're in a situation like that
You didn't cause that but you can use this as one of your toolkits to get out of it. So I think I do think it's definitely worthwhile
AFX asked what's the deepest rabbit hole you ever explored?
um
the conformers
the conformers that story still
The conformers 100 the conformers like I can't even go into detail about what happened
the conformers
I'm not yeah that that's the weirdest rabbit hole I've ever covered on this show
It's episode it's like episode 87 or something like that. It was weird when I covered it
It was weird when I was researching it. It has not stopped being weird
all this time
The conformers that's all I cannot go into any more detail about what is
the summary of the conformer's story was that there was an alien race of
um inorganic rocks
I can't do a follow-up
I'm barfing man the conformer's story is just so
The conformers are an alien race supposedly it's the only alien race and they're inorganic minerals
Their voices sound like pebbles falling in a metal bucket. They're extremely religious
Extremely violent and the governments of the world have made contact with the conformers on multiple
points multiple times
Try researching it
You're not going to be able to find anything probably only my episode
As I was researching it websites are getting deleted
as I was researching it
I heard about it. It was a throwaway line on a mysterious universe episode back in like 2005
2006 that you just mentioned it
It always intrigued me and I went looking for it found some stuff websites got deleted. I did the episode the weirdness
has not stopped
100 percent
The conformers
Yeah
Um
That's the deepest rabbit hole I've ever fallen into and the point the thing the interesting thing is
When when it comes to the show I'll say this there are times where I'll come across information
I like to share the information with you if I come across conspiracy theories that I can't talk about on the show
Like I used to be all about like gaining the knowledge gaining the knowledge, but the thing is is like
What what's the point of having knowledge if you can't share from it?
Sure, you can learn from it, but if you can't share from it
So if I come across knowledge if I come across stuff that I can't share with you guys, I'm just like
I'm good. I'm good like you can I'm good this conversation doesn't need to go any further. I'm
I'm fine. So that's when the rabbit hole that's to me is a deep rabbit hole
But uh, yeah now interesting story. It's over. I'm uh
Yeah conformers um someone asked
Maximilian have I ever heard of the green children of wool pit? Yeah, that's actually a pretty con like that
that's one of those
Stories that you and I'm not insulting you at all or anything like that
but that's one of those stories that like when you get the books of
Um like famous stories. That's one of them that that hasn't always been an interesting story
There's always been theories like they weren't actually green that it was a translation error that their clothes were green
Some people said they were obviously like from inner earth. I think that's the most popular one
other people saying that they had
um
Some sort there's actually a disease that turns them green turns people green eat a bunch of green beans
I think if I remember correctly the boy died in the girl stayed in the village and had kids and
Their kids could stick around like their kids didn't have any issues or anything like that
I I think it's I think it's interesting because we also have this story about that woman who gets kidnapped
Well, it was bigfoot who got kidnapped in Siberia
And they thought it was a bigfoot and they kept her captive for 30 years and the chieftain of the this back like in the 1800s early 1900s
The chieftain of the village starts banging the lady
banging bigfoot and she gives birth to a couple kids and then she dies eventually just of old age
and
Western or not western scientists, but scientists further out into russia hear this hear this old legend
They're like what you're banging bigfoot and there's still grandkids walking around they tested her
She wasn't bigfoot. She was a black woman. She was like an escaped slave in Siberia
That they thought was bigfoot because she didn't speak the language. She was tall
And they have a version of that type of cryptid over there
So I would be my reason that was an episode. I really like the episode
I'm wondering if they could do the dna test in wool pit to see if they could actually
Or if they have because again, I haven't covered that I haven't followed the story since I was a kid
But uh, yeah, it is an interesting story
Lanny lanny akea asked if I've ever heard of or what was springfield jack again spring hill jack
actually people now believe that he was a
Like a sexual predator like his whole thing when he would jump out and grab women
And then leave and over time the legend became he could jump over walls that he had springs attached to his feet
Or that he was an actual cryptid when really it was a guy jumping out of the bushes and grabbing women
We covered him briefly on an episode. I did an episode about the ghosts
Where the origin of ghosts like the white sheet came from it was sex
You used to take poor people in england
put them in a
White sheet and tie the tie the feet if when they when they died when they're alive
They're like hey, we're gonna pull a prank on you
They'd put a white sheet over you and then tie it to the feet and then you just pick it up and throw it into the grave
So the idea of someone standing there with a white sheet over them
Thought this guy's a zombie this guy's a ghost. So it was like 18 late 1800s england
Or maybe mid 1800s england where the image of the ghosts and the white sheet popped up because it was such a terrifying figure
What people were doing is they were putting on a white sheet
Jumping out at women mostly walking down the street and then while they were shocked
Assaulting them sexually assaulting them people would also mug you
They jump which would be a little less
Startling if you're walking on the street and a guy jumped behind
With a sheet looks like a ghost here. We're like, oh no a ghost, but then a gun shows up. You're like, oh, it's just
It's just the normal mugging
Here i'll give you some like the balloons or whatever they used back then so yeah that was spring heal jack was kind of the same thing
it was a
It was basically a guy committing sexual assault. That's what i've seen. That's what i've seen
Not seen myself, but i've seen that theory pop around
I
See mad says can native american bigfoot legends come from early african migrants
most likely not
um, the the led see the thing in russia
They were so far off
In syberia that they had never seen a black person before
But every other part of the world even if you had african migrants coming to other parts of the world like this story because you have bigfoot in
Asia you have bigfoot in you don't really have bigfoot in europe, but you have the green man
You have them in americas and stuff like that you have in south america
All of those other regions would be used to people with very very dark skin
If not from africa like in asia there would be africans walking around and stuff like that trade routes
So i wouldn't be so shocking but in syberia
They had just never seen a black person before and they did have those legends of those wild beasts running through
The syberian forest so they just kind of put two and two together and they were wrong
They were 100 wrong
But that that was how that worked out like that
Then so i don't remember what episode the formers was i think if you go to youtube and type in conformers dead rabbit radio
It'll pop up. Um, if you listen to it on the podcast
Here's a tip if you go to the dead rabbit radio website
If you go to the the podcast site of the website, there's a search bar
If you're ever looking for a particular term because that's how i have to find stuff from time to time
I type it in the search bar. I type in conformers. It'll pop up every episode where
In the show notes or in the title the conformers is there
So if i remember looking for her like i'm like
What was that story where a guy was changing his tire?
Alien alien popped out of the tire. It was really bad service from good year
I'll type that in and if i happen to have that in a headliner in the show notes or something like that
It'll pop right up and i can find that episode because my big fear. Okay, uh, lannick
Is saying it's episode 60 so it was real early on that would have been like
Three months into the show
That's how much i wanted to cover that story
um
Yeah, i have a um or is it episode 202
I don't know it's one of those two so anyways that would make i wouldn't be i would be surprised if it was early as episode 60
But it could be because i really wanted to cover something xm
64 what do you have planned for episode 666 dude this this podcast is hard enough to pull off without doing special episodes honestly
Like i didn't do an episode for 420 people are kind of like uh
I barely did an episode for 500th anniversary or i'm not 500th anniversary 500 episode
I think i did an episode i didn't even do a special episode for episode 100
It's really hard to just do a daily show let alone plan stuff ahead. I have a bunch of stories for
Christmas, but i'm not even going to do them on Christmas
I'm going to spread them out throughout the months because otherwise i'm just going to forget otherwise i'm just going to forget about them anyways
Shane Fitzgerald asked do i search every topic to make sure you haven't done it
Not every topic, but there's topics where i'll be reading something i'm like this sounds super familiar
There was one that i was like oh my god this sounds super familiar. No i was researching. I was like oh this is so awesome
I can't wait to tell this story and then at the ending of the article was a detail and i was like oh that sounds familiar
I'd already done it that would be embarrassing. You know again i'm 43 years old i'm
i'm physically fit
Maybe not fit i'm physically healthy
I even have i bought one of these micrometer
because i was like um
My brother got covid
dummy
He's doing fine. He's doing totally fine. But i was like
well
i'm gonna get me a little oximeter
um
But i'm healthy my my heart my rusty heart rates good
My oxygen levels good and everything like that so
Where were we going with that? What were we talking about?
even
This is what i was talking about i'm 43 years old so i'm like i'm starting to forget stuff
more easily
As i forget what i'm talking about because of the blinking lights on this machine. I'm like
Yeah, i started to get lightheaded early honestly guys. I didn't know if i was going to be able to the episode
You guys who were there from the beginning the first
I don't know like
What was it steward uh you guys steward sucker are you okay?
We were maybe 15 minutes into the episode and i was like i got lightheaded and i think um
I forgot who said someone else said
Breathe i think i was talking too quickly. I think i was de-saturating my oxygen level
Satan himself themed episode. You know what's funny? I've all this might be the ultimate
pacifist i'm not a pacifist
quite adept at punching people but
I would love to see
The story of reality end
With satan being like hey god, sorry about that whole
You know rebellion trying to destroy earth and god's like ah bring it here bro and give each other
I'd love to see that to be the end of the story whether or not that happens
Who knows maybe because that's what i want in the afterlife. That's what i'll see
Who knows?
That's funny xm64 says you should delete the episode and skip to 667 make it a lost episode
People would have my head dude. I when i miss number episodes i get email which i'm grateful for i'm grateful for you guys fixing my mistakes
But
We've been like hey man, uh, let's see your podcast for a while. I noticed that you have your episodes are out of order
I was like, oh thanks, dude. So no which is nice
Getting that fixed 14 family. I was thinking about them the other day. I actually christian
doll olmo
Mentioned the uh the fact they have podcast used to be called the 14th century 14th family and i might actually do an episode
On that i got it. Yeah steward. It was super weird. I just i part of i've blanked out my screen now
So i can see your comments
But i did this during the live stream i did um
The other day last week i stare at myself
I stare at myself and the i think i mean i'm staring
And i think it's messes with my eyes. I think it makes me lightheaded. I think i end up talking faster
But no i'm doing totally fine. Yeah, i was sitting here and i was
If you're curious you can go back and watch it like i was i sat here for a second i thought
What do i do like i looked over and i think did i drink something wrong?
Did i drink some dick of yammon?
oh man
Um, i was like what should i do?
And i and i was part of me was like no just wrap it up and i was like nah
And look at you power through it you power through it
Score order says my girl mentioned the ringing and you hearing that silent did not exist prior to the 1800s
Is that a conspiracy theory she heard?
It would be interesting to know i i doubt i would 100 doubt that people in the 1800s
Were subjected to the amount of noises and noise pollution. We are
I bet you if you took someone from the 1800s and put them not i'm not just talking about honking horns
If you put them in a movie theater their ears would bleed
I think we have become so accustomed to such a loud noise think about it if you lived in a village
All your life and then someone played
The the the inception trailer at the normal volume that the inception trailer is played at here
People would other than the fact that people think demons were coming you they'd blow their eardrums out
I don't think a cow could ever be as loud as
At a normal theater let alone an i max theater so
that could be
They could have never heard that ringing because their ears were never never even close to being damaged as us
Unless they're working in some massive factory
Oh
And let me so i'll get to that in a second chain
Someone earlier asked how come my older episodes aren't available on the podcast app. They should be
I know that would probably be the podcast app itself. I do know that they're listed all the way
Back there
It shouldn't be
I'm sorry. I saw that comment. I was going to reply to it
um, every episode I have never
Put anything behind a paywall and I have never purposely removed episodes
I've had to edit episodes because of like massive errors in them
But
Recently when I had to fix
That I had a patreon supporter. I think now I'm always going to remember him as kyle
But I think his name was marked and I kept calling him kyle
Oh, that was irritating
I think he needs another ride in the carpenter copter for that one
But I've had to do edits, but I've never removed episodes. They should all be there
Shane Fitzgerald, I don't know why that episode is is listed. I saw that too on spotify. It's listed as like
The test episode. It's not a bad episode. I think it actually would get people interested in the show
When you like because I could pin monkeys don't exist or Mormon bigfoot, but those episodes are so old
I still think they're great. I still think great. I think the show is less sucky than it used to be
I used to put out episodes that I was like this episode sucks. Thank you, but I had a deadline. I was like, uh
Nowadays I'm what the reason why I think the show is better is I used to
Research stories and put them together and I would spend time researching stories that weren't any good
I'd spend a lot of time researching stories that weren't any good
I have a whole maybe folder and sometimes they pop up
Sometimes I'll hold on to them for months and months and months and then I'll have another story that complements it and then it's
perfect
But it used to be I would just find stories and put them together and sometimes the story sucked and I wouldn't have any
Backup. Sorry. I'd release the episode. I stopped doing that
around episode 100 or
Something or maybe 200 but anyways, I think the episodes are much tighter now
You could argue whether or not the conspiracies are as good. I did cover a ton of great stuff in the beginning
Like monkeys don't exist like the conformers and things like that
But I really still like the direction of the show. I like the stories recovering
Yeah, dead rabbit radio is anywhere you can get podcasts. It's on spotify. It's on apple podcast
It's on a podcast addict. It's anywhere you can listen to podcasts. That's that
So, yeah, no, it's a um
It's a podcast that's on youtube as opposed to a youtube show that's turned into a podcast
To slight distinction. But yeah, it's where if you I prefer to listen to podcasts on podcast apps, but I love this interaction
I absolutely love the fact that people
Um that I can talk to you guys like this
Barfee man says I sort of missed the long period of butthole and poop themed episodes. That was a period
I still have a few
You have to space those out like the episode the other day by the guy who hung himself
That one was pretty gory. Um, steward said it was kind of creepy and it was kind of that balance
But you you have to balance out the gross episodes because otherwise you're just you just do gross episodes and then people
Don't want to don't want to listen to you anymore or
That's all they want to hear and that's not all I want to talk about
But you do need to be occasional I've done some bad episodes. I've actually probably could do a rerun week
The lord of the rings episode I think
Is the worst episode of the run of the show
Lord of the rings is lord of the rings real
Is awful
It's so poorly edited it went on for like an hour and I cut it down to like 30 minutes
Then I realized I cut out too much stuff, but I was super bored when I was recording it
I think I actually wasn't feeling good either
I have a better recording schedule now and so that fits
Yeah, khaki cube says I like most of the episodes. I think that's fair
Not every not every episode is going to hit for you. I always do the episode. I think
About me listening to it. I create the shows for
me
Not just saying it's selfish, but I think we're all kind of the same
I think now there are days where I'm like, oh, I don't want to hear about another UFO store
I don't want to hear about bigfoot store. I'm not interested in that conspiracy
So you'll hit play you'll listen to what the two topics are for the show
And then you maybe you listen to half of it and then shut it off
Totally fine. I do it too. There are podcasts that I absolutely love
And I'll be listening to it and I'll be playing video games and then halfway through I'll pause it and I'll go
Do something else and I'll never finish listening to the episode
That that's just the way podcasts are you're not going to love every episode. I hope the episodes are enjoyable
I enjoy making them. I enjoy the stories, but
Yeah
It happens
It happens not everyone's going to love every one episode
Yeah, khaki cube says episodes 200 or early 300s
I think the show was still really raw
Then again, I think the topic because the topics are something that they come
And no level of skill or production value or experience the topics are the topics
So you can't really replicate that I think the store I think the show now is much tighter than it used to be
I'll listen to early episodes and I'll be like
It's so
There are episodes that I can't listen to and somebody picked one
To be I'm going to show it during the reruns for our next best of I think it's probably one of the worst episodes
It's a really good subject matter
It's a great story, but I totally messed it up
Is really really bad really really bad. So anyway, oh no a a a it's lord of the rings is based on a true story
Not that it was real
Book but that it's actually actual history
History yeah, barfing that says doesn't let relisten to depressing episodes totally fine
I used to relisten to the show
I think I've used to listen to the show more often now
I just produce too much stuff and I listen to it two or three times and for its release while I'm editing it and things like that but
Good night free. Yeah, thanks for coming out. Have a happy Thanksgiving
Um
A bonkerman says when you consider request you have some criteria in mind
Yes
This is generally what I look at when I get requests one. How is it obscure?
Like is it super well-known because that's really the main
Thing if it's super well known. That's why I've never covered like the great reset
I've never covered
Basic references to like QAnon. I've never done a deep dive into that
The reason why I covered adrenochrome was because sean puff daddy combs wrote that book
Wrote that book the adrenochrome witch
So, you know, that was a if it's here's the thing is it obscure first thing? Secondly if it's not obscure
Is there a new spin on it? So adrenochrome everyone knows about that the adrenochrome rich
Written by sean puff daddy combs
There we go there
And then is it funny or creepy?
So when you're looking at stuff or super interesting someone last night
dear
Dear gobelman dear grobbleman. I think it's on youtube sent me an article
Or sent me a lead for the story. I spent the neck and I knew normally don't spend this long right reading articles
I spend the next two hours reading this guy's life story
Super obscure never heard about it. It's not spooky. It's not scary, but it's incredibly interesting
So that's really the criteria. How obscure is it if it's obscure? Is there something else going on?
Is it funny or is it spooky or is it interesting and sometimes it's all three?
Thank you. Thank you
I'm gonna try this zolo zolitz
kuintale
sf
I'm glad you're enjoying the show and you have a Thanksgiving. You have a happy Thanksgiving as well. You have a happy Thanksgiving as well
Thank you the rampart. Thank you. I really appreciate it soybean taking over the world
That episode gets my number one episode is nicotine conspiracy theory
um
Is nicotine healthy for you recently someone there's a big youtube channel called blame it on a whore hay
Covered some oh medieval found footage. They covered medieval found footage. So I've been getting a lot of hits on that video
And um, you have a soy beans is soy bean intelligent
So a grand grand unified soy theory. It was the name of that episode that one gets a lot of stuff
I'm worried was I a fan of art bills catalog? Yeah
Yeah
I'm I'm a bit of a hipster though. I don't know if this is anti hipster hipster. I um
I really like george nori
Um, he was the one that I listened to the most. I remember
When I lived in sacramento
I had a period of time is about three months. I didn't have any electricity
So my only entertainment was a portable dvd player that I would power up during the day at college
I think I might have had a laptop, but this was back in like 2004
I did have a laptop, but there was the internet wasn't around like it is today. I don't think youtube was around
So I'd watch star trek voyager on my miniature dvd player
And I would listen to george nori at night on my ray battery powered radio
So yeah, it kept me going. I think these types of these type of shows are important. They were important to me
So thank you callum for that question. They're you know, they were important for me
Like I know what it's like to be alone and I know what it's like
To have a hobby that either people think is super weird
Or they think you're super weird for having it or they think you're dumb for having it
And being able to sit in the dark and go to bed listening to
george nori talked to people like me
And then you know mysterious universe was the same thing where here is this guy
I I I've listened to it
Over the years, but when I first started listening to it was just a guy and
He's talking about cool ghost alien stuff. It makes you not feel alone
And I think that's the most important thing
That people can do for each other. It's not a special superpower. It's not something that because I'm a podcaster, right?
We can all make each other not feel alone. So yeah, that's what george nori did for me
All that stuff. Yeah, and that's a good question. Okay, what are some popular or non obscure theories?
This is a question from khaki cube. What are some popular or non obscure theories paranormal events that you think could possibly be true?
um
I think there's a lot of them. I think that paranormal events again most of the time people are like I saw a ghost walking on the hallway
That's fine. I'm not I that doesn't affect me whether or not they saw a ghost or saw an aura
Whether or not they they saw an alien or you if it doesn't affect me it doesn't affect anyone
It's probably an interesting story. It may be true. I'm gonna accept it
At a face value it's when people start trying to fleece other people and this I think you guys might have caught on too
I didn't say this when I was wrapping this episode up
When people when people are selling 90 dollar glasses telling you can see auras that's ripping people off when people are telling you
You can attend their workshops to find out if you
Were reincarnated from Atlantis you're ripping people off if someone's just telling you hey, you know, I'm from Atlantis
Okay, that's totally fine. Thank you, ug. Thank you. Thank you very much for that
But when people start grifting each
That's when I'm I get that's when I start to get skeptical. That's when I'm like, okay. Well, let's hold on here
Um, let's see what this is all about because I think someone's ripping each other off
But it's but I think as far as so paranormal stories when Miley Cyrus
And demi lavato recently said that they saw UFOs. I'm like, yeah, they probably did
They they very may well have seen an identified flying objects or actual
Alien ships. I don't know. I hope they had fun seeing them. They're probably telling the truth
But when it comes to stuff like yawning eggs, that's when I'm a little more
I'm not answering your question. It's funny because I'm thinking the paranormal part as far as conspiracy is being true
um, I think a lot of the I remember hearing a conspiracy theory a long time ago that
uh, Lou Perlman
The I don't know if it's a conspiracy theory that was a conspiracy that Lou Perlman the manager of the Backstreet Boys
Um, was raping them
I remember hearing that a long time ago through like some back channels in the music biz
I don't even remember where I heard that from it's from one of my friends
We were all making music together. I'd heard that and I was like, what he's like. Yeah. Yeah, apparently
He raped the Backstreet Boys when they first got started and I was like, what are you talking about?
And apparently I guess he did one of them like it turned out to be true
He's in prison now, but I think he's in prison now for like tax fraud
So it's something like that
It's those little weird
Conspirators that you hear like you've got to sleep your way to the top and then like bird man starts banging little wane and all sorts of
Weird those type of conspiracies. I believe more and those are again very mainstream if you're into uh hip hop
you've definitely heard about bird man and
Little wane. I hope it's not true
Let's see here
Yeah, no problem moss no problem at all
I'm just reading these here
Uh, lanny lanny akea said what do I think about when a place that's supposed to be haunted is guarded by other people
Not like monks and robes or anything like that but when like the county purchases the property
We actually did that
Another story like that just the other day where there was a house that was supposed to be haunted that the county purchased
I find that extremely suspicious
I find that extremely extremely suspicious
When you have the government blocking off access to supposed haunted places. So yeah, even though it is a
it's
That's funny because charging people to go in a haunted house to me that could be
Kind of a grift but again, it's not hurt anyone
You have fun time walking around in a haunted house to cost you five bucks when you're paying like
The rampart says two thousand dollars an hour to go to a seminar to see if they are from mars. That's a grift
When you're ripping them off william burtles. Thank you very very much for that donation
And then yeah, ug as well. I wanted to appreciate that ug said dr
Is the most underrated content on youtube really appreciate that and william burtles says that thanks for keeping company in my mind intrigued during a
Difficult lonely year. I've been hearing that from a lot of you guys
So i'm glad that this show has been there. I mean dude. It definitely helped me those first six weeks or whatever
was um
Dude, I was just petrified man. Nobody knew anything. I was super scared. Thank you jones. Thank you really really appreciate that
I was the little little pear dude doing the bow
um, I was super
Paranoid i'm glad that I had this show to do. I'm glad that it didn't take any time off
I'm glad the show helped you guys as well
helped the community going
Yeah, i'm glad I was able to help you guys out because you guys helped me out as well
Um ug says your sotomy gamora episode was dark dude. Was that the one
Where god was raped? I'm pretty sure that was that episode. That was a dark one
That's an episode that I thought was I enjoyed
Making that episode. That's not an episode. I don't think anyone could listen to
It's not like a serbian film, but it's not an episode you want to listen to
Twice I think it's an interesting story and I think it's a rough ending
um
Yeah
Yeah, god was raped. I mean that's a powerful statement
um
That was real like when I was doing the uh conspiracy theory iceberg
that was one of the um
That was one of the episodes that I really wanted to cover was that one
um
That topic because it was just so evocative
But yeah, no, it was really interesting the um, shane Fitzgerald said have I caught any flak?
No, the only episode the episodes that I caught the most flak for
Um, harry potter was not written by jk Rowling. I to this day
Get comments about what an idiot I am for not reading the books and having an opinion on it
Which if I responded to stuff I'd go you don't listen to every episode of my podcast
So how can you have an opinion on my podcast? I see the thing is is like I don't
React to negative comments. I stopped reading them at a certain point
And thank you fellow content creator you had mentioned that earlier as well about supporting the show and I really appreciate that
I
Don't read negative comments
I don't read negative comments
If I start to recognize a certain username they're constantly leaving negative comments. I just stop reading their comments
Um, because some people that's what they'll do. I got I'm too busy for that. I'm too busy for that stuff
Um, that's funny free number 22 said god was raped sounds like a dark metal band
I'm assuming band not a dark metal bank to go there. Everyone's in goth makeup
I um, no, it's a good episode. It's not an episode. You'd want to listen to twice
I think the episode with my uncle is probably an episode. You don't want to listen to twice
um
Yeah, there's some episodes that are darker
I try to space those out because I want to show it to be there's a difference between it being creepy
And it being depressing
And sometimes there's a line there
Um, sometimes there's a line there like god was raped wasn't supposed to be creepy. I remember the one the guy with the nail jacket
Um, that was one that I had I had those notes ready to go for like four months
And I was like, no, I gotta have the right time for this. This story is really really distressing
And again, it was a story that I recorded it and I actually edited some of the grosser stuff out
Like this isn't gonna this doesn't add anything to the story. In fact, it goes from being creepy to depressing at that point
So those are all determinations you're gonna make because at the end of the day
You listen to this because one you want the company you want to hear the stories
George nori wasn't doing podcasts. George nori on the radio wasn't making you go to he might make you scared as you were going to sleep
But
But he never made you as far as I remember I never felt depressed
Maybe a little hopeless if I thought the world was going to end but I didn't feel down
No
You guys always leave positive comments kekky. Shane. No, it wasn't the nail gun murders. I forgot about that one
It was the guy who had
Nail he had a jacket. He had a long nether jacket with nails sticking out of it and studded nail collars
And he was raping women
It was rough
It was like back in the 70s
Yes xm 64 I was thinking about that. I was listening to dead world the other day
I have two rap songs on my youtube channel
dead world part one and two
Yeah, I can't think of a good name the story with the gang that went to the diner in new york. That's another one
That there's a story that I have
That I came across and it was so horrific
I go I have to talk about that on my show and then I thought this is so horrific
I can't talk about it on my show
It's like something right out of a horror movie. It happened super recently. It happened in organ during the great fires
It's a horrifying
horrifying story
So you have to figure the that balance out. Maybe I'll do that story when more time has passed
Maybe
But you have to balance that stuff
The I'll do the quick and leave I'll do a quick rundown and then we'll probably wrap it up Levi
The cart the castration fetish to me they're see that's not to me those stories are funny because everyone in it is a willing participant
If they were kidnapping people and cutting their balls off just because they were serial killers or whatever like that
It would be creepy. I probably wouldn't cover it as often
It's the fact that all three people could get together and all of them decide to chop off somebody's balls
It's super weird. I'll tell you this story. I don't have all the details with it, but it may ruin your Thanksgiving. So
Um, we'll we'll wrap it up like this. I'll tell you this story that recently happened here in the great fires
And if you don't want to hear it if you don't want it to be depressing
Have a happy Thanksgiving
Here we go
So again, I don't have the details. I don't have the dates and everything like that. I'll put it in the show notes
I don't I don't have the articles
There was this big wildfire up here in organ
See you later team man
There's a big wildfire up here in organ. They were going on for a while
and there was
this house in the middle of the woods
and like many people they lived out there and the fire was
Approaching but it was far enough away. They weren't in immediate danger
so the dad goes
There's like a dad a mom a son and a grandma
and a dog I believe
And the dad goes I'm going to run to the town to get some supplies and then I'm going to come back
And I don't we'll just hang out here or something like that like I don't really understand what their battle plan was
but the dad leaves
And while the dad's gone, there's a huge change in the weather and the fire begins to do a beeline right for that house
This is again really depressing guys so this kid
and the grandma
And I think the whole family gets into the car the whole family gets into the car
Dad's gone. So the mom the grandma the kid and the dog are all sitting in the car
and
The fire engulfs the vehicle
And the woman the mother apparently
Like the tires melt
The tires melt. I'm trying to remember the exact sequence of events here
So they're all in the car
We'll jump ahead. So what happens is
The dad is driving back to the house
The fire enveloped the house. He doesn't know it yet. He's driving back to the house. I guess he has to like
Secretly stealth by some firefighters or maybe this part of the road wasn't even barricaded at this point
He's driving. He's driving. He's driving and there's just flames everywhere
He sees that the area that his house is on fire. He's totally freaking out
And then he sees a figure walking down the street
And it is someone burned from head to toe
Walking out of the fire fire just smoking skin still smoking
And he runs and he throws a blanket around this person
I can't tell if it's a man or a woman is just this person
Everything's burned off. There was a blanket around the person
Throws the person in the back seat and the person goes hey comfy. Hey, yeah, have a great one
or um, yeah, thank you and then um the person in the back seat he goes I need to um
The woman goes oh no, I gave away the person in the back seat says take me to the hospital
And the guy says I find my family have to go find my wife and kids and that's when the person in the back seat goes
I am your wife
And she was so badly burned. He couldn't even recognize her. Everything was completely gone from her true story
It sounds like an urban legend sounds like something out of a horror book
But he did yeah, he took her to the hospital and then it turns out that the car was completely engulfed in flames
I think she jumped out of the car and ran
Is what happened or the car caught on fire and the woman was still in the house
She couldn't get to the car so she just took off through the fire running
And the um the son they found the grandma in the car
Everyone was dead in the car
The grandma was trying to drive the car the tires and melted and the boy was holding
His dog and they were all burned to death. So super grizzly
Super dark. It sounds like an urban legend story. Yeah, I know I know guys. I told you
um
Yeah, yeah, it's a that was a story that I was like I remember reading that thing
It sounds like an urban legend. It sounds like rampart says sounds like a creepypasta. Joan says sounds like something on snopes
um
A a dark story a dark story. Um
But yeah, I was like dude, uh, I don't I think his wife may still be alive. I'm not for sure
It was big news. It was absolutely big news in the area because it was such a shocking story
but um
Yeah, I was like I remember
Prepping it up and stuff like that and I thought
um
No, I don't want to share this story like this isn't and you guys are like telling on thanksgiving
Telling on thanksgiving. I thought
You know, because you listen to the podcast again, you want to be creeped out you want to have a laugh
You want to hear something interesting? I have to be careful at how grizzly the stuff gets and when I do it
There has to be this story if I told on the podcast it would just be like
Oh, here's a creepy. You know what? I mean, it is creepy, but there's that depressing element to it as well
but
Happy thanksgiving don't let it don't let it be sad though. I mean, it's a sad story but you know, um
Yeah, it's it's a sad there's no uplifting side to it. There's no uplifting side to it
um
No, I have not heard of a hamper lady's song. I might be able to check that out, but yeah
They're writing about a burn victim. Um
Yeah, the barfing man that story about the guy who was wearing the santa claus suit and threw a molotov cocktail and it
melted to his skin
So, yeah, that was a story that I remember thinking was too depressing, but I the my level of interest
I'd been that it was a story I'd been thinking about for years
Oh, and then cat I will wrap it up like this because I do have to uh take off but
As far as going as far as what I think about skinwalker ranch. It's funny
I just read an article the other day about how the security personnel there makes stories up
Because their boss gets mad when people don't see anything. So they say that they actually they just make stuff up
Skinwalker ranch is one of those things. I know like jet propulsion labs
I believe is out there a bunch of scientific groups have been out there and things like that
I don't
It may be real
It may be real. Um, it's something that I looked into a lot back in the day
And then it became just so well known that I've just kind of gathered stuff through osmosis here and there
Um, again, it's one of those places that they're like here. We can get scientific proof of this stuff
Why do you want scientific proof of it? Like even if you have scientific proof people?
It's going to question the science just enjoy
Just enjoy it. Enjoy the experience. Don't you don't have to try to convert other people
And then um, yeah, you know, I've looked into it. It's not I'm not a huge
I've like Hitler conspiracies not see conspiracies to me. Those are pretty well known
Um, I've looked I've looked into some of the people who were involved in esoteric hitlerism
Like one of them killed himself by jumping into like a piano string or he did something super weird
He jumped he jumped into a piano
Like one of the guys killed himself by jumping like face first into a band saw or something like that
I was like, oh, that's interesting
But the fact that people think that a world leader is actually some sort of deity or some sort of god
Whether or not it's seen that's the thing like because it involves hitler
It has a certain level of like ooh it's more spooky
but it's no different than people who thought like Stalin was the reincarnation of a god or
Um, you know, all the chinese dynasties are supposed to be descended from gods
So the the story itself isn't super interesting to me
That's basically what it is a group of people believe that their leader is from god
And that it goes on this very day
Whether that leader is from your local church or it's the president or it's some king or something like that. So yeah
Yeah, I'm sure there are people who believe in esoteric Stalinism
Why wouldn't there be like it? I know that's the thing I've looked into and I was like, it's kind of interesting
Sometimes there's stuff where it's just like it would be me reading
Reading facts and that's not fun
So it'd be like this person believes this about hitler and this person believes this about hitler
And then this other person believes that there's like three of the main ones and I go isn't that wacky
Like it's interesting, but it's it doesn't really translate to a podcast
That basically be what it would be
um
And again, I think it's it's the same thing as there are people who it would basically be the equivalent of like
Anyone believing their particular world leader at that particular time
was a
Descended or chosen by god to run and things like that
Yeah, so I think that is interesting. So the same thing with uh adam waffen or the order of the nine angels
It would be me reading facts
About those groups. All of those groups are very well known. You can definitely check them out on wikipedia
There's been tons of articles written on them. I've researched them. It would basically be me saying this this this
is a thing
And that's not super interesting to me and I don't think it comes across well on a podcast
Especially when you can read that stuff online you can dig into it as much as you want
What would what would the podcast episode be?
Like what how would I what would I do what would I say about those groups?
It would be the same thing. You know what I mean? I get that those groups have a like people assign them a different level of
um, I don't want to say value, but a different level of
Intriguingness of intrigue because it's related to but I've never like I've never been super into
uh, Nazi myths or uh, you know, I've never seen them as
this like super um interesting thing
So I think that's why usually when I'm reading them. I'm just like
Because I was never into them and then yeah when when I'm doing stuff like a group. It's
It's just like here's a group. This is what they do
I've done death cults, but it's not just like the colonial dignidad
Um, that was that group had a middle of beginning and an end it ended
And I was able to tell the story of this rise of power and then the height of corruption and then they're downfall
There's a narrative arc by just saying these groups exist
There's not not really any narrative hooked there even esoteric hitlerism was like these people believe this thing
And then one guy jumped into a band saw or however he killed himself
And that's it and it's just what everyone else believes but no, I appreciate the suggestions, but
I a lot of people have recommended those over the year two years and it's just not
It's just not super interesting to me. Um, let's see here
Did you do do do
Take a look at these other things
Calla yuga I can look into it, but I
I might have come across that but I might have not it may fall into that same thing where it's just
um
A group that exists
So we'll take a look at it, but I'll check that out. Um
I would recommend
Emailing me that so I make sure you get credit because a lot of times when I have to give credit for the chat
I have to go fighting through it. I have to go through it, but I'm gonna head out now
I actually have to now process this episode get it uploaded to the podcast
I gotta do a couple little tweaks and stuff like that. Okay. Calla yuga is the nazi version of raggedon rock. Yeah, I can check it out
We'll see what it's like
We'll go from there, but guys go ahead and email me that stuff you guys have a good one guys have a happy Thanksgiving
Thanks for everyone coming out
um
It was a lot of fun. It was a lot of fun. Um, yeah, I just don't do like doing quick facts stories
I like telling a story. I don't they're boring to record and they're super boring at it
And I'm sure they're boring listen to but you guys have a great Thanksgiving guys have an awesome weekend
I'm gonna get this uploaded
We're gonna have uh you guys I'm gonna have a fun weekend. Hopefully I hope you guys have a fun weekend
Thank you for joining us here today at dead rabbit radio. I love you guys and I will see you on
Monday
Go back here. I'll see you guys on Monday. Hey, no problem you guys. Thanks for being here. Thank you for being here
Have a good one guys
Bye I'm a wave and oh, you know what let's give Veronica in here for the ending
She didn't get to join her episode
We'll end it like this
Um
[BLANK_AUDIO]