You've heard of cattle mutilations that have humans been subject to this extreme behavior
as well.
And then we're going to end on a light note today as we talk about the smelliest smell
ever recorded today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
I'm feeling a little under the weather.
I don't know if it's the weather change or if I was out in the cold a little too much
or a little bit of the flu.
It could be a combination of all three.
So we'll go ahead and get through this and then I'm going to crank my heater up and watch
some movies.
Yeah, I'm just not, my tummy's not feeling 100%.
I think I'm just tired though.
Like I've just been working hard.
And just another quick reminder.
After this week, I'm taking a week off.
So the first week of November, I will not be producing anything Dead Rabbit related.
We will come back with season three, the second week of November.
So after Friday, I'm going to go ahead and take a week off and just kind of rest.
I'm actually going to catch up on some research, but we're not going to be recording anything.
So we'll be back for season three at the beginning of the second week of November and I will
be ready to go.
So first thing I want to talk about, actually, you know, I want to talk about this first
too, because it's not necessarily a whole segment by itself is just really, really weird.
Something recently happened.
Okay.
So the article came out on Monday, which is today, but it was Friday.
So the 27th of October in Oakland, California, these police, they're working in their downtown
office, you know, just doing paperwork, stuff like that.
And some people come in and they're like, we think we found a human head.
And the cops are like, you know, it's a close to Halloween.
They figured either the people were pulling a prank on them.
They're like, oh, we're either going to laugh at this or we're going to arrest you for wasting
our time.
Or they thought, well, these guys probably just found some prop, some Halloween prop,
and it looks super realistic.
And they figured, you know, it's just a, it's a prank.
It's a prank, bro.
It's just a prank.
The cops go, the people bring the head and these two people, they're like, hey, we have
this head.
You might want to investigate it.
And they bring it in and the cops, it takes them not very long to realize it is a real
decapitated human head.
And they said, this was the quote, it was decomposed and had a little bit of flesh on
it.
I can say in my years of service, I've never had a human skull delivered to the police station.
And these people, they found it in the backyard of an apartment complex.
And so immediately the cops are like, okay, this is an actual, this is first off that's
gross.
Secondly, we need to investigate this.
Like I said, this just happened this weekend.
They don't know who the head belongs to.
They don't know how it got there.
They don't know how the person died.
They've been asking people around the apartment complex.
They see any weird stuff lately.
And that's pretty much all they have to go on is two people showing up with the head.
I'm sure they were initial suspects, but yeah, weird, weird.
Someone out there got their head chopped off and it was thrown in an apartment complex
backyard.
And it must have been there.
I'm wondering if it was either there for a bit and no one noticed it or it was somewhere
else and they transported it and got rid of it at the apartment complex.
But Oakland police, I'm sure they had other things going on that night or they were super
bored one or the other, but now they definitely have a case with very little evidence and
no crime scene that they now have to solve.
So we'll keep you informed if anything more comes of that.
I don't think it will, but yeah, we'll keep you informed.
Next thing I wanted to talk about.
So I did the episode on Operation Plate.
Now it's funny because I try to keep my shows relatively short under 30 minutes tops.
That Operation Plate, that segment alone was 28 minutes and it was funny because I recorded
it and then I'm editing it and usually I'll record it and then every episode gets about
20 minutes edited out of it.
That segment was so lean.
I left the bare bones of that story in to the episode.
I recommend you guys following the links and reading more because there are tons of first
hand, I took out, had to take out a couple of the villagers first hand encounters of
the Chupa Chupas because I was just simply running out of time.
There were, a lot of people had their own encounters with these vehicles or creatures
or whatever they were and I was like, I'd love to include all these little tidbits but
I just, I needed to keep it lean.
Having it clock in, I think the episode was around 35 minutes, was literally as short
as I could get it with having every plot point.
Everything that was in there almost had to be in there.
But I recommend out of all the episodes I've done, that's the one that you click on those
links you're going to read some really cool first hand UFO encounters.
So I encourage you to go back to that and check those links out.
But when I was researching that, I came across an article, it was deaths attributed to UFOs
or you know people who had died during the investigation of UFOs, things like that because
a couple people had died by the Chupa Chupas.
And I came across a couple stories too to be exact of human mutilation.
Now not human mutilation like some gross old serial killer or some like gang bangers, but
people who they suspected were human forms of cattle mutilation.
Now if you don't know what cattle mutilation is, it is the theory that cows are abducted
by aliens and they do these surgical procedures to them.
Generally their eyes are removed, their anus is removed, all the blood is drained from the
body, they have like these burn marks in their skin, they have these holes bore into them.
And the reason why we know about it is that we find cows in the middle of nowhere and
they're missing their eyes and they're missing their anus, they're missing their genitals and
they don't have any blood and farmers have been dealing with this problem for a long time,
I mean in recorded, like in the past mostly like say 40, 50, 60 years there's been more
documentation of these cattle mutilation.
And the theories started off as like oh it's a satanic cult or it's UFOs or it's some
sicko out there traveling all of the United States doing these things to cows, but farmers
do find these cows, they can't find them and then when they do find them they're missing
their eyes and other soft tissue parts of their body.
And the theory with UFOologists is that they're being abducted, tested on and then being
dropped back off.
Now the question of whether or not humans have been subjected to this, you know, people
believe, some people believe that we do have proof of it because we have two stories of
bodies that have been found in similar states.
So there was an interesting story that came out of New Mexico in 1956, it's known as the
Jonathan Lovett incident.
So Jonathan Lovett and William Cunningham were friends and they were in the military
together and they said, William Cunningham, so spoiler alert, you think you know what
happens to Jonathan, William Cunningham says that him and Jonathan were out and about and
they were looking for like missile debris, that there was a missile test or something
that had happened and they had to go find pieces of it that fell off for their job I'm
assuming, I don't assuming they're just collectors.
Cunningham comes back to the base alone and he says something took Jonathan.
They went to go look at these sand dunes to go find this debris.
Actually, and now I've kind of figured out probably what happened here, but they go to
the sand dunes to look for this debris and all of a sudden Jonathan Lovett disappeared.
He couldn't find like he was gone in a heartbeat.
And then Cunningham heard the screams, he ran over and he saw Lovett there and there was
a silver disc hovering over Jonathan Lovett and these like, he described him as snake-like
creatures but basically these tendrils came out of the vehicle, wrapped around Jonathan
Lovett and sucked him into the boat and a boat, sucked him into the spaceship or whatever
it was, the silver disc and then it flew away.
People were thinking that Cunningham know he must have done something to him and buried
the body or something like that, but what happened was eventually Jonathan Lovett's
body was discovered and he had these wounds such as removal of the eyes, ears and tongue
and according to this article on UFOinside.com, every drop of blood had also been removed
from the carcass.
So that's a little spooky.
You're out with your buddy, palling around the dunes and the little spaceship zooms
him up and then it flies away with him and then you find his body and he has the wounds
that we attribute with cattle mutilations.
The next story we have on that actually has less information but more documentation because
unfortunately we have photos of this poor fellow.
We don't know who he was and took place in Brazil which is kind of weird because we were
just there with our Operation Plate episode.
This took place at the Go...Gawana Paringa Reservoir.
It's south of, say, south...
It's south of São Pablo.
São Pablo is how you say it but anyways, so they found this body and the pictures are
quite grisly so don't be clicking on the links if you don't want to see a picture of a screaming
dead man because this guy, he has his lips completely eaten away, his anus is completely
gone, he has damage to the genitals, his organs are also messed up, gone.
Let me read...so this is from the autopsy report.
I'm going to read this specifically because this is important.
From the autopsy report, we observed the removal of the right and left orbital areas
such as your eyeballs, emptying of the mouth cavity, pharynx, or pharynx, neck, right and
left armpit area, abdomen, pelvic cavity, right and left groin area, the axolary regions
on both sides showed soft spots where organs had been removed and so on.
Decisions were made on the face, internal thorax, abdomen, legs, arms, and chest.
Shoulders and arms have preparations of 1 to 1.5 inches in diameter where tissue and
muscles were extracted.
The edges of the preparations were uniform and so were their size.
The chest had shrunk due to the removal of internal organs.
Cause of death.
Acute hemorrhage in multiple traumatisms.
There is a component of cause of mortis by vagus stimulation.
Implying cardio respiratory arrest caused by extreme pain.
So basically he had a heart attack as he was in so much pain.
The victim showed injuries of vital reaction characteristics.
As in there is the component torture.
The suggested modis operandi is incisions and soft parts natural orifices using sucking
devices.
He died of a heart attack caused by pain.
And I read on other websites too that his body was also completely drained of blood.
So here's the thing.
So cow mutilations for the most part have been debunked.
Yes, that is real.
The cows are being found with their soft organs gone.
And they're missing some of their blood.
And that's why hyperbole is very important with conspiracy theory.
They're missing blood but they're not completely drained.
There's not a single drop of blood in them.
So in 1979 there was Sheriff Herb Marshall.
Herb or herb?
I think it doesn't matter.
I've always said herb.
Herb?
Wait no do I say it?
I guess I say herb if it's a person.
Anyways he's in Arkansas and he goes you know what?
I'm having all these reports of cattle mutilations and the farmers and ranchers are telling me
that they think UFOs are taking them or satanic culture or whatever.
But I think it's something more natural.
So he took a cow carcass and he threw a freshly killed cow and he threw it out and they watched
it for 48 hours straight.
No one showed up to drain anything from it and they blow flies.
It was basically maggots turning it to flies and predators which will go for the soft tissue.
They'll burrow holes in you and they'll eat out your butt hole and they'll eat out your
eyes and your lips because that's all the easiest things to eat.
Path of least resistance.
And then after that another research group I believe it was in Canada did a similar experiment
and they said yeah I mean everything you can attribute to well let's let me back up.
Most of the things you can attribute to cattle mutilation happen just naturally in the world.
And you go well Jason ranchers and farmers they see dead cows all the time don't you think
they would know this was natural?
And they do see dead cows all the time but they don't find the carcass they see a dead
cow and they get to it before all the scavengers.
It's eat dying on their farm as opposed to a cow getting away from the farm dying and
then four days later they find it.
So the two humans who died.
It's possible that one the guy from Brazil was tortured to death and just the rest of
the damage was done by predators.
I think this the guy in Brazil was probably killed very horribly maybe they were like
sucking his organs out while he was still alive.
But again the most logical answer was he was murdered by other humans and we just found
his body later.
The guy in New Mexico I mean I don't want to cast dispersions or anything but it's most
likely again the most likely answer is he was killed by his friend.
I do think it's weird that if I murdered a guy in the middle of nowhere my go-to story
would not be a UFO kidnapped him unless I figured the body would never be discovered.
So if I murdered somebody in the middle of nowhere I would not then go to the cops and
say oh my god dude my friend something terrible happened to him they're like what happened
and I said a UFO abducted him like that wouldn't be my go-to thing so if he did murder him
I the story may have evolved over time because I'm seeing that a lot doing this podcast I'm
seeing a lot.
Now again let me go to that real quick.
Recently I'm sure the original story for both of these bodies were like there was no blood
at the crime scene like we didn't find a lot of blood and now it's become there's no blood
at all in the body it's been completely drained and I know that's 100% false for this Brazil
one because in the excerpts of the autopsy report that I just read to you there is no
mention of the body having no blood in it like zero blood whatsoever.
If it said that on the autopsy report this website would have definitely highlighted
that part because that helps their theory.
This website is one of the sites that talks about the body's drain of blood especially
when it talks about Jonathan Love it.
So if the body actually had no blood if the coroner could say this body has not a single
drop of blood in it I think the body probably didn't have a lot of blood in it and then
over time the story has morphed to saying it had no blood none at all it's just completely
dry.
There's biological actions that take place with blood and everything like that.
That's why there's not blood everywhere from every time someone spilled blood because
little things are eating it.
But anyways both of these stories can be logically explained.
The cows being found with their eyes being bore out and their buttholes gone and stuff
like that and these two gentlemen who have similar wounds my thing with the whole catamethyl
the catamethylation thing the idea of it is creepy to begin with that there's vehicles
out there beyond our understanding that are abducting cows and possibly humans and experimenting
on them and just dropping off in the middle of nowhere for us to find it it's creepy you
find like this carcass you don't know how it got there or why it suffered the wounds.
Some people say that some of the cows have looked like they broke their necks due to
drops from heights and how else would a cow fall unless it was beamed up and then dropped.
My pushback to the whole alien side of the catamethylation thing is that so what we have
to accept is a race of people a race of beings have built ships that are beyond our understanding
of technology and they also have the ability to beam things up or have tendrils that can
come down and grab you and pull you up into their ship and then they just throw your body
out when they're done with it they don't have an incinerator they don't have I mean we have
incinerators if we if somebody does something they don't want anyone to know about just
throw it in a fireplace at the very least or you take them to a crevatory but somehow
these aliens have all this advanced technology and they go man we're doing these experiments
and we hope nobody finds out because our experimentation isn't done yet we need to have all these cow
anuses to be able to take over the planet and yet they just throw the cows outside why don't
they fly over the ocean and drop them into the ocean make it more difficult for us to
suss out what their plan is so I mean the story of the aliens that automatically has
that weak point and you could say well the aliens want us to know no they don't know
they don't ever never ever that's there's there would be no reason for them to want
to leave evidence if the point of it was to do some sort of experiment on it they would
just dump them off when we kidnap monkeys and experiment on them to do makeup we don't
then take the monkey bodies and throw them back in the jungle to let the other monkeys
know that we're doing it or to so fear in the monkey population no we dispose of the
bodies in a laboratory or in a crematory I think well you know the the guy again the
the military guy I don't want to disparage him at all but I think him and his buddy were
probably out doing something that was frowned upon in the 1950s and something happened and
the best story he could come up with is a giant snake slithered out and got his buddy
which you can read in the Freudian implications of that if you'd like I think that's far more
likely than a group of beans far more advanced than us took a dude drilled out his butthole
and threw him on the ground I but I don't think that I for one the whole story may be
made up it may just be part of ufo ology lore but it's also very likely that he did something
to his friend and made the story up and with the new Mexico thing my question to be why
didn't you fo take the witness as well a man did die we're assuming the whole story could
be completely made up because one thing another thing I've learned during this podcast is
sometimes you see the same story repeated over and over again and then it turns out it's
just me it's just completely not true but let's assume the story is true why didn't
the UFO take cunning him to why did it let a witness go and again I say why did the
UFO then dump the body later why didn't it just incinerated and the guy goes missing
and that way the alien and whoever was piling in the ship would be like I pulled one over
on those good old Yankees flying away but instead it drops the body the guy got the murder
charges you didn't get charged with murder and stuff like that the entire story just kind
of smells in general hey you know what actually that's a good segue because speaking of smells
I came across this this is going to be really short because I think it's hilarious there's
not a ton of information on it it's true though we'll say that here is a word I can't pronounce
you I know you guys love this when I'm talking about stuff that I can't pronounce so this
is a compound called thioacetone thioacetone and it is a it basically is a terrible terrible
smell now you go all that you know that's not bad Jason stuff smells all the time you should
smell your mama's feet or something like that no this stuff is so gnarly and it spreads
out thioacetone is more than just a bad smell it's described as fearful quoting this article
here it says it makes innocent downwind pedestrians stagger clutch their stomachs and flee in terror
it reeks to a degree that makes people suspect evil supernatural forces so they don't know
why it smells so bad it has they believe it has something to do with the sulfur component
of the compound but it basically will just unleash through a city I think it's like up
to a half a kilometer it's this huge range where you will be just walking on the street
and you'll be like it's so bad when they back in 1889 was the first time that it was really
know this effect on it was truly notated it says the reaction produced an offensive smell
which spread rapidly over a great area of the town causing fainting vomiting and a panic
evacuation because people just started you were just minding your own business and the
worst smell you could ever imagine hit you and you're like you would think the world
was ending if you heard it is melt this so again I don't want to be reading quotes the
whole night but I just think these are so funny so this happened in the 1960s okay now
we're in I think Britain yeah okay recently we found ourselves with an odor problem beyond
our worst expectations during early experiments a stopper jumped from a bottle of residues
and although replaced it once resulted in an immediate complaint of nausea and sickness
from colleagues working in a building 200 yards away two of our chemists who had done
no more than investigate the cracking of minute amounts of triathletone found themselves the
object of hostile stairs in a restaurant and suffered the humiliation of having a waitress
spray the area around them with the deodorant the odors defied the expected effects of dilution
since workers in the laboratory did not find the odors intolerable so when they were super
close to it they didn't notice it and I'm assuming I know sometimes you're they have
that delicacy in Sweden that's the rotted fish and you open it up and the smell is so
bad it burns your nose so you can't smell it but if you like walk into the room after
the cans opened you're going to be physically sick because it smells so bad you have to
be there when it's open so these two chemists they're messing around they immediately like
they're not basically their nose hairs give up and die but as the smell left the laboratory
it was totally noxious now they said this the chemists were like there's absolutely no
way that was us because the laboratory is a closed system the smell could not leave the
laboratory to convince them otherwise we're going back to the quote here to convince them
otherwise they were dispersed with other observers around the laboratory at a distance up to
a quarter of a mile and one drop of either acetone gem I'm not going to go into that
and one drop of either one chemical I can't pronounce or this other chemical I can barely
pronounce were placed on a watch glass and a fume cup cupboard the odor was detected
downwind in seconds so now these two chemists now they're out of the laboratory and they're
walking around and they could just be like oh my god this is the worst smell ever I don't
know why they don't use this as a weapon I'm wondering if the smell how long the smell
lingers in a particular area but it seems like it would be a really efficient like you can
prepare for like loud noises you can prepare for bright lights but you kind of have to be
able to breathe like you can plug your nose up with stuff but in some sort of like right
situation you're going to want to have the ability to breathe in and out of both your
mouth and your nostrils if you're walking into a right situation you already have ear plugs in
heavy sunglasses and now you've got plugs up your nose you're really limiting your ability to interact
with other people in a rioting situation I we shoot tear gas into people's houses I think it
would and actually that probably answers the question right there tear gas can be fairly
contained but anytime you would use this weapon like if someone was in their house and you're like
come out of your house they're like no and then you're throwing stink bombs into their house
yeah everyone suffers you're gonna have a quarter of a mile of people being like what did I do
wrong what did I do wrong why does it smell so bad and then if you lived in a bad neighborhood it
would constantly be happening and so yeah I kind of want to end it on end on a light note today
usually like the end story is kind of the heavy story but I was like you know what we had a rough
weekend it's been a rough weekend for everybody involved you just had all that craziness that
happened here in the United States and I was like let's end on a funny note today plus I'm not feeling
100% as far as just my tummy but I know I talk about the grossest stories this episode but yeah
it was nice to end on a light note I should say dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our
email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @jsonnellcarpenter
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast you don't have to
listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys