A man is trying to have a nice relaxing nap on his couch, until the world of the paranormal
wakes him up.
And then we take a look at an amazing story that took place 19,000 feet in the air.
It was supposed to be a simple delivery on a FedEx plane.
Instead it turned into a life and death encounter in the not so friendly skies today on DeadRabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of DeadRabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are ready for a wham bam action packed episode.
You're like no I'm not.
You're trying to get your homework done, you're trying to get your finals done, you're trying
to relax.
Wake up!
No relaxing this episode.
First off, let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, coming in with
giant bags of stimulants for us all.
We gotta stay up.
It's WilliamFontaineDelator.triev.
And hopefully I just didn't out you as a speed dealer.
They're not real stimulants officer, they're magical stimulants.
Which are twice as powerful and ten times more illegal.
William, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or if you're not a truck dealer like William,
that's fine too.
Just helps for the word about this show.
Really really helps out a lot.
After we pay William's bail and get him out of jail, William, I'm gonna toss you the keys
to the Jason Jalopy.
We're gonna leave behind lock up and we are headed out to Chrisfield, Maryland.
This story was recommended to us by Kent Allard, long time listener Kent Allard.
He actually recommended two previous stories to us and all of these stories take place
in the town of Chrisfield, Maryland.
This town is a population of 2,726 people.
We have three episodes from this town.
This town is basically seven dead kids away from being Pennywise territory.
It's a lot of spookiness, a lot of high strangeness for such a small town.
This story and the other ones came from a history book about Chrisfield and the surrounding
areas so thank you Kent for sending this over.
We're at a little house on Charlotte Avenue.
Don't mean to dock you, don't mean to dock you.
The story is from 1943 so I'm pretty sure you're dead.
I'm not saying it like it's a good thing but I don't think you can docks the dead.
You're like, "Hey look at that gravestone over there.
That's Abraham Lincoln."
We're at this little house on Charlotte Avenue.
It's the home of Captain Jim Tucker and it's July 19th, 1943.
And Captain Jim Tucker is out there working on his boat and he's like, "Ah, the pirate's
life, I'm not a pirate.
The captain's life for me," he says and he's like working on his boat and he's like, "That's
I'm done.
I'm leaking.
There's a bunch of barnacles trying to pilot it away."
He's like, "I'm done."
He leaves it because it's too hot outside.
It's July in Maryland.
He's walking back to his house.
He goes, "You know what?
I'm just going to lay on my couch, catch a couple of z's and wake up later.
Hopefully my boat is still afloat and I will finish working on it."
But as he's laying down, he feels a hot flash right in his face.
Wakes him up.
You know what that is, right?
It could be a fireball.
That's pretty much the only thing he could be right.
He jumps up.
He jumps up off the couch and he's trying to figure out what it was and he realizes now
his entire house is as hot as it is outside, which is not what you want.
Which is not what you want.
That's why we have houses in the first place for it to be different than the elements.
And while he's trying to figure out what's going on, Martha, Martha, did you feel that?
He's looking over.
He has this mirror in his living room.
It's a big round mirror.
It's about 24 inches in diameter.
He's looking at the mirror and he goes, "Oh my God."
Word starts getting around town.
Captain Jim Tucker is going around town.
He's a bit of a braggart.
He's a bit of a boaster.
He's going around town.
He goes, "Guys, you won't believe what just happened.
I was outside working on my boat.
It was super hot outside.
It went in the house.
The house was as hot as it was outside."
They're like, "Maybe you should shut the door when you go."
And he's like, "No, you don't let me finish the story."
The mirror is magic.
I have a magical mirror now.
Did you know that?
I probably should have started with that instead of the whole lead up about fixing my boat.
So people are like, "We want to see your magical mirror, of course."
No one's going to be like, "Oh, check it out later.
I got better things to do."
Everyone's coming to his house to check out this magical mirror.
Now this is what was going on.
This was reported in the Chris Field Times newspaper.
On the one hand, it's really weird that the newspaper is reporting this story.
On the other hand, previously, they reported a story about a man who shot a photo of a
witch, thinking it would kill the witch.
Instead the bullets went through the photo, went through the photo, and into the house
next door making the next door neighbor scream.
Slow news day or just the coolest town ever you'd decide.
This is what's going on with this mirror.
When you look at it, it takes a second for you to see it, but then you see an island.
You see an island with palm trees off in the distance.
And it's not like you're looking at a drawing.
I know when I was reading this story I was imagining like the far side of just like a
little cartoon island.
No, this looked like you were looking through a window.
You were seeing an island covered in palm trees off in the distance and then up to nine different
ships.
They said there were some tankers, some freighters, some warships.
They didn't actually make it.
It wasn't cool enough.
It wasn't television.
It wasn't making sound effects.
They're watching these boats go by.
"All hands on deck."
Oddly enough the newspaper described one of the ships like this.
Because the journalists of the Critsfield Times went here as well.
First it was just a bunch of Captain Jim's drunk buddies coming from the bar.
And then a really small word spread in town.
The journalist, he might have been a drunk too for all I know.
He is reporting on witches.
He has this quote.
He wrote in his article, "One ship has its stern up out of the water so the keel can
be seen and apparently is about to plunge beneath the sea."
So again it's not like just these vague images.
It's action packed.
Something's about to go down here.
This story is taking place in 1943.
So during 1943 Captain Jim Tucker had a lot of relatives, a lot of young men he knew
in the Pacific fighting against the Japanese.
Even everyone in town knew at least one person who was overseas and a good portion of them
were in the Navy and a good portion of them were in the Pacific front.
So he's looking at this and he's afraid it might be an omen.
Obviously the island with the palm trees would make you think tropical.
And then the warships and the boat that looks like it's about to go under kind of made him
think it was an omen.
That's the end of the article though.
We don't have any more information.
This is a collection in this history of Chris Field book.
This particular section is some of their weirdest articles.
Some weird true crimes, some weird paranormal stuff like this.
So this was actually reported in this newspaper.
I was able to verify this newspaper existed when I covered it on previous episodes.
But there's no follow up to it.
We don't know if his loved ones made it home safely.
We don't even know how long the images lasted.
They lasted long enough for multiple people in town to see it but after this article was
reported we don't know if you could still see them to this day as they were a mirror
somewhere in Chris Field, Maryland.
The most cursed town in the United States that is still displaying this image.
Or a different image now.
Something else.
Something showing another vision of a future or a past or something happening right then
but across the world.
And what did the hot flash have to do with anything?
Here's the thing, it would be one thing if he came in and had a heat stroke and he was
like "Ugh, I shouldn't have been drinking all that seawater while I was working on my
boat" and solved this.
That would be totally one thing.
It could still be reported in the newspaper.
Very very slow news name, Mansover's Heatstroke hallucinates.
But the fact that other people were able to see it as well.
What was up with the heat?
Was that creating the effect in the mirror?
Is that what opened the portal of the mirror?
Was it something completely unrelated to it?
It's just a weird story.
It's one of those stories that I like.
Sometimes I love stories that have concrete answers.
I love solving mysteries.
But you don't get that a lot in this line of work.
And then I like the stories like this that are just super open-ended.
We don't know if this is some sort of magic mirror.
We don't know if this is some sort of fortune telling mirror.
Which is the same thing technically.
But you know what I mean?
Was this a ghost event?
Was this telling the future?
Was it an alternate reality?
Was it showing him in another world?
What was behind this?
What crafted this?
That's what I like about this story.
We don't have a concrete answer.
It's not aliens.
It's not ghosts.
Not demons.
We don't know what it is.
It's just a mirror.
The reason why I like those stories is because they're the stories that can happen to anybody.
And also it's not terrible, right?
It's not like he looked in the mirror and saw himself holding his eyes out and he goes
"Soon!"
Like that's not fun.
I don't want that to happen to anybody.
But if tomorrow I want to go brush my teeth and I'm looking in the mirror and I see like
a boat sailing by and I see much dudes singing a sea shanty, that's cool.
I'm in the shower and they're like "Yo ho ho.
I'm trying to sleep through it.
Yo ho ho.
That would get annoying after a while."
But I'd still invite people over to see it.
I wouldn't invite them over to see an image of themselves holding their eyeballs going
"Soon!"
They're like "Jason, I don't know if I want to come over to your place while your friends
have cut their eyeballs out."
I'm like "What?
That's fake news dude.
Come on over man.
Nothing's going to happen."
Yet.
William, I'm going to toss you the keys to the Carbentercopter.
We're going up, up and away.
We've got to get high in this story.
Not the type that requires all those stimulants.
William, I'm going to toss you the keys to this Carbentercopter.
We are leaving behind Chrisfield, Maryland.
I have no doubt we will be there again soon.
Because there's a bunch more articles from there.
We are headed out to Memphis, Tennessee.
I'm going to Graceland.
Graceland.
Every so often, and this is one of the things I love about doing this show, every so often
I come across stories that I can't wait to tell you guys.
And I'll tell people about them.
I'll tell people about them.
They're like having lunch with me.
They're like, "Guys, you won't believe this.
This is one of those stories.
I don't want to hype it up too much."
But when I read it, I was like, "Dude, this is so dope."
And it happened in most of our lifetimes.
And I never heard of this before.
William, go ahead and land us here at this airport in Memphis, Tennessee.
It's April 7th, 1994.
And I got most of my information from an article written by Max Garland for the Memphis Commercial
Appeal.
We're walking around this airport.
We're walking around with our aviator glasses, our cool jumpsuits, the theme song to Iron
Eagle is playing in the background.
When I did that last story, right, when I did the story about the mirror, I go, "Oh, Captain
Jim Tucker."
And I always like to dig a little bit more.
I wanted to find out, I wanted to find out, like, did he lose a loved one in the war?
What happened to him?
Did he ever get his boat repaired?
These are questions I needed answered.
So when I typed in Captain Jim Tucker, this story came up because this story has a Jim
Tucker in it.
So oddly enough, whether it was fate that brought me to this awesome story, whether
this is his descendant, who knows, maybe he survived a boat tipping over in the Pacific.
And he's here now, but it's April 7th, 1994.
There's a FedEx flight, a Federal Express flight that's going to take packages from
Memphis, Tennessee to San Jose, California.
It is a routine flight on a DC-10 cargo plane.
This plane, you had Captain David Sanders, first officer Jim Tucker, and flight engineer
Andy Peterson.
Now, they were actually called in.
This story is so dope because it's just weird the way fate works.
These three dudes were all called in at the last minute because the crew that was supposed
to fly this DC-10, it was a man and a woman.
They had worked one minute over the FAA regulated shift.
Like, if you work over this shift, you can't fly a plane.
Safety reasons.
They worked one minute over their shift so the FedEx guys go, "Well, we're going to
have to bring in another crew.
We can't take the risk."
You know, of course you'd go, "Oh, come on, man, one minute."
Well, we can't do it.
So they bring in David, Jim, and Andy.
Now, these are three...
I've never met these guys, but the article described them as they're pretty broad-shouldered
guys.
These are not...
If you had to fight three pilots in the world, you wouldn't want to fight these three, right?
Maybe you wouldn't want to fight the red-bearant either.
I'm sure there's other guys.
Lewis Gosta Jr. as well, but definitely not these three guys.
They're not Arnold, but they're also, you know, they're broad-shouldered.
They're pretty fit dudes getting into this plane.
Now, this plane is not headed to a bodybuilding contest.
It doesn't matter how physically fit they are on any other flight.
In any other flight in the world, it would not matter that these three dudes are on it.
They're getting ready to take off.
It's a routine flight, and this other employee of FedEx shows up, and he's like, "Hey, guys.
Hey, guys, do you mind if I take a jump-seater?"
And they're like, "Yeah, sure, no problem."
A jump-seater is where any employee of FedEx, apparently...
I don't know if it's like the guy working at the FedEx store in your neighborhood, but
if you are a FedEx employee, you can catch a flight.
You're basically mail yourself.
If you're at the airport, you go, "Hey, can I just..."
Because the plane's going out there anyways.
Can I just hop on board since you're going out there anyways?
I'll go to San Jose, California.
Yeah, sure.
Jump on.
His name is Auburn Callaway.
Now, David, Jim, and Andy are pretty fit.
Auburn is buff.
Auburn is this big buff dude who gets on a plane and he has a black belt in martial arts.
And a guitar case.
That's his only luggage as a guitar case.
They're like, "Oh, this is dope."
And hopefully there's a guitar in there and he'll play some jumpy tunes.
Now what they didn't know is that Auburn is a man with a plan.
Not a good one, but a man with a plan.
He was about to get called into corporate.
The very next day, he was going to have to go to corporate and he was going to get a
disciplinary action labeled against them.
He believes he's going to get fired.
So he has a man with a bad plan.
And the plane is getting ready to take off is when we start getting the black box recording
of what's going on.
So there is a full audio recording out there of all the events on this flight.
There's a transcript, a written transcript, but you want to talk about lost media.
The black box for this flight is nuts.
The flight starts off totally normal.
They're doing their checks, hitting buttons and stuff like that.
The plane, taxi's, it takes off, it's in the air.
The crew is in the cockpit.
David, Jim, Andy, they're just sitting in the cockpit flying the plane.
And Captain Jim is sitting there and then all of a sudden he hears a commotion.
It happens so quickly.
He's not really thinking about what's going on.
But he hears this commotion in the cockpit and he turns and he looks and he sees Jim
and Andy slumped over blood gushing out of their head.
In an instant Auburn launched his attack.
So Auburn's plan was this.
He figured he was getting fired.
He hated FedEx.
So two birds with one stone.
Or technically three pilots with two hammers.
He decided this.
He took out a lot of life insurance on himself and he took out workplace, deft and dismembered
insurance, accidental insurance at work, stuff like that.
His plan was to get on this plane and crash it.
Everyone on the plane would be dead including him and his family would make a lot of money.
But he also wanted to make sure, I mean obviously if there's a plane crash and there's a bunch
of bullet holes, people would know something was up.
So he brought weapons that would mimic a plane crash death.
He had two claw hammers, two mallets and a spear gun.
So Captain Jim sitting there, he hears this commotion.
He turns and within a second both of his coworkers are slumped over blood pouring out of their
heads and he sees this dude with two, he came in with both hammers and started hitting them
at the same time.
So hard knocked him out.
Captain Jim puts his arm up to start deflecting these hammer blows.
They're in the air, they're 19,000 feet in the air.
He's getting hit with his hammer.
Captain Jim knows this is a matter of life and death.
This is not a normal hijacking.
The guy's not going to take the plane to Cuba and make demands or anything like that.
He's going to try to murder himself and his crewmate.
So he starts fighting back in the cockpit of the cabin.
But as this fight's going on Jim and Andy start to come too.
What?
What just happened man?
I was just sitting here all of a sudden blood shooting out of my head.
A full on brawl is now going on in this cockpit.
The plane is still in flight and everyone but Auburn is bleeding profusely.
They are able to push Auburn out of the cockpit but he grabs his spear gun and aims it right
at Andy's face.
Blood is just pouring down Andy's face.
He can barely see what's going on.
All he sees is this spear gun aimed right at his head.
He grabs that spear gun and he just lands on top of him and they're wrestling over this
spear gun now.
Captain Sanders jumps out of the cockpit.
He's fighting over the spear gun as well.
The only person left flying the plane is Jim Tucker.
And he's sitting there at the control panel and he is trying to make sense of everything.
And at this point this is happening so quickly no one has radioed in to traffic control.
The plane is in flight as far as ground control knows everything is A-okay.
There's his blood squirting everywhere.
Jim Tucker is sitting at the cockpit and he hears his two coworkers beating this guy up
and they're not doing that well.
They are grievously wounded and they're fighting against this guy who has weapons, who was
prepared and is a martial art black belt.
Jim Tucker wants to get up and fight.
The plane is on autopilot.
It's going to be able to go straight for a while.
It's going to be able to fly a bit for a while.
So all three of them can fight.
But Jim Tucker from that rain of hammer blows, the very first attack, he's paralyzed now
on the right side of his body.
So he can't get up and fight.
He's sitting at the cockpit of this DC-10 cargo plane and he hears a fight for survival
happening 8 feet away from him.
And if that fight goes sour, he's next.
First thing he does is he tips the plane nose up, sending all of the combatants rolling
towards the back of the plane, even his buddies, right?
He's trying to give him an edge.
He tips the plane up and he hears them start rolling down the aisle.
Fight continues.
He's in a DC-10 cargo plane.
He does a barrel roll.
If you don't know much about cargo planes, they are not designed to fly upside down for
any amount of time.
He does a barrel roll in this DC-10 and at that point, ground control realizes something's
up.
They notice that this plane is flying upside down.
So now ground control is calling into the flight.
And as he's doing this barrel roll, this is the way combatants think.
When you're life or the life of your loved ones, your teammates, your crew, are in danger,
you think incredibly fast.
As he's doing this barrel roll, he knows that this is throwing everyone off their guard.
But he also knows eventually the barrel roll has to end.
If you were in a fight and all of a sudden you get thrown into this roll, you're in a
fight in an airplane, you're thrown into this roll, you would know eventually this roll's
going to end.
So all I got to do is hold on until the roll is complete and then I can get back up.
He knew that he had to keep Auburn off balance because he was going to mop these two dudes
up.
The other two dudes had too much damage to him.
He didn't know this dude was a martial art.
He didn't come in wearing his black belt.
But just from his size, you knew that this was going to be a tough fight and he didn't
have blood shooting out of his brain.
So as he's coming out of the barrel roll and this plane was never designed for a barrel
roll, a DC-10 has never done a barrel roll intentionally.
As he's coming out of the barrel roll, he goes "Okay, I got to do something else to
keep Auburn off of his guard by some time."
The plane's coming out of the barrel roll, he does a nose dive.
No DC-10 in history has ever flown as fast as Flight 705 did.
He's in that nose dive and they said that as he was performing his maneuvers, the fighters
went from a moment of being weightless to having more than three times their weight in G-forces
on top of them.
And he's hitting this nose dive and he's watching the instruments showing the speed.
These DC-10s were built to hit like 510 miles per hour and he's going, he's going, he's
doing this nose dive and he's watching the instruments and he's going so fast the instruments
can't even register how fast he's going.
The problem is, the problem is he might have postponed the fight a bit.
He needs to now level the plane up.
The problem is, is that to do that easily, he needs to de-throttle.
The throttle control is on his right side.
He's paralyzed.
He can't move his right arm or his right leg.
So as this DC-10 is flying faster than any DC-10 in history, straight towards the earth,
Jim Tucker fighting that control, finally, finally able to level the plane off, reaches
over, decelerates the plane, hits the call button and says, "Hey, FAA, yes, sorry about
all that stuff."
It happened so quickly.
Guys, we're under attack.
There's a dude on here.
He's beating us up.
There's a police at the airport right now.
We're turning around.
We're headed back to Memphis.
The flight had only been going for about 30 minutes, so they came back around and air
traffic control goes, "We're going to have everyone there for you.
We'll have police.
We'll have paramedics.
You land that plane.
We'll take care of it."
When the plane landed, the paramedics were actually the first to board.
They were the first there.
Paramedics were the ones that handcuffed Auburn.
The article said that when the paramedics got on board, it looked like a grenade exploded
because there was so much blood.
These guys were just bleeding out of their head and punching and rolling around on the
ground and having G4.
There was just blood everywhere.
Auburn didn't really have an alibi.
He really didn't have an excuse for that.
He was like, "No, no, it was the other guy.
He parachuted out and I'm his evil twin.
I mean, he's a good twin.
I'm the good twin."
He actually got life in prison for this.
Luckily, all three dudes fully recovered from this.
The one who had it the worst was Jim Tucker.
He was paralyzed for about two years, but over time he regained use of his arm and his leg.
He's still blind in one eye.
I mean, that's how vicious this attack was.
Remember, he was only attacked for just like a couple seconds in the initial flurry of
hammer blows, but it was enough to paralyze him for two years and then still lose sight
in one eye.
But man, can you ... This is one of those stories.
So you can read the transcript.
Let me read you part of the transcript.
I thought this was the ... This is the black box recording.
I would love to hear ... Because everyone survived, but I'd love to hear the audio of
this.
Let me read you a clip of this black box recording here.
Do you live over in ... These are the crew ... This is the crew talking.
Do you live over in Arkansas, Dave or ... Nah, I live in Fisherville.
Ah, Fisherville.
Great spot.
Sounds of hammer blows striking pilots.
Ow!
Oh, God.
Oh, ah, God Almighty.
Ow!
What the ever are you doing?
God, ugh, God Almighty, God, God.
Get him, get him, get him.
He's gonna kill us.
Get him.
Get up, get him.
I can't.
This one would have been funny.
I would not have read this if they had all died horribly.
I don't think they were saying ow.
I don't know if that's an actual word people say, but yeah, it has the whole transcript.
It goes all the way to when they land, basically.
It ends when the door is being opened.
And yeah, they're fighting him to the very end.
They're fighting him to the very end.
But they stop him.
So an amazing, amazing story.
Yeah, look at it.
He's still fighting for the hammer at the very end.
The plane is still landing.
And there he's still trying to grab one of the hammers.
So hey man, he's relentless.
Very, very interesting story.
I would be shocked if this hasn't been made into a movie or a TV movie or something like
that.
It's a fascinating action packed adventure.
The heroes win.
The villains lose.
I didn't even know this happened.
It happened in my lifetime.
There is action and adventure everywhere.
You don't want to live through it right now.
I'm not saying I want to be one of these dudes.
I'm not saying oh man, my life sucks.
I wish some guy attacked me with a hammer.
Absolutely not.
But it's cool to know that when the action starts, there's real heroes out there to stop
it.
They're just trying to do their job.
They're just trying to deliver some mail.
Instead they go toe to toe with a big buff martial artist in a plane.
He's wielding weapons and they win.
Not just using their fists.
They use many of those.
Not just using their wits, but using physics.
Turning that plane into an ever changing battlefield.
Fascinating story.
Thank you Captain David Sanders.
First officer Jim Tucker and Flight Engineer Andy Peterson.
Truly heroes of the skies.
None of them flew.
None of them ever flew again after this.
They were all done.
They were all like nah I'm good.
I'm good.
I'm probably getting pretty good retirement from FedEx.
But the plane, despite it going faster than any DC-10 had ever done, despite it doing a
barrel roll and these planes are not designed, they've never been tested to do a barrel roll,
they still flew for years and years after that.
Came out without a scratch.
That is the story of Flight 705.
They thought they were just going to deliver some packages.
Instead they delivered some punches into the face of a madman.
DeadRabberRadio with gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also go to stuff at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
Twitter is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
(upbeat music)