A sexual subculture many thought did not exist, but new video evidence has come to light.
And the wonder drug you've always wanted, but never heard of, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day. I hope you're beating this heat
that seems to be beating the planet up right now. The sun is taking its revenge against us,
or the ozone layer has a big hole. Maybe the reptilians are terraforming our planet to make it
more suitable for their alien needs. Or maybe it's just a heatwave. I don't know.
But it doesn't matter. It's really hot. Just think, soon you guys won't have to hear me complain
about this stuff. And I'll be happy about that too. I'm not a fan of doing stuff for the sake of irony,
like liking something to be ironic. I like stuff that I genuinely enjoy. I like the first three
Transformers movies. The second one sucked, but the third Transformers movie Dark of the Moon,
argue with me on this. The third Transformers movie Dark of the Moon is the best alien invasion movie
of the 2000s, and in the top five of all time. It is an amazing alien invasion film. The Battle of
Chicago is great. Anyways, I'm getting off topic. Watch Transformers 3, argue with me if you think
I'm wrong on that. But one of my likes that I genuinely enjoy watching that people think that
I'm an idiot for is I love watching reality shows. And I like, I don't watch them so much now, because
I never have my television on. I just watch movies. And they're on Netflix, but I really don't like
watching Netflix that much. But when I do, I'll binge watch a reality show. I just like watching
real people, and I know a lot of it's staged. I know a lot of it's edited up, but I like watching
these subcultures. I think the best reality shows are about subcultures. Not a fan of stuff like
Big Brother, or what was that one with the girls on the beach with the boy, and all the chicks were
hot. It was called like the Hill Laguna Beach. Laguna Beach never was into that. Early real world
was okay. I liked watching stuff like the Dallas cheerleader reality show, which really is the
perfect example of dad porn. That's what I talked about on the last episode, where it's, it's porn,
you know, air quotes that you can watch that a man can watch and people don't think anything is going
on. You're watching these young, beautiful, new biowomen dance around. They were in really short
skirts. What I like about it, that, I mean, obviously these beautiful women, I also like
competition based reality shows. I like this, not like a game show one, but shows where people
are competing in their subculture. Like the Dallas, you're watching this huge group of women, and you
know by the end of the season, there's only going to be seven of them who are going to start a very,
very hard job, because they have to try out each year. Okay, that being said, I really join watching
reality shows. So back when I was about 35, I got mono. Really bad. They had to put me in an
isolation ward in a hospital, and I was there for three days, and all the nurses and the doctors and
stuff had to mask up before they came in. I had a terrible infection, and I didn't have a smartphone
back then. This is probably like 2010. So I had no internet, but I did have access to the television
hospitals have great cable nowadays. And I flip through the channels and I found two programs
to watch. One of them was a two hour sit down interview with President George W. Bush, former
president at this time. Now I was never a big fan of President Bush when he was in office. Watching
him give this really candid interview talking about how he felt making these decisions in his
presidency, his regrets, the stuff that he the decisions he still stood by was fascinating.
It's fascinating. It was almost like watching someone that you considered a direct enemy to you,
sit down and explain to you why they made the decisions they made. Didn't agree with everything
he said in that interview, but it was fascinating nonetheless. The other option that I had to
watch the other thing I was and of course I had 100 options, but the other show I kept flipping back
to was toddlers in TRS, a reality show based around six year old girls trying to win beauty pageants.
Again, it was a competitive based reality show of a subculture I am not a part of. I don't have any
other interest in it if it didn't exist in a reality show. You're watching these mothers
basically berate their children while roughly combing their hair and the little girls are
going back and forth between being super happy that she's in a beauty pageant to being bored
and the mothers give them pixie sticks to keep them all hyper during the competition. It is a
incredibly bizarre alien subculture to me. I'm flipping back and forth between the two shows,
Bush interview toddlers in TRS, Bush interview toddlers in TRS. When each commercial rate comes
on each, go back and forth, toddlers TRS, it was like a marathon. So I'm sitting there in the hospital
and what happens when you're in the hospital and they're pumping you full of painkillers?
You fall asleep, but a half hour later I wake up a nurse is walking into my room to deliver me
some more pain medication and in that darkened room late at night a grown man is watching toddlers
in tears. Oh, if you're listening medical staff of the Folsom hospital where I was treated,
I was just flipping between channels and I really like reality shows and involve competition.
Nothing else. Let's go ahead and get started with the episode. So I'm going to give you a little
warning right now. I'm going to cover the miracle drug story now because the sexual conspiracy story
we're going to cover is so gross that it's you don't want to be making food or eating food or
thinking anything about food or really anything while you're listening to that. So I'm putting
this story first so you can go click at the end of it and go man that was a great episode
and keep your mind pure of what we're going to talk about. What we're going to talk about right
now is a miracle drug, a miracle drug that could change the way people achieve beauty. I don't feel
like I'm overselling this. This is amazing. I came across it. This one was actually on the
conspiracy list surprisingly enough. I found it very quickly and I thought well this is going to
be what they're talking about but this is a miracle drug. So the miracle drug is and I'm
going to mispronounce this but I'll have the links below Melanotan2. Melanotan2 it's a steroid
and the doctors were trying to create something that would prevent skin cancer that would help
people not get skin cancer. So they invented this steroid and they began testing it and what they
realized that once you inject this you can inject it into the fatty tissue of your stomach.
They've also created nasal spray version for wimps like me but what they realized is you take it,
you go out to the sun for an hour, an hour, two hours whatever, you begin tanning, your skin becomes
darker and that does help definitely with skin cancer but the doctors are like whoa whoa whoa
wait a second so this actually is a tanning aid. Like if you take this you no longer have to sit
out in the sun for hours on end. You can have or even do a quarter of the time tanning your skin
will become dark which you know a lot of people find very attractive. I personally like my choice,
I prefer very pale girls like jellyfish pale, translucent. I want to be able to see their
organs inside of like I grew up in that age of Gothic girls. I just love like that super pale
skin but tan girls hey man yeah that's pretty hot too you know it's not my go-to or anything but
so this drug they're like whoa it really helps you tan. Now it has a second effect it's not as
big as the tanning thing and it's a lesser effect but you take the steroid you lose weight so not
only does it give you a tan, a healthy tan and it doesn't like age your skin because it's the UV
rays that actually make your skin get leathery. The darkening of the skin itself with this drug
doesn't give you all the bad side effects of being out in the sun forever it also helps you lose weight
and if that wasn't good enough I own no stock in any of these companies there's not going to be an
affiliate link below all of the links below are going to be information I think one or two of
them from a store but I don't have any affiliate deals with them I don't want you to think that I'm
a spokesman for this product. Not only does it give you a tan not only does it help you lose
weight if you're a man it gives you an erection and there is a spin-off version that if you're a woman
it gets you wet a wonder drug. One of the scientists tested it on himself and had a four
hour long erection now I gotta say I admire the guts on that scientist to go you know what here
screw it and just inject himself with this steroid they're working on now the only side effects
a little bit of nausea dizziness that's it I think a little bit of vomiting which is probably just
more of a side effect of the nausea they tested this and tested this company so fought over it
and they had to like split the patent and then reunite the patent they're working on all this
stuff when it's already on the market it's already on the market you can order it now
my thing is like I'm not going to buy a little clarivial of liquid on the internet and then
inject it into my body actually surprisingly I have a story about that one day I got a letter
with a product on it and so I opened up the envelope it's just a regular white envelope
had a piece of paper a little baggie at the top of it and stapled to the piece of paper and inside
it was a pill and I'm reading the letter and it says congratulations you have been chosen as one of
the first people to take our new supplement it will increase your sex drive it'll make your dick
bigger it will make you last longer as I'm reading the article I have already opened up the baggie
swallowed the pill now I thought about it maybe a half hour afterwards to put a little time period
on this story this happened I got this letter maybe two months after 9/11 and I thought about
a half hour later after I'd taken this pill I thought if Al Cato wanted to kill a million
American men overnight they would just send out cyanide pills and say this will make your dick
bigger and the next day the streets would be a wash of dead men obviously it wasn't cyanide
and to top the story off the pill didn't even work didn't work for me but this this melaton
and melaton too and the on the conspiracy list it's listed as trend tanning because trend is
another term I think trend is another term for steroids in general but it's another term for
this steroid this is on the conspiracy list it's listed on there because it's basically a wonder
drug that nobody knows about and the fact that it's not the most popular supplement at Walmart or
every store across the planet is shocking and I think it's probably the delivery method more than
anything people don't want to inject themselves with stuff but they perfect that nasal spray
everyone will have a tan everyone will lose weight and everyone will want to bang all the time
we're going to go ahead and move on to this story now this story is like I said really gross so if
you want to cut out right now I don't blame you and Veronica dear dear sweet Veronica I know you
have an aversion to I know you're a germaphobe so it was great having you listen to this far
of the episode and I will see you on tomorrow's episode you should leave now bug chasing people
believe there was a myth for a long time people believed that bug chasing was not something
they thought it was a smear campaign against gay men so what is bug chasing bug chasing is a
subculture of gay men who knowingly and willingly affect infect themselves with the AIDS virus or
HIV I'm going to use them interchangeably I know that the terminology is different but
so they will go out and get AIDS on purpose they consider they call it the gift so I'm a man and
I'm a bug chaser I'm going to find a gift giver I want the gift I want that virus inside of my body
when a man gives me his gift I want it to be as toxic as possible I want the strongest form of
AIDS that you can give me there have been stories of people it's getting it's going to get rough
from here on out guys so if the rest of the audience wants to leave go ahead there are stories of
people who will cut their butthole open to make it easier for the semen the infected semen to go
into their bloodstream because you can have sex with someone with AIDS and not catch it just like
any disease I can swallow someone sneezing in my mouth and not get the flu that's actually grosser
than the semen thing I think but so they will you know the the bug chasers who aren't infected yet
lament the fact that they don't have it and so they will engage in random generally it goes in
stages they'll engage in unprotected sex with random people then they'll begin seeking out gift
givers and usually people in the subculture who have the virus will have a biohazard symbol tattooed
somewhere on their body to let people know that they have it and then when that doesn't work if
they still don't get the virus they'll begin cutting their butthole open or injecting injecting
AIDS infected blood right into their own bloodstream or into their butthole and then when that doesn't
work they go to even more extreme measures now this like I said was considered an urban legend
for a long time people just thought it was a smear campaign and you would see evidence I had heard
about bug chasing years and years and years ago and I thought that's just insane oh and you know
people always go what's the motive and there are several motives some of them just want to get it
over with they go you know what I know I'm going to get AIDS eventually so I just want to get it
out of the way other ones see it as a form of life living inside of them it's their version of having
like a life form like a baby almost another life form inside of them they needed to take care of
some of them just like the thrill of possibly catching it they'll have parties where there's
20 minutes in a room and one will have AIDS and the rest of them will be clean and you just have
sex randomly and will you get it will you not I read a heartbreaking article some people get it
in certain cities so they can get benefits I read an article today when I was doing some more
research on bug chasing there is these young men in New York City who were realized that if you had
AIDS you could get housing allowances and public assistance and all of these things from the government
this one kid got it and accidentally he didn't mean to get it but once he found out that he
could get all these benefits he was like I'm glad that I got AIDS because now I'm not living on the
street anymore there isn't a the apartment that costs $1500 he only has to pay $200 for it the
state pays the rest because they're taking care of these people one of the dangers too with bug
chasing I just got more than the obvious one that you have AIDS now is some people who say well
Lisa have AIDS now I don't have to worry about getting it anymore the pressure's gone you can
actually get two different types of AIDS because it's this constantly mutating thing where if you
already have AIDS and then you're still out engaging in unsafe sex and someone else has AIDS you can
create super AIDS in your body and you die within weeks so it's not like this super manageable thing
that people think it is a lot of people go oh you just take a pill every day or every you know you
take your medication every month and you'll be fine and it's not that straightforward you can
some people still die very quickly of it if it mutates too much so again I have to keep saying
this if people thought it was an urban legend for the longest time about a year or two ago
there was a video released a porn video released it was from a treasure island media which is a
gay porn company and I read about this on vice media and it is a video of a one of those roulette
parties but like I said there's 20 men in a room and one has AIDS and the rest are clean this one
it's mostly guys with AIDS who are positive or pause is the terminology used only some are negative
so it's this gay porno now I haven't been able to watch it but I did have to get a copy of it because
and my copy is labeled do not watch in big bold letters 200 pause loads the culmination of this
video there's photos of this on the vice article by the way is they take a jar of
they have a big mason jar and it's filled to the brim with you ever seen milk go bad
and how it separates and all the cream rises to the top
and the rest is like a yellowy liquid that's what this jar is but this jar is full of 200
pause loads of semen so all the men in the room who were HIV positive jack jacked off
into this jar the star of the video the guy the main bug chaser gets a funnel put into his butthole
and and the jar is emptied into it now all of my wretched noises I would like to say was for
comedic effect but like I said I own this video and I can't bear to watch it I have it more as a
curiosity than anything it's like I've said before I don't watch porn I don't have a huge
collection of porn at all this is what one of the videos which means when I die and someone's
going through my computer they're like man he has a lot of pictures of Kate Upton and look at this
old Sarah Michelle Geller photo whoa what's this video do not watch 200 anyway so he gets the funnel
put in his butt and they dump the cum inside of him and at this point people are like okay this is a
true fetish and what's interesting is the director goes on to say there's this isn't as small of a
community as you may think it is I get over letters from a lot of people who fantasize about this I
think that's the key I think a lot of people fantasize about a lot of stuff they would never go
through with but bug chasing is real there are whole websites and forums and dating apps dedicated
to it so people are willingly infecting themselves with aids for a multitude of reasons I can get
being homeless and thinking well if I have aids at least I'll have a roof over my head very short
term thinking but you know I can that's more logical than well I'm gonna get it anyways
or creepier the group that's like it's this life form inside of me a part of my lover is inside
of me I've come across stories I'll try to find some read it your own risk but I've come across
stories in the past too where gay men who are the who carry the gift will have sex with other gay men
who don't know they're infected that's a real problem too but that's part of the fetish as the
gift giver is having unprotected sex with unknowing men and giving them the gift and now I'm a part
of him forever I've changed his life in these five minutes his life will never be the same
and when you read those stories on there the fetish person side who's writing it you're thinking
this guy's really messed up and then to say the least but then when you think about the
young man who's now you know if the disease takes their life has changed radically especially for
men who are just curious and now they have AIDS and you know they're married or whatever they
have a girlfriend and now they have something you're gonna have to do with the rest of your life if
you are engaging I'll put this out for everyone if you're engaging in any sort of if for gay men
you use be safe for straight men don't have sex with anyone you don't plan on having a baby with
I know that sound may sound very period technical but that's something that I've learned as I got
older I look back at women that I was with and I was like dude if that if I got that cheek pregnant
would radically change my life just just use common sense guys use common sense use protection
I'm not I don't really like it myself but nowadays if I'm with someone and I think that they would
make a bad mother or I don't want to be with them outside of this small moment in time this use
protection the same thing you may like for gay men you may like the semen in your but whole more
but there are people out there there's small minority but there are people out there who
will willingly infect you infect you with it is it really worth the risk is anything this is the
key is anything worth the risk of that five minute moment of your life it's the same thing when I
think of people who in Hood River we just had some guys arrested for trying to meet up underage girls
and it's like is really what you're doing worth the rest of your life being changed that five minute
moment the rest of your life being changed and it's not it never is however no wait there's no
however to that it never is it never is I did want to say this though imagine if there was a bug
chaser that you couldn't avoid imagine if there was a bug chaser who was spreading it randomly
truly randomly I came across this post this is creepy and Veronica if you are still listening
definitely shut it off now I love telling you people my secret I have bad genital herpes
when they flare up I go to the supermarket I'll go to the back of my van and pop
I'll go to the back of my van and pop some juicy herpes and wipe it on my hands and fingers then
go into the store I touch as much produce as possible sometimes I go to the store's bathroom to
reload just to give you the freshest of my herpes juice sometimes I go to the baby section of
the store Jesus Christ sometimes I'll go to the baby section of the store little teething babies
love to chew on toys gross I forgot about that part this is our secret now you're good at secrets
right yeah you're real good at secrets there are certain people who just need to be locked up
and removed from humanity and this guy needs to be in a cell if he if this is true and he's rubbing
what he calls his herp juice on produce and teething rings again it's probably his fetish
he's probably jacking off the whole time thinking about it and the whole time doing it and then
when he goes home he's fantasizing about doing it again now luckily for me I never eat produce and
I don't use teething toys but whoever you are herp juice guy come on that's there that's a level
of inhumanity that I think even shocks me dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email
address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio or you can twitter me @jasonocarpenter
well you guys made it if you're still listening you guys made it to the end of the bug chasing
episode we had a little bit of the good and the bad the trend stuff that's awesome hope it comes
to market and I hope it gets easier to use not saying I want the deepest hand but it would just
be interesting oh oh the dick thing is probably the best part button and then of course we had the
bug chasing which I think again your germaphobe the herpy thing was really I hate to use this term
but the icing on the cake as far as germaphobia goes that's going to be it we have one more episode
of our sexual conspiracy list that will be tomorrow we're going to end it out with some
interesting little tips here I'll give you a spoiler alert we're going to be talking about
supernatural sex with demons and love spells I think those are interesting topics dead rabbit
radio is the paranormal conspiracy and true kind podcast you don't have to listen to it every day
but I'm glad you listen to it today I will see you tomorrow have a great one guys
you