I, Jason Carpenter, have discovered a new intoxicating drug.
I found it out myself!
Firefighters, I don't know why I was so excited that I may be the inventor of Jinn 2.0.
Firefighters go to a farm in the middle of the night to put out a fire and end up in
a sticky predicament.
And then we take a trip on the SS Valencia, a passenger ship that ran aground off the
coast of British Columbia.
And to this day, the horror stories of that night are still etched into the soul and the
sand of a lonely beach.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
So I discovered a new drug.
Shake it up here.
Shake it up.
That'll be the theme song for the, when I start advertising this drug, when I become a drug
baron.
Actually, why am I telling you guys about this?
I should probably patent it first.
It is saying something.
It's a public patenting something.
I'm gonna walk out and I'm like, "Self driving wheelbarrow."
And then everyone's like, "Damn, I can't do that now."
Let me take a sip of my new drink.
This is the true Jason juice, by the way.
If you drink this, you will feel like me.
Because when I drink it, I feel like, "Whoa, whoa, okay.
That's a side effect.
It wants to explode."
So I discovered this.
Actually I don't think I can patent it because I bought it.
But if you take a sparkling water drink, like none of that gross stuff like Bubbly or LaCroix,
get a real drink.
I choose sparkling ice.
Cherry limeade.
Sparkling ice, cherry limeade.
Or clear American ice, which I think they're discontinuing.
Cherry lemonade.
And then you take 500 milligrams of turmeric with ginger in it.
It's the little pills you can buy.
I'm not asking you to go to the steps of Mongolia and start picking turmeric yourself.
You can just buy little turmeric supplements or the powder itself.
It doesn't matter.
And then you insert, you break open the pill if you have the pill and you put the powder
in your drink.
And then I'm going to take a drink here.
Here's the thing.
Either I've discovered that a combination of sparkling water and turmeric has a, I wouldn't
say intoxicating, but definitely a light-headed, pleasant effect.
Or I'm giving myself an allergic reaction to turmeric.
But I've taken turmeric before.
I've been taking turmeric supplements for a while in pill form.
And then one day I got some powdered turmeric and I was like, pour it in your drink for
a boost of energy.
So technically I can't pan it because someone else did it.
But I did it and I was like, whoa, man, where's the floor, dude?
Why are we like on a ball in the darkness of space, man?
Like, I was like, good thing I don't have a car because I was not feeling good.
Well, I was feeling great.
That was the problem.
I had a turmeric, sparkling ice or clear American ice, whatever flavor.
But I know for a fact the cherry limeade stuff works or the cherry lemonade.
And yeah, dude, it's really weird.
It's almost, I don't want to say like I'm already floating through the void, but we'll
see.
And it's hard to overdose.
Okay, let me rephrase that.
You can overdose on it, but it's like the overdose is like 1500 milligrams.
So you'd have to do it three times a day.
Which to be fair, as good as it can make you feel, it's probably not hard to do.
But anyways, turmeric, clear American ice, please don't everyone go up.
What if this becomes the new face eating drug?
This is bath salt 2.0.
I just haven't figured that out yet.
I think I'm feeling like super chill and everyone else is like hiding the silverware from me.
I'm like, yeah, dude, I'm feeling good.
Okay, let's go ahead though and get started with the actual episode.
Let's go ahead.
We're going to hop into a fire truck.
We're going to sneak on.
We're going to get all, you can get on my shoulders and we'll wear a giant fireman's
costume.
What are they called?
The uniform.
That's normally what they're called.
Hey cop, nice costume.
Yeah, I don't say that.
You get on my, I'm assuming we're both only like three feet tall.
So we're like the little rascals.
You get on my shoulders and you're like Jason, that's very, very kind of you.
Normally you make me carry you around.
And I'm like, I know, right?
I am a good host, blaming on the Jason Jews.
So I put you on my shoulders.
We're both three feet high.
So it takes both of us to fit into one fireman's costume, walking into the fire station and
I'm being extra wiggly.
You're all, and the firefighters, we are actually in Yaram, which is in Victoria, Australia.
So Yaram is probably the city in Victoria's, the state or province.
Australia.
So imagine everything's upside down in this story.
It's September 2019.
So very, very recent.
And we're all sitting in the playing cards and I'm kind of like falling asleep.
You're like, oh, my legs are asleep.
And you're just kind of like, waking me up because the alarm goes off and it's like,
and so anyways, all the firefighters are getting up and they're running around.
They were wondering why you were wearing your fireman's giant jacket that whole time.
I imagine they never think about it.
Firefighters don't wear the giant jackets anymore.
They go all the way down to their ankles.
They may not have ever worn them.
I think I just saw them in a cartoon or something.
It's 3 a.m.
We're riding with the firefighter crew.
We get a call out to a barn, well to a farm.
It's multiple barns.
It's not just one.
It's a very successful farm.
And it's called Yaram Herd Services.
So Yaram, the firefighter truck, fire engine, it's the name of it, drives past the signs
as Yaram Herd Services and we all jump out.
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, getting the hoses ready.
And I'm making sure we're getting super close to the fire.
You're like, no dude, stop.
I don't even have a hose yet.
I'm like, hehehehe.
Because I know what's going to happen here.
Yaram Herd Services, what they do is they provide breeding services.
Breeding services, right?
So there's all these cylinders lining the farm.
They're all giant.
They're all these giant cylinders.
They're all full of bull semen.
And they're on fire.
And so they're full of boiling bull semen.
[Bulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbulbul
It's not like some dubstep song, but it's not.
It's bubbling, boiling bull semen.
And it's so hot that the lids are exploding off the cylinder and bulges is just flying
all over the place.
It's like the Indian Ghostbusters when the marshmallow man blows up.
But not that.
It's not that substance.
You're like, I've been slimed and then your whole body becomes HPV.
Actually, I wonder, I know animals can get, actually no I don't.
Can animals get STDs?
Like I'm sure, monkeys can have AIDS, but it doesn't affect them, right?
Can a dog have gone real?
Just stating that question made my stomach hurt.
Ugh.
I'm not acting.
Just that visual is making me...
Let's table that discussion.
I think that's a dead rabbit radio first, where I'm just like, nope, I can't go down that
path.
Anyways.
Oh my god, that's disgusting.
Anyways, I'm sure animals can have some sort of STD.
We'll just leave it at that.
Anyways, bull semen's gone everywhere.
Now, I didn't know this.
You there, here's some bull, so they put the fire out.
It's not still raging.
There's not boiling bull semen epidemic.
It's traveling across Australia.
But here's some bull semen tidbits.
One of them is not about STDs, that's disgusting.
Bull semen is measured in straws.
Which is disgusting.
Like, don't measure it in something that you put your mouth on.
If you have a disgusting, you're like, hey, how many feces do we have?
Oh, we got about three mouthfuls.
Like what?
No.
Don't measure it and why a straw?
Jason, because it's a tube, name it a tube.
I got 35 tubes of bull semen over here.
Because if you say I got 35 straws of bull semen over here, the visual is you are ready
to go.
It's not a straw, it's something you put in a milkshake.
It's not something that you feel full of bull semen.
Here's a bull.
You're like, Jason, when did your podcast become paranormal, conspiracy and bull semen
tips?
I just got one more.
Bull semen.
So this guy's bull semen wasn't that valuable.
This per straw was about $5 to $95 per straw, which is more valuable than a straw full of
my semen, sure.
But I would be disappointed if I had a bull that I raised and it was like my prized bull
and you only got five bucks for some of the semen.
I'd be like, oh man, I'd be disappointed.
And then this other guy's bull can get 95 bucks for a little bit of a semen.
So I just find that weird.
So this guy, but that was like bottom of the barrel stuff.
That was like lame-o semen because some of these straws go up for $8,000.
And it's like wagyu beef.
Wagyu beef, it's that special beef they eat in Japan.
You get them big bowls, those perfectly bred bowls, $8,000 for a little bit of their semen
so you can go inject it into a, not inject it, you can pregnae, be the proper term.
Into a female cow and then have little wagyu babies.
But anyways, so there you go.
There is your daily bull semen.
I'll have more bull semen tips tomorrow on Dead Rabbit Radio, the Daily Paranormal Conspiracy
and Bull Seamen Podcast.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
We're taking off our uniforms and you're going to go take a shower.
And when you're done, you're going to meet me on the deck of the SS Valencia.
Birds are flying by.
Do birds fly at night?
Anyways, no.
Birds aren't flying by because it's midnight.
It's 1906 so it's old, tiny.
Everything smells like sepia tone and it's January 22nd, which is not a good combination.
You're in the middle of the night.
January 22nd, which means it's going to be cold.
Oh, we also were in British Columbia, so Vancouver Island, British Columbia.
So winter up north, midnight, not a good combination, right?
We like those things, except like the wind to go.
The SS Valencia is a passenger steamer.
56 crew members, 108 passengers.
So everyone, it's midnight.
The only people who are really awake are the crew.
No one else is kind of dancing around.
It's not the Titanic.
Just everyone's asleep at this point.
Now they've been having some problems.
The weather was bad.
They had navigation tools, but their navigation tools were based on the stars.
So at this point they had to do a thing called dead reckoning, where they're like, if we
were headed in this direction before we lost all this visibility, we must, we have to assume
we're still headed in this direction.
Very, very dangerous way to pilot a ship, but it's what they have to do.
It's midnight and the boat is going through the water.
The SS Valencia is going through the water.
Apparently also a giant is walking across the landscape.
So we have a storm that's picking up.
We have midnight.
It's winter.
The boat can't see where it's going.
And then of course, tragedy strikes.
So the boat ends up hitting a bunch of rocks.
So they're like, well, we were headed in the right direction because we were trying to get
to land, but not this way.
The boat just gets tore up in the bottom immediately begins taking in water.
Now the captain comes out.
Everyone at this point, everyone is awake.
And if they were dancing, they definitely stopped boats taking water.
And the captain goes, okay, this is not good.
I'm not, I've been in the captain for long, but I'm pretty sure boats are supposed to
be on top of the water.
Let's, and there's no way, they're just massive damage.
So he goes, okay, this is what we're going to do.
100 yards out.
They can see it.
100 yards out is a small beach.
We're going to crash the boat onto the beach on purpose because otherwise we're going to
sink and everyone's like, are you sure captain?
And he's like, yes, I just said that I'm not spitballing.
This isn't a committee.
Let's just do it.
I'm not a captain.
And that's not a bad plan.
I mean, at that point, the boat had taken so much damage that they weren't going to be
able to repair it.
And land was only a hundred, a football field away.
So they decide to go and purposely crash the boat into the land, but they don't get far
at all.
They end up crashing into more rocks.
And now they're actually stuck on the rocks.
The waves are so high.
The storm is so bad and now they're not moving up and down with the ocean.
Now they're actually stuck to the ground and they can still see the beach still around
100 yards in front of them.
The waves are so high at one point.
So after the boat hits the rocks the second time, a bunch of people came up out of the
hole of the ship to see what was going on.
And as people were coming out of the door, a wave came over the ship, washed like 10 people
overboard, killed them.
At this point everyone's like, "Oh my god, this is not a good situation for us to be
in.
We're stuck and these waves are actually bigger than the boat.
We're not moving with the ocean anymore.
We're basically its prey."
Wave after wave of just this cold January water is just smashing into this boat.
And unless you were holding onto something or inside the boat, you were going overboard.
The problem is the inside of the boat was filling full of water.
Winds of up to 35 miles an hour, people are dressed in their nightgowns.
Their little booties, little pajama slippers, little sleepy time cap, freezing cold winter
water is attacking them from both above and below.
Here's a quote from one of the survivors.
Screams of women and children mingled in an awful chorus, with the shrieking of the wind,
the dash of rain, and the roar of the breakers.
As the passengers rushed on deck, they were carried away in bunches by the huge waves that
seemed as high as the ship's mast heads.
The ship began to break up almost at once, and the women and children were lashed to the
rigging above the reach of the sea.
It was a pitiful sight to see frail women wearing only nightdresses, with bare feet on the freezing
rat lines trying to shield children in their arms from the icy wind and rain.
If you weren't in a safe area and they were quickly running out of safe areas, they were
tying you to the ship.
So you would get hit by that water and you'd get frozen, not like in place, but you'd get
really really cold, but at least you wouldn't be going overboard.
Because people were just getting knocked overboard.
Captain goes "Ok guys, I mean this is not good, obviously people are getting tied to
the boat."
Captain goes "Let's lower the lifeboats, let's get the lifeboats ready, we're not going to
drop them yet, but we're going to bring them down and get them ready so when we're ready
to drop them, we can drop them."
Am I clear?
And everyone's like "Yes sir."
And then the power goes out.
So now they're in the pitch black, middle of the night, just huge problems going on.
And people start seeing the lifeboats come down to the side of the ship.
So passengers begin to jump into the lifeboats.
They're like "Oh come on, finally, here let's take this rope off my hand, come on get the
kids on the boat, come on, doot, that was the sound of someone being put in the boat,
doot doot doot doot, more people being put in the boat."
And the captain's like "What is, hey guys, no no no no, we're not lowering the lifeboats
yet, don't lower the lifeboats."
But people in the lifeboats were yelling "No no no, lower it, lower it, lower it."
And the crew, in the middle of the night, in this huge super loud storm, couldn't really
figure out what the order was.
There's seven of these lifeboats.
As the captain's trying to figure out what to do in this huge storm, people are like
"They're telling me to lower the lifeboats, so I'm going to lower the lifeboats."
So they start lowering these lifeboats full of people.
And as they're lowering these lifeboats, whether it was a snag, human incompetence,
the storm, whatever.
The captain was right to say "They don't lower those lifeboats yet."
Because there's seven of them.
Six of them have people in them.
The first three flip over as they're being lowered.
And you have 10 to 20 people per boat fall onto the rocks, mostly women and children,
and smash into the rocks that have trapped the boat in the first place.
Killing them instantly.
Those that didn't die by hitting a rock was just swept out into the cold wet darkness.
Three lifeboats snag, jump, jump, jump, just emptied their contents, screaming people falling
into the darkness.
Now the captain realizes what happened at this point and is flipping out.
Obviously the crew, everyone's panicked at this point.
Because you think about a lifeboat is supposed to be your way.
It's a lifeboat.
It's the way you get out of these bad situations.
And that safety mechanism has failed so catastrophically that they are watching women and children
fall into the ocean.
The other three do get successfully launched.
So it really was luck of the draw.
You had 50/50 chance whether or not you just fell under the dark water or ended up in one
of the other three boats.
But those boats, two of them capsized.
Because it was not, you're lowering them onto basically rocks.
And then they had to get off the rocks because that's where the boat is locked in, into the
water.
Two of them get in there capsized.
Now these people, they didn't smash in the rocks but they drowned very, very quickly.
The third lifeboat never seen again, some say.
And we'll get to that.
We'll get to the legends in a bit.
But this is a 100% true story.
This isn't a legend.
Out of the lifeboats on the other side, 12 men were able to survive.
The women and the children in those boats too, absolutely dead.
Absolutely dead.
So now the only people you have, you have the crew on the ship, you have the male passengers,
you have the remaining women and children who stayed on the boat, smartly stayed on
the boat and were getting tied down to it.
And now you have these 12 men who have tried to go on a life raft and it capsized and everyone
else died on it but them.
One of the men finds himself on a wet rock that's poking out of the ocean, he's holding
onto it.
Just wave, wave, land is less than a hundred yards away.
You can look at it.
And after an hour of holding onto that rock, a wave finally smashes into him and everyone
just sees now an empty rock.
I think that honestly is the worst.
Like it's one thing to be like, "Ahhhhhhh!"
Fall on a rock but for an hour hold onto a rock and then eventually lose, that would
suck.
That would be the worst.
First off, I don't really like doing anything for an hour.
I don't even like standing up for an hour.
So the fact of holding onto something, but each minute passing and going like, "No, no,
no, I don't want to go, I don't want to go."
After about 45 minutes of that I'd be like, "Yeah."
But just to tear an hour long.
So out of the 12 people, 12 men in that boat, one of them got washed away on a rock.
Two of them ended up getting separated from the group.
Not like the war group.
They were just a bunch of panic dudes trying to make it to the beach who happened to survive
these capsized boats.
Two of them ended up in a cave.
That's not a good place to be next to the ocean when the tide is rising so they're in
a cave and the tide is rising.
Now, there's a beach here but it's not a tropical resort.
There's a beach and then there's a 100 foot high cliff.
So it's not like if they can get to the beach they're going to sit and they're going to
start drinking out of coconuts.
They then have to scale 100 foot high cliff to get rescued.
So these two guys are in this cave and the water's getting higher and higher and they're
like, "We can't swim for it.
We can try climbing this 100 foot cliff."
And they start climbing the cliff and they both fall off into the rocks and die.
And horrible.
Like just die in the beginning.
If you're not going to make it.
Like obviously they don't know the end of the story.
I do.
But I think that's just the worst.
So what happens is those remaining nine dudes who are now on the beach, they also have to
climb this 100 foot cliff in a rainstorm in the middle of the night and dark.
But they do.
Now, boats are situated with these things called Lyle guns.
And what it is, it's basically like a really cool looking harpoon that goes *poof* and it's
a hook with a long rope on the end of it.
And I had to do a bunch of research on Lyle guns.
Like the rope can't be too thick, but it can't be too flimsy.
And what it does is you shoot it to shore and tie it around something and then that gives
a way for people to be able to climb on the rope to get to safety.
So it's a last ditch thing.
Here you've used life preservers and lifeboats and life rafts and all this stuff.
Because it's hard and they have special equipment like baskets they can shuffle.
Basically it creates like a zipline type thing.
But in this case you're shooting it.
On the captain goes get the Lyle gun ready.
We're going to shoot it to the top of that cliff.
It'll give us at least a way to start moving people off the boat.
Not the easiest thing to do, but it's their only option.
First shot doesn't work.
These things were actually quite fragile.
Because you had to load it just right.
As you would imagine a bullet made a rope would have to be done.
But they do shoot off another Lyle.
They see it go off into the forest on the top of the cliff.
The captain's like, "That's awesome.
All we need to do is get someone here, get the Lyle gun rope lying on that side situated.
He's another terminology either.
We'll be good."
So the crew has now climbed this 100 foot cliff.
They have a decision to make.
So they're right, they see a telegraph line.
Again, this is 1906.
People aren't picking up the radio in the middle of the ocean being like, "Made a made a."
Unless you can see their little flippy floppy light things, you're toast.
They see a telegraph line running through the forest.
And they go, "We should go that way."
And then that's obviously the best decision because they could go, "This must be civilization
that way."
And then they had turned to the left.
They would have been a short distance away from where the Lyle gun had landed.
They would have been able to tie that down and start getting people off the boat.
But they didn't.
They had no communication with the ship.
They didn't even know the Lyle gun was fired.
They had right.
While all that was going on, there was still that one remaining lifeboat.
They didn't really know if anyone had made it to the beach because it's pitch dark.
They just saw the three boats tip and then the three boats capsized so they don't know.
So the last lifeboat, a group of guys is like, "We need to get off this boat.
We need to get help because we're totally done."
And the captain goes, "Okay, you can take this lifeboat, but your main priority is to
get to the top of that mountain and tie down that Lyle gun.
We can start getting people off this boat."
And the rescue team at this point says, "Yes, that's exactly what we're going to do."
Now the state of the boat at this point is basically graham crackers and milk because
it's so heavily damaged and these waves are hitting it so hard, chunks of the boat are
getting destroyed.
Little bit here, a little bit there, but because the boat has no give, it's basically just
a block of wood and metal in the middle of this giant storm, which is every boat, but
boats go up and down.
This boat is not moving.
It's stuck.
The waves are hitting it so hard, it's starting to fall apart.
And so they're running out of time.
Now these other dudes get in this boat, they take off.
They actually, the boat land successfully, they get to shore and they see a sign that
says, "3 miles to Cape Beale."
And they're like, "We can make 3 miles, we can do this."
And the other people are like, "What about the Lyle gun?"
They go, "Forget the Lyle gun."
We're going to get to Cape Beale because they had no idea where they were at at this point.
They didn't know if they were near civilization or this was an abandoned island until they
saw that sign.
They go, "Oh, you have the other team that found the shack."
But again, nobody knows that they're even alive.
This rescue team goes, "Let's go to Cape Beale, let's call for help."
Then we can tie the Lyle gun down.
We just, we'll get some other boats here.
So they take off, take some 2 and a half hours, they make it to Cape Beale.
They run in, they're like, "Oh, kicking doors down."
They're dripping wet and they're like, "We need a call for help.
We need a call for help."
This boat, and they tell the whole story, and someone turns around and goes, "Yeah,
we just got that call for help like four minutes ago."
They're like, "What?"
They're like, "Yeah, somebody from some cabin across the island called up, sent out the
distress call saying that there's a boat wreck down there, rescue crews on the way."
So they had already been beaten to the punch on that, but it's fine.
They wasn't a contest.
No one's keeping score.
Now here's the weird thing about this story.
A day has passed at this point.
So it's not like, again, it's a certain point where you're on a boat and you're like, "Oh
no, we're gonna sink.
We're gonna sink."
And then 23 hours later, you're like, "Oh no, we're gonna sink.
So the sun comes up.
There's still this massive storm going on.
People are getting hungry.
They're like, "Oh, I'm so hungry."
"Waves."
Like you're going through all the normal stuff you go through throughout a day.
No, I'm sure they had to go to the bathroom, but you know what I mean?
You get tired, you want to take a nap, and you're kind of hungry, and then you're thirsty
all that's said.
This isn't happening over the course of two hours.
It's day two of this, and people are still soaking wet, freezing.
There's blood in the water, the boat's stuck, and you can see land 100 yards away.
But now they can actually see boats in the distance.
And people are like, "Oh my God, the nightmare is over.
There's boats here.
We are gonna be rescued."
Now on the boats, they're like, "Okay guys, let's get ready to rescue these guys."
But the Valencia was so close to the land, the storm was raging, the boats cannot even
come close to this thing.
They ended up finding a barge, like recruiting a barge with a flat bottom, but even that
was like, "I can't get to it."
And so the captain said, "Hey listen, we got a couple life rafts.
These are those little cheapo ones.
They're not the big life boats that everybody loves, that everyone died in.
We have these really flimsy life rafts.
Let's get in them."
And we'll start shuffling people back and forth between us, and the SS queen was at
boat that was out in the distance, the big boat.
Get in the life raft, we'll go out, and then you can come back, go out.
Most people said, "Absolutely not.
Absolutely not.
I will take my chances on the SS Valencia.
I'm not getting in the life."
Every time someone has gotten off this boat, they have died.
They don't know what's going on with the rescue crew, although they could probably figure
it because now there's ships in the distance.
But for the most part, everyone who's gone off this boat has died.
I'm staying on the boat.
Captain's like, "Okay."
And so people start getting in the life rafts, and they go off towards the queen.
The boats that can't get to Valencia say, "You know what?
We'll go over land.
We'll have to go through the forest and see if we can figure out a way to save them."
The plan at this point is because they know the Lile Gun was shot, because the one team
told them.
They just didn't do an overland rescue.
They're going to bring all their rescue stuff to the cliff face.
They attached the Lile Gun.
Good to go.
So at this point, the overland team, they come to the edge of the cliff.
They see the Lile Gun hooked there, and they're like, "This is perfect.
We're going to tie this down.
We're going to get this going.
Everything's fine."
As they're tying the Lile Gun hooked down, you have this entire crew of people looking
over the cliff at the SS Valencia, and a giant wave just goes...
Smashes into it so hard, the giant steam stack.
You see how those big old boats just falls over.
And that was the last thing that was protecting the inside of the boat from the water.
You had the people that were lashed down to the sides of the boat.
You had a bunch of people inside the top portion of the boat, because everything else was flooded.
And you had the giant steam stack, basically the roof, that when the wave hit it, it basically
ripped the roof off.
And that was the end of it.
That was absolutely the end of it.
The water began rushing into...
Every wave now came directly into the top of the boat and washed people out.
The people on the cliff are actually watching.
Dozens of people just fly out, not like Peter Pan, but being lifted out of the boat.
Each wave grabbed a handful of humans and just threw them against the rocks.
The people who were tied to the boat were basically human debris.
Because once the support structures were gone, every time a wave hit, a chunk of the boat
would go flying off and you would be tied to a piece of wood or a piece of steel that
would either float you out into the darkness or drag you to the bottom of the sea.
All in all, there was 56 crewmen, there was 108 passengers, 20 people survived.
All men.
Captain was never found.
His body was never found.
And that boat is still there.
You can actually go to this beach and you can still see the whole...
Not like it's not like a little skeleton of a boat.
It's not super dramatic, but you can see the flat pieces of steel that are just on the
beach.
It's considered a protected artifact.
The government leaves it there as a reminder.
They ended up, there was this huge controversy, they ended up having to build a bunch of lighthouses
in the area.
Not all in the same place.
They didn't just build three lighthouses on the beach and go, "We're done."
27 years later, lifeboat number five.
Seen just kind of drifting through the bay.
Someone walks out.
They don't walk out, they take a boat.
Boat out to it.
That's weird.
It says on it, "SS Valencia."
What?
And they said it was weird because it was a 27-year-old lifeboat in good condition.
Been floating in the sea the whole time.
Pretty good condition.
It's now in a museum.
That's an anomaly.
It's weird that a boat would last that long with just floating in the water.
That a bunch of crabs didn't take it over.
But then we have the stories of fishermen in the area early in the morning out plying
their trade, trying to catch fish.
And they see a life raft float by them.
And they just see skeletons rowing it through the fog.
And then more horrifying than a bunch of skeletons rowing a boat, which would be kind of funny.
Xylophonemies explain the whole time.
That's Calliope, by the way, but it doesn't matter.
More horrifying than that story is the stories of the SS Valencia itself as a ghost ship.
Sailors have said late at night in the fog or during particularly stormy nights, they
can look out through the mist and see the ghostly outline of that passenger ship.
And people strapped down to the sides of it.
People's faces looking through portholes, screaming for help.
Ghosts eternally drenched in winter water, forever replaying that descent into their
watery grave.
Ghosts walking down hallway is one thing.
Just hitchhiking down a dark road.
Creepy, yes.
But not terrifying.
Not a reminder of the end that waits for us all.
But when you have the ghosts of women and children screaming in the darkness, reaching
out for you with a dripping wet hand, it only reminds a sailor that his fate may someday
be that of the specter just off starboard.
[Music]