Is the movie The Conjuring 2 haunted? Yes, we're finally getting to that story.
And a conspiracy involving J.K. Rowling? The Harry Potter books? And the oddest
thing is, the conspiracy might actually be true today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Karpner. I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too.
I'm having a great day despite the fact that my apartment, as much as I love my
apartment complex, the hallway lighting is not turned on. This place is known for
being haunted, my apartment included. We'll do stories on that later. And I'm
doing laundry. And I've been trading ghost stories with Lana all day long. Oh
morning long. Well, I know I pretty much all day long. Anyways, I was talking to
Lana all day. We were trading ghost stories on Facebook and my clothes. I got
to get them out of the dryer and it's a dark hallway and it's spooky and it's
raining up here. So I've been drinking that Rose energy serum. I don't know how to
classify it. I got it at the Free Food Bank, the corner food bank in town. I took
that and some applesauce. I ate the applesauce a long time ago. Man, it really
does work. It gives you a lot of energy. I feel myself talking very quickly. So it's
like, I almost have to like slow down and restrain myself. But I think we got a
good episode today. I'm very excited about that. So, the Conjuring 2. Now, the
Conjuring 2 was the sequel to the Conjuring 1. It was obviously, but what it
was really setting up was building the Conjuring universe. The Conjuring
Cinematic Universe actually may be the closest competitor to the Marvel universe
that we have. Because you have like Annabelle, you have the Conjuring movies,
you have Annabelle, you have the Nun. Now, they're doing quite well. And James
Wan is a completely underrated director. He came off of Saw movies. He's done
these Conjuring movies. He's done Fast and Furious. He's doing Aquaman. Very
underrated director overall. I really like his style. However, I didn't like the
Conjuring. And I wrote a full review of it on my movie review website, Video
Vandals, which I'll put in the link below. I wasn't a fan of it. So, when I started
doing this research, I started reading stuff that the movie The Conjuring 2 was
actually haunted by demons. There were rituals in the movie of The Conjuring 2
that made people get possessed and brought demons into your house and movie
theater and things like that. And I was like, okay, you know, again, take off my
skeptic hat because that sounds completely foolish that a movie in such
wide release could have something like that in it. Take off my skeptic hat. And
I'm doing my research and they're like, a woman was possessed watching this movie.
And I was like, okay, you know, looking at it, the woman's like in the audience
going, "Raaah, raaah." And then it was debunked. The video of her free-- she
related freak out during a movie. It was probably some sort of epileptic fit, but
it wasn't The Conjuring 2. It actually happened years before The Conjuring 2
came out. So that story got debunked, but people still passed it around and said
there are real rituals used in this movie to bring demons out. Now, I will say
this at this point. Before I prepped this story, I was like, well, I should watch
The Conjuring 2. And it was-- okay, there is a-- and I talked about this when I
talked about the boo pill, how I think that a lot of girls are more into horror
and paranormal than people think. The Conjuring and The Conjuring 2 and the
Annabelle movies are what I call date. They're basically date movies. They're
either movies that girls go in groups together to watch, or you bring a girl
to see it. Guys don't-- you don't get, "Hey, bro, what's happened this week?" And
"Oh, yeah, dude, the nun's coming out. Hell, yeah, let's go see." That's not who
those movies are made for. The audience of that are women. Conjuring movies and
Annabelle, they're all set up for that. They're perfect date movies, honestly,
because you know it's not gonna be super gory like Saw, and it's gonna scare her,
which is gonna turn her on. Perfect date movies. But I'm watching it alone in my
apartment, and I was like, "This movie is boring." It wasn't-- I didn't have a date
with me. The storyline was, "Oh, there's a haunted house, and there's like an old
man walking around the house. Had a lot of jump scares in it, which I'm not a huge
fan of. I enjoyed tension more." You can have both? So I didn't finish it. To be
honest, I watched it, and then I was like-- I watched probably about half of it, and I
just wasn't feeling it. So even though I'm supposed to do the research for the
show, I clicked it off, and instead I watched the row about a group of sorority
girls being stalked by a serial killer who is chopping their body parts off and
turning them into dolls. Starring the girl from Vander Plump Rules. I guess
that's a reality show. And Randy Couture, the fighter. I think he's a-- I think he's
a UFC guy. I don't think he's a wrestler, but anyways, I watched that instead. It
wasn't good either. The girls are hot. It was terrible though. Anyways, so I stopped
watching The Conjuring 2 to watch the row, and I ended up being disappointed on
both counts. So story's over, right? You're like, "Jason, you watched The
Conjuring 2 or half of it. Half a demon didn't show up." The video of the woman
being possessed in the movie theater was not true. It had really happened, but it
had nothing to do with that movie, and it was most likely like an epileptic fit.
So the movie's not cursed, right? This is where it gets weird. And I tried so hard,
so hard to debunk this. And I'll tell you why, how these things work. Because this
is an interesting little view on fake news, and because this is also kind of an
interesting view on how fake news spreads. I'm not saying this is fake news, but
you'll see the difference. So The Conjuring 2 comes out. In India, there is a man named
G. Ram Mohan. During the climax of the film, he's watching The Conjuring 2, he
has heart attack and dies. His buddy, H. Prasad, who said, "Hey, let's go see it, you
know, together." They're like, "Hey, let's go see The Conjuring 2." That's actually
weird, because it was two dudes seeing The Conjuring together, and I was just
talking trash. I said, "Dudes, do not go see these movies together." So I could be
wrong on that. I want to go see the movie with bunch of dudes, and I don't know
anyone, any other guy who would go see it with me. We'd go see, you know, Saw or
something like that. But anyways, are they still making those? I think they're
none. So H. Prasad and G. Ram Mohan go to The Conjuring 2 to see it in this
province in India. G. Ram Mohan has a heart attack and dies, and they take him
to the hospital, and they're like, you know, he's dead. And again, this could be a
cultural thing, but the hospital staff said to his friend, H. Prasad, "Can you take
him to The Coroners?" And H. Prasad goes, "Yeah, sure." He loads him up in what's
known as an auto rickshaw, and they leave from the hospital to go to The
Coroners. Neither of them are ever seen again. Completely gone. Now, of course, it
creates this vision of driving. Your friend's dead body is in the back of
your auto rickshaw, which I imagine is kind of like a rickshaw with a motorcycle
or a motorbike attached to it. I guess I should have researched that before I
started this, but you have your friend's dead body in the back of your rickshaw.
You're driving through India at night. The body reanimates, glowing eyes, attacks
him. Auto rickshaw goes off the side of the road. I mean, that's obviously a
fantastical interpretation of the events, but what we know is people were never
seen again. The friend or the guy or the auto rickshaw. Now, I read that story and
I immediately go, I put back on my skeptic hat and I was like, okay, that's
foolish. And I started to see there was a ton of articles about this. They were
all referring to each other, which you kind of see, and they were all clustered
within a group of days. So you would have like all of this stuff happened back in
June 2016. So they'd all be days apart. It was an international story because it
involved a hit movie, but you'd see the Daily Mail report it. You would see the
New York Post in an article on it. You saw the Kaleach Times, which is an Indian
newspaper, do a story on it. And they're all grouped in this time period. So I go,
okay, this happened back in June of 2016. Obviously, we have learned more
information. No. To this day, there is not an article explaining where those
people are. I go to Snopes. I'm like, obviously Snopes must have debunked
this. Nothing. Nothing at all. I typed in conjuring to missing person debunked
nothing. No one's debunked this story, though this happened. And I want to say
this too. A lot of times when I'm reading stuff, generally it's on like the
Daily Star, but here's a little hint as far as like fake news goes, especially
involving paranormal events. They will not use names of people. They'll say an
unidentified woman complained that aliens are sneaking into her house late at
night. That's nine times out of ten, totally false. Sometimes a person may
want to, you know, be anonymous, but for the most part, that is a fake story. They
don't use exact locations. Sometimes they'll say things like in Northwest
England, you know, in Southern France. So this article, like the College Times
says, gives his name, gives where he was born, names the hospital that he was
brought to. I can't pronounce it, but they named the hospital of where he was
brought to. They talk about how the police are trying to locate the corner
office in the place where he grew up. It's very, very detailed. And as I was
looking through the articles that were coming from other countries, it left out
a lot of those details, and that's why I was super skeptical about it in the
beginning. But when you look at the articles from that province, they're
like, here's his name, here's where he was born, here's the exact hospital that
this guy was brought to. So that allows people to then track that story back.
They can call up the hospital and say, hey, I just want some clarification.
Did this event happen? Did a guy have a heart attack and go to your hospital
and then you tell them to leave? If it's real, the hospital can say yes.
If it's fake, the hospital can say no. But most stories involving paranormal
that are fake will just say a man in India died of a heart attack and his body
went missing according to authorities. He was taken to a hospital and then his
friend loaded him up in his car and drove away. Neither have been seen since.
And for a lot of people who do paranormal stuff, read this stuff, that's enough.
But when you again, you put that, you put a little bit of weight on that story,
it falls apart. This one has enough detail that I honestly think, I at least
think the first part is true. A guy had a heart attack during the conjuring,
his friend took him to the hospital. I think honestly, the second part is true.
Now, whether they were beset by raiders or pirates, I don't know what area of
India this looks like. I don't think there's like pirates roaming the jungles,
or even if there's jungles. But it's very likely that these people did go missing
because this story has not been debunked and it was a very high profile story.
It was covered in newspapers around the world. What happened to this body and the driver?
Was the man killed by the conjuring too? Was it a normal heart attack and
something normal happened to take them both off the roads and to disappear from
the face of the earth? Was the man possessed by the rituals in the movie
that I failed to finish? Who knows? It's a weird story. I think this one
is true. I don't know if he was possessed by a demon or if him and his
buddies possessed corpses are roaming the wilderness of India looking for more
people for their undead army. That's unlikely. Very unlikely. But yeah,
what happened to these two guys? Weird. Weird stuff. The world is full of
weird stuff. And again, the story just disappeared. You see all these articles
within the course of the month of June and then you see some later ones happen
around Halloween and then gone. But it is still, the story is less than
two years old, so we may get more information coming up. There may be a
500,000 man army of the dead roving India when they start to cross into another
country. Yeah, creepy. There's a billion people over there, so I mean, you can
miss two. Probably pretty easy, but yeah, creepy. But anyways, let's go ahead
and move on to the next story. Yeah, let's go ahead and move on to the next
story. Okay, so we talked about this a couple episodes ago, how my birthday
was kind of a bit of a bummer. But it got better. I went out with a couple
friends that night and then about two nights later, my friends Hank, Dors,
and Wayne took me to the Trillium. If you're ever in Hood River, Trillium
has great burgers. Stop by there. I prefer the Wrangler. I actually prefer them all.
The Uranium is very good as well. Anyway, so we're out and there's one thing
that I've noticed that when I'm talking to anyone considerably younger than
myself, for whatever reason, two subjects always come up. Harry Potter and
Firefly. I dislike them both. I think Firefly is completely overrated and I
think Harry Potter is lame. I've never read the book, never seen a movie. I will
go over now very quickly everything I know about Harry Potter. Harry Potter
gets touched by a dude on the forehead and gets a lightning bolt. His parents
get killed. He ends up living in the closet with his uncle. Now he shows up,
invites him to go to a school. He goes to the school. There he meets a dwarf
named Dobby and a gay wizard named Dumbledore. Then I know nothing about
him. I know nothing that happens at all until Edward from Twilight gets killed
during some sort of tournament and Dumbledore falls off a building and
then a guy named Voldemort, aka Tom Riddle, I know that for some reason,
decides to fight Harry Potter and they shoot magic at each other and then
Hermione turns black. That's really all I know. I know stuff like I know the
names of the four schools, unfortunately. I know the names of the characters.
I know... I mean really that's it. I know there's something called a
time-turner and there's stuff you can drink that turns you into the opposite
gender. Very, very basic knowledge of Harry Potter. Now you think, oh, that
Hermione turns black thing, that was just some sort of flippin' thing, but
it's important to this conspiracy theory. This conspiracy theory started in
2005 by a Norwegian director named Nina Grunfeld. She was doing an interview
for a Norwegian newspaper and she claimed that J.K. Rowling did not write the
Harry Potter books. She didn't write them. They wore a manufactured series of
books. This was her quote. "But can a person be so productive and commercially
successful in a media industry where nothing is left to coincidence? Is it
possible that a person can write six thick books that are translated into
55 languages and sell more than 250 million copies in less than 10 years?
Is it probable that the stories then get filmed and commercially exploited to
a degree scene here without any well-thought-out strategy or highly
professional players behind them? Is it possible that J.K. Rowling exists?
Well, who do they think they're kidding? Not me." She thinks that J.K. Rowling
is an actress that basically a group of marketing executives hired a bunch of
writers to crank these books out. They hired a face with a story. She's a
young woman. She's a single mother. She's dirt poor. And she's sitting at the
train station one day. The train is late. She comes up with the idea for Harry
Potter. She ends up writing notes on little pieces of paper while she's
sitting at cafes. She creates the first three chapters of the book, goes to
the publisher, they buy it, it becomes the biggest book series of all time.
That's the official story. Nina's pushback on that is, and this was
interesting, so the first part of that you're like, "Well, you know, I guess it's
possible to write seven books in 10 years and it's just like every book's
phenomenal, has this great marketing rollout and so on and so forth." And the
movies are super successful as well. Her pushback is Nancy Drew, the author of
Nancy Drew never existed. That was also a huge series. Each book was written by
a group of writers. So they wrote the books, they just had one name. That was
the series. So she goes, "There is precedent for this as well." The defense,
they, you know, obviously when Nina said this stuff, people started going,
"What? That's ridiculous." They talked to this Norwegian translator. He worked
on translating Harry Potter books. He says that, "No, the books, this was
their defense. The books were definitely written by one author because if you
look at the books, he sees a consistent weakness in Rowling's work." And he goes,
"A group of writers could not have the same weaknesses when they write." So
basically, the defense is, she sucks and take a group of people can't suck in
the same way as just Rowling sucks. Now again, I haven't read the books. They
don't really appeal to me. I'm not a fan of fantasy magic. But anyways, the
defense basically. And then the other defense is that's Ludacris. No, she did
write those books. But is there proof that she wrote those books? Well, I mean,
you know, unless we go through and find the notes and all that stuff. And the
story makes sense on one level that you could see a marketing team say, "Hey, we
have this cool idea. We're just going to pay these young people to write these
books." And J.K. Rowling will be this fictional character we created. However,
the conspiracy theory didn't catch on. And Nina admits it's a conspiracy
theory. She gave the interview in 2005. And that was it. It was just a little
article in the back of a Norwegian newspaper that a couple other newspapers
addressed as, "Look at how crazy this is." And that was it until 2011. Now,
in 2011, The Simpsons did an episode called The Book Job. Now, I am still a huge
fan of The Simpsons. And anyone who says the show ended in season seven or season
nine or whatever, you're not watching the new stuff. And it is still really good.
The Book Job is one of my favorite episodes. This is season 23. It's a good
episode for two reasons. One, because it talks about the conspiracy theory that J.K.
Rowling did not write the Harry Potter books. It's obviously referencing her.
So, in The Book Job, Homer, Principal Skinner, Bart, Moe, and one of the sisters,
one of Marge's sisters, gets together and they decide to crank out fantasy novels
because now they know that the whole thing is fake. It's just a group of writers
writing one series of books and they have a face for the novel. And so, it takes
this conspiracy theory and turns it into the plot. And the whole thing is set up.
It's called The Book Job because it's set up like a heist. It's set up like a heist
movie. They show them assembling the team and pulling off the con. It's actually
kind of like an Ocean's Eleven parody. It's a very, very funny episode. It's a very
clever episode. And it talks about a conspiracy theory that up until that point
was relegated to the back page of newspapers in Norway. It's one of those
conspiracies that actually rings a little true. I first heard about the conspiracy
theory. I worked backwards on this. I saw the Simpsons episode first and thought
it was funny. And when you're watching it, you're thinking, "That actually sounds
fairly accurate." The whole episode is about the marketing teams that create
these young adult novels. And they keep referencing this idea. And it almost feels
when you're watching it, you're like, "That sounds so true." And James Fry,
who wrote A Million Little Fibers, he was the guy who wrote that book that ended
up being not true. He said it was a biography, not true. He started a company
that would hire young writers who just are out of college, graduate school, to
crank out novels. And I Am Number Four came from that workshop. It's not even a
workshop. It's a job. You show up there, you write for eight hours a day. You go
home and it was just full of people. I Am Number Four. So we have proof that young
adult novels are cranked out by teams of people. Twilight was four books. They're
fairly... I read more of the Twilight... I read three of the Twilight books and I'm
the Harry Potter. But if somebody told me no, that was actually also a team of
writers or 50 Shades of Grey after the first one, it was a team of writers.
It wouldn't shock me because at a certain point, the publishing company has
invested money into you. So they may not just have an editor work on your stuff.
They may have another writer come in and spruce it up. Harry Potter is a phenomenon.
No other young adult novel has its own version of a theme park. None of them have
the level of video games. It would not shock me if the allegations are true.
J.K. Rowling has not responded to these things. And you could say, well, yeah,
who's going to respond to every conspiracy theory? Obama released his birth certificate.
J.K. Rowling hasn't responded to this stuff. Not after the initial allegation,
not after the Simpsons episode that I've seen, that I've been able to see at least.
Here's the thing, this is one of those conspiracy theories where if it's not
true, it's definitely possible. It's definitely possible. Now, let me go back
and this is where I think kind of the proof comes in. When I was saying about
what I know about Harry Potter, I said at the end, Hermione, whatever,
becomes black. And I think this ties into the conspiracy theory.
So when they moved it to the play, they did a Broadway theater,
Hermione was portrayed as a black actress. And J.K. Rowling was like,
"Yes, I'm totally fine with this decision. It's 2016. Everything's great."
But let's look at some other stuff that happened. In the Harry Potter movies,
I found all this stuff when I was researching it, there were two young black kids
who later in the movies when they got speaking lines were replaced by white people.
There was a young actress named, not actress, there's a young character named
Pansy Pinkerton or Pansy Parkinson's or whatever. She was played by a cute little young girl
and the rumor is, and there's a little bit of truth to this, J.K. Rowling hates that character
so much, it reminded her of all the girls that picked on her in school, that she asked
them to replace her with an ugly actress. Because she didn't want to see a cute girl
being someone who reminded her of a bully. And they did. I don't think the girl
that they replaced her with is ugly, but definitely not this cute little girl.
You have Dumbledore being gay, which J.K. Rowling was like Dumbledore's gay.
And now that they're doing the prequel movies, the director's like,
"Ehh, we're not really going to show that." And the fans are all upset and J.K. Rowling's like,
"Ugh, you have Johnny Depp, accused wife beater, being in the prequel movies of Harry Potter,
the Fantastic Beasts movies. And J.K. Rowling is a very big, like, proponent of women's rights.
She's been brought to task for that." So from those little stories, I think you could say,
and I think through J.K. Rowling's tweets and all that stuff, she's very social justice conscience.
You know, racism and all that stuff, sexism is very in her consciousness.
And yet she's supposed to also have tons of control over this franchise.
And black people are being replaced by white people when they get speaking lines.
That's ridiculous. Accused wife beaters are in movies that are based on her work,
but then she has to defend. She outs a character as being gay,
but when someone else has control of it, they change that, or they're not revealing that.
If she has all this power over this franchise, why can't she just say, "No, I don't want these actors,
I don't want these black kids to turn into white kids." That's racist. That's totally racist.
You give the kids lines and they become white.
So either she's this literary mastermind who's written the best-selling book series of the past 100 years,
or she's an actress who has no control and no say over what goes on in the stories.
And you may go, "Well, Jason Warner Brothers bought the movies, they can do whatever."
And fair. That's fair. But it still doesn't jive with the idea or the image that she has control over this franchise,
over the books, or over the movies, or some sort of input.
E. L. James, who did 50 Shades of Grey, she was allowed on the set of at least the first movie.
She went in with almost total control, creative control, and she butted head with the directors and all that stuff.
And that was the first time they didn't even know if that movie was going to succeed.
J.K. Rowling apparently has all of this, she's this mega star, she has more money than the Queen of England personally.
She has like $900 million, she has all these homes.
She's constantly talking about the social justice causes, but when the rubber meets the road, they're gone.
So it could be one of two things. She's a hypocrite, only in it for the money.
Or she is an actress who can say whatever she wants, but the real power, the marketing team, the writers behind the scenes,
they're the ones who are like, "Oh, J.K. Rowling's talking about refugees again, but we're not changing the script."
These black kids become white.
You go, "Jason, if that's true, why did Hermione become a black person in the play?"
I don't know, throw her a bone.
But Hermione being portrayed by a black actress in the play was like, "Oh my God, look at how progressive we are."
But then there were two black kids who didn't have any lines, and then they became white and they had lines.
You can turn Hermione into a thousand people.
That's totally racist.
That is so racist.
I just found out about that tonight.
Okay, anyways, I'm getting off topic.
Let's wrap this up.
I personally think it's very plausible that she didn't write those books.
I'm not saying it's true, but I'm saying it's very plausible.
I'm saying it's a conspiracy theory that -- what's the pushback on that?
Oh, yes, she did.
It's a conspiracy theory that makes sense.
There's precedent for it before and other forms of the same genre.
Recent precedents, we can never really prove that she wrote those books unless she like hands-over handwritten notes and things like that.
I think -- if somebody came to me tomorrow and said, "We have proved JK Rowley didn't write these books," then it wouldn't shock me.
I think it would shock a lot of people.
To go back to her, Nina said, "The only way this thing will ever be exposed is if JK Rowley admits she didn't do it because she's tired of living her life," or the writers who wrote the book come out.
And again, the defense is, "Well, if she's an actress, why does she have all this money?"
Well, she doesn't.
It's all an act.
Just like when you see rappers walk around with $500,000 of gold chains on their necks in front of the Lamborghini, it's rented.
So those houses exist, and she has a pretty big bank account, but everything else is fake.
You know, it's not like she owns five houses.
The company owns five houses, and she's allowed to live in one and travel to the other and things like that to keep the story going.
So that's it.
You can research this one.
You're not going to find a lot, unfortunately.
But maybe some people will be able to provide us evidence one way or the other.
You could all -- I keep saying if someone told me that she wrote these, then it had proof that she wrote these, I'd believe that, too.
But as it stands right now, if someone asked me to bet $100 that JK Rowley wrote the Harry Potter books, I'd hesitate to take that bet.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can hit a set -- you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
I'm going to go and get my laundry in my dark hallway now.
If I get attacked by a ghost, this episode won't get uploaded.
If it's uploaded, I was not attacked.
Maybe possessed, but not attacked.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[music]