are black helicopters, the scourge of conspiracy theorists and ranchers everywhere,
really organic living creatures.
Then we take a look at a laughing epidemic that struck several girl schools in Africa,
and then it spread into the nearby communities.
And then finally we take a look at the history of ghost steamboats.
Some say they still sail down the river.
I don't know, swim, whatever a boat does, move down the river.
Some say even today you can see their ghostly boat figures, whatever.
You get it, you get it. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
You know you're in for one of those episodes and I can't even get through the intro correctly.
A lot of times I go back and have to rerecord them a couple times.
We're just gonna let that one stand for now.
We're just gonna let that one stand because we got a lot of good stuff today.
Now, first thing we're gonna talk about is actually a recommendation from Shakira Shakira.
Now Shakira Shakira has given us some great stuff in the past.
I mentioned this briefly the other day.
I was dead asleep and I didn't... usually I have my notification shut off on my phone
because I get email at all matters of the day and the night and things like that.
And I got a notification. My phone's all ding and I was like, "Ugh, woke up."
And Shakira Shakira had sent me a link about organic black helicopters.
Now I was actually really excited because organic black helicopters is on the conspiracy theory iceberg.
It's something that I wanted to talk about but I could never find any information on it.
So I was like, "Okay, cool." He or she, I don't know, might actually be the real Shakira, possibly.
But I was like, "Okay, awesome. This person gave me this resource.
It gave me the link to the official page of the organic black helicopters."
Brief, brief overview.
Black helicopters are basically a theory, a thing that's been around since about the 60s and 70s
where these relatively silent, completely black helicopters, so they're painted black
and they have no registry numbers on them.
Most helicopters have like aircraft to have like a registry number.
These helicopters have no markings so you don't know if they're federal, you don't know if they're state,
you don't know if it's some sort of private company or anything like that.
They're relatively silent and a lot of times they're in connection with the men in black.
A lot of times they're in connection with cattle mutilations.
The militia groups, which is a, it still kind of is a big thing in America,
but it was more big during the 80s and 90s.
They always thought that the black helicopters were government controlled.
Here's the thing, black helicopters was one of those things that conspiracy theorists talked about a lot
and I always thought, well, duh, of course the government has unmarked helicopters.
Of course the government has silent helicopters.
It always seemed to be a no-brainer.
To me, you could always, I could just, I don't think they had anything to do with the men in black or cattle mutilations,
but I'm sure that black helicopters, unmarked helicopters actually existed.
I never understood why that was ever an issue.
We did have it, we do have stealth helicopters.
One of them crashed during the Osama bin Laden raid.
They actually have technology so they're not as loud and they have a very low radar signature.
So black helicopters, the theory that they're out there and either the government's using them to spy on its own citizens
or it's some extra governmental agency or they're connected to some interdimensional or extraterrestrial group.
That's been around for a long time, but on the conspiracy iceberg,
there was the listing "Organic Black Helicopter".
So, like I said, I was excited when I saw this website and the next day when I woke up,
I took a look at it and it has, it's totally fake.
It's a joke. The whole theory is absolutely a joke.
And it's funny because it's hard to tell sometimes.
I had a friend, Mitchum, who sent me a thing called "Birds Aren't Real".
I think I talked about that quite a while ago.
And when you first look at it, you're like, are there actually people who believe that birds aren't real?
But once you kind of start digging into it and you see a lot of the photos, you're like, okay, this is a joke.
Like, this is making fun of conspiracy theorists.
Organic black helicopters are the same thing.
And after probably spending about 20 minutes reading the website, I saw stuff like,
"How to fight a baby black helicopter?"
And they're like, "Here's step one, get a flyswatter."
And I was like, "What?"
And then the logo for the anti-organic black helicopters is a flyswatter.
There is a video of an autopsy or a photo of an autopsy on a baby black helicopter.
It is simply someone taking a model helicopter apart piece by piece.
So it's very tongue-in-cheek.
But again, I'm thinking maybe this guy's just delusional.
I went to the frequently asked questions and it's very tongue-in-cheek there.
So it was just a joke.
There could be someone else who believes that theory out there and has a different take on it.
Oh, and the idea was that black helicopters can have sex with each other
and make other black helicopters appear.
Or black helicopters can have sex with you.
And you either turn into a black helicopter or a bunch of baby black helicopters come out of your skin.
But again, it's hard to tell sometimes.
This site was obviously tongue-in-cheek once you kind of know what to look for.
Like I said, I went to the frequently asked questions and it was like,
"Oh, no one lies on the internet, right?"
And I was like, "Okay, this guy knows what's up."
But there are other people out there who have crazier beliefs
and you just, again, you have to kind of go, "Well, maybe they believe this, maybe they don't."
So you're thinking, "Jason, okay, that's really going to be one of your topics for the show."
Well, I was like, "Okay, I can talk about that a little bit. There's not much I can do."
But still, you know, I got to fill out the show, right?
You can't leave you guys wanting.
I was thinking about this today.
Black helicopters aside.
Why don't we have good mascots anymore?
And not like baseball mascots and stuff like that.
But when I was a kid, we had Spud's McKinsey and we had like Chester, Cheeto, Dude, the Cat.
And we had the, um, the, oh, the Yo-Karro Taco Bell dog
and the little rat people for Quiznos and Jared Fogle for someone.
But we had like mascots. Actually, that's probably the reason why we don't have mascots anymore.
It's because Jared Fogle, but we used to have a lot and I don't think we have them anymore.
And I was thinking about that as like, those were always good ways to connect with the brand.
Like, you should have mascots.
To be fair, we don't necessarily have a mascot here at Dead Rabbit Radio, but...
And then I started thinking, there is a subculture of mascots that I want to have sex with.
There is a subculture of like sexy mascots.
Sexy mascots.
So you're like, Jason, are you really talking about this? Yeah, yeah, you know, here.
There are, I have a list of mascots that I want to have sex with.
Flo, the progressive girl, she's pretty hot. She looks like she'd be kind of crazy.
The E-surance girl, remember the little cartoon chick? She really, she had a really nice body.
Plus she was athletic, that's always cool.
There was this girl who was in Honda ads. She was like the, not the car salesman,
but she was like the girl behind the counter. She was really hot.
See, it's kind of like that down to earth hot. It's kind of like that down to earth hot.
I was watching a movie last night called Sex Files, She Alien.
And I thought it was just going to be like a, what's it called?
A type of movie like Species, but it was actually like a soft-core porn.
And it was bizarre because the actress didn't talk the whole movie.
Someone else did the voiceover and it was actually a totally different actress.
You could tell because sometimes they would show the person talking.
It was someone totally different. It was super bizarre.
But she was like super, super hot. And like sometimes you want like down to earth hot.
Down to earth hot.
The Sunmaid Raisins girl on a little box, she's hot.
I know a lot of people like the Wendy's girl, but she looks too young.
I know they've tried to age her up recently. So she looks like she's in her 20s.
But it's still, she still looks young.
Side note, Grimace, if you type in Grimace porn, you will get no joke.
Multiple images by multiple artists of Grimace eating the Wendy's girl.
What? So bizarre.
The Green M&M. The Green M&M, she has been like, she's sexy.
Like she's a bit round, you know, she's a bit Ruben-esque.
She's not, you know, but there's just something attractive about her.
She has no like female characteristics other than like I think lips and big eyelashes and a feminine voice.
But she's still quite attractive.
Any commercial that involves a librarian taking off her glasses and throwing your hair back.
Those pop up every once in a while. Rare. Mostly in 1980s music videos, but you'll see them every once in a while.
So there we go. That's organic black helicopters slash mascots that I want to have sex with.
I didn't have enough. I didn't have enough for the black helicopters thing, but I didn't want to just end it.
Okay, the next story we're going to talk about is you're like Jason.
We'd prefer if you just didn't put filler in the episode.
We'd just prefer if you said there's nothing here and moved on.
The next story we're going to talk about, or maybe you don't prefer, maybe you do want to know that probably not.
Okay, so then it's Friday, so this is my crazy day.
The next story we're going to talk about is weird because it's one of those stories that either reason behind it is bizarre,
but one is far creepier than the other.
So we're going back to Africa. We've been in England a lot now.
We spent a lot of time in England, a lot of time in Africa.
Most of the time in the United States. We're going back to Africa though.
Now, this was in the region of Tongaika.
And what happened? It was just kind of a creepy visual the way everything sets out.
It's January 30th. It's 1962. So we're back in time.
And all the, it's like this girl's school and everyone's just, you know, taking notes, listening to the teacher, messing around, shooting spitballs, whatever.
And there's these three girls in school in the class who just start laughing.
[Laughter]
And the teacher's like, "Okay girls, you know, stop laughing. You're in class."
And they keep laughing and it's getting disruptive. They're not stopping.
The teacher gets frustrated. She goes, "You know what? You guys go out to the schoolyard. Go out to this courtyard. You guys are disrupting the class."
So the three girls march outside and they're in the courtyard.
And the teacher continues her lesson and then one of the students goes, "Teacher, they're still laughing."
And the teacher looks out the window and she sees these three girls just standing there.
[Laughter]
At nothing. And then other kids in the classroom start to get like wide smiles on their face.
The kids were described as having no joy on their face.
Their eyes actually looked like they were on the verge of tears.
But they had these big smiles and they were laughing uncontrollably.
So you had 160 kids at the school total.
Out of those 160, this laughing virus hit 95 of them.
And some of the girls would start crying, crying out loud as they were laughing.
And the adults now are getting really concerned about what's going on.
You have almost 100 kids just laughing and they'd ask, "What are you laughing about?"
They're like, "I don't know. I don't know."
Some of them use the term, "Things are moving in my mind."
Now, teachers were getting frustrated by this, but at the same time they're getting concerned,
they begin to try to physically move the kids to airy because they don't know what's going on.
So they're like, "Get up. Get up." And the girl would just be laughing, laughing.
They'd pick them up. The girls would start fighting back very violently.
And the teacher would have to back off.
These symptoms of this laughter, they had to dismiss the class.
They're like, "Everyone go home. Everyone go home."
But even when they went home, these kids would be laughing for a couple hours, just laughing to themselves.
Some of them laughed for up to 16 days.
Now, this is so recent that a lot of researchers went out there.
So it's not something that has a lot of hyperbole behind it.
It's not something that it's like a laughing fit that happened 400 years ago where you could be like,
"Well, maybe it wasn't that long. Maybe it was just hyperbole."
But there were researchers going out there to try to figure out what this was,
because what happened was, this continued for a while, obviously, the school actually shut down.
They're like, "We don't know what's going on. The kids are super disruptive.
We're totally afraid that this might be some sort of viral thing."
School shuts down. And when the school shuts down, a lot of the kids who were from neighboring areas went,
you know, some of the kids, like I said, went home who were around there,
but other kids went far away back to their homes, and the laughing virus spread in those towns as well.
They had another nearby middle school. 48 girls start laughing.
In all, in total, this thing went on for about six months to two years, depending on what area you were in.
Overall, 1,000 people infected with this virus. 14 schools just had to close until they could figure it out.
There was other physical symptoms, pain, fainting, flat flatuance,
which would just make you laugh more as, like, everyone in your family is laughing and your dad's passing gas.
Now, there's two theories here again.
The first one is what you would assume, which would be mass hysteria.
And they were saying that these kids were coming like a war had just ended in their area, a conflict had just ended in their area,
and now they're in school, so they're like, they're dealing with the stress of school,
and they're dealing with basically the PTSD of this conflict, and they're breaking down.
It was just this case of mass hysteria, which again is creepy because it shows how simple the human mind is,
how easily it can break.
But there's another actually creepier scenario.
There's one researcher, Sylvia Cardosa.
It was a literal viral infection.
It was something in their brain, some sort of parasite, some sort of virus, some sort of bug in their brain that got into their brain,
and her theory was that brain damage can actually result in uncontrollable laughter.
So her theory was these kids may have actually been passing on a viral infection to other people near them
that was causing temporary brain damage, which was causing them to laugh.
And that's creepy.
Other people have said, "No, we did brain tests, and that's probably not what it was."
But if it was a virus that had not been detectable, a virus that we haven't encountered in such a large group,
they may not know what to look for.
So again, it goes with the dancing madness thing.
Like, both of those scenarios are creepy.
I think the fact that there could be some sort of viral infection that could cause temporary brain damage,
that would make you uncontrollably laugh, is even creepier.
One is just our brains are very fragile, and anyone can fall into mass delusion.
The other one is that despite how powerful we think we are, there is some sort of parasite that can actually override parts of your brain
and turn you into the Joker, basically.
I mean, turn you into someone who just laughs uncontrollably for days on end.
Quite terrifying.
And it's never been replicated.
In the area, they never had any problems with it afterwards.
It was just kind of a one-time thing, but it did last quite a while.
And it's always that thing like, if it popped back up, what would we do?
If all of a sudden, like, a town, the town of Hood River, everyone just starts, you know,
out of the 10,000 people who live here, 2,000 of them just start laughing uncontrollably.
It'd be terrifying.
Think about that.
Think about, you know, you're trying to get a date, you're going out to the club, and everyone's just laughing.
I mean, you walk in a club, everyone's laughing at you?
That'd be terrible.
I'm going to now chalk up that when anyone ever laughs at me, I'm like,
"You gotta bring a pair of sight, don't you?"
And that will be my defense against that horrible, horrible laughter when I walk into a room.
Okay, so our last story is going to be ghost boats of the river, and specifically steam boats.
Now, I'd love to say ghost boats of the Mississippi because that has kind of a cool tone to it,
but they weren't on the Mississippi, so I can't say that.
I mean, you know how big I am on hitting my facts right.
These are actually both of these boat stories are in Alabama, and both of these ghost stories I got from the National Directory of Haunted Places.
I always like plugging that book. I think it's a great book.
I don't own it. I didn't write it, anything like that.
If you use the affiliate link below, I'll get a little kickback, but, you know, I get no--
I'm not sponsored by them at all.
So we're going to look at some ghost boats.
We're going to look at boats that are ghosts or boats that had ghosts on them.
Or, yeah, that's pretty much it.
So we're going to Alabama, Alabama.
And down in Alabama, there's a place called the Tom Bigby River.
Tom-- Tom Bigby. I wonder if that was a guy named Tom.
I wonder if that's Native American, or if there was actually a guy there named Tom Bigby.
I don't know. Maybe his name was Tom B., and he was big.
But anyways, there's a river called the Tom Bigby River.
Now, we're going back in the-- Now, this story is really interesting to me, because I think there's a lot of facts to it,
and then there's a lot of legend to it, and it's-- You kind of got to figure out which is what.
So in 1908, there was this guy named Norman Stales, and he had a dream.
He wanted to build the most beautiful steamboat since the Civil War.
And in 1908, that was only like, what, 60 years ago, 40 years ago, something like that.
So he was like, "I'm going to build the steamboats like they used to have."
So he got a bunch of investors together. He got this boat, this beautiful, beautiful boat named.
And he named it-- I thought this was sweet-- he named it after his father.
So it was called James T. Staples, or James Staples boat.
James T. Staples palatial steamboat. I don't know. It was something hoity-toity, but it was definitely named after his dad, James Staples.
And he was so proud of it, and he's like, "I've built it. I've built this great boat. Like, this is ready to go."
But what happened was in 1912, he started to fall into financial distress.
They were starting to have money problems, so his creditors took the boat.
So it had been an operation, but the creditors took the boat, and he couldn't bear to have his life work, this beautiful piece of machinery,
that he sweated over for years with his dad's name on it taken from him.
And in January 1913, so basically a year after he lost the boat, he put a shotgun to his chest, killed himself.
Almost immediately, there were sightings of his ghost on the James T. Staples boat.
The crew saw him in the boiler room. Like, enough people saw him. They saw him walking around the boiler room.
The crew quit. The crew were like, "No way. There's a ghost on this ship. This is a real bad omen. We quit."
Another interesting thing that happened was all the rats jumped off the boat.
Now, normally that would be a good thing. Normally, they would be like, "You know what? That's weird. All the rats jumped off this boat.
You should be like... First off, you should be like, "I didn't know there were that many rats on this boat. Look at them!"
They're making like... They actually like, are so many rats, it looks like a small island floating down the river.
How did we have that many rats on this boat? But again, that was a bad omen that all the rats jumped off.
Again, like, if I walked in on McDonald's and I saw all the rats leaving, I wouldn't think that was a bad omen.
I wouldn't go back to the McDonald's, but I wouldn't go like, "Oh, that McDonald's is going to blow up."
Spoiler alert. And then to top it all off, James T. Staples was supposed to make a run, and the run was going to take it past Norman Staples' funeral.
And the captain was like, "You know what? That's completely disrespectful. I'm not going to sail his boat. Can't we take another route to get to where we're going?
I don't want to sail past his funeral." It was a paddle boat. It was a steamboat. It didn't sail, but I don't know the right word.
I don't want to paddle this boat down the river, and so he got fired.
And so the company hired a new crew and a new captain who didn't know about the ghosts, didn't know about the rats.
People are coming on the boat. They're like, "Man, this is a clean ship. I haven't seen one rat on it all day long."
You get on the boat, the boat's sailing, paddling down the river. It gets to where Norman Staples' grave is. The boiler blows up.
[BOOM]
"Whoa! I'm on fire! If only there were some rats here that I could milk and put the fire out!"
26 people dead, including the captain. I think the captain was down there. It doesn't matter.
It's all just blown up by the force or by the scolding hot water and all sorts of stuff. And the boat sank.
And so that's the legend of the James T. Staples boat.
What's interesting, so we know what's 100% true. Norman Staples built the boat. He killed himself. It wasn't named after his father.
The crew quit. The captain quit. They got a new crew, a new captain, and the boiler blew up.
What we don't know for sure. What's interesting about it, you can say whether or not they saw the ghost.
But the part of the story that gets suspect-- and it did blow up, but the part of the story suspect is some reports say it blew up six miles from the graveyard where Norman Staples was.
Some reports say it blew up as it was passing Norman Staples' grave. Which is a big difference. I mean, six miles is just a faulty boiler.
At the site of his grave, you could be like, "Woohoo, that is spooky."
But the fact that we have a six mile difference there makes me a little more suspicious of some of the other details in the story.
But even at the time, there was a newspaper, the Columbus Commercial, and they in their article were like, "Man, that was really weird."
But it's interesting to think how much the story's changed. I'm sure the original report was it blew up six miles from his grave.
And then over time, it's become like right as it passed his grave, which is what I read initially that it blew up.
But I thought it was an interesting story nonetheless. Now, you're thinking, "Jason, you promised me ghost boats. You promised me boats that were ghosts."
And you just told me a story about a ghost blowing up a boat, which I think is pretty-- oh, and 21 people got injured, too.
So that's a pretty good attack for a ghost for an incorporeal spirit. Or is it non-corporeal?
But anyways, that's a pretty good body count. But anyway, so let's talk about a ghost boat.
Now, we're still in Alabama. This story is equally terrifying. It's a Titanic on land, if you will.
The Eliza battle. So now we're back in 1858. So this is way back in time from the James T. Staples Riverboat.
Riverboat! That's what they're called. Anyway, so Eliza battle was a-- I'll just call it a steamboat.
What's the difference? The one with the paddle, right? I think is that a riverboat and a steamboat?
'Cause like, "Too-too!" Like, has like the smoke coming out? I should research this before I do the show, but--
Ghost steamboat. Eliza battle. 1858. It had a crew of 45. You had 60 passengers.
They're going for a nice leisurely trip down the river. It starts raining.
And well, actually, it's already raining. And they're like, "Oh, you know, coming down the river, playing ragtime music or whatever."
And, "Doo-doo-doo." Yeah, I can't do ragtime music. But anyway, so the boat's coming down the river.
And it's raining already. So everyone's kind of inside. And then it keeps raining and raining and raining.
And then it starts to flood. And they're like, "Uh-oh, this isn't good."
The temperature drops. And everything turns to sleet and ice. And the people on the boat are like, "We just need to keep going."
'Cause this is getting really, really bad, really, really fast. You have to be inside now. It's freezing cold outside.
The whole front bow, the whole sides of the ships, everything, are covered in icicles.
The temperature drops so quickly that everything's ice outside.
What happens, though, is that the stern catches on fire. I think that's the back of the boat, right?
But anyways, one of the sides of the boat, it's the bow, port, starboard. Yeah, the stern is the back.
So anyways, that part catches on fire. And they were saying that the people on the boat, I'm trying not to laugh,
but this would be a sucky thing. The people on the boat had a choice. They got either burned to death or freeze to death.
Like, you could either stay back where the fire was and be warm, but eventually burn.
Or you could go to the front of the boat and just freeze to death, because you weren't prepared for the weather.
It's super, super cold out there. And you couldn't jump into the river 'cause you'd freeze.
It was just a bad scenario altogether.
What's interesting is that the boat, because it's a flood, so the river's over the banks, and the boat starts to go out of the river
and begins crashing through the forest. And at this point, a lot of people are like,
"As bad as this seems that this boat is just, you know, smashing into trees and getting these huge gaping holes in it."
This is our chance. Because before we could either freeze to death on the boat, burn to death on the back of the boat,
jump into the river or freeze, and people start saying, "Dude, just jump onto a tree."
So as the boat was crashing--this is all real. This is all historical.
As the boat was crashing through the trees, people began jumping off the side of the boats and hanging in trees.
Overall, 29 people died. And remember, it had about 105 people on the boat, so 29 people died.
Some of them burned to death. A lot of them froze to death.
And when the rescue crew showed up, they were basically pulling people out of trees.
Some people grabbed onto the trees, they still froze, but for the most part, when they showed up, they were able to--
they were like, "What the hell? They see boat wreckage, a fire, a bunch of ice, and then a bunch of dudes up in the trees."
And it's not like they were like, "Hey, what are you doing up there?"
You're just like rescuing people, but they weren't questioning them. But you have to wonder, like, the rescue people were probably like,
"What the hell happened here? Why is a boat in the forest and the people on the boat in the trees?"
But anyways, so--and how did they have ladders back then? I wonder when--here's an interesting question.
When did we invent the ladder? Like, at what point in human history--I'm sure it was like Egyptian, like, way, way back in the day.
Wait, Jacob's ladder was in the Bible, so they were like, old things. But I wonder who the first person who said, "That's high."
I'm gonna build the ladder. And don't laugh, because that's actually, like, hard, because you don't just build--
well, I wonder what came first, actually, stairs or ladder? Like, which one? Well, I guess there's not Jacob's stairs in the Bible.
Well, I know they had stairs in the Bible. Anyways, anyways, I'll have to figure that out what came first, staples.
I'll have to figure that out what came first, stairs or ladders. I'm gonna bet--I'm gonna bet it was--I'm gonna bet it was stairs,
because you can carve those out of dirt. You can, like, make stairs in a cave. A ladder, you need, like, trees.
You need to cut a tree, and then another tree, and then, like, little trees in the middle to climb.
Stairs, you just go, "Oh, I'm just gonna move some dirt, and then I'm gonna step up and move some of the dirt."
Anyways, so the rescue crew, yes, they had ladders and possibly stairs with them. They get everyone out of the tree.
To this day, people still say that on a foggy night, you can see the Eliza battle going down the river.
A river in Alabama, which I don't remember what the name of it is, but you'll know it because you see a ghost ship.
That's creepy enough. The ghost ship going down the river is creepy, but fishermen, other boats in the area have reported,
not only do they see the ghostly image of the Eliza battle, but they hear the cries and pleas for help of the 29 people who died that night
still stuck on that ghostly steamboat. That always creeps me out. Like, they're stuck in that torment for eternity.
So I don't like rivers anyway, so I don't go down them in any type of boat, especially a ghost boat.
When it do it, I probably just fall through the bottom.
But luckily, I'd fall onto a bunch of escaping rats from some other doomship, and I would just go off to the shore.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend, guys.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]