A terrible crime spree, an unfortunate accident, and then we travel to Spain, where a family
in the 1930s was constantly being harassed by a goblin who lived in their chimney.
Sounds like a folktale, but when you had hundreds of police officers descend on the scene, everyone
heard the voice of the goblin of Zargosa, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I really, really do.
You know, I don't think I'm gonna do anything special for Christmas.
I haven't figured that out yet.
I kinda, that live Thanksgiving episode, that live episode on YouTube, it took an odd amount
of energy out of me, and I had fun doing it, but yeah, it kinda worn me out.
I'm not still worn out, I'm not all, uh, now, but it was at the perfect time, it was at
the end of the season and everything, like, I don't know if I could pull something like
that off at the beginning of the season.
I'll probably do something for Christmas, but I don't think it'll be a live episode
or anything streaming wise.
You know, and I'll address this now actually, I was gonna talk about this a couple days
ago.
You know, YouTube is making a big push, their anti-bullying push.
So, obviously this show can be considered bullying for some things, 'cause I'm debunking
or making fun of topics.
I got accused of bullying the Forrest Finn people, I got accused of bullying Hans, and
all these other groups.
Now, is it bullying?
No, not really, but I mean, the argument could be made.
I don't believe it is, I think I'm attacking the beliefs, not the person behind the beliefs,
but.
So, I don't know how much I'm gonna invest in a YouTube infrastructure at this point.
'Cause all it takes is for me to do one too many episodes on some weirdo group, and the
channel gets demonetized, which isn't a huge issue, but the channel getting taken down
and things like that.
So, I don't know how much I'm actually going to be looking at doing video or building up
the YouTube structure.
We'll still continue to post our episodes on YouTube as long as we can, but if the channel
gets taken down, we're just gonna be doing it on the podcast apps.
And we're everywhere that podcasts are available.
iTunes, Stitcher, Spotify, if you can listen, I listen to it on Podcast Addict, anywhere
there's a podcast feed, Dead Rabbit Radio is there, plus you can listen to it online as
well if you go to DeadRabbit.com, you can listen to it there.
If the channel, I don't think anything's gonna happen anytime soon with YouTube, but that
may happen.
So, I don't know how much I'm going to be, I was originally going to, you know, get
some Adobe software and start working on video editing and stuff like that, and I just
don't know if that's feasible for this show.
'Cause it's not a bullying show, but you listen to how many episodes do I make fun of people's
weirdo beliefs, weird new-agey or cultish or dangerous ideas that, you know, the channel
could get taken down for all that stuff.
We may end up just going strictly to being a podcast, which is how I always envisioned
the show, and it was, sorry YouTube guys, we're gonna keep putting it out as long as
we can, but that is unfortunately the brave new world that we live in.
Just putting that out there.
Let's go ahead though and get started with this episode.
And we're gonna start off this episode, let's go ahead and hop in the Carvener Coptor.
So get on in guys.
We're flying away, we are flying out to Nigeria.
It's November 2019, so super recent.
We land.
Oh, and also we have a new Patreon, Kyle Blank.
Kyle Blank, thank you so much for supporting the show, really, really appreciate that.
Means a lot.
And if you can't support the Patreon, get the word out about the show, that helps a
lot as well, so thank you very much Kyle.
We jump off the helicopter because Kyle is our Patreon for this episode, we're gonna
give him the honor of carrying all of our luggage, we're like, ah, giving it to him,
he's like, ah, thank you Jason for this great honor.
I'm buying more luggage in Nigeria, I'm like, hey, can I, can I look at your heaviest suitcases
just to give it to Kyle, he's like, ah.
Anyways we're in Nigeria, we're in the Yukiri community in Edo state.
And there's this woman named Ekater, Ekater, and an unnamed husband, and I know what you're
thinking, this story's fake.
Now generally when we come across stories and we don't have people's names, they tend
to be fake, we don't have her, her name is Ekater, I believe that's the last name in
the region because I was looking this stuff up, but we don't have any information here.
Anyways, long story short, she accuses him of cheating on her, and he slaps her, ah,
we're just looking at all this through the window, we're like, oh that's horrible, that's
horrible, Jason this is a horrible story, this isn't funny, and I'm like, I know, but
it's about to get funny, kind of, kind of, if you enjoy human suffering, he slaps her,
and she then reaches into his pants, I didn't know this was possible, I know it's possible
to reach into people's pants, but I didn't know this second part was possible, she reaches
into his pants, she grabs his testicles, and squeezes so hard, he dies, kills him, kills
him on the spot, and she gets arrested and she says that the devil possessed her, now
you may or may not believe in demonic possessions or the devil himself, however, I think the
ability to squeeze testicles so hard and kill someone is definitely a demonic power, is
definitely something that most humans don't have, but I would be wrong and so would you
if you agreed with me, because it's not the first time that's happened, hop back in the
carbonic hop to your leg, you're like, ah, you're like holding your legs, unless you're
a woman then you're like, this story doesn't affect me at all, I guess it still would affect
you, I remember once I kneaded this chick on accident, right between the legs and dropped
her, because it's the same thing, like you have, that's your reproductive organs, right,
it's like punching a bear in the nose, not like their nose is a reproductive organ, but
it's a soft spot, I remember once, I've actually done it multiple times, but I remember the
first time I did it, I was surprised because I accidentally kneaded this girl between the
legs and she dropped, and then I remember, I don't know, a year or two later, I was with
this other girl, and we were laying down and I moved very quickly and I kneaded her right
between the legs and she was all, ahhh, now guys have been kicked between the legs all
the time, I mean, we're not all stuntmen or we're not all members of the jackass crew,
but I remember once I hit myself with a lead pipe between the legs and I was like, ahhh,
it just caught the tip and that was bad enough, I'm like, oh, but I think eventually you
catch so many baseballs to the crotch, that still hurts, I'm not diminishing that, but
a woman who's never been in a fight, who's never been kicked between the legs, it's
some brand, it's like an astronaut landing on the moon for the first time, she has no
idea what to expect, anyways, so yeah, women can also be like, ahhh, anyways, June 20th,
we're back in the Garbinder Copter, we're headed to India, it's June 2017, there's
a cock fight, blah blah blah blah blah blah blah, these roosters are pecking at each
other, I guess Puerto Rico just made cock fighting legal or made it more legal, I don't
think people weren't cock fighting down there, I mean, people cock fight everywhere, but
I guess now it's legal, blah blah blah blah, these big chickens, it's brutal dude, they
have metal beaks, well, they have regular beaks but then they have like a little armor
put on them and then they get these gauntlets, like these Wolverine claws on their feet,
super brutal, they just attack each other, now there's a man and his wife watching their
rooster fight another rooster here in India, it's Saitola India and rooster, their rooster
loses, now I don't know if they fight to the death, they might just fight to the point
where the one rooster is just laying against the ring and just waving the other guy off,
but most likely the loser does get turned into chicken nuggets, husband and wife start
fighting over the fact that their rooster lost and you're like, oh, okay, is this story
Jason, is this story gonna end with the wife squeezing the dudes, not so hardy guys, no,
don't interrupt me, don't interrupt me, as we're having this conversation, Kyle's getting
attacked by roosters, he's still holding all of our luggage, people are like Jason, we're
gonna donate to your Patreon, they died, you're having Kyle Blankett attacked by roosters
while he's still holding our luggage, while we're having this argument and we hear Kyle
go, ah, he can't see what's attacking him, he has bunch of suitcases in front of him,
but no, she does not reach into her husband's pants and destroy his testicles, that is not
true, her father-in-law, her father-in-law steps in between the couple and goes, hey
guys, break it up, it's really not, ah, he's trying to break up this fight, she reaches
into her father-in-law's pants and squeezes his testicles so hard, he dies on the spot,
it's a real thing, it's an actual real thing, she said it was an accident, I don't know
how you accidentally, I accidentally have kneeed girls between the legs, okay, those
are accidents, I didn't like square up and then like start running towards them, it's
not an accident to reach down and then to close your fist, and then to hold on, there's
multiple steps there, April, we got one more, April 2013, hop back in the Garbinder copter,
ah, fine, we're going to China now, now again, these stories seem suspiciously fake, because
they take place in far off locations, unless you live in India, then it's across the street,
but these stories are being put out in western media, so they seem a little fake, we don't
have all of the names, but they're reported over and over and over again, so they're
most likely real, the one, well I shouldn't say that, they're probably 50/50 real, the
one in India, it says that she went to jail, but I couldn't find any follow up on the story,
now we're in China, we're in a place called Hikau China, this one actually was real,
there was a big court, there's trials for this, I was never able to find out what the
sentence was, but there was several articles on this one in China about the trial, there's
a woman who parks her scooter in front of a business, it hops off the scooter, okay,
she's going to go shopping, she just needed a parking spot, now we're sitting across the
street, all of us have our legs crossed, just in case she has testicle vision on, she's
just looking for something to destroy, destroy, destroy, it's all red and for red vision,
looking for heat signatures between legs, but anyways she doesn't see us, so she parks
her scooter in front of a business, and the business owner comes out and goes, "hey you
can't put your scooter there, that's parking for my business," and she wasn't shopping
at the business, it wasn't like she was coming, he does that to every customer, he's like,
"hey what are you doing, why are you parking there?" they're like, "I'm going to shop there,"
and he's like, "oh come on in," I guess he knew that she wasn't going to shop there,
and he comes out and he goes, "you got to move your scooter," and she looks at him
and they get an argument, and then she reaches into his pants, okay so this one, again last
one she reaches into his pants, or maybe outside his pants, maybe he was wearing like thin
pants or spandex or something, but anyways she grabs his junk and she says, "I'll squeeze
it to death, you'll never have children again," and he's first probably thinking, "I don't
have children now, so technically I can't have them again," grammatically bad threat,
second thought, "ah the pain, the pain," she squeezes his tentacles so hard they say with
me now, explode.
So Gizmodo actually, because of these articles have been going around for a while, when the
Chinese article popped up Gizmodo, that website that I think just, they don't do video game
reviews, but they do like nerd stuff, they looked into it and they asked the urologist,
"is it possible to die from having your testicles destroyed?"
The urologist said yes, there's actually a couple different things that can go on, you
can get them crushed so badly that you bleed out, that it causes like internal rupturing
inside of your body, and you can have a heart attack from the pain, the level of pain that's
going on, there's a couple that you can go into shock and then die, there's a couple
different things, well maybe you go into shock and then you fall down and hit your head, there's
a couple different things that can happen when your testicles are squeezed, but it's
definitely not outside the realm of possibility to have your testicles squeezed and die from
it.
I remember when I was in high school, I had a friend, so here we go, here we go, but
I had a friend who told me this story, and he said, he said that, so my buddy, let's say
his name is Jim, Jim tells me the story, he had a buddy named Tyler, again just making
up the name, they were playing basketball, they were playing like junior varsity basketball
game, and Tyler ended up getting knead in the nuts, really, really hard, he was going
up for a shot, the other guy jumped up to block it, he just got knead in the nuts, and
he, so if you're eating, you may want to pause, finish your food and come back to this, he
gets knead, right?
Now he continues, he's in pain obviously, but you got the adrenaline of the game, he
keeps going, and then they go back to the locker room for half time, I was not a witness
to this, this is a story I heard, maybe an urban legend, I don't want a doctor being
like, well that's impossible, because actually I think it's quite possible, they go into
the locker room, and the coach is like, come on guys, you guys got to do better, or maybe
they were winning, and the coach is like, good job, I don't know the score, but they're
taking their clothes off, they're getting ready to like, do they take their clothes off
at half time?
Maybe it was after the game, doesn't matter, the point is, is that my friend with the fake
name of Jim, saw his friend with the fake name of Tyler, take his clothes off, and at
that point he said that he could tell, just being a kid that something was wrong with
his genitals, he said that it appeared, he goes, this is what it looked like, he goes,
I look like his actual ball was busted, you have the testicular sack, and then inside it
are two testes, and they're balls, they're like, I'm assuming you know human biology,
and he goes, I look like one of them was busted, he goes, one side looks lopsided, and then
I'll never forget this, this might have been the best analogy I've ever heard, so he's
looking at this and he believes, and he saw the original accident, so he's thinking, oh
I'll do this, this guy's ball must have got busted when he got in need so hard, he said,
his testicle, his sack looked like, quote, a bag full of soup, and I remember laughing
so hard, because that's such a perfect visual, because you have a sack, and then you just
have, first off you never just put soup in a bag, so it's an alien idea to begin with,
but then you have, you're looking at this bag, and you're looking at this, he could
see the liquid sloshing around, which would technically be like, sperm and, not sperm,
what's the stuff sperm comes in?
Seamen, semen and blood, it was just full once, and thank you for listening to today's
episode, people who were formally eating, come back to tomorrow's episode, so you imagine
it's like, I don't know, just this white red mixture, something pink floating around in
it, his testicle did end up getting exploded, he lost his testicle because of that game,
I also heard a story once, when I was in middle school, there was a guy, this is most likely
in urban legends, I don't know how this would happen, but there was a naked guy, one of
my friends said he knew a guy, I believe the best, well sorry, this one I'm a little iffy
on, but I still laughed hard, there was a naked, his friend was naked, and he was jumping
on his bed, and then he jumped off the bed into his closet, and I don't know if my friend
and then goes on a magical adventure with a witch and a lion, no, I don't, that would
suck if you got teleported to an alternate dimension, like the lion, the witch and the
wardrobe or something like that, while you were fully naked, you're on the toilet, you're
taking a dump, and that's the day the portal opens up and then you're in like Narnia, you're
like half pooping, and all of a sudden there's like a little satyr in front of you, being
like ready for your adventure, anyways, where was I, oh yeah, yeah, so naked guy, my friend
told me the story, but I don't know if he was there when this happened, I think you
just heard about it later, the naked guy jumps off the bed and weee, into the closet, he
jumps into the closet, his balls, his nutsack gets caught on a, now again, I don't, let
me just tell you and then we'll discuss if this is possible, he jumps into the closet
and his balls get stuck on a coat hanger, there's a wire coat hanger, because when I
was a kid we actually had wire coat hangers, and it penetrates through the skin and like
rips the ball out, so basically like the clothes hanger I guess was like, went through
the scrotum, into the testicle, and then, or maybe just went into the scrotum and ripped
it and his testicle like dangled out, like the ball itself dangled out, his ball came
out somehow, it was hanging out and I think they had to remove it, I think it actually
penetrated both, as you're eating, as you're eating Vienna sausages right now, you're like
"Ugh, my morning is ruined Jason."
I don't know if that's possible because you think about it, you jump off your bed into
a closet, that's possible, jumping naked on a bed, that's possible, but how high would
you have to jump in the coat hangers, clothes hangers are normally fairly high, they're
on a, like a wooden beam, unless his closet floor was just a bunch of coat hangers down
there, some sort of really like basic home alone trap, in case someone gets in there
and they're like "Oh no, I'm mildly inconvenienced as I'm stepping on coat hangers, unless they
were laying on the ground, I don't see how that's possible."
But anyways, my friend told me that was true and I laughed super hard and had an odd fear
of coat hangers and jumping around naked ever since.
So yes, you can get killed doing that.
That story went on way longer than I thought it would, we're going to skip the tragic accident
story, that wasn't it, I had another story about a tragic accident, let's talk about
the goblin of Zaragoza, I think I pronounced it wrong in the beginning, I almost for certain
almost pronounced it wrong in the future.
This is actually a recommendation from Pawn Rall, Pawn Rall been listening to the show
for a long time, thank you so much.
And this is an interesting story, it's from Spain, it doesn't have a ton of detail, I
really want to cover it because of the implications.
So I'm going to go over the narrative itself is fairly brief, we're in the year 1934, it's
September 27th, there's a town called Zaragoza Spain, look at I already mispronounced, I
already had to reload to see how to pronounce it.
I've also seen it spelled with an S, Zaragoza, there's a family called the Palazón family,
now there is in Zaragoza there is a really nice apartment complex, it's like state of
the art for, not state of the art now, but in 1934 state of the art.
And so it was real well off families, they had housekeepers and these people had good
jobs and stuff like that.
And then one day you start hearing screaming, crying, banging, kind of emanating from the
walls, poltergeist, people can't figure out what's going on.
And they kind of narrow it down to the kitchen and specifically the chimney that does lead
to the ceiling and it's shared with other families so you're thinking well maybe someone's
making noise in another apartment, but they start inviting their friends over, hey what
are you doing tonight, I don't know, probably just gonna, what's 1934, there's nothing
to do, listen to the radio I guess, kind of lame, gotta use my imagination, ah forget
that, why don't you come over to my house, there's a goblin, there's a goblin living
in the chimney, plus maybe you can help me figure it out so people, the neighbors start
coming over, and it actually, this is one of the interesting things, they talk about
the goblin talking to them, but there's only one transcript, there's only one conversation
we have a record of, so apparently, like when we look at Jeff the talking mongoose, there's
a lot of, it was an old episode I did, there's a lot of references to like what he was saying
and stuff like that, in particular insults and things like that, like he called the guy
a couch potato or a big dumb oaf, just want to really have one conversation, but so people
start coming over, and of course like these things do, it's 1934, it's super boring, they're
on the edge of World War 2 so everyone's kinda stressed out anyways, so the fact that this
family has like a little monster living in their chimney, no one can figure it out, you're
gonna get people who believe in monsters and you're gonna get skeptics, this gets out into
the media, people start swarming the house, massive crowds outside, and of course the
police get involved, so now you got police scooting around trying to figure out what's
going on, Scotland Yard is looking at coming down because they're like what is this, what
is going on, plus they also want to probably spy on the Franco government, that was British's
excuse, they're like hey let's go down and quote unquote check on the goblin, as they're
really putting spies in because they know World War 2 is right around the corner, by
November you have, the police can evolve, so here's where we have a transcript, the
police ask, who are you, why are you doing this, do you do it for money, which is a dumb
question to ask a goblin, I guess they probably think it's a human at this point, but the
voice simply says no, the police go do you want a job, like what, who are these cops,
your question should, it's weird because at first they go who are you, why are you doing
this, do you want to, do you do it for money, and it's like no, that should have been three
separate questions, who are you, I'm a goblin, like they didn't even get that one, so they
ask do you want a job, he says no, and then the police go so what do you want man, that's
so weird, I didn't know they used terminology like that back then, and the voice goes nothing,
I'm not a man, so if they had said so what do you want dude, would it have been like
I'm not a dude, like this is such a weird terminology, that's the only conversation we have a transcript
for, that's it, there's no follow up to that, this story is fairly obscure, especially in
Spain's the west, but in English speaking countries, it's very rare, I found a couple
articles about it in English, I think I only found two, and the other ones I had to translate
and there's so many translation errors, so much grammatical stuff is driving me nuts,
anyways what happens is the voice kind of starts being a jerk to people, and what people
think to call this thing is in the culture of Spain there's a thing called a duende,
which is an elf or goblin would be the best translation for it, and it's funny because
those are two kind of different things, elf is kind of like this spry happy little guy
in a goblin, it's a monster goblin's an evil thing, and the duende is both as well, he
can either be totally nice or a horrible horrible jerk, it's one name that includes both types
of personalities, just like humans, we don't assume all humans are good, some are bad,
and so, but elves are generally seen as helpful, and goblins are normally seen as monstrous,
duende kind of combines the two, so what happens is it starts basically just talking trash
to people, and specifically talking trash to the maid, the maid of this family, the palazon
family, her name is Pascuala Alosa, Alosa, starts talking trash to her and all this stuff,
now the police are getting really frustrated because there's massive crowds outside this
apartment building, the other tenants are getting a little frustrated because they're
just trying to get into their apartments, so the police end up like cordoning off the building,
they won't let people into the building, they have people on the roof, cops on the roof,
standing by the chimney to see if anyone's talking in the rooftop chimney, they bring
in priests, they're spreading holy water all over the place, the voice disappears, so you
go "oh, the holy water got rid of the ghost" and the skeptics are going "it was the massive
police presence that got rid of the ghost."
Cops leave, people are let back in the building, the voice returns, and this is another quote
we have from it, "cowards, cowards, cowards, here I am!"
Family, the palazon family actually leaves for good, people are trying to record the
voice, a radio station comes in to get a recording of the voice, and then the governor of Zaragoza
is like "this is, I'm done with this, December 4th rolls around, this all happened within
a course of a couple months, runs around and he says that we figured it out, it was the
maid doing it, the maid was doing this thing labeled as unconscious vinquilitrism, and
it was labeled as quote "a psychic phenomenon produced only in certain circumstances" unquote,
so he said it was a maid, the maid was making these voices but she won't remember making
the voices, she'll never admit to making the voices because she doesn't know she made
the voices but she's making the voices, it's not a goblin, everything's fine, that was
pretty much the end of it actually, the family never came back, that explanation made the
crowds go away, people are like "oh it must have just been this girl doing this voice
on accident or unconsciously."
People still in the building afterwards said "oh you know sometimes when we walk around
there's cold spots or there's like spooky stuff happening" but it never really caught
back on and people never really associated, people figured you're just a scaredy cat because
there used to be a goblin in your fireplace, now the building was eventually torn down
you know just because it's built, well actually probably several bombs were dropped on it
during World War II but there's a new building in that spot and it's known as edificio duende
or the goblin building, I'm assuming that's a nickname, I'm not assuming that you have
a law office and people are like "hey where's your office at" and you're like "oh it's
being owned by goblin building" but stay away from the fireplace, I think someone's
eavesdropping on us, it's an interesting story for two reasons, one it's one of those things
that you have this massive police, first off the police getting involved in paranormal
stuff I'm always fascinated by, sometimes they do it just because they're curious because
police officers are humans, they still go home and watch television shows and stuff like
that, they're not like this faceless force, same thing with the military, it's really
easy to look at law enforcement in the military, it's just like this other part of society
but they're also sitting around being like "dude I wonder what it is" but they'll have
the means to say "hey let's hop in the car, let's go down there and see if we can see
someone on the roof" like they have more ability to go investigate this type of stuff, they're
curious also the fact that the traffic was getting snarled in the area, that's when they
really had to bring in a police presence to try to find out what was going on and also
to make sure that society can still function, that cars can still move down the street.
So is it possible that she was doing the voice?
Yeah it's definitely possible when everyone was moved down and the cops took over the
building the voice disappeared and then the cops leave and the voice comes back.
And she's never admitted to it, she goes "I don't know what they're talking about, I
didn't do it, they're saying I did it unconsciously and that's kind of like the perfect alibi because
then you can just end everything" but I think there's a bigger topic to this story, I think
there's a more interesting thing to this story and we'll end it on this.
There's an interesting thing to this story and we'll end it like this, is that you have
a completely audible voice, people can hear it, neighbors can hear it, police heard it,
they're interviewing it and then eventually it goes away.
Hokes?
Sure, possibly, most likely hoax.
But let's assume, let's put on our believer hats and assume that it is some sort of supernatural
force.
Why don't we have stuff like that anymore?
Because we do have "Gef the Talking Mongoose" which was a similar thing, it was kind of
just a jerk living in the house that sometimes what appears in mongoose, again, possibly
a fake, most likely a fake story, other people were hearing the voice and all that stuff.
So why have we, let's assume that it's real, let's assume all of this stuff is real.
Nowadays you gotta have the EVP.
It used to be that you could have a spiritual thing, you could go to a spiritual list of
medium, you'd ask a question, "Will I marry Bobby?"
Oh yes, four knocks means yes, but it'll be a short marriage, huh?
Used to be able to end that again, was mostly fake, but let's assume that at least some
of them were true.
Why is it that things seem to have gotten less concrete over the past 100 years, 150
years of ghost investigations or talking to ghosts?
It used to be you could have a spiritualist ceremony, you had these voices emanating from
the walls that anyone could walk by.
Now you have people walk through a haunted asylum walking with a tape recorder, maybe
they'll hear like a bang down the hallway, could just be a raccoon running around, but
they'll walk down a haunted asylum where people were being experimented on by horrible doctors
in the 1960s.
They take the tape recorder home, plug it in, slow it down and they hear "Good for
out there."
They're like, "It's said by oatmeal here."
Oh my god, you're right, I had oatmeal on me.
I forgot to wash my shirt.
So what, why in the world of supernatural, why has that changed so much?
It's an interesting thing.
It's an interesting theory because sometimes we have to step back.
It's really easy to get lost in the supernatural stories as they come about, but when you step
back to look at patterns, you start to see some more bizarre things.
Why is it that our connection to the spiritual world is getting less and less?
Why is it when we look at old stories of aliens, there's hundreds of different types of alien
races, but nowadays there's pretty much just grays?
Like I'd say since the 1980s, it's pretty much just gray aliens.
The world of the paranormal seems to be getting less and less diverse.
Why is that?
How can we go from powerful voices in the past to completely silent voices with a tape recorder?
Why is it that we used to take photos of full body apparition ghosts and now you're happy
if you can catch an orb on camera?
I think the fear has always been that the divide between the dead and the living, between
the explained and the unexplained, was going to grow closer and closer together to the
point where the mysterious is right beside you.
The creatures of our nightmares are truly under our beds.
Maybe it's the opposite.
Maybe the world of the real and the world of the dream are separating and growing farther
and farther apart.
There may be a day where there are no ghost sightings.
No EVPs.
No UFOs.
No alien encounters.
The rift could grow so wide between the realities that we are trapped in the mundane and the
story about a goblin cracking jokes in a fireplace will seem not simply unbelievable, but unfathomable.
Something that a human in the future could never even dream of in a mundane world of
the super normal.
[Music]
(upbeat music)