A personal mystery may lead to even bigger questions about the way the world works.
What happens when you're watching lost media being lost right before your eyes?
And then we travel, and then we travel to Guyana to meet a young man whose village has come
under attack from gang members.
As the chaos spreads and this young man tries to flee the gunfire, he realizes he has an
ally on his side.
A man from another world.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvera, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too, hope you guys are having tons of fun whatever
you're doing.
Unless it is currently raiding an African village then that is not good.
Do not have fun doing it.
Or just don't do that.
Even if you're not having fun doing it, just don't do that.
But someone who always has fun, everyone give a round of applause for one of our Dead Rabbit
Radio supporters.
Give it up for Shawn.
Wooo!
Everyone give him a big round of applause.
Shawn recently bought me a book off my Amazon book wish list.
That's in the show notes.
Shawn bought me a book titled, this is dope, Alien Invasion, the ultimate survival guide
for the ultimate attack.
And he read it.
He sent me a note saying that he read it and that it was an awesome book.
So thank you so much for sending that over Shawn.
I can't wait to dig into it.
Shawn, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially or buy me books or anything like that, that's
fine.
It really is just help spread the word about the show.
That also helps out so much.
You have no idea how much it helps when you tell people about Dead Rabbit Radio.
Shawn, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're gonna drive all the way down to Sacramento, California.
We're driving down to Sacramento, California because that's where I spent a lot of my
adult life.
And this first segment's gonna be really, really short.
It's a mystery that I hadn't thought about for years.
Shawn, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jet.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're flying all the way out to Sacramento.
The reason why we're headed to Sacramento because I put together this weird pattern when I was
dating.
In my dating life, I started to notice something.
Now it took me a couple years to notice this.
I'm not really quick on the uptake when it comes to personal relationships, but I started
to notice something.
The pattern I noticed was this.
If I was out on a first date with a woman, we're getting to know each other, trying to
figure everything out.
This is so weird.
And I never thought about this for a long time.
It popped in my head the other day and I was like, "Oh, that's super weird."
She talked about it on my show about paranormal and conspiracy stuff.
I'd be on a first date with a woman and if she went to the bathroom in the middle of
the date, it was over.
If on the first date, the girl goes to the bathroom, when she came back, she wanted nothing
to do with me.
And a lot of times, it wouldn't like she'd come back and be like, "Hey, thanks for the
meal."
Or "I had a nice coffee.
It's time to go."
No.
She'd come back, she'd sit down and she would be mean to me.
She would be mean.
And I could never figure it out.
Again, it took a long time for me to put it together, but I remember the exact moment
when I go, "Oh, this isn't going to work out."
She went up to go to the bathroom and I thought, "When she comes back, she's going to be mean."
Just watch.
Just watch, Jason.
I'm sure enough this girl came back and she sat down and she was mean.
She cruel almost, right?
And I didn't know what that was.
I could never figure it out.
And honestly, I had completely forgotten about it until the other day.
And I mentioned it to my friend Sabine and I go, "What could have been..."
No, this is before the era of smartphones.
I know a lot of people just figured, she went and she looked up your social media and she's
like, "Oh, this guy's a weirdo."
No, it was before that.
It was before you could find out I was a weirdo via technology.
I go, "What could have been causing that?
Why it was happening all the time if the girl didn't get up to go to the bathroom at any
point in the date?"
It was perfect.
It was a great date.
I had a second date.
What have you?
But if she went to the bathroom in the middle of the date, it was over.
They were mean to me when they came back.
And Sabine, she goes, I'm paraphrasing, but she goes, "You're a charmer, Jason.
You're a salesman."
And I can just imagine when these women are with you, you're just laying it on real thick.
And then they get up and they go to the bathroom.
Once they're out of your sphere of influence, once they go into the bathroom, they sit in
the stall for a bit, they come out, they look in the mirror, they splash a little water
in their face.
They realize, "I don't want anything to do with this guy."
Not maybe he's a nice guy, but this isn't the right time.
It's not the right time for me.
This is over.
And I go, "What?
They have to be so mean when they came out.
They get it just locked away."
You said, "It was nice meeting you."
And she didn't have an answer for that.
But I remember.
That might be, right?
That could be what was going on.
But I remember as this phenomenon kept happening, again, if they didn't go to the bathroom,
everything was awesome.
They went to the bathroom.
I knew it was over.
I remember thinking to myself, "I am a paranormal guy, paranormal conspiracy guy."
I thought, "What if women have some sort of telepathic link to other women?
Apparently, they have to go into the bathroom to activate it."
They go into the bathroom and they sit down in the toilet and they play with the knob a
little bit.
And this holographic view screen appears and it's like, "Hello, Betty.
We see that you're on a date with Carpenter, Jason.
That guy's a bad dude.
Stay away from him."
And I'm like, "Yes, Master.
Thank you, Matriarch, for giving me the orders."
Then they come back.
I remember thinking, "What if women have this psychological link to each other?"
And they communicate and they get bad advice.
I'm awesome.
Now, obviously, I didn't put too much emphasis on that, right?
I wasn't trying to infiltrate the female underworld.
Tell me who your telepathic masters are.
But I remember thinking that they were legitimately popping up in my head.
I go, "What if they can communicate with each other telepathically?"
But here's the thing.
I can never figure it out and it was definitely a pattern.
It was something that I observed over time.
It's a perfect segue into the world of gang stalking.
Now again, when I'm sitting here talking to these girls and they get up to go to the bathroom,
I think that they may be telepathically hooking into the plumbing of a bathroom and talking
to other women.
I know that's not true.
But to someone who feels they're being gang stalked, that would 100% be true.
If I was in that paranoid state of, "I thought I was being gang stalked," this is what they
do.
They look for patterns where...
What was weird is this was a clear pattern.
This happened every single time.
Or at least, I don't remember the times when the girls went to the bathroom, came back,
and we continue to have a lovely date.
I don't remember those times.
Sometimes even with gang stalking, you see a pattern.
If something doesn't fit the pattern, you forget about it.
People who are being gang stalked, they walk down the street, they see two black Honda
Civics drive by in five minutes and they go, "Oh, today the gang that's stalking me is
driving the black Honda Civics."
That's why I saw that.
None of us would even recognize that.
You'd have to see like six of them in a row to go, "Oh, now I am being gang stalked and
being gang stalked by the Honda Boys, the most vicious gang in my area."
But we've covered a lot of gang stalking stuff.
We've done some great episodes.
I'll put them in the show notes.
This is an interesting one because this is lost media and gang stalking smashed into
one.
You can accuse people who think they're being gang stalked, targeted individuals.
You can accuse targeted individuals of a lot of things, but you can't accuse them of being
lazy.
Like, they put out so much content.
They're shooting videos all the time.
They're constantly writing things down like long posts online.
They're constantly producing content because they're trying to convince people and in a
way maybe even themselves that they are being gang stalked.
So all of their faults, all of their faults, one of them is not laziness or lack of imagination
in a long time.
They're definitely imaginations.
They're part of their imagining being stalked by everyone on the planet.
A long time ago I found this and I thought about doing a story on it at the time and
I didn't.
And it's one of those things that I kind of regret because I didn't do that.
We have a case of lost media.
Some of this is still around, but the series is very short.
So I wanted to share it with you guys and I'm hoping that maybe we can start a preservation
project on this because this is one of those things that it's really just one in a million
that it gets created.
We're flying out to this unnamed American city because this is the location of a...
Because this is a location where it is.
The location is so awesome.
It's so awesome.
It is a gang stalking comic strip.
It's the story of a man named Targ.
It's not Viking.
It's not a prequel to the Northman.
It is called Targ the Target.
And it's a comic strip.
It's like set up like a Sunday morning comic strip, but instead of the story of like a
talking cat or the story of a young boy and his stuffed tiger, it's a story of a man who's
a targeted individual.
Now obviously it's a podcast and I'm going to be talking about a comic strip.
There's some stuff that's going to be lost in translation, but trust me, I think you'll
get the gist of it.
Plus go to the show notes and please help me save this comic strip if you have your
own.
You're currently a web comic artist.
Maybe you can do a spin-off.
Maybe you can do a crossover.
Who knows?
Targ the Target.
So the very first comic strip.
Very first comic strip.
He tells us about this.
My name's Targ.
My name's...
My parents should have named me Peaceful or something.
Instead they named me Targ.
I'm Targ the Target.
I'm being gangstocked.
And here's proof.
Every night someone bounces a tennis ball against my house.
Sometimes when I'm walking down the street there's pennies and cigarette butts laying
around.
One time I went to work and my...
This is actually pretty hilarious.
One time I went to work and someone took apart my work chair.
And the last panel.
So all this stuff right?
Maybe he lives next to a tennis court or maybe there's a gangstalker thrown at tennis ball
against his wall.
Maybe he lives in any major EO city or where there's pennies and cigarette butts everywhere
or there's a gangstalker who likes to smoke cigarettes and I don't know throw pennies at
ants.
Maybe he works with me and I took his work chair apart.
But all this stuff he's taught and he says like he comes home food's missing.
And then all this stuff's going on in the last panel.
He goes this is the last panel.
And this shows the mind of the gangstalker right?
Like he's finding patterns everywhere.
And then the last panel he goes even my neighbors suddenly act as if I'm some kind of sex criminal.
Now if you're waiting for a punchline I should tell you right now these comic strips aren't
funny.
It's in a comic strip...
Well I am laughing at them but they're in a comic strip forum and I go wait a second.
So cigarette butts and the food's missing and so that means I'm your roommate.
They act like you're a sex criminal.
What?
That's kind of a downer too.
Don't hit your comic strip like that too.
Family circus is like daddy why do you have to talk to all your neighbors whenever we
move and the dad's like oh I wouldn't include sex criminal stuff into your comic strip.
I am not a comic artist myself but that's how it ends.
Again not a joke.
It's not funny.
I'm laughing at it because this is insane but then the second comic strip starts up
and someone spits while he's walking past the target.
And he takes that as the fact that this guy is gangstalking him right?
This is one of these signals.
If you spit near me it must be like you're trying to harass me.
That's the whole thing they just want to harass you leaving pennies.
Well I don't know why leaving pennies and cigarette butts would be harassing.
I'd have a bunch of money each day.
And on all the free nicotine.
Guy spits near him and that he realizes he's being gangstalked today and then the third
panel.
First panel is a guy spitting.
Second panel is Targ going spit like questioning it.
And then the third panel says quote what is going on?
I had something to come on to.
There must be something else going on with you.
And the third panel goes what is going on?
I had someone call me pedophile the other day.
What?
He never brings that back up.
He never really addresses it.
I don't know if this guy actually is a sex criminal.
I don't know.
He's like man it does sure suck that people are giving me weird looks since I put my flyer
up everywhere because I'm not allowed within 50 feet of a school.
Why is everyone treating me like some sort of weirdo and spitting at me?
He keeps bringing this up that people act like he's a pedophile that he's a sex criminal
but he never addresses why those allegations would be there.
What's interesting is the comic strip is written by someone called Eleanor but Targ
is a dude and you could go that's fine Jason you know they're a dude to write wonder woman
comic books you don't necessarily have to be the same sex as the person in the comic
strip but this Eleanor breaks the fourth wall at one point and begins taking photos of their
house.
Targ is narrating their life.
It gets so weird and all we have this series used to be super long.
There used to be a time because I remember reading this probably about a year ago when
I was laughing.
I was having a good laugh when I thought but it's hard to talk about a comic strip on a
podcast.
It's really hard because you kind of have to see it and hopefully I'm making it slightly
entertaining and easy to follow but he had a ton of these and he even had a spinoff series
called Peter the Perp where we got to see the other side of the game.
It wasn't as funny.
I was like boring but what's happened I went to I was going through my bookmarks I was
looking at something else I was looking for something else and I go to Targ the target
dude I'm gonna see like where this guy's at is this guy currently still putting out
comic books gone it's gone.
There are 18 strips on a Reddit page and I've archived the Reddit page but even then
it no longer posts them you have to like click on each one and then so I don't know if I
have to archive all those because that this guy already thinks he's being gangstalked
to Google don't feed into that.
I don't it's possible that he published something super egregious towards the end and it got
scrubbed but it's gone like these 18 comic strips are all that we have of this long saga
of Targ the target.
But at one point he starts taking photographs Eleanor starts taking photographs of their
house but it's also Targ's house and it's like photographs of a chair someone broken
it was house apparently and sawed his folding chair in half and took the teeth out of his
zipper he bought a new jacket and then someone broken it was house and pulled two teeth out
of his zipper so I mean this is all still really hilarious stuff right but so he couldn't
zip up his jacket anymore and it's so weird and it's so like we talk a lot about like
the gangstalking mindset on this show we have a lot of writings about it and we have videos
about it people shooting videos of them walking down the street being like why are you gangstalking
me why are you gangstalking me but a comic strip like I think this is new this ongoing
saga of Targ this comic strip detailing all this stuff because we really got to see the
day to day life the videos are just I feel bad for the mailman some guy jumping out of
the bushes and being like why are you following me why are you coming to my house every day
and put stuff in a box this was really like a day to day and they were showing photographs
of he had a container of creamer and he would put marks on it to show how much they were
using each day and he showed his heating pad he's like someone made my heating pad all
furry it's hot when I touch it it gets hot I'm like ouch ouch what did you do to my heating
pad it's so weird someone messed up his velcro shoes there's photographs of this and then
he just then he has a panel he has a comic strip where he goes to his boss and he's like
hey boss I'm so sorry I was late for work a bunch of cars boxed me in and they made me
go really slow all the way to work and then someone like at some point when my car is
parked someone drilled a hole in like my radiator I'm sorry I'm late and the boss is like if
you're late one more time you're gonna get fired you you're crazy I don't believe any
of that and that probably happened not that he was actually gangstalked up that that stuff
happened but I'm sure he was going to his boss and being like hey I'm sorry I'm late
I was gangstalked on the way to work they made me be slow and how would you deal with
that like I guess I didn't really thought about like on the outside because we get to
see targ dealing with other people it's show like that's a real thing your boss would have
to deal with that being like what in the world is going on he's telling me that there is
a gang of unidentified people who not only came to work and disassembled his chair when
that was clearly Jason clearly Jason did that not only did they disassemble his work
chair they follow him to and from work and make him drive super slowly when in the real
world we just call that traffic really really interesting story at one point his cat gets
its throat slit I know it's a super weird escalation the cat gets its throat slit and
the cops blame him and say listen you've been calling us you've been making all these complaints
for a long time we're a little concerned for your mental health and that becomes a reoccurring
thing he keeps bringing up the cat so did he kill his own cat did someone else kill the
cat weird it really really is weird and it's disappearing and I wish that if someone else
I'm also putting if someone else can recover the other couple dozen I think there was like
30 of these comics originally I have in the show notes you're going to be able to read
the first 18 strips of target the target and then there's a couple panels a couple strips
also of Peter the perp this is a series but this is lost media that's going to disappear
and it's one of those things that's lost media that nobody would have even known was lost
I stumbled across it a year ago I had a good laugh I said it's really hard to talk about
pictures on a podcast and let it go but now that this thing may be disappearing it is our
duty as listeners of a paranormal podcast to try to save us and try to recover some
of it because it's it's crazy it's absolutely crazy so that is the saga of target the target
is this the end will it just fade away I don't know what happened to the dude it doesn't look
like he's posting anything else Eleanor whatever name whoever is doing it's target the target's
creator isn't putting out anything else that I can find so interesting lost media right
for our eyes the ramblings of a madman put into comic strip form and telling a story
that's just completely unbelievable but to the person in the story and the person writing
the story it's true life absolutely fascinating Sean let's go ahead and toss you the keys
of the carbonic copter we're leaving behind the city as I'm throwing pennies out on the
street I'm like haha I will be part of your madness we're leaving behind the city we are
headed all the way out to Guiana the story was posted online by a user known as GTR Nick
so we're just going to call this dude Nick in Guiana there is an unnamed village that
Nick lives at and this village is near the outskirts of Georgetown so it doesn't have
the same amount of safety that a major city would have for the residents and because they're
this farther off town every so often organized criminals will come through the village and
basically shake down the people there Raiders I mean if any other period of time you would
imagine like Mongol warriors on horseback or Vikings coming into France and just taking
what they wanted and leaving but nowadays it's organized gangs with guns and cars not an easy
life for Nick and to make it even worse he had chronic asthma so he had a hard time this
is super stressful right it's super stressful and you're like you're trying not to get too
freaked out because your asthma is going to kick up but constantly dudes are running around
with guns taking your newest toy they're like alright so he had chronic asthma as a kid
he could run but he couldn't never really run at full speed and he couldn't run for
that long so it made it a little bit harder probably to play soccer and to have a lot
of fun with the other kids but what are you going to do you have bigger problems every
so often armed Raiders coming to your town if you're not picked first for a soccer game
I think you'll be okay but Nick he was dealing with this chronic asthma as a kid and at this
point when this story takes place he's 12 years old now what would happen and this this
makes sense right after the umpteenth time some Raiders came into town it's not like
it was even the same group of Raiders you could get a bunch of people come into town and be
like give us all your money and they leave and then two days later a different gang
shows up and being like hey guys guess what we're here for all your money and they're
like we already gave your date your couple days late buddy you already gave all our money
to someone else the leaders of this particular village were like we're not doing this anymore
we're not doing this anymore we're done so they started to put up a fight now when the
Raiders would show up and they weren't easily getting what they wanted a lot of times that
sometimes that's all it takes right it's for someone to be like no and then they leave
like I don't recommend that if you're getting mugged just give me your watch and your wallet
but sometimes that's all it takes but this time in this story we don't have a time period
for this story but I'm just gonna place it's probably somewhere around the early 2000s 90s
probably somewhere in there on this particular time the Raiders show up to the town the village
leaders go out and they say we are not going to give you anything you gotta leave and the
Raiders go that we're not gonna accept that you gotta give us something you gotta give
a I don't know what about that goat over there it looks a little sick you don't need to know
we're not giving you anything the village leaders said we've had it up to here with you guys
coming into town and trying to take our stuff as silence fills the village for a moment little
nick is in his house looking through the window there with the rest of his family the village
leaders are out there the gang members are out there there's an eerie silence and soon
the silence was replaced with wave after wave of automatic gunfire people just start running
out of their houses they know at this point the gang is most likely most likely gonna
win and they're just gonna go house to house and start taking stuff and if you're in the
house who knows what's gonna happen to you Nick and his family run out of their house
and they're running down the street and everyone's running out of their houses trying to get
away from what's going on and there's gunfire echoing everywhere and there's so much chaos
in the street everyone's just kind of running in different directions kind of pushing stuff
around Nick realizes very quickly he is no longer running with his family he's running
with some people that he doesn't know and then he's running with some people he does
know in this group and some of them he's like I don't know you nice to meet you my name's
Nick but he does realize that he happens to be in the group of people out of all the groups
of people that are running through the village now he's running with the village leader who
started this whole thing by not giving them anything he's literally running with the one
guy they want to kill more than anyone Nick's running with this group of adults and he says
one by one he's watching bodies drop on each side of him because the leaders with them
this is the group that the gang is targeting the most and Lil Nick 12 years old can you
imagine this running watching adults get blown away right next to him he's never run this
fast in his life he's never run this far in his life he physically can't but he's doing
it because he's going to die otherwise he has to run and all of a sudden the sun in
the sky begins to glow so bright Nick's never seen anything that blinding and this white
light begins to encompass his entire vision until he can see nothing but the light and
he thinks in his head my body's shutting down like I've run so far I'm not able to get
enough breath my brain shutting down my body shutting down this is the end he's seeing
this great white light because his body just can't handle all of the pressure he's putting
on it but then the bright light focuses to a single point and once again Nick can now
see the village clearly and he's running like he was running before but when he turns to
a side he sees a stranger running next to him he says the guy was wearing this kind
of weird outfit it was nothing that he recognized that any of the other people in the village
would wear this guy's running next to him and he goes he was keeping pace with me but
I knew he was running faster than me like we're side to side but he is running so fast I look
down and his legs are moving so quickly they're leaving a blur he goes I can see an after
image of his legs as he's running I'm keeping up with him and the man it's an adult looks
down at him and smiles and says quote just keep running we're almost there and you're
doing great Nick said the man was so confident he just exuded this confidence it comforted
Nick he felt safe he felt protected he himself little Nick felt powerful in this moment a
gunshot rings out right behind Nick it's too close it's too close and the stranger just
gently pushed Nick's arm just gave him a little shove the world goes black
Nick wakes up in a hospital in Georgetown he's being attended to and everyone's asking dude
how did you get here how did you run all the way from that village to Georgetown he doesn't
have an answer he didn't know he didn't know he was in Georgetown I was running this guy
showed up and we were running together and then I blacked out I don't know what happened
after that years later Nick and his family moved to the United States the land of opportunity
there they can leave behind the chaos of this village him and his family come to the United
States he said I'm in high school I'm reading this book about Greek mythology reading this
book I love it I love all this stuff about all of these gods that I've never heard of
in these stories and I remember I'm reading this book and I turn the page and there on
this page was a drawing a drawing of the man who ran next to me that day he said the man
running next to him was wearing a golden half helmet with metal boots that reached to his
knees and he was wearing a white and gold leather vest that even in the daytime shown
brightly looking at that page and continuing to do more research he came to the conclusion
he was saved by the Greek god Hermes fascinating story I love this story I love this story
this guy got shot out and a bunch of people got killed in his village but it's such a
fascinating story of a Greek god coming to earth to save this kid and it's one of those
things that this might be the outlier when we're looking at the world of paranormal this
might be the outlier this may be the only story we can really find where a version of
a Greek god comes to earth and save someone one thing I've learned on this show sometimes
it's not the outlier it's the only story we've found a long time ago I did an episode about
someone waking up in a pitch black room they're just locked into this black bedroom void I
thought it was an outlier is a one-off story and then I started finding more and more and
more and now it's one of the official mysteries of dead rabbit radio it's something that I'm
really interested in and I cover it every time I find it because it turned out not to
be an outlier it turned out to be it was so weird it was hard to find stories about it
it was so weird people didn't even want to talk about it so could the same thing be happening
here could people be in dire circumstances and they're being saved by old gods and actually
I just thought of this what would be even more interesting is he didn't know that's
what this was at the time if someone was a devout Catholic and they believed in God and
the Virgin Mary and Jesus and they're in a horrible car accident and in their time of
need Zeus showed up to help him would you repeat that story the car goes off the road
crashes into a ravine everyone's unconscious there's blood everywhere I don't know if it's
mine or my loved ones I'm hanging upside down in this car and then Zeus showed up and ripped
open the car door and charge my phone my phone was dead he charged it with a little lightning
bolt and then said everything's gonna be okay ma'am everything's gonna be okay and the next
thing I know I'm in the hospital apparently I called 911 we were all airlifted out of
there would they tell that story because I think if you accept the existence of the old
gods you accept accept the existence of all gods and if there's all gods then where does
God fit into that it's fascinating it actually might this might be a one-off story it could
be a fake it but it could be a story that it's one of those things people don't talk
about it because it actually makes you question the religion that you were raised in or the
religion that you converted to because it was the one that spoke most to you this might
be a more common not saying super common right but saying this might happen more often people
don't feel comfortable talking about it because it could make them feel like their religious
faith their belief is a little less true whether or not this is a worldwide phenomenon whether
or not this happens all the time and people just aren't talking about it none of that
matters to Nick all Nick is concerned about all Nick cares about is that day that whether
or not anyone else believes him Hermes the Greek God came down from the heavens to save
his life he can't make sense of it he doesn't know why it happened but he does know the
only reason he's alive today is because a man who the modern world says never existed
did in fact exist and they ran together until Nick lived to tell the tale
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address you can also put us
up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio tick tock is at dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio
is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to
whatever day I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys.
you
[MUSIC PLAYING]