A fourth of July party turns into a terrifying ordeal for all involved.
And then we take a look at the curious case of Thomas Mayhan, a businessman who left work
and was headed home.
But he never reached home.
He was spotted in three locations around town and in one of those locations he was already
dead today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Season 6 starts now.
Now you may go, "Hmm, Jason, the audio quality is a bit different.
I'm on vacation, man.
I'm in sunny, sunny California.
In sunny, sunny Sacramento.
Sack of potatoes, sack of tomato.
The city that always sleeps.
I'm kicking it down here.
It's like 97 degrees.
I'm in an un-air conditioned apartment like I normally am because I can't have air conditioners
or fans running while I record this show.
So if you hear the occasional drip drop that is sweat leaving my body.
But we got a lot of good stuff for you today.
We got two really interesting stories.
The first story just happened.
It actually happened as I basically while I was recording, the end of season 5 was on
July 4th.
So this episode basically all of this stuff was transpiring while I was messing around.
And actually it was all transpiring while all of us were watching fireworks or sleeping
because we're 80 years old.
But remember what you were doing 4th of July.
Think about what you were doing 4th of July.
And now forget that.
Forget that happened because we are going on an adventure.
We are going to Bodega Bay.
Bodega Bay, little town in California.
The sunny sunny state.
I'm just joking.
Okay so anyways, sun's always in California.
Anyway, so I'm surprised there's no conspiracy yet about the earthquakes.
I'm surprised there's no one saying that it's the lizard people or...
I saw someone trying to say that the LA earthquakes was a sign that the Yellowstone geyser was
going to blow up the planet.
Not a geyser.
It's actually like a super volcano under there and it is quite dangerous.
But I'm surprised we don't get more.
I wonder how flat earthers, how they explain earthquakes.
Anyways, anyways, I should note to self, look up what maniacs think about natural events.
Back to Bodega Bay.
Let's go ahead and get started with the saga of Batai Coffee.
Batai Coffee is a 32 year old man.
Stanford graduate.
Upper crust.
Upper crust old chum.
Actually he's born and raised in LA.
But anyways, Batai Coffee is like, he's a software engineer at YouTube right now.
He wakes up from a coma earlier this week.
He wakes up from a coma.
He can't move the left side of his body.
He's like, what happened?
Sexy nurses are all walking around taking his temperature, like filling out charts.
A little short nurse skirts and they're like, oh, the patient's awake.
This is my dream hospital.
Not this guy.
This guy doesn't need to be there.
But bunch of sexy nurses are like, oh, let's go get a doctor.
A doctor comes in, sexy female doctor, even shorter skirt.
I didn't even know it was possible.
She comes in, she goes, Mr. Coffee, you're awake.
And he's like, what happened?
What happened to me?
She goes, well, first off, everything we're about to talk about is alleged.
And secondly, everything we're about to talk about is true.
And it's alleged in the sense that everything that happened, like the first part, is true.
But it's alleged whether or not coffee did it.
And coffee's like, what does any of that have to do with my medical condition?
I want to know why I can't move the left side of my body.
Sexy doctor turns back away from the camera and goes, well, Mr. Coffee, I think the police
should explain to you what happened.
Maybe you can answer a few questions.
She gives a sexy wink at us as she walks out of the hospital room.
So here's what happened.
That was our little intro for the day.
Here's what happened.
Coffee?
32 year old Petite Coffee, software engineer for YouTube.
Stanford educated.
Good old chum.
Cream of the crop of American society is hanging out with five of his buddies in Bodega Bay.
They rented a place so they could spend 4th of July all the weekend partying at this house.
Now I don't know, I party.
I'll kick it with a couple friends, drink a couple beers.
If that.
Usually I just hang out and talk about magic the gathering.
But these guys said nah nah, we're not none of those plebs.
We're not any of those working class that drinks Budweiser.
Those drop acid.
Taking it up a level I guess.
But anyways they decide to drop acid.
Now I know a lot of my listeners do acid.
Not a sizable amount.
But I know a lot of people have experimented with it.
I don't mess with hallucinogens.
I already see ghosts flying around me.
Not all the time.
I'm not a lunatic.
But the line is so thin.
Where if I saw a goblin just appear I'd be like oh my god that goblin's real.
So I don't want to take a drug that's going to increase the likelihood of goblins appearing
in front of me.
So they decide to drop acid.
Now I'm assuming it wasn't their first time.
Maybe it was.
But I'm assuming it wasn't.
Now they all decide to take half a tab of acid.
Except for coffee.
Because coffee is an overachiever.
Stanford graduate.
Software engineer at YouTube.
He takes two hits of acid.
He's like oh good ol' chums you don't understand.
Acid is what you Americans refuse.
Acid is American too.
I don't know.
I just imagine him very posh.
Because Stanford graduate right.
I graduated from community college.
So anyone who graduated from college is posh.
Anyways he goes I'm going to take two hits of acid.
I'm going to do better than all you guys.
Just like I did better than you guys on the SATs.
And they're like dude we all have the same job.
You don't have to be a jury.
So they're partying.
Now at 3pm so they started pre-gaming really really early.
At 3pm coffee starts freaking out.
He's like oh man I don't know what happened ol' chum.
I don't know.
It could be the four times amount of acid I took over you guys.
And they're like yeah probably.
About an hour later he goes oh old bean I don't know what's going on.
He looks at his friend he's actually an old bean.
He's like oh I don't know what's going on.
I need to study myself.
And he takes two more hits of acid.
He's already having a bad trip.
Takes two more hits of acid.
His friends are like don't do that dude.
That was the wrong move.
And he's like oh don't tell me what to do talking watermelon.
I'll take all the acid I want.
Now that happened at around 4 between 4 and 5pm.
He takes the two additional hits of acid.
At 8pm fireworks are going off.
Kids are poking each other with sparklers.
Dogs are terrified.
It's a great quarter of July.
He wants to leave the house.
He wants to leave.
Like dude you are in no condition to leave the house.
Friends won't let him.
And then like that our fake British pal our Stanford graduate turns into Jason Bourne.
Now this is where the first off you're thinking oh Jason a guy who's getting taken a bunch
of acid he's going to end up running around street naked.
This guy turns into an action hero or more likely an action villain because of what happens.
This is why Kofi ended up in the hospital paralyzed on the left side of his body surrounded
by sexy medical staff.
First off so he's surrounded by his friends and they're like come on Kofi settle down
you can't you can't go anywhere.
He punches the woman in the chest picks up a pencil stabs another one of his friends
and other dude climbs on top of him he starts choking him while punching another man in
the face.
So within a second he's taken out four people.
He takes off outside the house.
And he's playing in his head because he's tripping hard on acid.
Allegedly this is where all the crimes begin.
He jumps out he gets in his rental car starts to drive away.
One of his friends jumps in front of the car to be like no no no don't do it don't do it.
And he ends up trying to hit his friend in the car allegedly and that's the last time
I'm going to say allegedly it's all allegedly.
Tries to hit his friend with the car misses crashes into the house.
Can't get the car out.
Jumps out of the car.
He looks and at this point a local like security guard for the subdivision they're staying
in is approaching.
He jumps out of his van pulls out his little flashlight.
Freeze evil doer.
Coffee looks at him and goes evil doer more like can't think of anything.
Think of a catchphrase.
He starts running towards the security guard security guard starts running towards them
split screen two different faces looking at each other.
This is this 100% real not the split screen that didn't happen but all of these events
did.
Security guard has like pepper spray billy club it doesn't have a gun but coffee doesn't
have any weapon at all but he's running and he's this is insane he sees those little lights
that are like stuck into the ground you know like the little solar panel lights that people
put around their yards it kind of like makes it look nice I guess but it's these little
lanterns that are all over the lawn or along the line of the lawn does that make sense
but underneath the way they stick into the ground they have a long metal spike they stick
them into the ground you don't have to worry about them falling over during rainstorm.
Now that's as beautiful as it may look as a lawn ornament coffee goes uh-huh it's time
to make my point.
I didn't really say that but we'll just assume that he did because he picks one of those
things up and stabs the security guard right in the chest so hard the security guard then
falls to the ground like a straight up and the guy's like falling back in slow motion
hits the ground coffee looks over and goes you light up my life and then it lights up
no okay so anyway coffee goes running goes running off and he's happy that he came over
that catchphrase he gets into the security guard's car he left it running he's in the
ignition peels off starts driving through the subdivision it's 8 p.m. it's 4th of
July people are outside of their houses just hanging out eating hamburgers throwing sparklers
in each other's eyes causing harmless mayhem coffee had other plans he sees a young couple
walking out the street hits him hits him with the vehicle and then like you're at that
point you're kind of like Jason this stopped being a funny action story now he's just running
over bystanders and you would think at that point he'd be like wait a second I'm not Jason
born anymore actually some sort of horrible terrorist he then sees an other young couple
walking across the street hits them too so at this point it's pandemonium in this neighborhood
the police show up sheriff and chp they're like we need to get these sirens fixed that
sounded terrible cop cars pull up coffee is driving down the street in his van towards
the cops cop jumps out of his car stop stop the car is coming closer and closer and closer
cops like stop stop the car coffee goes things are about to get complicated he's gunning
it right towards the cop the cop waits until coffee's van actually strikes his vehicle
before opening fire hitting him three times one time in the head putting him in a coma
and paralyzing him from the left side not left side down it's the left side over paralyzed
everyone survived so I don't want you to feel bad about the one of the women who got hit
by the car was airlifted out but everyone was survived probably got a couple broken bones
probably pretty scratched up dude who got stabbed with the light survived and everything
I'll tell you one thing that didn't survive coffee's freedom he's facing five counts of
assault with a deadly weapon two counts of attempted murder two counts of assaults on
an officer and one count of carjacking because he took the dude's car you'd think it would
kind of just be theft but anyways 32 year old stanford graduate software engineer at
youtube 2.35 million dollar bail for taking four hits of acid but I find that stories
like that fascinating we've talked about it before about people just snapping to me that's
the scariest of crimes like organized crime stuff like that like they always have like
an end result serial killers they can't get it up women intimidate them they're a bunch
of just weak spineless individuals so that's why they kill their mama was mean to them
that's why they kill they can't get it up their dick doesn't work organized crime they're
saying we need money like this is one of the things we do to keep order is commit these
crimes to do these murders but when people just snap I think that's the scariest thing
because it really is unpredictable this dude was probably never on anyone's trouble charts
for years and years and years and years and then this happens now yes the four hits of
acid did help that but still though and his life will radically change he'll probably
do eight to ten years plead down because he has a you know doesn't have a troubled life
stuff like that he might do eight to ten years he's going to be sued into oblivion by these
people but because of one afternoon his life has changed forever I find that fascinating
and and he almost murdered multiple people he tried to allegedly I find that stuff fascinating
but anyways let's go ahead and move on to our next story which actually is a story that
I came across both of these stories I came across right after the end of season five
there's a couple that popped up and I was like oh man but I had to take that break off
it really is refreshing for me to take that break off so I'm glad you guys are coming
back to the show and yeah it'll probably be about two weeks I'll be in Sacramento but
we'll be on a regular schedule and all of that so let's go ahead and move on to the
story of where'd you go bro I saw a movie last night I've been watching a ton of movies
on my vacation like I've been doing nothing it was Jersey Shore shark attack I will tell
you this and I know a lot of you people will not agree with me it's not a very popular
opinion may lose a couple listeners over it Jersey Shore shark attack actually was pretty
good but that's not the unpopular opinion it was a parody of Jersey Shore but a bunch
of sharks showed up I think Snooki is hot I know a lot of people like think she's like
trashy I've always had a thing for Snooki and she's one of those women who gets hotter
the older she gets like normally well I'm not gonna finish that sentence but Snooki
actually is really hot like now that she's a mom she has like three kids and stuff like
that I actually find her more attractive than when she was like a drunk chick on the boardwalk
so good on you Snooki god I love Snooki so anyways and they had an actress portraying
Snooki and somehow she was actually even hotter very distracting movie but anyway so it was
good though check it out Jersey Shore shark attack it was funny too which is really hard
to pull off horror comedies are incredibly hard let's go ahead though and get to our
second story for the evening the year is 1963 February 1st and Thomas Meehan 41 year old
state worker is driving home from Eureka California to Concord California now that's
quite a distance it's quite a distance he was on a business trip he had to drive home
and he was a prominent member boy he was a prominent member of the community in Concord
he was like on the hospital board people knew him he was very very well liked at work and
around town a stable individual if there was one four hours out from home he calls his
wife and says you know I'm not I don't feel good something's wrong with me I don't feel
good and his wife's like oh honey just get a hotel somewhere you'll be fine you'll be
fine that's why my wife sound like a creepy goblin all of a sudden but he ignores that
so he goes to the town of Garberville and checks into a hotel around five o'clock around
five p.m. nothing suspicious about that just another businessman traveling through a sleepy
little town in California at 645 Thomas Meehan walks into the Garberville General Hospital
nurses like smack and gum yeah what do you want Buster we got a lot of injured people
tonight what are you here for and Thomas goes I feel I feel dead I feel dead all over was
his exact words nurse goes take a number go sit in that other room now you may think I'm
making a joke she didn't have a she wasn't from the Jersey Shore but oh that'd be hot
if she was snooki as a nurse sexy nurse outfit they were busy and they did say go sit in
another room we'll see you in a bit and Thomas just like he had that conversation with the
sexy sexy snooki nurse and then hung around for a bit but then left at 7 p.m. so 15 minutes
later two witnesses are driving down the road they're driving down highway 101 and they
see a car go off the road into the brush and where the eel river is eel river is this river
that cuts through that part of California they call the cops now again there's a bit of delay
there no one had cell phones back then they go to a pay phone to call the cops say we
saw a car go off the side of the road and cops of course like where's that da da da what time
did you see the car they say 7 p.m. is when we saw this happen 8 p.m. Thomas mehan walks
back into his motel and the night manager sitting there filling out some paperwork and
Thomas mehan walks in and what the manager notices is that his ankles like the pants
his ankle pants the what am I trying to his pants his pants from the ankles area I don't
know why I'm having such a hard time telling you this his pants were wet is what I'm trying
to say and his shoes were wet and he could hear him going they're like you chewing gum
mist he's like yeah I got it from snooki but that sound you heard was actually my wet wet
shoes walking through your lobby and Thomas mehan walks up to the manager and goes this
is a exact quote he goes do I seem dead to you feel like I'm dead managers like no no
you don't I mean you look you know the kind of weird and Thomas mehan just kind of walks
away it's not like a mysterious he just turns like a zombie walks away he also says hey
can you call my wife and conquer yeah yeah yeah I'll take care of conversation doesn't
really go anywhere and Thomas mehan goes to his motel room anyways at 9 30 at other motel
employee goes into his room and says hey we tried calling your wife and conquered but
there's something wrong with the phone connection we can't get a hold of her Thomas is like
okay okay and then that employee says we just haven't talked about the weather for a bit
like it was a normal conversation there was nothing weird about him except for one detail
he was wearing different clothes now he seemed to be wearing like a formal attire like a
black tie suit black slacks black jacket white shirt and he goes and what was weird is I
didn't really see him come in with any luggage but he was wearing different clothes and we
had seen him earlier and you figure yeah his pants were wet so he's going to change his
clothes at 10 45 p.m. the cops are at the river the eel river and they're looking around
and they see this car in the river the convertible roof had been ripped open the front end had
been damaged so it definitely had gone off the road and impacted into the river it wasn't
like under 10 feet of water it was just like poking out of the river and hit something but
there was a pair of glasses just reading glasses just neatly folded up and sitting on the passenger
seat all this violent action around the car and you have those glasses cops are like looking
around and they're like well we don't see a body this is weird and the other guys like
hey Tommy look over here and shine the flashlight all dramatically on the ground they see a set
of footprints not magically appear in front of them but they see a set of footprints in
the mud heading up the bank and they're like oh whoever was in this car accident that happened
almost four hours ago it took us that long to get out here that's weird actually that's
a weird detail it took them that long but we'll get to that that's weird I didn't put
that connection anyways the cops are out there oh you know what actually now that I think
about it the cops probably showed up shortly but it took them a while to find where the
car was I don't know that's kind of weird detail but anyways the cops start following
the footprints up the bank and they're looking at these muddy footprints leaving from the
car up the bank and then they just stop cops are looking at each other shining their flashlight
around looking through the brush and they see where the ground was still soft they see
where there still should have been more footprints but nothing it was like someone was walking
up out of the bank it just vanished that all happened on February 1st on February 20th
41 year old Thomas Meehan was found in the eel river drowned but it just floating around
bobbing around on the river now this story is very twilight zone-ish it's very carnival
of souls but what's interesting about it was this was reported on by the Los Angeles Times
and I think it was the San Diego Times it might have been the San Diego Tribune and
a couple other newspapers major newspapers at the time because it's such a bizarre story
and it's one of those stories that everyone kind of goes what it really makes you scratch
your head now one thing is clear is that he was some people he interacted with people
in these different locations it was Thomas Meehan's car in the river they knew that
from the make a model of the car registration things like that that was 100% his car but
the people who saw the car go over they didn't couldn't identify the driver but you had the
person at the motel take his payment have several conversations with Thomas Meehan
and then you had the nurse at the hospital Snooki who identified him as well had to take
his information to treat him at both of those locations he said I feel like I'm dead I feel
like I'm dead and the first time that he was spotted acting like a big old weirdo at 645
he walks into the Garber Village General Hospital at 645 he checks in with the nurse and says
I feel dead I feel dead all over can you treat me 15 minutes later his car is spotted going
off the road it's possible yes Jason that he left that he was not feeling good he already
called his wife and said he was not feeling good he went to the hospital said I'm not
feeling good they said you're gonna have to wait a bit he waited a short while got in
his car drove away and whatever he wasn't feeling good about crashed into the river but from
the hospital to any point at eel river from Garberville to any point at eel river it's
a 55 minute drive so he would have had to driven incredibly fast to leave the hospital
and crash into that river 50 minutes later it's nearly an hour away is that impossible
could you go 150 miles an hour sure but it's an odd detail you think he would have been
seen speeding 150 miles an hour before I got it odd detail the car crashes this was what
I thought happened because I'm fairly skeptical about a lot of this stuff this was my read
on this the car crashes he gets out of the car he starts walking up the bank and then
he just stops leaving footprints not because of any magical thing but his feet aren't
sinking in as much as they were and what the cops had just misidentified the scene he then
goes to the hotel like I don't think he was feeling good at all he's driving along he
does starts feeling sick he calls his wife he goes to the hospital he's not feeling good
he goes this isn't worth it he goes to the river somehow he gets there going 150 miles
an hour crashes into the river and then walks out and when he goes to the hotel he says
I still don't feel good but I think he's still in shock that the fact that he got in this
car accident goes to the hotel his pants are dripping wet he goes he changes his clothes
and at some point he suffered some sort of brain damage or was not feeling good already
plus the horrible car accident at some point he goes oh crap my car is in the river because
he's not thinking right he got some brain damage he will then walk back to the car and he drowns
like he's messing around with his car he's trying to pull it out or whatever and he drowns
the thing about being skeptical is usually like everything I said as stupid as a decision
it could be are things people would do i.e. taking two extra hits acid when you're already
having a bad trip people do stupid things especially if you've had a concussion or something
he could have walked back to the hotel and then realized you know what I'm just gonna
go back and pull my car out of the water myself the problem with that version of events is
that he would then have to walk back you would figure that actually now to think about it
if he way whoa okay I didn't think about this if he if Garberville's 55 minutes away and
he drove there in 15 minutes and gotten this car accident at 7 p.m. at 8 p.m. he comes back
to the motel you couldn't a 55 minute drive you couldn't walk in 55 minutes that's impossible
and there's no I didn't see any record of a taxi cab picking this guy up so as a skeptic
I thought that it was probably something likely happened but at the same time we also have
to say there are a lot of weird things going on here let's throw off our skeptic caps and
put on our conspiracy cap guy gets in a car accident this is my this is my conspiracy
not conspiracy there this is my paranormal take on it he knew he was going to die his
body knew that this was his last night on earth wasn't feeling good but it was time
to go so he's facing two different things his body is basically saying goodbye to the
mortal world because I've always wondered if the day you die if you know you're going
to die we look at people go whoa he was just walking on the street got hit by a car but
we don't know if that person was like you know what just have a feeling I'm going to
die today and for someone who suffers anxiety attacks like I do that's not a fun thought
because I always think I'm going to die every single day but I wonder that so maybe that's
the reason why he wasn't feeling good was that he was like I'm going to die today and
he goes to the hospital because he thinks I'm going to die today and they're like no
you're lunatic he goes drives he gets in the car accident and at that point he basically
splits into his own little multiverse he basically quantum reality or quit as a basically quantum
immortality is where you die you've moved to another universe he just kept moving into
the same one I know this is getting really weird he dies in the car accident and his
body floats out into the river okay but his him not his spirit because he's walking around
signing paychecks and opening doors and stuff like that him also splits off into the Thomas
mehan who starts walking up the bank of the river but because that's a physical impossibility
everything's like things are happening that are impossible to happen IE walking a 55 minute
drive in an hour he appears at the hotel he goes there do I feel dead he was already dead
at that point you can make the argument he may have even died of a heart attack way before
he even got to Garberville like he could have been splintering out every single way the
fact of the matter is he is dead and people seeing him around town around the time he
should have really been floating down the river face first I know that's kind of a brutal
image but it really makes you quite I really makes you question a lot of things that's
why I really like this story because it makes you wonder if you've ever interacted with somebody
who's already dead this was a big story because he was such a prominent member of his town
the sheriff from Concord drove hours and hours and hours and up with like a team of 20 people
to investigate this they wanted to know what happened to their buddy that's why it was
such big news but you wonder you ever go to like a fast food restaurant you're sitting
in a bar there's a kid sitting next to you on the bus you look over at him and they look
normal but something a little off about them now they're not going to turn to you and say
do I look dead they don't know you they just know they're not having a good day they know
that there's something not right in the way they feel today you just kind of sit there
and you watch them they just seem to be staring off into the distance then eventually something
catches their eye or they get reminded of something and they stand up and walk away you never
see him again you're just a passerby we run into hundreds of people a day in the modern
world but what are the and it's statistically improbable that this would happen but what
if that person was already dead at home sitting in their favorite chair they passed away but
somehow they're not a ghost they can still interact with the environment they can still
talk to people they don't have chains but they're still able to move about the world
for a short amount of time and them not really knowing that they're dead still interacting
with us do you think that's possible and if that is possible who's to say I'm not already
dead and you're listening to a podcast recorded by a corpse.
you
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]