China shoots to the top of the arms race and is autism the next step in human evolution today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone, this is Jason Carpenter back for another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. Hope you're having a great day
It's the July 3rd. It's the day before the 4th of July. I think I'm gonna do a couple episodes
Record a couple episodes today. I'm probably gonna be out doing stuff tomorrow
I hope you guys are having fun to whatever you decide to do wherever you're at
Hope you guys have a good day tomorrow and today not just tomorrow
Don't let that despair code get you down the despair code in the last episode
It's funny because I know that I'm gonna get some pushback on that episode
Because I kind of said this is what the despair code is
there's a lot of theories of what the despair code is and
That one seemed to be the most succinct so if you've ever been curious about what the despair code probably actually is again
It's a conspiracy theory and it's most likely made up
but the idea that you make your own reality and
It can be a reality of despair or it can be a reality of hope and it really depends on on
Your worldview and remember you can always change your worldview. You can have
some negative feelings and
Bring them around to something positive and the same thing you can be on the top of the world
And you just like let life beat you down, but but don't let that happen. I'll always try to be on the positive side
You know when I was talking about the despair code yesterday
I was like, oh, you know the despair. Hey, everyone's like don't research it. Don't research it. It's totally awful
And I'm like, yeah, yeah, whatever. I have had the worst diarrhea since I've done that episode
The worst okay, not the worst, but it's been pretty bad. I had left work early because my stomach was killing me. I
was
dodging I
Was basically pulling the matrix with my butthole
I was barely making it
In time to the bathroom my pants were like kneel like just sliding off in slow motion
bending backwards to avoid
To avoid what was coming forth agent Smith is now my colon
It was bad. So maybe that's what the despair code actually is referenced to it has nothing to do with
Being trapped in your own universe. It actually makes your gut
Feel despair. That's where you feel it all
All I ate today. I had a little coconut oil, which you of course you're like, well Jason, that's really bad
But I have coconut oil all the time I got used to it. I had some beef jerky and cheese sticks and it was
I was reacting as if I had like stage four
Spanish flu
You know given to me by a
Swine in the middle of a Chinese chicken factory. It was bad
I held up a good front. I didn't let anyone at work see how distressed I was
But I think they picked up on it when every five minutes. I just clutched my stomach said I gotta go to the bathroom
So maybe I didn't come off as cool as I thought I didn't
It was pretty gnarly though. Now. I know you're thinking what does this have to do with anything and
um
Doesn't really oh it will does because I think
I should probably put a disclaimer at the beginning of that last episode
May cause intense bowel
discomfort
because I I uh it may now this episode will probably be
edited quite a lot as I stop it
Run away
And then come back
You know what I think's weird
Is people don't like to use public restrooms
Now i'm not saying i'm like a public restroom aficionado, but
Actually, I am I've actually thought about starting a website where I review public restrooms because I spend so much time in public restrooms
I go
To the restroom like not all the time, but generally if when I'm out at a restaurant
I use the restroom I'll use the restrooms at
Grocery stores and gas stations too gas stations are the worst, but we know they're the worst
But I've been in some good. I've been into some amazing restrooms
Like you're like this restroom is nicer
Than the house I grew up in I've never been to a restroom where someone's giving me a towel like a steam towel
I always thought that would be interesting
And of course we've all been to those disgusting restrooms that like have no toilet seat
And you kind of have to like put your hand against the door otherwise it'll open up
The worst are the bathrooms where the door opens out instead of in because then I'm always afraid someone
Can just get in I all like I'm always afraid someone's going to either
That actually happened once so I was in the restroom in a mcdonald's in sacramento on how avenue
And it was like seven in the morning
I used to go in I had to work like at eight or nine, but I used to go into mcdonald's buy a newspaper get a couple cookies
Drink some coffee
use the restroom
And so one day I go into the restroom and I'm I'm actually reading the newspaper in the restroom at this point and
I hear someone into the restroom
And then the lights go out
And it's pitch black because obviously there's no window
And I'm sitting there in the pitch black and I know someone else is in the bathroom with me
And I just yell out who did that like I had to not say it as loud possible because I'm have this condenser mic
But I'm like who did that
And I hear this voice sound like a homeless person. They have a distinctive type
I think their vocal cords have evolved to be homeless and he's like I don't know man
I don't know and the whole time I'm expecting someone to grab my ankles because
The thing the you know how they have that huge gap between the floor and the bottom of the door
I imagined someone cut the light off and was going to crawl into the stall with me and grab my ankles
And I was ready to step on a dude's neck
Like I had one leg up and I was like if I feel anything grab me they're crippled for life
I will I will begin just smashing their skull in
And he goes I don't know man. I don't know and I'm all turn the lights on
I'm cussing a lot now too and the guy's like I don't I can't I can't and then the door opens
And now I'm getting the light from the mcdonald's and he steps out
And then I sat in there and I
Wiped obviously. I don't think I washed my hands if I got to be completely honest and I walked out
And it was just a fuse something went out in the bathroom when pitch dark, but oh dude that was terrifying
But even then I mean
I I don't have a problem. I know people who hate
Hate using public restrooms
And they'll like oh they'll refuse to use them. It's always like dude. Just just go to that. No, no, no, I'm good
And I did learn just for you know, here's a conspiracy. Why do women always go to the bathroom in pairs?
This is really why I mean people go so we can talk about but but but no
It's because women don't sit on the toilet seat
They squat and they can't hold their purse while they're squatting so their friends are there to hold their purse
Bam mystery solved dude. Just be honest if girls are just like oh, yeah, I hate sitting on toilet seats
So I squat and I need someone to hold my purse
Just why don't you just be honest just be honest with us ladies will cause far less gossip about you
Now I will still gossip about you. Let's get started with the episode after I go to the bathroom
We got some good stories for you today
One of them actually came from a friend slash listener of mine that I've talked about before Veronica
I was talking to her yesterday about the despair code and during the conversation
She brought up an interesting topic
Is she she believes
That autism could be the next step in human evolution
So we're going to go ahead and take a look at that but first
First I got to address this story because it's the front page of drudge. It's been big news for about two days
I wanted to talk about it last night. Didn't have a ton of time
China
Is ready to mass produce
quote unquote laser guns
China's getting ready to mass produce these guns
I want to put the link on the show notes. You have to look at the pictures of these things
Now what's amazing, you know the problem they've always had with laser weapons in the past
Is the amount of cooling that is needed. We've had laser based weapons on our on a like our huge cargo planes
And they every after each shot they would have to empty up the empty out the bay and just all this water would have to
Flood out of it. They were constantly having to cool these big space guns down
They were basically made basically used to shoot down missiles
China's china's claiming to have invented these laser rifles
That weigh as much as an ak-47. He uses a lithium ion battery just like your cell phone does it will allows it to have 300 at two second long shots
And basically cooks you it puts a it puts an invisible
Beam on you for two seconds that burns your skin
It's this the article describes the pain as being excruciating and what's worse
If you're wearing anything flammable
It catches on fire now. You probably it's probably not like one beam and you're just like oh
You're like totally like torched and you're like running through the street
But it'll probably burn the area around that enough to panic you god knows what happens if they shoot you in the face with it
I mean two seconds of a beam that's enough to set something on fire in your eyeball
You're not going to have a very good day china said they're going to use these for
Anti-terrorist actions and they do actually have a pretty big terrorist population over there with the Uyghurs
It's not as bad as in other parts of the world, but it you know
They are running into that it can also be one of the one of the examples
They give is that it can be used in military action to set a fuel depot on fire. So these are these are pretty beefy
I guess right now
The production cost is about $15,000 per rifle, which is far far exceeds
What an ak-47 is or another standard
military rifle, but that's still incredibly cheap for technology like that that you're not
carrying the added weight of
You know 300 rounds
300 rounds now you have a battery that can fire
They're in the shots. They said the whole thing weighs like six kilos
They said it's close to the weight of an actual ak-47. So good on you china. Don't use them against us
Because that wouldn't be good
But i'm sure here's one of those things if they're announcing these now
I'm sure that other countries have had these for a while or been working on these for a while
I think if you had something that was this much of a game changer
You wouldn't announce it in your newspaper. You'd use it a couple times and
Different actions and maybe now they're announcing it because they're going to start mass producing them and obviously people are like
Hey, how come that dude is carrying around that?
Awesome looking starship trooper rifle and they're like, oh, no, no, no, no, you know like don't pay attention to that now that they're mass produced
It's uh, it's going to be a good thing. I think we're going to need them when we go to war
with the aliens
again
Aliens could be interdimensional or from our own planet most likely not from space, but either way we're going to blow them out of this
Blow them up
You know nothing can defeat humanity
We are the reigning champions on this planet and in this solar system and most likely the galaxy
So nothing can stop us. Nothing can stop us. They could have all the laserships and
Garbage and teleporters and whatever other sci-fi nerd stuff. They want they can't stop us. You know that I know that
They'll know that soon enough now
you know, it's funny because
sci-fi science fiction
Play such a big part in what we invent
Science fiction really dictates where science goes. I believe
The reason why people
Beam down on star trek
The reason normally everything before star trek other than like obscure sci-fi, but generally in
Mainstream like flash gordon and stuff like that
You would they were all shuttles like a ship would go here and flash gordon would out of it
And what happened was gene roddenberry wanted to do this television show
But it would cost too much to make all these models of these runabouts. That's the name of the shuttles on star trek
I'm a huge star trek nerd by the way. That's like
I forget harry potter forget, you know, all of that other nonsense star trek is my nerd jam
But anyway, so they
Instead of having those little runabouts and having shots of the ship landing each time and having to build like a life-size model
Of the runabout for them to keep coming out move them set to set gene roddenberry goes
Ah, I just haven't teleport down there
That way we save tons of money each episode. We're just gonna have people slowly dissolve and slowly appear
And that became such an iconic thing. You know the the term beam, you know, beam me up scotty
Which actually was never in the show, but you know to to beam up and they go back and forth
Young people watching that
They are like, oh my god, that's so amazing and they start to try to invent teleportation
They start trying to invent teleportation devices
Um, I think that would we've been working on teleportation without star trek possibly
But I don't think it would be so in the consciousness to want to do it the taser
Well, not a lot of people know this the taser is actually the guy who invented the taser
It's an acronym
for tom a swifts electric rifle
because
Back in the day like in the turn of the century there was a
Character named tom swift and he was like a little like huck fin type dude
And he had an electric rifle and he would shoot the bad guys and it would stun him
And the guy who invented the taser that was his favorite series of books
So he wanted to invent a weapon that using electricity electricity would stun people that weapon has saved lives
The taser gives people the opportunity between
You know going toe to toe with someone and blowing their head off a taser gives you that middle ground
If that
Inventor had never read those books and was never inspired by those books
We wouldn't have that or we most likely wouldn't have that
You get that vision in your head
So I always thought that was fascinating. How many people have tried inventing lightsabers?
How many people have tried working on anti gravity devices and things like that? So the the old
The old inventors they would look at nature and say
How does a bird fly? I want to build something that flies like a bird and the new inventors will look at pop culture and say
We can do this
I I think we can actually do this what this fantastical idea is I think we can do this which I find fascinating
I think science fiction is important as much as I poo poo people for being nerds and stuff like that and I will do that constantly
I think it's great now
This is a little there's not much of a segue here. So I'm just going to roll right into it
So I was talking to Veronica the other day. Uh, she was saying that she feels like autism
Is an evolutionary step. It's the next
stage in human evolution because
They have more empathy and they're kinder
And they have this connection with nature that
uh, neurotypical people don't have that wasn't her term, but that is the term for
Normal people is you know neurotypical people who don't have autism
And how they're they can she's telling me about how she knows people who can like communicate better with animals and how they're just this
Next they could be this next step in human evolution and
She said, you know what the world would be like without people with autism like 70 of mit graduates have autism and
So on and so forth now. There's a couple of issues I have with that
assessment one, I think that you can have this the
Signs of autism and not be autistic just like you can have the signs of having the flu and not have the flu
I could have diarrhea and vomiting
And still not have the flu
That doesn't mean I have the flu that just means I have some of the symptoms
So if you're get really obsessive over certain details and you're
You're just like hyper focused on one particular field that is a sim that is like a sign of autism
I don't believe 70 of the people at mit if the word tested would actually be diagnosed with autism or aspergers or anything like that
That being said
I took what she said she was like, okay. This is interesting. It's her theory actually
She's not alone. There are other people who believe that autism
That that's a possibility that autism is the next stage in human evolution now
What was interesting is the fur I found two articles
One was from 2007 from discover magazine
and they basically say that
The they basically say that same position that the someone who is autistic
They're basically evolving past our society because our society is basically become poisonous
And only by turning inward
Can you actually
Like grow because our society has become so toxic over the centuries
To to pull yourself out of it to be inside of yourself more than a part of society
Is an evolutionary benefit and those people who are hyper focused and things like that will go on to succeed
I'm gonna I'm gonna come back to that article in a second because this article is how we're gonna end it off
but I wanted to give you that
that lead in because
The article discover magazine is is fairly well written. The next one is basically a letter to an editor
where a
author
A woman I believe
not like that matters, but
Truly believes that autism is the next step in human evolution and and this is it
What if those who fall anywhere anywhere within the autism spectrum disorder a sd are actually the next step in human evolution
In my opinion anyone within the autism spectrum are gifted
Pure empaths most certainly and probably
Depending upon how high one is on the spectrum gifted with other psychic or new age gifts
I think they were born feeling everything to such a high degree
Their emotions are akin to someone whose raw nerves are exposed because they do not have their protection
Layers skin provides
They find it difficult to exist in a busy noisy dysfunctional world where there is so little peace to be found
If you stand back and look our society is hurtling towards something ugly
We interact less with each other on a personal level
We care less for our neighbor. We find it easier to hate to destroy
We have no respect for others and dishonor the earth. It's like the world is speeding out of control and no one cares
so
So what if
The chosen few within a sd are actually nature's solution
An attempt to save us all from the destruction society is speeding tour
speeding toward
And so on and so forth. She continues to
give everyone with autism a
hand job but now
Here's the thing that is the most hippie-dippy highfalutin
ridiculous
Read on the situation
Anyone within anywhere in the autism spectrum disorder is gifted
They are the beauty of the world. They are true empaths now
That's just that is just flat out false
It's a spectrum for a reason because on the one reason you have
You have a person who is again
Hyper focused and working tends to be a withdrawn has a hard time communicating with others
But successful in their given field and then you have
The person who can cannot take care of themselves at all and unless you prepare their food in the exact right way
They will not eat
That's the spectrum
You can't lump them both in and say they're both the greatest balance of the universe that
There's some sort of connected to the plant life and the and the atoms that grow within the kidneys of the
Comquat
It's ridiculous. It's ridiculous. If you want to pull. I mean again, this is
She's basically making up her own version of the world
Which I guess is fine
But the promises can be destructive because when you have the kid who has to wear a helmet because he's constantly punching himself in the face
And biting anyone who comes near him. This woman walks up and goes oh
Parents you need to learn how this child is the next stage in human evolution. You're just neurotypical
You don't understand you're treating this child wrong now the child has some
Problems that need to be addressed to keep him and other people safe
I can understand someone saying that you know, maybe somewhere in the spectrum. They have this
this sense to then client to then make the leap of logic to say that
They are then they're basically where we are
The we're basically the homo sapiens and they're the homo superiors to
Take the terminology from the x-men comic books because you think oh jason years are blowing up
She's just you know, she's going on about this. We have any this is how she ends it now. Okay
Go a couple hundred years into the future
Man is having to rebuild from scratch because everything was destroyed by the so-called normal people
Wouldn't it be interesting if those future people are able to look back on history and see that present day a sders
special gifts to society who were labeled by away it filed away and dismissed
Or actually the leaders who could have saved planet
Saved people and the planet if only the ego-ridden normals of the 21st century pause to consider the possibility
So again now
Anyone who doesn't have autism is just a horrible person and the people with autism are like god's gift their nature's gift
I mean this this is bordering on
reverse eugenics
I I she's all I mean if the normal people
The the everything was destroyed by the so-called normal people
Oh when you hear me like doing weird inflections with this article
You'd be surprised how often she put stuff in all caps and italicized a lot of stuff. I'm not just being a dick
I am generally a dick when it comes to stuff like this
Now again
You know I got you guys know I have trouble when these conspiracy theorists acts for money
That's what bugged me about that lord of the rings guy too. I never got to that
That guy is a whole series that you have to pay for to watch him go on and on about how lord of the rings is based on
True life and people pay for it. He's making good money. I saw a bit of a video and he's dressed. Well, he obviously can buy a nice suit
This is just as dangerous though because again what you're telling
People and really you're telling parents of children who have autism and people with you can I can someone has autism
I'm not going to say hey, dude. You're broken
Because there are with there is there is a spectrum and some people are far more successful than me
And some people have a hard time, you know functioning within a family unit let alone society
But for her to just say no, they're all better than everyone else that is such
a
Like right there I can say listen there's a spectrum and there's these group people these group people
There's everyone in the middle with her it's all normal people are destroying the planet and everyone with autism are our only hope
That is well, you know now the thing about the author probably has autism that hadn't dawned on me, but
That being set aside that's that's a very hateful ideology
That's a very hateful ideology and when you're preaching hate like this really, how are you any different?
Than someone carrying a tiki torch from through charlotte's fill. That's what this is
That's what this is you're claiming that everyone who doesn't have autism is going to destroy the planet
And people with autism are the saviors now. We're going to go back to that original article
Because I think this sums it up perfectly
In the original article that I was talking about and discover magazine
It said I'm going to quote this here because this is again
We'll go through the the different ways these are these articles are constructed. Here's the quote from discover magazine
And the going on the assumption that autism is an evolutionary trait here we go
Even if the assumptions are correct her evolutionary hypothesis doesn't work
Mutations don't have a purpose natural selection works on individuals and not the whole species
The rise in autism if it's even real has happened in just the last 20 years
Unlike the evolutionary leaps the anthropologist's sights
Autism involves many genes and would take even more generations to spread if it was advantageous
And most of all there's the sex
It's only an adaptation if it makes you have more kids. So a literal human connection is essential
And that it's it's one of the key components of autism you withdraw from other people
So short answer no, it's not a step in human evolution
If anything they will have they're less likely to have kids
What is causing the rise in autism? We don't know that I've heard theories that it's not and that's without our
Kind of says if it's even real autism hasn't increased. It's just what we define as autism has increased
There's the idea that it is a cultural social thing with the way children are brought up that's environmental toxins
Then you have ideas like the vaccines and then you know you could have it that it's like a genetic quirk
In the system it could be a combination of two or more of those
so
I think I think we can kind of close the I'll close the case on that conspiracy
I do not think that autism is the next step in human evolution
I don't think it's weird to think that there is going to be a new a new step in human evolution
But I again, I think it'll be so small the changes are going to be so small. We won't even see it
So I think we're going to end this episode today. I got I'm going to put all those article links below
Dead rabbit comm is where you can find our website. You can email me and dead rabbit radio
And
Oh @jasoncarboner is our twitter
So that is today's episode. I hope you guys had a great time listening to it. Let me know what you think
shoot me an email
But more importantly have a good day today. Have a good day tomorrow. We will uh, we're gonna post in that video
We're gonna post the podcast tomorrow and we're just gonna keep going and I'm having a lot of fun
I'm hoping you're having fun too. Thanks for joining the rabbit league and we'll be hopping into your life tomorrow
That's not really my outro
Trust me that'll change. Have a great day guys
You
(upbeat music)