Season 16 is here and we start off with a bang! First off, what happens if someone's
furry fetish becomes contagious? And then we take a look at a terrifying true crime story
ripped right from the pages of a horror novel. A young woman named Nelda leaves a note for
her living boyfriend saying, "I'll be right back, I'm going to the store." And she is
never seen again. Or was she? Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carbner. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I just got
off of my two week vacation that I take every 50 episodes. It's always super invigorating
for me to do that. I played it to the Fortnite. I shot a bunch of children in the head. That's
basically what Fortnite is, right? I'm basically demolishing 12 year old children for my own
entertainment. But I'm glad you guys are back to listen to more Dead Rabbit Radio. The
show would be nothing without the fluffle. First off, let's go ahead and introduce one
of our new Patreon supporters. Coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now is longtime listener
of the show. Long time giving me stories guy. I don't know if we should have an official
title for that. It's Fabio Nurbon. Everyone give a round of applause to Fabio. He's walking
in the Dead Rabbit Command. I don't want to dox the dude, but he's like our Italian correspondent.
He's like, "Tang it. I'm in witness protection. You're supposed to say what country I was
in." He's been our Italian correspondent. He sent us a bunch of stuff. Fabio, you're
going to be our captain or pilot this episode. You guys can't support the Patreon. I totally
understand. Just help spread the word about the show. That really, really helps out a
lot. Word of mouth helps the show grow. Fabio, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys
to the Jason Jalopy. Let's get it out of the garage. We haven't used it in a couple weeks.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We are headed all the way out to old timey
Germany. Old car, old Germany. That's perfect. Now when I say old German, I'm not saying
like 1944. That's not where we're going. We're going like way old timey back, like
past black and white. We're in sepia-toned land. This is like pre-1879. That's somewhere
between the evolution of life on earth and 1879. This story takes place. You can picture
dinosaurs in the background if you would like, but I honestly don't think it took place
that far back. We're in the town of Do-Dow. That's in Wittenberg, Germany. In this town,
there was an old, you're like David Jason. Are you just reading this? Are you just reading
that? It's a fairy tale. Hold on. Hold your fairy tale related suspicions till the end.
There's this old woman living in the town of Do-Dow and she always has poultry to eat.
She always has like a duck or chicken or a geese and she's always like, oh man, she's
brady. She's walking around town. She has a big gold chain. That's a picture of a turkey
leg. I mean, I don't know if everyone else in this town was going hungry, but it was
suspicious that she was always eating big geese. She's this old lady, right? She's
not walking around with an Elmer Fudd musket. People were a little suspicious. Specifically
her grandchildren. We're like, I bet you there's something about grandma because she
seems to, she's always flossing on us with how much meat she has. Look at our bones.
So they spy on the grandma and they realize that, I didn't know this was a thing. It makes
sense. There's a thing called a fox strap. Now I know what a wolf strap is. It's like
a belt made of wolf fur. Turns you into werewolf. But this old lady, she had a fox strap. So
she'd put it on and she'd turn into a fox and she'd run and then she'd kill geese and
chickens and ducks and stuff. Then drag them back to her hovel and then cook them. I don't
know why she just didn't eat them raw as a fox, but you know, maybe raw geese taste disgusting.
I don't know. So anyways, the grandkids are like, Oh, dude, that's dope. Our grandmas
aware of Fox. But you know, they also know that like snitches get stitches, so they're
not going to turn their grandma in. Plus now she's cutting them in now that they know the
secret. They're like getting extra meat. But one day at school, the teacher was like
teaching class and he goes, Hey, everyone. So we've learned the alphabet and we've learned
all about these numbers. I start to talk about that's all he knows. For whatever reason,
they start talking about magic in the class. And he's like, Yes, magic is real because
it's old timey Germany. We still believe stuff like that. And the kids are super excited.
They're like, Oh, now we can finally participate. We never learned the alphabet, but we can
participate in this discussion. They start to tell the school master and the other students
are grandmas as magical powers. She has this Fox strap that she puts on. She becomes a
Fox. And I think the people in class probably didn't believe them. They believed in magic.
They believed in the evil iron curses, but they're like, I don't know. I've heard of
a wolf strap never heard of a were Fox. So the kids need to bring this in for show and
tell. So they go to the grandma's house. Jason, this is a fairy tale, right? Like hold on.
Let me finish it. So they go to the grandma's house and they sneak in this fairy tale music
playing. There's a fairy narrating the whole story. They crept around the corner with little
kid feet and they get into their grandma's storage center and they steal the Fox strap.
And I don't know what the grandma was doing right now because she should have caught these
dudes, but she didn't. They got the whole Fox strap and they take it to school the next
day because they're like, we got to prove to these dudes that magic exists. So they bring
the Fox strap to the schoolmaster and they're like, look, this basically they give him a
grody piece of Fox skin. Like dried up Fox skin and goes, my grandma wears this at night
or during the day or whenever Fox's live. And she runs around and chases geese and brings
it back home and we all eat geese. And the schoolmaster's like, oh, you know, I've heard
the legends of the wolf strap. This seems odd. I've never heard of the Fox strap before.
So the schoolmaster gets the Fox strap. And he's like, I don't know, this is just kind
of like a gross piece of fur. It's the kids feelings are like, oh, and then I if someone
gave you a wolf's belt, you would assume you'd put it on like a belt, right? Hold up your
your trousers or your pantaloons or something. But apparently with a Fox, this makes sense.
Actually, I think about it. Foxes are tinier. So a Fox belt wouldn't wrap around your waist
unless you were like a little thumbelina person. So this belt isn't activated by putting it
around your waist. This belt is activated by putting it touching it to your forehead.
And the schoolmaster unknowingly, like he's maybe saw like a fly landed on his forehead
and he wanted to swat it or there was just a swat on his brow. He goes, oh, this smelly
Fox meat will get rid of this tiny drop of sweat. He touches his forehead with it and
instantly in front of the entire class turns into a Fox. He makes a little Fox noise. Now
the class freaks out, right? And they scream so loud it scares Professor Fox. So he jumps
out the window and runs away. Now everyone in town is made very aware of this situation.
It's not something that kids would go home. They're like, what happened at school today?
Nothing. And they're just like eating their porridge. I'm sure I'm pretty sure class was
dismissed for that day, right? Everyone went home. And so everyone in town knew about the
professor who turned into a Fox. What are you gonna do, right? It's like a Fox. There's
a bunch of Foxes in the area probably that grandma starving to death. She's like, oh,
no, where's my where's my belt? She's withering away. Fox takes off. And the Fox finds this
little hill and makes a house, makes a Fox house, a nest, whatever that is, a cave. So
when I'm reading this, when I'm reading this fairy tale, when I'm reading this, what could
only be described as a fairy tale, I thought, man, he's really adapting to Fox life very
quickly. Like if I turned into a Fox, I'd be like, bros, help me. And then I assume I'm
doing it on a Friday night when I'm sitting around with my buddies. They're like chasing
me, told you not to touch that Fox into your forehead. I'm like running around. I'm like,
guys help me. And then we maybe go on like some hangover jackass, esk adventure, where
I'm just like a Fox and like we go to Vegas or something like that. I would assume that's
what I would do. And my whole goal would be to want me to sexy Fox. And then to, um,
to turn into a human. And now I have a sexy Fox. Like, oh, no, these babies, these babies
are going to be monsters. But you know what I mean? Okay, maybe scratch the sexy for the
people who didn't shut off the podcast scratch that part. But you'd want to turn back into
a human as soon as possible. Sexy Fox or not. He doesn't do that. He just makes a house.
That'd be the last thing I would do. I want to make a house. I would live in my human
house, but he makes a house. So he's like in it for the long run. Being a Fox must be
pretty cool. So what happens though is everyone in town is like, dude, don't go outside for
a while. You can't go outside because there's a human Fox. There's a where Fox running around.
Even though we can't, we can no longer attend the funeral of that poor old woman who starved
to death. Don't go outside. But there's a random group of hunters in the area and they're
hunting Foxes and they see this Fox running around on the hill and they're like, oh, dude,
this is perfect. Let's blow this thing's brains out. They load their muskets and they fire
and all of a sudden the naked dude is sitting on the hill. And he's like, oh, don't shoot,
don't shoot. What had happened was the bullet had hit the Fox strap and shattered it or
ripped it into pieces and then he immediately turned back into a naked dude. And then at
that point, since he like werewolves, the penalty of werewolves was death. If you could
shapeshift, you were immediately put to death. So that, you know, he was probably a little
worried. There's a bunch of guys with guns. Luckily it takes them like three minutes to
reload them. So they have time to think. But he's like, I listen, I didn't mean to become
a Fox. This kid brought this thing to school. I thought it was fake. Had a little bit of
a sweat on my forehead. I touched my forehead and they go, how long ago did that happen?
He's like, I don't know, eight months a year. They're like, well, you took to being a Fox
pretty quickly. So that is the, he goes back, he goes back home and apparently gets his
job back. He just get fired for turning into a Fox. The union's going to have to update
their contract to make that a fireable offense. And then the, the hill that he went to make
his house on, they named Fox Hill. So today you can go to the Dow. You can go to Fox Hill
and you can probably like walk around and maybe, maybe find his babies. Maybe he met
as sexy Fox as well. I think they probably named it Fox Hill just so he would never
forget the fact that he became a Fox because I mean there's a hill, there's animals on
every hill, right? There's not where animals on every hill. Turtle Bay wasn't named that
because there was a where turtle floating around. But yeah, so Fox Hill, a constant
reminder to this man that one day he turned into a Fox in front of all of his students
and then spent quite a while in the middle of nowhere naked. And then had to come back
home and ask for his job back. So I did find that story in a book written by a guy named
Carl Barge. He's an author and a historian. The book was called Legends, Fairy Tales and
Customs. So take, take a choice, right? I consider that a legend. I consider that an urban legend.
But Legends, Fairy Tales and Customs from Mechlenburg. I say it's a legend, you may say that sounded
suspiciously like a fairy tale. I looked into some more of the stuff that Carl Barge wrote.
Because he did a lot of research on like medieval time Germany. And he had this tip, he had
all these tips on like how to not have nightmares. Which I assume you have a bunch of nightmares
if you lived in Germany at any point in your life. So let's say you're having, this might
actually save your life. Let's take another vehicle for this. Fabio, I'm gonna go ahead
and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible. We're leaving behind Germany. We're headed
to your bedroom while you're sleeping. We're standing, you're asleep. If you're listening
to this, you're asleep right now and the rest of the show is standing around you staring
at you while you sleep. And then I talk really loudly to explain this. The way to stop nightmares
is this. You have a keyhole in your door, you stuff it, you put like tissue, you don't
have, I mean apparently once you do this, you're never leaving the room. Right? You're
all using superglue. You put, generally they used hay and the keyholes were bigger. I think
if you stuck hay into a modern keyhole, you're gonna have to call a locksmith. You're like
"Oooh, what a perfect night. No nightmares at all." You realize you died of carbon
oxide poisoning. You sealed off the room. You stick in hay or whatever into your keyhole.
That's step one. Two, put your shoes with the, take your shoes off. I should have said
that for you, for you dummies out there who would have spent the rest of the night just
standing there. Take your shoes off and place the toes facing the door and then walk backwards
to bed. He has another tip which may be more or less feasible depending on your bed. You
take a piece of steel and you put it in your bed straw. So back in your bed, then you're
basically a bunch of hobos that are sleeping on piles of hay, super itchy. But you put something
in there. Now if you're like on a Tempurpedic mattress or you're in a water bed, I did not
recommend doing this. You're like "Aww, no nightmares tonight as you're drowning." I
don't know in a modern like sleep foam bed if you can take like a file, like a steel
file and shove it in. But my favorite way to stop a nightmare. This is one you can do
today. You don't sleep on straw. You're no longer riding the rails like some crazy hobo.
You don't wear shoes. You wear crocs and they can't face the door or you don't want to stuff
up your doorknob. I totally get it. This last one you can do today. Why did you live
near a body of water? This one's great. This one's great. First off, it has my first favorite
ingredient ever to any sort of spell or ritual or just anything. Urinate in a clean new bottle.
So you got to get a new bottle for this. You have these horrible nightmares. So you go to
the new bottle store and you grab a bottle. You take it home. Don't do it at the store.
You will get arrested. You urinate in a clean new bottle and then you have to hang the bottle
in the sun for three days. So you got to let that urine just bubble up. It's super hot.
It's like you're in the Sahara. You're like, "Eh." It's bubbling. It's boiling. Then after
three days you have to carry it without saying a word to a running stream and then throw
it over your head into the stream. After that you have no nightmares. I read that and I thought
that's not true. Not that I don't think it would work, but someone made that up as a
joke. I'm not saying Carl did, but someone made that up as a joke because let's picture
this right now. You have to walk through your village. You have to walk through your medieval
village holding a bottle of three-day old hot urine. People are like, "Hey Joey, what's
up bro? How have you been? Hey Joey, what are you carrying? Joey? You're just walking
through town. You can't say anything, right? You're just walking through town. Hey dude,
what's- Dude, are you carrying urine? Hey Joey, Joey, what's going on? You just walk
through the village totally quiet and then they see you get to stream and you check it
on the river and then you walk up and you're like, "Hey man, how's it been?" We need to
hang out more often. That has to be a joke. No one could do that. I mean I guess if you
weren't walking through town and you're like sculpting through the darkness with the- Actually
that's even worse because they see- They know you're like the town weirdo who's always
like hiding behind bushels of fruit with your- You're constantly spilling it all over their
grocer stand. I think someone made that one up as a joke. I guess we can figure it out.
Test this. Test this. If you live near a stream, live stream yourself, not the urinating
part. We can skip that part but live stream yourself throwing urine into the river unless
that is considered pollution in your area. Oh man, I guess probably you can't do that
this day but I think out of all of them that is the funnest one and we had it ended on
something fun because this next story is super creepy. Fabio, I'm gonna go ahead and toss
you the keys to the carpenter copter. We are leaving behind your bedroom. We are headed
all the way out to Lake Charles, Louisiana. It's October 14th, 1993. We're in Lake Charles,
Louisiana. There's a little house on 18th Street and in this house there is Nelda Louise
Hardwick. She's a 34 year old woman who seems to have lived a pretty rough life. She has
numerous surgical scars all over her body. She has a full set of dentures and her left
leg is shorter than her right leg so she walks with a very noticeable limp but she's living
her life. She's living her life. She has four kids and she lives with her boyfriend and
they all have this little happy family and on October 14th, 1993, bathing the kids, beat
boxing, beat boxing on the kids, scrubbing them down with a big old brush and then the
boyfriend takes the kids and reads them bedtime stories and they're like, "That is the fairy
tale of the teacher who became a fox." The kid's like, "I think it's more of a legend."
All the kids go to sleep, the boyfriend goes to sleep and then the boyfriend wakes up next
day and he sees a note on the table and says, "I'm going out to the store. I'll be right
back." Nelda. She's like, "Oh, okay, you know, that's fine." She left a note but then he
realizes this note was left in the middle of the night. It's the morning now, she's
still not home. He calls the police and the police begin an investigation fairly quickly
on this because of, I'm assuming, health concerns. What's interesting about the story is there's
not a lot of information out there on this. It's fairly sensational but I couldn't find
a lot of stuff on this but the police begin an investigation relatively quickly. When
adults go missing in situations like that, the cops could be thinking, "Maybe she just
want a new life. She has this boyfriend she doesn't want. She doesn't want the kids."
She's like, "I can't bathe these kids anymore. They're super gross." She bounced but they
start an investigation right away to believe that not only is she involuntarily missing
but she's at risk and they just believe that there's foul play involved. The boyfriend's
like, "Listen, she loved the kids. She never would have left the kids, family members,
everyone are saying this is so out of character for her." They start looking for her and of
course everyone's hoping for the best but she's not found.
Five years later, May 8th, 1998, we're in Hancock County, Mississippi that's 242 miles
away. On Interstate 10, cars are flying down the road and out of nowhere, a woman runs
onto the interstate and is instantly killed when a car hits her. Someone get an ambulance.
Can I get a statement please? It's so anyways. Horrible, right? She's an identified woman.
They take the photos of her hoping someday they could find the loved ones but they don't
know who this woman is. They do the autopsy cause of death, getting hit by a car. She
is a Jane though so she's buried in a potter's field which is where you put people who don't
know who they are, they don't have enough money. Prisoners end up in potter's fields,
people, unidentified victims end up in potter's fields. They're basically just, your gravestone
is like a number because they don't know who you are. They put the body to rest, they
give you a sign, you a number like 191, unidentified body. In 2013 the hardwicks are still looking
for her. Nelda's family is never giving up the search and you do start to look at Jane
Doge, you know, checking hospitals, checking morgues, stuff like that. They and investigators
come across the story of this woman who ran onto the road, they look at photographs of
the body, they identify this deceased woman as Nelda. The coroner is then asked about
this and apparently he's shown the photographs as well and he believes that it's Nelda. And
he said it's actually a one in 1000 chance that it's not her. This has to be the same
woman. And they go there's only one way to be sure. Go to the potter's field, dig up
the bones, do it at midnight when it's super spooky, there's a raven on a nearby gravestone,
dig up the bones and do a DNA test because she has relatives that are alive and then
you could conclusively say this was Nelda. So they dig up the grave, open up the casket,
eeeeeee, spooky jack-o-lantern is there, flame, little candle flickering. They open up the
casket inside this coffin is a male's skeleton. Her body's grave marker was mislabeled and
they look out at the potter's field all of these other graves. They have no idea where
the body of Nelda is and the investigation is called off. To this day Nelda is still
reported as missing but it's most likely the family and investigators believe there's
a pretty good chance that she's in this potter's field. But what makes the story so terrifying
is what the coroner says and really what I think a lot of us think when we're hearing
this or reading this. She gets abducted in 1993 and five years later a woman, Nelda,
is running onto the interstate and gets hit by a car. The coroner's theory is that she
was kidnapped and kept alive for five years in captivity until one day she finally escaped.
And as she's running free for the first time in five years she's also panicked and fearful
that she will be caught again. She sees the interstate and she keeps running. Maybe she
was trying to cross it assuming that her pursuers would not be so risky she could just get over
the busy interstate. She has a shot, she has a chance at getting back to her family. Maybe
she was running to the interstate and was hoping to flag down a car or maybe she knew
she wasn't going to get away. This wasn't her first escape attempt. She'd done it before
but she knew this would be her last. She ran onto that freeway hoping she wouldn't make
it off the interstate alive. Suicide as opposed to slavery. Whichever one it is or any multitude
of others since a terrifying ending. The thing is even if we could with 100% certainty prove
that that was Nelda on the interstate. If we could find the right set of remains through
the DNA test and prove that was her we still would not come any closer to answering the
question where she had been for the past five years. What her life had been like. A young
woman leaves her house at night says goodbye to her sleeping children and her slumbering
boyfriend and goes to the corner store to get some groceries. She is then held in captivity
for five years and then dies on a freeway. We know how depraved human beings can be towards
each other. But a lot of us only know it in theory. We read about it in newspapers or
we read about it in books or see it in movies and we understand that humans can be this
dark. But Nelda knew it as a fact. She experienced day by day the brutality of humans. Humans
so brutal they kept her alive for five years after snatching her away from her family. Where
was she all that time? Who had her? And are they looking for fresh victims to this day?
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also go to stuff
at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Tiktok is at DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it
every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]