When a group of friends have a car accident in the middle of nowhere, it seems like the worst is yet to come.
Until a little old lady showed up.
And then we talk a lot about Doomsday Colts on this show.
Armed offshoots of major religions that believe the world is going to end soon.
These Colts often just fizzle out, are dismantled, or are gunned down.
But today we're gonna take a look at one of those Colts that actually succeeded.
In leaving their mark on the world. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having a lot of fun doing whatever you're doing. We got a really cool episode for you.
So first off, let's give a shout out to one of our legacy Patreon supporters coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now.
It's Mokushi! Everyone give it up to Mokushi!
Yay!
I think that's the first time I've ever shouted out "Yay" during one of these introductions.
So there you go Mokushi. Mokushi, you're gonna be our captain or pilot of this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show.
There's flyers on the show notes if you want to print them out.
Pass them around town. Tell your friends. Tell your family. Talk about it online.
We also have a merch store. I always forget to mention that. So that's another way to support the show.
Mokushi, I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy. We're gonna take a little road trip.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We are headed out to Karelia, Russia.
*Pfft*
Mokushi's driving this beat-up old junker that we still drive around after what? 696 episodes?
Out to Karelia, Russia. Specifically, we're headed to the Vusko Lakes in
Karelia, Russia. It's summer
1993 and it's nighttime. The stars are in the sky. The moon is looking down on earth.
It's jealous because got a bunch of cool people living on it and
there's a car full of tourists driving through the Vusko Lakes area. This car of tourists,
we don't have the names of these people, so we'll say Benny is driving the car.
I don't know how many people are in the car. I don't need to give them all names and backstories.
Anyways, Benny is driving the car. We got Veronica and the passenger.
I just said I wasn't gonna do this and I did anyways. Benny's driving the car.
I'll introduce the rest of the people if needed.
*Drumming*
Driving through the Vusko Lakes area. It's a magical place. Every time you pronounce it, it comes out differently.
No one has figured out why that happens. And there's a car accident.
*Eeeek*
So someone's like, "Great driving, Benny!" and Benny goes, "Oh,
Charlie, the guy sitting behind me, the guy sitting behind me, Charlie, you're always criticizing my driving."
Literally backseat driving. But then Veronica, who was in the passenger seat, is holding her head and she's like,
"Oh, I don't feel so good. I banged my head against this thing in front of the car."
The tree she flies out of the car, she hits the tree. One of the people in the car is injured.
*Uhhh*
And they have a concussion. They have a concussion. So Benny, Charlie, and then the other people in the car,
they have to take care of Veronica. This is 1993. This was back when cell phones were fairly rare.
And I'm pretty sure in the Soviet Union, they were non-existent. Well, this point, it was still Russia,
but they still didn't have the top-line technology. Vanessa, they're in the middle of nowhere. Her name changed due to the concussion.
Now she's Vanessa. The point is, is that- *Laughs*
Let's back every- The point is that a group of tourists
got in a car accident and one of them got a concussion. Let's- let's- let's cut it down to its finest details.
They see a little hut nearby. They see this little
building off on the side of the road, and they're like, "Dude, we have to like go there."
Like, we don't have a cell phone. This car is all busted up. Maybe someone's living in the hut.
Maybe they have a cell phone. Isn't that something that people who live in fat houses tend to have?
They take her to the hut and there's this old lady, and she opens the door. Old woman's kind of
motioning them in, so they bring Vanessa in and they lay her down on the table, or maybe a bed.
They're probably something more comfortable. They're knocking over the old lady's soup. Y'all get out of the way, hungry lady.
We have this person to take care of. They lay Vanessa down and the old lady walks up, and she doesn't say anything to anyone.
She's just like
tending to their wounds. Other people have like bumps and scrapes and things like that, and Vanessa could walk on her own.
She just had a concussion. It's not that bad, but she just- *Laughs*
She's a bit of a drama queen. They made her carrier everywhere.
And the old ladies tending to all of their wounds and stuff like that, and they'd be like, "Ah, Dasvedanya, lady."
And she'd be like, "Nah, nah, nah, nah." She wouldn't want to talk to them. She's just like cleaning out their wounds,
putting like goo, putting like old lady stuff on them.
You know, I- *Laughs*
I said that, I meant like stuff that like a witch doctor would make, not like old women's secret something.
Anyways, she's taking care of their wounds, and then all the tourists, Benny and Charlie and Vanessa, are like,
"Oh, we're super sleeping." The other unnamed people, they get sleepy too, and they all fall asleep.
And the old ladies just standing over them as they're like, "Uhhh..."
The next morning,
Benny wakes up. He's the first to wake up. He's like, "What? Huh? What?"
The last thing I remember is walking to some old lady's house in the middle of nowhere, but
he's looking around.
He's out in the open.
He's laying out in the open. The fresh Russian grasses against his back tickles him.
And he looks up and he sees this beautiful blue sky. Might have been overcast that day. That wasn't in the notes either.
But he looks up and he sees a beautiful blue sky.
And he notices he's not in the thatched house anymore.
And he goes, "Dudes, wake up, guys. Wake up. You won't believe what happened." And everyone wakes up.
They're not in the house.
They're now in this...
They're now all in the ruins of a
granite stone walled house that had collapsed.
And they're like, "Whoa." And then their wounds healed rapidly.
He looked at them. They're like, "Ahh!" The scabs are disappearing. They fall off.
So that...
That's the story.
That's the story that's not like some
goofy story that your brother told you because he couldn't come up with anything scary that night.
That's actually from the book The Soviet UFO Files written by Paul Stonehill.
I got it from thinkaboutitdocs.com. One of my favorite websites.
The reason why I wanted to share the story with you guys is because this is one of the stories where you think
what is the phenomenon going on here? Assuming the story's true. Assuming the story's true.
Could be completely made up. Paul Stonehill could be a really bad older brother and he's like, "Oh, this story will really scare those kids."
So keep those kids from driving through Russia and getting car accidents.
It's funny. We're in episode like 696. I have mentioned the Fae
maybe once or twice. They are not my favorite form of paranormal activity.
I don't like those stories. I don't really...
Sometimes I've covered stories about dwarfs dressed up as ninjas. I actually really like that one.
But like fairies in general? I'm not a huge fan of them. Little people floating around wings and stuff like that.
The whole like fairy circle. I did another one as a long time ago. It was the one that was the city in the Philippines.
That if you went there and you ate a piece of cheese, typical Fae stuff.
It was actually from the conspiracy theory iceberg. But if you eat their food, their trap there. I've never really liked Fae lore.
Because it's all the same, right? The idea...
Some of you guys are like, "Jace, I have no idea what you're talking about."
Fae lore is Fae-ry. It's basically the British version of that. And all the stories are the same.
They kind of collide with alien abductions where you're going about your own business.
And due to no fault of your own, you're taking to an alien realm. In this case, some sort of Fae realm.
And you're...
If you eat any of their food, you're stuck there forever. That detail is not in accounts with gray aliens. But a lot of people
consider Fae encounters similar enough to alien encounters that they think one may be the other.
Some people say that old-timey Fae encounters are actually based on
middle ages people getting abducted by gray aliens. And how would you
describe that?
You'd say I went to some Fae realm because you have no other sense of context for that.
Some people say, and this is less popular, because that kind of makes sense. If you believe aliens have been around for tens of thousands of years,
they would have to pop up throughout human history.
Other people say that, no, gray aliens are actually Fae-ries. That will never catch on. I don't believe that will ever catch on.
Because it's just not intriguing enough. And yeah, I'm not a huge fan of the Fae, but when you read this story,
I don't think of it as
Fae-ry. I don't think of it as any sort of Fae-ry activity. Although it does fall into those things since I don't really like Fae-ry stuff.
I think this falls into
portals, time slips.
Because the fact that they saw the huts and they went in there at night, and then it's not like they
were ever tempted to stay in this special realm when they woke up,
they were still in the same general area.
But the house that they saw the night before was actually
gone for ages. It was just this structure that had been up. Or
there's even the thing that this is where I was thinking of. I think of it more like this.
Like the television show Twin Peaks, a lot of it is based on
you'll be walking through a normal part of the world. You'll go, you'll stand on a rock and you'll get electrocuted.
You'll be walking through the forest and the next thing you know, you're in some other dimension.
This one guy's walking down an alley and he ends up in the white lodge and there's this eight foot tall duty.
He tells him to go get a green rubber glove. It'll turn him into a superhero. The show's bizarre. The show is bizarre.
I love it. I just watched it again all the way through for like the third time.
But I'm thinking that. I think that the car crashed. That happened. They were all busted up.
And what was really there, what they really would have should have seen, if they had just continued on their journey, would have been
a granite stone structure. It looked like an old building that had started to collapse.
But because they got in this accident, they kind of moved to a different mental state when they looked at it, they saw the hut.
And that hut and that old lady were not of this
not only not of this timeline, but not of this earth. The fact that the old lady wasn't even talking.
Makes me think that the old lady knew.
You know that if she started talking to me, dead giveaway. She'd have like 15 tongues in her mouth and her eyes are rolling back.
So it's an interesting story. That's the way I read it. That this was some sort of interdimensional
being and she appears as this old lady because that's who takes care of you, right? If you had to imagine
a caretaker. Yeah, you could be a flaming angel with 10 wings and he's like, "Let me clean your wounds."
But it's most likely going to be a grandmother, a maternal figure.
And that's how the universe portrayed this. Could be Faye. And if it was Faye, I apologize for wasting your time.
Because I don't like covering the Faye. I actually know you guys enjoy the Faye. It's just not my cup of tea. But
could be Faye, could be a time slip. She could have been an old lady in ancient Russia and one day she tells her neighbors, "Guys, you won't believe what happened."
These people showed up in the oddest of clothing and I just treated them and then I gave them a bit of sleeping drugs and then I dragged them out of my house
and I don't know what happened to them. They were gone the next day.
Or it could be this interdimensional
healer event. We don't know. It's in the UFO files. I don't think it really has anything to do with aliens.
But who knows? I just think it's an interesting story and it's one of the stories that because it doesn't precisely fit the lore of any real one category,
it's truly a puzzling story.
Mokushi, I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonar copter. We are saying goodbye to Karelia, Russia.
We're there like, "We still need help working on our car. We're like, see you guys later. We're flying away from these people."
They're still stranded out there to this day.
Mokushi fly us on out to
Saudi Arabia.
I was shocked when I found out that this story happened. I've mentioned it recently on this show. There's a website called crazy facts
that I go to every day and you just hit a button and gives a random fact.
It gives you a little dopamine hit when you learn something new. Plus, I found a lot of cool stuff from there.
I was shocked this story was real. This sounds like it should have already been like
at least a couple movies.
We're in Saudi Arabia
specifically
at the great mosque of Mecca.
It is the home of the Kaaba. It is the direction that Muslims worldwide pray to.
Once in their lifetime, a Muslim must make their pilgrimage to Mecca.
This is
it's hard to
overstate its importance
in world religious history, especially in the Muslim religion. On November 20th 1979,
it's just a day like any other.
The prayer services start at 5 a.m. There's 50,000 worshipers
at the great mosque of Mecca.
As people are sitting here praying,
they start to hear commotion to their left to their right.
Often the distance in the crowd, they see people jumping up.
They see movement in the crowd.
The prayer has been interrupted as
four to six hundred people are jumping up during the prayer.
Men and women alike throwing off their robes
and brandishing automatic weapons
panic immediately sets in. You have a crowd of 50,000 people packed into this area
and all of a sudden orders are being shouted. You're standing there and you see someone with a weapon
at the great mosque of Mecca where violence is forbidden.
He points it at a local police officer and shoots him dead.
There were police officers at the great mosque of Mecca, but because violence was forbidden
they only carried Billy, they only had these little billy clubs, right?
They could kind of push people out. You're getting unruly. They could get you out of there.
They weren't armed with weapons.
And all of a sudden you had four to six hundred people.
They were never able to figure out exactly how many people had infiltrated the great mosque of Mecca that day.
Orders are being shouted. Everyone's freaking out. Two police officers end up getting shot.
People are pulling out chains. They were fully prepared
to take over the mosque. They begin to chain the exits shut.
And you're stuck there. At the time the great mosque was being renovated. There was a worker up there
and he sees all of the stuff that's going on. He's able to get to a phone, starts calling for help,
letting people know what's going on. That is when the phone lines are cut.
This group releases most of the 50,000 hostages because you really just can't keep control of that many people.
But a couple hundred are kept behind.
As thousands and thousands of hostages are running out of the area,
this group is putting snipers and the minarets that surround the great mosque of Mecca.
They now have complete control of the area. But who are they?
They are followers of a man known as Muhammad Abdullah al-Qatani.
He was believed by his followers to be the Ma'adi or the Redeemer. He's basically a figure in
apocalyptic Muslim belief. He was a man who was going to come to earth before the final days,
before Jesus comes back and begins to destroy the evil of the world. The Ma'adi would come and
be the Redeemer before this process. Every religion is going to have people pop up and claim to be
important figures. And there's a whole list of people over the centuries who have claimed to be the Ma'adi,
who've claimed to be this figure in the end times.
But the reason why Muhammad Abdullah al-Qatani was able to convince 400 to 600 people,
because again they don't know for sure how many people moved into this area,
of this was he was popping up in Saudi Arabia at a time of change, at a time of social change.
And this seems to be the best time for any sort of hardliner to make their case.
Saudi Arabia was becoming very westernized at this point.
And for the people of Saudi Arabia, they go, "This is not right. This isn't right.
There's, I'm opening up the newspaper. There's pictures of women in the newspaper.
This is borderline pornographic." And the power step B in Saudi Arabia goes,
"No, this is the way the world is going. Like, yeah, I know we have those old ways, but listen,
this is progressive, right? I don't think that was the actual word they used, but
it's okay. We're going to become a more open society. We're going to become more free.
We're going to become more liberated." And then Sidwell, with followers of Muhammad
Abdullah Akhtani, and his followers were growing every single day. When you have social change,
you will have detractors of that. This was this group's goals. They wanted to kick out all the
western powers of Saudi Arabia. That was bin Laden's goal as well. That was one of his main things.
To this day, there are a lot of people in Saudi Arabia who do not like the fact that there are
westerners, that there is US military equipment right outside of the great mosque of Mecca. It is
a sticking point for a lot of people in Saudi Arabia. So they wanted to kick out all the western
powers. They wanted to kick out all non-Muslims. You have to be a Muslim to visit the great mosque
of Mecca, but they wanted to get rid of all non-Muslims in Saudi Arabia altogether, and no
television, because they saw that as a leading factor in the degradation of Saudi Arabia. Muhammad
Abdul Akhtani had support where it counted. He didn't control the government. He didn't control the
media, but he had a lot of allies in the National Guard. When his plan was being talked about in
mosques, his plan was openly preached in the streets. People knew that there were elements
out there who did not like the way Saudi Arabia was opening up. It was touching these people's
hearts, and they began funneling weapons into the mosque. This was something that was planned for,
and people would learn that because of how hard it was to remove these men and women from the
great mosque of Mecca. After that phone call was made, thousands of people are running out of the
great mosque. A hundred security officers are sentenced to retake it. They don't know really
what's going on. They got a phone call saying that people with guns are taking over the mosque.
They see thousands of people running out. They have no idea about the snipers and the minarets.
They learn that very quickly. As these hundreds of security officers are running into the mosque,
sniper fire is just taking them out. And the people in the mosque who are heavily armed begin
shooting out of the mosque, and it is a bloodbath. These security officers have to pull back.
Their losses are too heavy. So a meeting is called now. You get members of the Saudi Arabia army.
You got members of the National Guard, which they don't know that members of the National Guard are
in on this, not all of them, but some of them are. This meeting had the Saudi Arabian army
officials, the National Guard, and there was a French special operations team in the area.
They just happened to be there. And they begin talking about this and trying to figure out how to
retake the mosque. Because you just can't have a bunch of people with weapons take over the holiest
site in the Muslim world. They begin coming up with a plan. Step one, by that first night,
the entire city of Mecca, there's a city that surrounds this mosque, the entire city is evacuated.
It's a ghost town. Saudi Arabian army comes in National Guard, the French special ops team is
there. They now don't have to worry about civilian casualties. They don't know what they're going
to do, but they wanted to clear this out. They have no idea what's coming next or what this
group's goals are. They haven't communicated this yet. Now it is religious law. You cannot commit
violence in the grand mosque. Now, obviously, these people in here are not playing by that rule.
They had no problem with slaughtering these soldiers. They had no problem killing these police
officers. They have no problem holding these hostages. But according to the religious laws,
you can't even uproot a plant in the great mosque. So the government reaches out to the Ullama,
which are the interpreters of religious law. There's this long discussion of finally the
religious leaders come forward and they say, in this instance, yes, you can use deadly force.
So this is the plan now. Now that they've got their clearance, the Saudi forces are going to have a
three pronged attack towards the great mosque. There's three main gates. It makes sense. They're
just going to push through overwhelming might. They rush in, they're better equipped, they have
numerical opposition. It doesn't matter. It is another bloodbath. These snipers are wiping them
out. You can't get in with raw military might outside of bombing the area, which was nothing
they had planned on doing. So now they've had two full assaults towards the mosque, completely repelled.
So they pull back. I can't believe this story is not more widely known. Am I the only one who's
never heard of this? I mean, I was alive during, I mean, I was three, but this is insane. Because
what happens next is the government of Saudi Arabia says, listen, we've sent in two waves of forces
to try to retake it. They're picking us off. We need this back. But let's just starve them out.
We're just going to surround the place. We're going to lay siege to the great mosque of Mecca.
Eventually they'll just give up. They won't have any food. For two weeks, the army surrounded the mosque.
For two weeks, nothing changed. No one gave up. No one begged for food.
No one came out hoping for forgiveness. The hostage takers were resolute.
Remove all Western powers. Kick out all non-Muslims. Remove television. We need to return to the old ways.
At this point, it's become incredibly embarrassing for the government of Saudi Arabia.
You have the Saudi king Khaled. He's watching this whole thing and he's seen the holiest site
has been taken over on his watch. He can't break the back of these hostage takers.
What is he going to do? Two weeks is too long. He orders a final assault. We have to go in.
Casualties be damned. The Saudi Arabian government calls the special forces, the French special forces,
and say, we want, we know you guys, this is what you do for a living. This is what you literally do
for a living. You break into places and take them over. We want you to join us on this raid. However,
you can't enter the great mosque of Mecca unless you're a Muslim.
So will you convert to Islam and fight alongside us?
The French commanders go, yeah, let's do it. So they had this short ceremony.
They converted to Islam. They geared up along with their Saudi Arabian army compatriots
and they headed off towards Mecca. The grand mosque of Mecca apparently has tunnels underneath it,
which would kind of be a no-brainer if you're going to infiltrate an area. It seems the reason why
they weren't using these tunnels in the first place was because you couldn't, originally they were
just trying to send a bunch of people in. They were trying to invade it like you were, like you
would any fort. So you just send in a mass amount of people, you'd overwhelm them with numbers.
Hopefully you could just overpower them and save hostages. When they start using these tunnels,
they know that the combat is going to be very close quarters and extremely high casualties
for even the hostages. Because when they're getting in these tunnels that take them
underneath the mosque, the special forces and the Saudi Arabian army get into their positions.
And the first thing they do, they begin to pump gas into the tunnels. They begin to pump knockout
gas into the tunnels. So that way anyone who is posted in the tunnels, because most likely the
hostage takers know about them, they're going to get knocked out. The special forces move through
these smoked filled tunnels. They get underneath the mosque itself and they begin drilling holes
through the floor and then throwing grenades up into the mosque. Grenade after grenade after
grenade is popping up through these holes. Nobody knew what was going on in the mosque.
And this is why this was not the best plan. You had insurgents and hostages who had been
kept away from their loved ones for two weeks sitting there and a grenade would roll towards them.
And explode. Grenades just being lobbed blindly into the mosque. The rebels start to try to regroup.
They don't, they didn't expect this. You know that there's tunnels underground, but you don't
expect grenades to come out of them. They try to regroup. At this point, they're trying to get out
of the mosque. And as they're running through the courtyard, they are now being shot on site.
During this chaos, snipers begin to panic. They begin missing their shots. They begin to try to
retreat. They are also killed. Most die of the scene. Some are captured and a few escape into
the empty city of Mecca. Still abandoned for days. Small gun battles erupted across the city.
As military forces were tracking down these dudes, killing them on the spot.
These numbers are debatable, but the generally accepted numbers. Some people say these are too
small, but general accepted number is on all sides. Military, insurgent and civilian. 300 people
were killed over the course of this event and a thousand people wounded.
But there are people who believe the number is much higher because they don't even know how many
people had come into the mosque. They said four to six hundred. They don't have an accurate count.
68 of these insurgents who were captured were actually taken to different cities
across the country and publicly beheaded. King Khaled wanted to make it known that this is what
happens if you follow the path of extremism. He could have executed them all in a single location,
but no, he wanted to make it known across the country. He had these 68 people taken to all
these different cities and they were publicly beheaded. But how this story ends is actually the
most fascinating part of the story because I'm telling you this story about women appearing in
newspapers and Saudi Arabia becoming more westernized and more progressive and you're listening to it.
Like I was reading it and I thought, but wait a second, that's not Saudi Arabia today.
Saudi Arabia is, I just read in the news today, Saudi Arabia executed a kid. He took part in an
Arab Spring protest when he was 17 years old and they arrested him when he was 23 and they cut
his head off about two days ago. They said they found a photo on his phone that was obscene
and he did the whole Arab Spring thing when he was 17, which was years ago.
They chopped his head off yesterday and you're looking at this stuff and you're like, wait a
second, Saudi Arabia, I mean, it's probably a fun place to visit, right? But I wouldn't say it's
westernized. I wouldn't say that it has like these, I know WWE had a hard time wrestling over there.
There's like no women wrestlers, but this whole kind of thing started because people were seeing
that Saudi Arabia was becoming too westernized, too liberal. It's not those things at all. Those
definitely those words I would not use to describe the government of Saudi Arabia.
This event actually worked. King Khaled watched this happen. Had these people execute and go,
this is what happens if you believe in extremism, but then he thought, I don't want that to happen again.
Like if that's, I got these people on this side who are saying we need to be more equal and we need
to be open and we need to be more tolerant. And then I have the people on this side who are willing
to take over the great mosque of Mecca at gunpoint. These people are telling me, you know,
I might win the peace prize and these people might overthrow me. You had members of his
cabinet of his court saying, King Khaled, we brought this upon ourselves. This was divine
retribution because we fell too far. We were publishing pictures of women in the newspaper
like what's next? Like are we really becoming a decadent society like these guys were saying?
So King Khaled actually looked at this and said, maybe they're right.
Let me read you a quote from a book called Inside the Kingdom, Kings, Clerics, Modernist,
Terrorists, and the Struggle for Saudi Arabia, written by Robert Lacey.
"Those old men believed that the mosque disaster was God's punishment to us because we were
publishing women's photographs in the newspapers," says a princess, one of Khaled's nieces.
The worrying thing is that the king probably believed that as well.
Khaled had come to agree with the sheiks. Foreign influences were the problem.
The solution to religious upheaval was simple. More religion, unquote.
One of the things that grew out of this ruling was the Committee for the Promotion of Virtue and
the Prevention of Vice, which was basically a religious policing force. They would drive around,
they would famously make sure that women were wearing the proper dress code that
there is gender segregation in public spaces. Most controversially, one of the things they
did, this sounds insane, on March 11, 2002, there was a burning school in the city of Mecca.
This elementary school is on fire, and these schoolgirls were trying to run out of the burning
school. The religious police wouldn't let them. There has to be more, there has to be more to
the story, but apparently they wouldn't let them because they weren't dressed in the headscarves
and the black robes, and they didn't have a male guardian with them. They couldn't do this,
so they weren't letting them escape from a burning school.
That's insane. 15 girls died and 50 were injured in this fire. There's actually widespread outrage
over this, and they're like, "Oh, they're just doing their jobs. They're not supposed to be outside
with headscarves." The school is on fire, so these groups like this were empowered by the
mosque seizure. There's a difference between saying, "Let's slow down social change," and another thing
by not letting girls escape a burning school unless they go back to get their headscarf,
which is probably on fire itself. So it went from a society that was becoming more open,
which there were people inside the array who didn't like that, to becoming something that was
almost a parody of conservative beliefs. That's just absurd. Fascinating story.
I think there's a thing when we look at history, we always see it as a march in one direction,
but it never ever is. Nick Buston Guston asked me, he's a Patreon supporter, if you don't know
who that guy is. Nick Buston Guston asked me a question for my third anniversary special. I
didn't get to cover it on the show, but what's a conspiracy theory that's unpopular that you believe?
And I say this all the time, and people always argue with me on it,
but I say this all the time. I go, "We are, maybe two weeks to a month,
away from at best a crackdown at worst a genocide at any given time."
I believe that at any moment in human history, something so bad can happen, a meteorite strike,
a massive plague, huge economic downturn, and people will immediately look for someone to blame.
And they will beg their leaders to do something about it.
Now a lot of people don't agree with me on that. A lot of people have a little more
hope in the human race, or faith in themselves that they would try to stop that. People were
pulling their neighbors out of their house and beating them with clubs. But I do think we're
that close. I'm an optimist too. That's why I'm giving it two weeks to a month. And I think stories
like this go to show that. It's just crazy to think that this event changed the course of an
entire nation. At the end of the day, people are fearful, and people hate how much they're afraid.
I think this story just highlights how fragile the social contract is between people and their
government, and people and their religion, any religion. This can happen with any religion out
there. When people are afraid, people demand answers. They demand help. Even if that comes at the
expense of other people's freedoms. We have seen it throughout human history. And if you think for
a moment that we as a species are past that sort of primal fear, you really haven't been paying attention.
And it could pop up again. It will pop up again. The question is, what will you do
when they come for your neighbors?
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime
podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]
[MUSIC]