A judge overseeing a murder trial has his own secret to hide.
And then we take a trip around the United States to visit haunted asylums.
Are you ready to walk down those dark halls?
It's an interactive adventure today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You know, we have a new club.
There's one member. He's the founder.
I call it the Golden Rabbit Brigade.
Because a listener, I have a listener named Chris Kaye,
made a great donation to the continuation of the show.
I don't have a Patreon set up. He went about it and did it himself.
I didn't even know that was possible, but I appreciate that.
It really, really helps out a lot.
And so Chris Kaye, thank you. You're also now on the show notes as the founder of the Golden Rabbit Brigade.
Which I think is kind of cool.
Now from now on, imagine Chris Kaye decked out in Golden Rabbit Armour.
It's like a real cool suit of armour, but it has rabbit ears as well.
But again, I want to say thank you one more time. Really, really helps. Really, really helps.
I'm not going to say what the dollar amount was, but I do like how he announced,
put the change is 33 cents.
Uh, uh, Masonic. Masonic symbols. Masonic symbols everywhere if you know where to look.
Let's go ahead and get started with the first story here.
Now this story I had heard a long, this could act, you know, I haven't done in a long time, new news.
Because I read this way back in the day and I laughed so hard and I stumbled back across it a couple days ago.
And I was like, I got to cover that story.
So we are going back in this case to the magical year of 2003.
We're in Bristow, Oklahoma.
And we're sitting in a courthouse. We're sitting in the back, just chilling.
Checking our chairs, make sure there's no snakes.
And we're sitting in a deep cut. That's an old episode.
And I usually don't do in-jokes, but I couldn't resist.
We're sitting in these chairs and we're watching this trial.
And it's a trial for a murder, a quite grisly murder.
Court reporters sitting there typing, juries sitting there going,
"Hmm, they're all making those noises. Hmm, they question everything."
Prosecutors giving his case.
The man here murdered this person in a horrible way and we should have to do in the whole Atticus Finch thing.
And we just see the judge sitting on the stand, not on the stand, sitting at the bench, sitting on the podium, whatever it is.
You know what, you've seen Law and Order, you know where judges sit.
And we hear a "pss, pss, pss."
And I'm like, what is that noise?
You can see the jurors looking around going, "Hmm, hmm."
Now they're saying it even louder.
Prosecutor kind of gets distracted for a second, but just has to keep going, doing his job.
Psss, psss, psss.
And the judge is just kind of sitting there looking at everyone where nobody can know where the sound is.
Is it a mouse with a pneumatic gun shooting potatoes at people?
Did a balloon hide as a person and now it's slowly deflating?
Nobody knows.
Nobody knows. I am poking people with pins though to test that theory.
But the court reporter does know.
And she's sweating as she's typing her notes because she knows what's going on.
So Lisa Foster was the court reporter and she had worked with this particular judge for a while, right?
And she had seen, because of the way she's positioned, she's typing in her little stenographer's chair,
she is able to every so often kind of look over and she sees the judge sitting there with the penis pump attached to his,
that's where it goes.
And he would sit there during trial and just go psss, psss, and masturbate while people were on trial for murder.
Now, she didn't say anything.
And this is very telling.
This was a quote that Lisa said because after everything came out, they asked her about it.
And she's like, "Yeah, I know. You had the penis pump and all that stuff."
They're like, "Why didn't you say anything?"
This was her exact quote.
"I didn't want to be found dead in a ditch somewhere."
That's just insane that she was basically like, "If I rat this guy out for masturbating in a trial,
there's a chance no one will believe me and I will be retaliated against."
That's harrowing.
It's really scary to think she works in the judicial system and even she's like scared of like the bad guys in the system.
But what happens is people, he does this for two years.
He's not constantly, it's not the same jackoff routine.
He takes it off every once in a while, otherwise he just has like this massive, he needs another robe for his genitalia.
No, during trials and stuff, every so often you'd be like, "Oh yeah, what am I doing?
Oh yeah, I have supposed to masturbate now."
And he'd put the penis pump on.
Sometimes he wouldn't use the penis pump, sometimes he would just masturbate under his robes.
And people, you know, you have the same people come into the courthouse all the time, police officers, lawyers and stuff like that.
They started to think, this is so funny, because every so often, they'd see him fiddling with his hands behind his big old desk.
And you know, like in the courthouse, behind the big old like, judge's throne, we'll call it, whatever it's called.
They would see him playing with like, moving his hands and looking down.
And they thought he brought like a Game Boy.
They thought he was playing straight up Game Gear down there.
Golden axe too, while these people were on trial.
But they'd ask him and they'd be like, "Oh no, no, no, that was fine.
I had an itch that took me five minutes to scratch and then I moaned when I got done scratching it.
I guess that makes sense.
At one point though, a cop was testifying against somebody.
So he's sitting on the stand and he sees, looks over while he's giving a testimony, looks over and he sees a plastic tube going into the judge's robes.
So his little detective instinct went off and he's like, "Ah, better investigate that. That's why his wife left him.
Because he just investigated everything. Who ate the pie?" He's like putting up little police tape around the pie.
He doesn't let anything go by. He has to investigate everything.
After they break for lunch, the cop goes over and looks at where the judge sits and sees the penis pump.
It's just sitting there behind his podium.
So he ends up, the officer ends up reporting it. They start investigating and the judge goes, "Oh, that thing? Yeah, I never use it.
It was a gag gift and I probably should have thrown it away, but I did get it."
And they go, "Well, why is it in your workstation?"
I know there's a hundred law students right now pulling their hair out because I don't know the name of where the judge sits,
but why did you have that there?" And he goes, "Well, sometimes they keep it in my office, but I always show off when I bring it out here."
And people, that's even more, but that doesn't answer the question. Why are you carrying a penis pump around?
And he goes, "Listen, I'll be honest with you guys. This noise you hear going, 'psshh, pshh,'"
because it actually was so loud it appeared on the audio tape of that trial.
You can hear people arguing about whether or not this guy is a murderer and you hear a 'psshh, pshh.'
He says, "Listen, I'll be honest with you guys. I'll be frank with you."
I'm just kind of weird because my name is actually Donald.
And they're like, "This isn't a dead silent. Dude, just tell us the story."
He's like, "Okay, here we go." Scratches that off of his stand-up routine list.
He says, "That noise you hear is actually me pressing the penis pump."
And they're like, "Oh, thanks for being honest." He's like, "No, no, no, but it wasn't on my penis."
You see, sometimes I just absent-mindedly reach for it and press it.
It's just like a stress thing or I'm just not really thinking.
And they're like, "That's not true. That is 100% not true."
So the cops ended up having to go and they're like, "We know this guy's masturbating during these trials."
They got a hold of his robes.
They went and they took a sample of the carpet underneath his chair and his chair and ran tests on it.
And it was all covered in semen.
So he was masturbating into his robes.
I don't know what his output was, but apparently he was everywhere down there.
I guess if you're masturbating for two years in the same spot.
Chris K's like, "Great, this is the episode I donated to him on."
I guess if you're masturbating in the same spot for two years, it's gonna get everywhere, but come on your robes.
On your robes.
Lift those up.
That's gross because you know, once he was finished, he just sat in those robes for the rest of the trial.
Or the rest of that day. I'm sure he washed them, but...
He didn't because they found DNA on them.
Anyways, so he ended up getting four years for it because they could charge him on like four times of doing it.
They gave him one year for each time. They absolutely knew he was masturbating during trial.
They gave him four years in prison and a $10,000 fine for each time he did it.
So he got $40,000 in fines.
And defense lawyers were basically, they were masturbating because they were so happy.
They were like, "We can totally get our client off."
And... but that doesn't seem to have worked because all of this stuff pretty much happened back in the early 2000s.
I didn't see anything about a bunch of defendants getting retried or anything like that.
But Judge Donald Thompson, 59 year old man in 2003, masturbating.
I'm sure he's still alive now, but I really doubt he's a judge.
But I just find that story absolutely hilarious.
Okay, so let's go ahead. It's true crime, right?
Conspiracy, investigation, you know, I can wrap it in there.
Maybe it was ectoblasm, ooh, paranormal.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
The next story I wanted to turn a limb in and to eliminate.
I've been so hard on Backpackerverse in the past, they gave me a list of ten of the most haunted and sane asylums.
With ten of the dumbest ghost stories possible.
And I said, "You know what? I'm gonna find the true history of these haunted asylums."
I will take Backpackerverse, if you don't know, as a website that basically just makes stuff up
and then passes it off as paranormal truth.
So basically, like most paranormal websites, but they go the extra mile.
They just absolutely make everything up.
I said, "You know what? I'm gonna take these insane asylums, I'm gonna find out about them.
I'm gonna find a real ghost story in there to chill your bones and you get to play along with this one."
Because who doesn't want to have an interactive adventure where you get locked in a place with people who are mentally insane?
So pick a number between one and five.
Okay, you got your number?
Let's go ahead and hop on board the Carpenter copter.
And we are flying to Spring City, Pennsylvania.
In Spring City, Pennsylvania, we have the Pinhurst Asylum.
And the helicopter's flying overhead and you look down and you're like, "Oh, great. This looks super spooky."
I was like, "It is. It is super spooky."
The Pinhurst Asylum was originally known as the Pinhurst Home for the Feeble-Minded and Epileptic, which...
So apparently back then, epilepsy was considered a mental...
I have a really good friend of mine who has epilepsy really bad.
And I felt bad for him because he had epilepsy.
He had a stroke so bad or seizure so bad that his...
He said his brain doesn't work like it used to.
He goes, "I talk really slow." And I go, "Dude, I've known you for years. You talk the same speed."
But because his brain is processing the language slower, he thinks he sounds slow, so he's super self-conscious about it.
But anyways, you can have like...
Imagine you have epilepsy.
Like, you're a total functioning adult, but you have some short circuit in your brain and your body will start to seize up and stuff like that.
And they put you in a place with like drooling lunatics who have like, were butchering pigs.
That's kind of how it was back then, which totally sucked.
And it's almost like prison where you would have to group up.
You would be like, "I better find the other epileptics and like, hang out with them."
In case there's like a rumble or something like that, because everyone else in here is a raging lunatic.
So nowadays, they do ghost tours there.
And that's where one of these ghost stories come from.
One of these ghost stories comes from a ghost tour guide.
He's walking through the spooky, spooky asylum.
It's no longer full of a bunch of people with medical problems.
It's just full of tourists and tour guides.
And he's walking through the asylum.
He's all alone.
And then he turns.
And he sees a young woman standing behind him.
And her face is covered in blood.
Makeup! Just bloody makeup.
And he goes, "Whoa, I didn't see you there."
And she stands there and then he turns, his boss walks by and he goes,
"Boss, check out this girl."
The girl had finished.
Now I was like, listen, listen.
That is the story from Backpackerverse.
And I thought, if you're gonna make it up, why does she not have just blood on her face?
Why is it bloody makeup?
And I've realized something.
A lot of these ghost stories involve guys, like running into girls,
and then the girl disappearing.
And I wonder if there's something Freudian about that.
Or if they're just normal girls that these guys are running into
and the guy acts kind of awkward and cringey around her,
and then he's like, "Hey boss, meet this new girl."
And then she like sneaks out.
She's like, "Weirdo."
She leaves.
There's so many of these stories involve guys meeting girls,
and then they go, and then when I turned around, she was gone.
Which is basically any guy at a bus stop.
Any guy trying to pick up a girl at a bus stop.
I did that once.
Don't do that.
So here's the thing.
You go, Jason.
That was the story from Backpackerverse.
You promised me an interactive adventure, and I did.
So here we go with a newer ghost story.
A newer ghost story.
Now this one also seems to be fairly made up.
But, let's do this.
Pinhurst Asylum was overcrowded, and it was a horrible place to be.
They ended up shutting it down because it was just so awful.
But there are stories that are promoted by the current owner of the haunted house.
The attraction known as Pinhurst Asylum.
That the previous doctor was killed by the inmates.
[Groaning]
And the asylum just burned down.
And so please donate to my GoFundMe to get it rebuilt.
But, before you do that, you should know, after all the crazy people escaped,
people are like, "Are you saying a bunch of epileptics are like serial killers?"
The guy's like, "No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, they're totally normal."
I'm talking about the crazy people.
The crazy people.
They escaped, but sometimes they come back late at night to find you.
And the mad doctor who performed all these experiments on them,
that I forgot to mention earlier, mad doctor performed experiments on all these guys.
Sometimes he comes back too, even though he's dead, he's a ghost.
Sick with the program. It's a ghost guide, it's a ghost story.
You're like, "Dude, this is a really confusing ghost story."
He's like, "Shh." So, you're walking through the asylum all by yourself,
in the dark halls with just a flashlight you little urban explorer you,
wanting to get some good footage for your YouTube channel.
And that's when you feel cold, icy hands grab you.
Not just grab you, but grab into you.
Grab your spine and pull you into a dark room.
And there you see the ghastly doctor.
His medical staff standing all around him.
And you see a tool in his hand that you saw once in a horror movie,
or you're just a crazy person and you know what it looks like anyways.
It's a lobotomy needle.
And if you picked number five, you feel a little bit of pressure right above your left eye,
as it slowly cracks bone and then slides into your brain.
And then he stirs you up like a coolin, like a blue jug of cooling.
And you are now one of the crazy people stalking Pinnhurst Asylum.
So, I like that ghost story, that's much better than the blood de-makeup.
Like, it's a much, much better story than that one, but that one's also totally fake.
The guy, people in town want him to shut down his haunted house attraction.
They go, "This is so demeaning to people with mental illnesses."
And the guy's like, "Dude, I'm just making it up.
Just making it up that every night these mental people come back and might murder your children."
They've been trying to shut it down for years.
But, let's go ahead and go to our next encounter.
Our next encounter is in Ohio.
So hop on board the Carpenter Copter.
If you're number five, we left you, you're just sitting somewhere in the asylum.
We didn't keep track.
I should have counted people before we went on this trip.
People, someone's like, "Hey, didn't we have five people on this trip?"
I was like, "Yeah, now just get on the copter. Just get on the copter."
Fly away.
[imitates flying]
We're going to Athens, Ohio.
I wonder if that's close to Helltown.
Anyways, we're going to Athens, Ohio.
We're going to an asylum known as the Ridges.
I thought this one was funny, because the one, I shouldn't say funny, but it's known as the Ridges today.
And that name came out from some sort of name, like the county had a naming contest.
Spooky, spooky buildings out in the middle of nowhere,
which would be the perfect place to have a mental institution.
You don't want it in the middle of town.
The one in Sacramento, though, is like right off the freeway.
It's like in the middle of town.
You can buy candy at the gas station and then walk into the mental hospital in Sacramento.
Anyways, this place is known.
This has some real ghost stories, so don't shut it off.
You're like, "Jason's just going to keep reading ridiculous stuff."
This one actually has some real ghost stories established in 1874.
And actually has an interesting question about ghosts, too.
That's the reason why I included this one.
There's a shadowy figure located around the buildings.
So you got the shadow man, right?
Walking around.
You turn.
See, shadow walk by.
Now, what's interesting about this shadow guy
is that he walks weird.
He walks with a weird walking style.
Doesn't walk like a person would normally walk.
And so apparently, according to this part,
according to Backpackerverse,
someone brought a tape recorder to the ridges
and did an EVP and it told this story.
They basically asked it the shadow man questions,
and this is the story that we heard.
The shadow man is a ghost,
and he's the ghost of a guy who had epilepsy.
And he felt so fine.
I think this is so funny.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But he falls in love with a woman
who has a mental problem.
It's too late to get your money back.
I already cut it out of my paypal.
You're like, "Dude, I've never given this to you."
Okay, there's this guy.
There's this guy.
Okay, there's a guy with epilepsy,
and he falls in love with this girl in a mental asylum.
Sounds very sweet, right?
Sounds--it's adorable.
Everybody needs love.
But unbeknownst to the both of them,
she was scheduled for a lobotomy.
So he's like falling in love with this girl,
and she's falling in love with him,
and then one day he basically just goes to her room
and is like, "Hey, Natalie, what's going on?"
And she's just--uh, she had a lobotomy,
and she doesn't remember him.
That's tragic.
I don't know why I think that story's so--
Anyway, so here's--let's try to save this as much as we can.
So the question is this.
So they said that the Shadow Man is the ghost of that man
still pining after his lost love.
So here's the thing.
Why would the ghost have epilepsy?
Like, if the ghost is walking around all weird,
the idea is that the ghost is the ghost of the man,
and the ghost is walking like someone who has severe epilepsy.
Why would the ghost have epilepsy?
If that's true, if you're blinded and relive,
or you're in a car accident, or you're falling on an airplane,
and you're flat, is your ghost flat?
Like, do you just kind of score him along the ground?
Is your ghost blind?
Like, it doesn't make sense,
because then all ghosts would be crippled in one way or the other.
But anyways, according to this, that this ghost has epilepsy.
But that's not the fate you get,
although that'd be kind of funny too if you pick this number.
The love of your life gets a lot of lies.
But no, no, no, we're gonna do something else here,
because there's an other more chilling story than that one.
What you get is this.
The story of Margaret Shilling.
She was a patient there, who really liked to play hide and go seek.
"Hey, catch me, guys. I'm gonna go hide, and you seek me."
And they're like, "Yeah, Margaret, we know how to play the game. Just go hide.
We'll find you."
"Yeah, yeah, yeah."
She runs down the hallway, she shuts the door, and hides.
"No one will find me here."
And the nurses would find her and take her back to her room,
and she'd be like, "He he he, I'm such a good hide and seeker."
But one day she started the game, and the nurses got distracted.
And she hid the perfect hiding spot.
And a month later, they found her, dead in the room.
Now, obviously, someone who was lucid would go,
"Oh, they haven't found me in an hour. I guess the game's over."
But to her, the game of hide and go seek was so real, it never ended.
And even today, when you go into that room, presumably,
you can see the imprint of her body on the ground.
No matter how many times they wash it, it won't come out.
So if you picked number three, you get to play hide and go seek,
and you're never found.
You're running away from us, you're like, "Hey guys, I'm gonna go hide in here,
and you guys find me."
We're like, "We're not playing that, bro."
And you go running down the hallway, dodging different aisles,
you're like, "They'll never find me here."
And you hide, shut the door behind you, and you're like,
"He he he he, they'll never find me."
But I left out one other detail.
The number one reason why men were admitted to the ridges,
the number one reason, 81 different cases of this,
of why people were admitted to the ridges mental institution,
was for excessive masturbation.
So you hide in the room, no one will ever find you.
And then the ghosts of 81 masturbating men appear around you
and say, "We found you, and you're it."
And then you can imagine what happens after that.
But we don't go looking for you, you are lost to your fate
if you picked number three.
A lot of masturbation during this episode.
Not while I'm recording it, but maybe while you're listening to it.
Let's go ahead and move on to the next asylum.
And I honestly might take one out here.
Let me take a look.
I might make you guys delete a number again.
Let's see here.
Yeah, okay, I'm gonna take one out.
Yeah, I'm taking one out.
I know I've done this before.
It's just, I'm, okay.
So, so, I can either go and rerecord everything I recorded
where I mentioned the number, or if you picked the number two,
now you can pick between one and four.
There you go, one and four.
We've said goodbye to five, we've said goodbye to three.
We hear a lot of moaning as we're leaving the ridges.
And I'm like, "Hmm, that's weird.
It kind of sounds like one of my listeners and a new one other people."
But we're getting back on the Carbentercopter.
We are headed to East Bethany, New York.
And in East Bethany, New York, we go to Rolling Hills Asylum.
This place sounds absolutely horrible.
They've done a little bit of recovery today,
but how it sounded back in the day was horrible.
Because remember how I said you had like, epileptics?
And then you had people who were just like, nuts.
And you'd be like, "Dude, I can do my taxes.
Like, I know how to pet a dog,
and I'm stuck with this guy who does his dog
and tries to pet his taxes.
But this Rolling Hills was actually even worse,
because it started off as a poor house.
So basically you went there if you were homeless,
or you were a widow, you'd end up there.
If your family was homeless, you'd end up there.
But then they're like, "You know what?
We have this great facility with all these homeless people in it.
And we got all these crazy people running around.
Let's combine them.
Let's Reese's Peanut Butter Cup these two things.
What could go wrong?"
So they took in blind people, disabled people,
alcoholics, orphans, widows, like I said,
and then just people who were crazy,
all packed into this facility.
That would have to be the worst.
If you were basically like, "Man, I lost my job.
This sucks. Oh no, I got kicked out of my apartment.
Oh no, what am I going to do?
I'm sleeping on the street.
Cop arrests me, sends me to jail,
and I wake up and people are just pooping on me
and like, clawing at my body and telling me
all of them are Jesus."
I'd be like, "This is the...
That to me would be the worst."
I would want to be crazy with them.
Think if you were crazy locked up with other crazy people,
it'd probably be more tolerable
than if you were one sane person trapped in...
And you would have to group up.
You'd have to form like a homeless league
to protect the other homeless people.
So anyways, Rolling Hills Asylum.
This one has some real ghosts.
This one has some real ghost stories.
Here's so these ones, people are known to get ectoplasm on their face,
which I think might actually be a little bit of blowback
from the ridges that's flying over state lines,
but people said they'd wake up and have ectoplasm.
Again, that's probably something else,
but they'd wake up and have ectoplasm on their face.
Sharon Coyle, she's the current owner of the Rolling Hills Asylum.
She kind of turned it into a tourist attraction
and shut down now.
There's not just a bunch of crazy people.
She's like, "Oh, don't go in Ward H.
That's still an operation.
A bunch of poor widows being like, "Help me."
They're getting dragged off by insane people.
Sharon Coyle, she's the current owner.
She has brought in paranormal investigators
and stuff like that.
They have a shadow person.
We've talked about shadow people before.
Generally, they're very tall.
They're known to be very tall.
You see a little shadow person.
You're like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
But anyways, there's a giant seven-foot-tall shadow person there,
and you're like, "Dope, I want to wrestle a shadow person.
If I pick this number, can I wrestle a shadow person?"
This isn't technically a shadow person as we know it.
This is a dude named Roy who had gigantism.
So it's actually a giant ghost,
which I don't know if--
I don't know what's more scary.
A shadow person who's known to be kind of an interdimensional being
or just a seven-foot-five ghost man who roams the halls.
And she says one day she was walking through the halls
and she saw a rat and it scared her and she ran away.
And then she came back later and the rat had its neck broken
and there was a bloody handprint on the wall.
Now, I don't believe that story.
Like, I'm sure that she saw a broken rat.
She probably saw a rat and then came back and saw another rat
with its head broken.
But again, if the ghost of Roy can do that, do the laundry, dude.
Like, if you can pick up a rat and break its neck
and then, like, leave a mark on the wall,
you could easily put on a tool belt and fix the heater down in the basement.
Like, why not?
Why are ghosts super helpful in some aspects,
but whenever she's back in her car and her parking spot is not back there,
waving her on and going, "Stop!"
A little bit more, a little left and then it vanishes
when she has the perfect parking spot.
Why not?
But you want to know what your fate is,
because you just want this episode to be over at this point.
You're on the tour, it's just me, number one and number four,
and then number two's like, "I can't believe I got left out again."
Come on, number two, pick another number.
We're all sitting there and I go, "Are you ready to know your fate?"
And you're like, "Yes, I'm ready to know my fate."
This one has so many ghosts that it is known for its ghost tours.
So I look over at you and you're like, "Oh, that's interesting. I love ghost hunting."
It has events like four to eight hour ghost tours.
So from midnight to 8 a.m., people walking through the asylum with their tape recorders,
their flashlights and their other made up devices, those things are actually real,
but I have this Kalong Nar 2000 that detects the renal gland of a ghost.
And I go in, just walking through.
It costs me $500.
They have movie nights where you can sit and watch a movie like the original Poltergeist,
and then afterwards go on an optional ghost tour, maybe you're too scared to go.
They even have painting with the spirits where a bunch of middle-aged women get together,
drink wine and draw in a supposedly haunted building.
So the scariest of all, the scariest of all on their calendar of events is July 26th to be determined.
What horrors does the universe hold on that day?
What will pierce the veil and take us onto the other side on July 26th?
It's to be determined.
So, if you picked number one, you are trapped here and every day is a ghost tour for you?
Not as a ghost, that would be cool.
No, no, no, you can never leave this building.
You walk through it every single day on the exact same ghost tour with the exact same tour guides,
telling you the exact same stories.
And they always go, "Oh, you just missed it, a ghost walked by."
It's like Groundhog's Day, but with ghosts.
And you have to spend your nights watching the original Poltergeist,
and every night is painting with the spirits night as you're surrounded by these women whose lives hold no excitement.
So they get together and paint as an excuse to drink.
And you're like, "Jason, that's ridiculous, that's not you."
Now you're just, "Oh, you don't let me finish."
But at the end of each night, just when you think maybe the next sunrise will let you leave this prison,
that's when the shadow people come, because there are stories that when you look down the long hallways of the asylum,
every so often you'll see a head peek around the corner.
Think it's a trick of the light, you've been down this hallway a hundred times, you've been trapped on this tour forever.
But you see, every single night that head pokes out, and then the tall shadow person, not Roy, not Roy, another one,
he's changing someone's brakes, gets down on all fours, and slowly begins to crawl towards you.
And like that is on top of you.
None of the other people on the tour see it, as this shadow person is tearing into you like a wild beast.
You feel that experience every single night.
You feel your own body be pulled into the shadow realm.
And then you wake up the next morning on a bench in the lobby of the Rolling Hills Asylum,
knowing not only are you going to have to experience that same thing again,
but that shadow creature running at you down the hallway is actually you.
And that's spooky for some reason.
Okay, let's go ahead. That's trippy at least, right?
Okay, let's go ahead and move on to the next one.
That was number one, did I see that was you?
If you picked number one, I don't remember.
Let's go ahead and move on to Byberry Mental Hospital.
I enjoy these. I really hope you guys too.
This one's gone a little off the rails, but I really enjoy these.
Okay, so Byberry Mental Hospital, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
This one was so bad that in 1945, some dude took a bunch of photos of what was going on in there
and released it to the public and there was this huge outcry.
And they immediately shut it down in 1987.
It took them like 40 years to shut this place down.
So the photos won, there was poop all in the hallways, which you're thinking,
"Oh, that's fine. I'm in my room. I don't have to worry about that."
But the place was so overcrowded, people slept in the hallways.
So people were sleeping in their poop.
There was an urban, oh, so the place had been torn down at this point.
The place has been completely torn down.
But we will, through the magic of time travel, we're there.
After all the poop is cleaned up and all the people are freed,
we're in the building, it's slightly derelict.
And it also had a huge underground system to get from building to building.
The people didn't want to walk in the poop, so they would go underground
and walk and pop up in another building.
You open the door and a bunch of poop falls on you.
But anyways, us remaining two people, me and you who have picked number four,
we are going to experience this ghost story in the tunnel.
Well, let's go. After you. After you, sir.
So we're walking through the tunnel and we hear a chuckle.
[laughs]
It's like, "That's weird." It's a weird laugh.
I don't know, and then our flashlights die.
[imitates explosion]
Now we're standing in the darkness, just me and you.
The musty dark darkness underneath this former insane asylum.
And that's when we smell something.
You smell that? You go, "Is that the smell of 81 people masturbating?"
And I'm like, "No, no, no, no. I know that smell."
This smells like rotten flesh.
And then right when I make that realization, both of us get pushed from behind.
And both of us hit our heads on several walls and we're knocked unconscious.
And then the next day, some other urban explorers, part of our crew, the Urbex crew,
kick down the door and they're like, "We gotta save them."
Actually, they just stumble across us. We're both laying there unconscious.
Urban explorers wake us up. They go, "Hey, you okay?"
And we're like, "Yes!"
Even though we were knocked unconscious for 24 hours in the dark
and haven't suffered any real brain damage, we are fine.
And then they're like, "Oh my God, look at you."
And we look down, both of us, and we have huge cuts across our skin.
Like we were attacked by some sort of wild animal.
We're like, "Ahhh!"
We're both taken to the hospital. Hopefully you have insurance, I do.
And they treat us and we get hundreds of stitches each.
So about, let's say, 250 stitches between the both of us.
Wait, would that be enough?
You had hundreds, that would mean you would have to have 200 or more.
So we got 500 stitches total. We're the stitch bros now.
That's how we're known. Me in number four.
And we're also briefly hospitalized for our head wounds,
because we were knocked unconscious for 24 hours.
Now, if that story is true, it's quite skeptical it is.
It actually makes a lot of sense. You walk through a tunnel.
You walk through an abandoned tunnel. You get knocked from behind.
You do get knocked unconscious, that's possible.
And the deep gashes on you was any number of wild animals,
raccoons, or rabbit hobos that stumbled across you
over the course while you were unconscious.
Which definitely, a reason why that could be fake.
It could also be fake, because that was one of the ghost stories from Backpackerverse.
When I looked into this hospital, most of the stuff on Bibery Mental Hospital
was about how horrible it was.
Not a lot of ghost stories coming from it.
So I really had to reach out for that one.
But, I mean, who wants to talk about ghosts when you have like that level of human suffering?
So you're thinking, "Number four, man, I got it good.
I just got a couple hundred stitches. They will call me,
I'm a stitch brother now with Dead Rabbit Radio. That's cool, right?"
But, no, no, no, no, no.
Because you see, we are stitch brothers now, you and I.
We went through this horrible experience together,
and I just can't let it go.
So one night while you're sleeping in your bed,
you're all alone sleeping in your bed.
You got those horrible memories of that mysterious ghost assault behind you.
I sneak into your room with a giant, giant needle
and a giant like roll ball of yarn,
and I go, "Stitch brother! We're gonna be stitched together forever."
And as you wake up as the needle goes into your side,
you realize that I'm connecting our bodies with unbreakable titanium string
that I called yarn earlier, sewing us together.
We'll never be separated now.
True stitch brothers till the end.
And as you're howling in pain, not just from the needle penetrating your skin,
but you also know that I often rewatch transformer movies,
and you're now gonna be stuck watching those things with me.
You realize that number four was the cursed number.
The other people may have died or become trapped,
but you will live forever as just a part of Dead Rabbit.
[music]
Dead...
[coyote howl]
Dead Rabbit Radio at email.com is gonna be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great weekend guys. Thank you so much.
[music]