Hey guys, huge news just came up. So as I'm getting ready to record
The episode today Wednesday's episode really I get a Facebook message from Beatrice Leiva Beatrice Leiva
I think that's how you pronounce it. I'm not for sure and I'm sorry if I mispronounce it like I mispronounce everything
But I get this message this huge news
Beatrice, thank you so much forest fins treasure has been found forest fins treasure has been found now
Today's episode and tomorrow's episode they were pre-recorded a lot of times I do that over the weekend
Just save myself some time and some headache
So in an upcoming episode we are fully going to look into the fact that I was wrong. I was wrong
I will always admit I was wrong. I said forest fin didn't have a treasure. I said the whole thing
Apparently forest fins treasure has been found. So this is a little update to that. We'll get into it later in the week
Thank you so much Beatrice for bringing this to my attention. We'll get into this
Listen to today's episode, but we'll talk about this on Wednesday episode
We're gonna talk about forest fins treasure being found enjoy today's episode and thanks Beatrice
Is it possible that you are the only person on the internet and then we take a look at a truly terrifying
alien encounter
What happened on the ride home today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
*Music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys had a great weekend
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna hop right into it first off
I want to give a shout out to our newest at your own supporter Paul Martinez
Paul Martinez you are going to be our pilot our
Shofur you're gonna be our bodyguard for this episode. We really really appreciate it that you're supporting the show
If you can't support the show via patreon, that's okay too. Just help get the word out about the show that helps a ton
Also, we have a merch store. I always neglect to talk about the merch store
So if you can't support the patreon, but you do have some extra money you want some cool Dead Rabbit swag
Check out the merch store in the links below. I never mentioned it. It's been around for a while
Let's go ahead and get started here
Paul we are gonna start off
Let's hop in we're gonna get into Jason Jalopy, but it's digitized
It's like that Tron machine
shoots it and makes it we should have been in the car while I was doing this we have to run we jump into the beam
We get digitized now Paul we're driving through the cyber freeways at the time
This is what's they called information super highway. Was that the old term? What?
cyberspace you guys are like how old are you Jason?
Yeah, I know there's like surfing the web, but wasn't there an old term like I think it was information super highway
You're like shaking your head. You're like no, it's not anyways. We're driving our car. It's total like lawnmower man graphics
Everything's all blocky. I will control you
Or I'm your god. Whatever he says. I don't even know the reference
Paul's driving our digitized Jason Jalopy through this 3d 1990s level computer graphic landscape
So Paul keep going down the super information highway see that super information off ramp
You we stop at a super information Denny's and eat some digitized food, but we notice something we notice something
There's not a lot of people in this digitized Denny's maybe because they have better taste in food
But no that can't be it Denny's is delicious as we're drinking a car off of digitized wine
It's just ones and zeros, but it looks so good. There's a conspiracy theory going around this is straight from the conspiracy theory iceberg
It's no one as empty internet
And the conspiracy theory is what it sounds like basically there's far less people on the internet
Than you would believe it doesn't sound super compelling at first glance
But something about it makes you a little suspicious, right?
Something about it makes you a little suspicious because the thing with the internet is it gives you the illusion of communicating with other people
But you can never really prove anyone else is there
You have the sneaking suspicion now when we're back in the real world when we're not digitized
And we're on the bus or walking downtown or at school. We see everyone on their phone
So you go they must be on the internet the internet must be full of people everyone uses the internet
I use the internet. I go to the internet. It seems populated, but in the back of your mind you think
Maybe that's not the case
Now I could go over a ton of statistics now when saying that that means that I did research
And I have a ton of statistics how many people actually use the internet
And how many people upload videos to youtube every hour stuff like that those those are pretty common statistics
I'm not gonna bore you with those
But there's two
Items that we really want to look at here two items that may make the empty internet conspiracy theory
Actually true paul pay pay my digitized bill, but you have to pay with real money. We're leaving denies now
We're gonna take a look at this conspiracy known as the empty internet. Also. I want to give a shout out real quick
There was a twitter user known as some weirdo on twitter aka jack
Jack actually listened to all the episodes of the show and went through the conspiracy theory iceberg
Created an excel spreadsheet of all of the topics i've covered so far
All the topics you have to be covered that was a huge amount of work. I really really appreciated it
something that I have wanted to do or have done
by someone else
And he took it upon himself and asked him to do it. That's absolutely amazing. I wanted to thank you so much for that
I know it took a ton of work if you look in the show notes from now on it'll say archivist
Some weirdo on twitter aka jack because I really appreciate it. I know that took a lot of work
So I appreciate that
As our official archivist there's a little digitized jack waving at us also
Oddly enough a year ago a different listener named jack actually wanted me to cover empty internet theory
And the reason why I waited so long is because it's one of those things like I said
It kind of you kind of feel that it's true, but it's kind of a feeling
There's recently come to my attention some evidence that may make this theory a little more than just another
series of words on the conspiracy theory iceberg
Something that I noticed recently and I found this very fascinating is that
twitter gets 145 million visitors daily
This is where we get our statistics out. So sorry guys, but this is important
According to the pew research center 10 percent of twitter users make 80 percent of the posts and I remember when that came out
and twitter is
Super oh, they really it's oversized importance in today's society if something goes trending
Companies will cut sponsorship deals
Something goes trending
policies can change in the government
But 10 percent of the users on twitter create 80 percent of the tweets. There's 145 million visitors daily on twitter
So let's break that down 10 percent. That's 14 million people and every day. There's 500 million tweets
That means those 14 million people. They're tweeting 35 tweets a day simply that number
14 million people putting out 35 tweets a day can reshape
business and government
14 million people a day that that would be an incredibly small country. That would be a large
massive city
But a small country is able to affect the policies
Of the government and of corporations. So right there
You have this site you think of twitter as being
The marketplace of ideas you have it where people go and just kind of say what's on their mind
That was kind of how it was set up
But that's not how it is now 10 of the people 14 million people
Can affect massive change and again sometimes it's just a company going
We we don't we don't want to be involved in this controversy. We're out
So that in a sense creates this idea of an empty internet
It seems like it's this bustling thing when you look at it
But most of those are coming from 14 million people
So it's not at twitter is not as massive as we think it is a lot of people start twitter accounts
Never use them. They never read them. They may check it because they get a message sometimes. I had a twitter account for years
Never used it at all. I didn't start using it until I started doing this show
So it's empty
It's a bunch of people talking to each other and then talking to one person all of a sudden they go from having
No interaction to 10 interactions and they go whoa, whoa, I better do I better change something
Because if these 10 people hit me up when the rest of them are coming
So that kind of gives you a sense of how we see the empty but that's not really what we mean by empty internet. Is it
empty internet is more of a
idea that
There's no one else not even 14 million people
Putting stuff out on twitter. It's just you. It's just you. You're the only person
The truth lies somewhere in between just you you're the only person using the internet and then a small group of people
Controlling one of the biggest mouthpieces on the internet the empty internet
Kind of floats somewhere in the middle there because I know I'm on the internet. I know other people on the internet
You can't just say there's one person but is there something in the middle there?
Is there something is the truth closer to the middle? Let's take a look at this
There's a subreddit. No one is shills and this is their mission statement
Exposing corporate and government shills on social media. So they're basically going out and looking for
things being socially
blown up
by
astroturf campaigns
shoe company wants to make a statement they create
Fake accounts to make it look like their new shoe is going to be totally awesome. That's what this group does. That's what the subreddit goes
There's a username for friend dongles for friend dongles
And for friend dongles did a little investigation into this
So he created a reddit post and it was called what I've learned fishing for shill ip's and this was written two years ago
He wanted to track down
Some shills he wanted to track them back to their corporate overlords to just expose them see
You know, it's basically a thought exercise. Maybe maybe he could expose some stuff
He said that what happens is these guys tend to have this thing the service called amazon aws
It's like a server farm as he described it
So even if you can track it back to there it allows someone to use one mobile device to access tons of accounts
So you can track it to the server farm, but you're never going to find out the actual ip of who owns it
That's fairly normal. That's fairly normal. And what he did was he created a post
That said this is your face
I had a little link to just a random youtube video
So you'd click on it now when you click the link it'll allow him to track your ip
Take you to a certain website to allow you to track your ip
But he figured it's just going to go to amazon aws. I just want to see if there are any patterns
So let's take a look at one of these statements he made quote
So I noticed that when I was wrong and contacted a real person as opposed to a show as opposed to a show
So I noticed that when I was wrong and had contacted a real person
It took them a humanish amount of time to click the link
Maybe five ten minutes when you send the link to a shill though the response is immediate
I'm talking like in the time it takes you to hit send on the bait message and click over to refresh the ip logger page
They had already clicked that happens every single time
Think about what that means for a bit. So he says that he thought it was weird. He's sending it to these people and sometimes
They would sit in their inbox
Sometimes it'd be immediate. He'd go to the refresh page. See that they clicked it
He goes maybe it's a glitch with
How I have this set up so he started sending them to his friends and says hey, I'm doing this ip logger thing
He sent some to his own dummy accounts
And sure enough it would take the the buddy to go open up the document click the link
Show up in his ip logger when he'd do it. He would go over to his account click the link
Check there would be a period of time where he had to log out of one thing go to the other thing
Click the link, but there were accounts he would send it to and it would immediately get clicked
So it made you start to think who's clicking these so quickly
It's not a web crawler
Someone is clicking this link on a heartbeat and he realizes
That his idea that you had companies hiring these shills hiring these people to hype their products or to downplay other stuff
He wasn't finding shills. He was finding an ai
So you go okay links are automatically getting clicked, but that's not all that was going on take a look at this
Here's another quote to test it. I sent a few shills messages that said the link in the body of this message will give me your ip
On the assumption that a piece of their code is check links for context or something
They still clicked with the same speed
And
Responded differently each time with things like you don't have my ip you little bitch or nice try shill
Things like that seemingly baiting me into an organic seeming conversation
You would not believe how often this happens
We're talking major threads the top three posters each of them shills or at least the people who will click on a fishing link
When you tell them to entire mod teams
All of whom responded but one individual who said what the f?
And that was it
I cannot come up with a theory that takes into account all of those factors
Other than to say that I think a good portion of shills are not real people
And that you find shills at the top of many many of the threads that make it to the front page of reddit
He's talking about
Maybe they have real people that take over when a conversation can't be completed by script. I don't know
But the fact remains you can tell a shill that a link will collect their ip and they will still click it
After making this post
His account was banned
This is what we are talking about when we're talking about empty internet
Did for friend dongles actually uncover this because it's not just that these links are getting clicked these are people
Who he was having interactions with the top three posters of threads that were some of the biggest threads on reddit
Is there an ai that has been developed by a company or multiple companies?
That simulates human conversation
Shills to promote a product to de-ongrade another product to push an agenda to hold back another agenda
All of these competing ai's fighting for space
And we're just going on checking our bank account laughing at memes
Reading the news and all around us the internet seems like it's bustling with activity when in fact
It's fake
like a movie set
It looks real, but when you get close and you dig into it, it's artificial sounds paranoid
Sounds crazy, but you never really know who you're talking to
But you always do assume you're talking to a human. Can you be sure?
Let's go ahead and let's go ahead and leave this digitized world. You see digitized tumbleweed
Starting to glitch out paul get the jason jalabi going. He's cranking it super hard
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
We get in it the world starts to de-digitize faster faster
Show notes
You can probably dig more into that. He actually says this is the program I use. Here's the links I use try it for yourself. It's super super spooky
But you can do it. So
Thank you jack for creating that conspiracy theory excel document
Thank you other jack for recommending the story and paul
Let's go ahead and hop in that carbonar copter. We are headed out to new york
We're flying over the night sky rig. We're specifically going to
Mow Hall Poc that's in puttnam county in new york. It's august 15th
Helicopters flying through the dark night sky. It's 2 a.m. Helicopters flying through the dark morning sky
I got this off a think about it dox.com one of my favorite websites for this type of stuff
And it was reported by an author named phil
in brogno
So thank you phil for doing the ground research and thank you again think about it dox.com is such a great website
carbonar copters flying low
Do is like landing on the propellers and it's like flying away and stuff like that
There's a nameless couple driving out of the road. So let's give them names. We're going to call them pete and karen
Yeah
Cars driving down the dark road at night. Damnit dark road in the morning and they see a brush fire
Out in the field. What was the guy's name again? Peter Peter?
Jason okay, so peter if that's if that's your real name peter's driving the car karen's in the passenger seat
Yeah, they see the fire
Burning and peter wants to pull over and take a look at the fire now karen's like no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Burning and peter wants to pull over and take a look at the fire now karen's like no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
And they take a little turn off and they're driving towards the fire and at that point
Parks the car and it just does seem to be a little brush fires. Peter gets out of the car
He's walking towards it. It's cold august morning and he sees lights coming up the road behind him
He goes oh somebody must have contacted the authorities. This will be great. Maybe I'll just stop and talk to him go
Hey, yeah, make sure they don't think that I actually started the fire
And he sees the lights get close and they kind of come to a stop and he sees two officers get out of the car
And he's like, oh, okay
Yeah, all's well that ends well. I'm gonna take my girlfriend home and then he goes those aren't cops
Those are kids
Because this he get closer and he's starting to see the silhouettes get a little more defined
He notices they're under five feet tall
Children
And the two figures are starting to walk slowly towards him and panic sets in because at that point peter realizes
They're not children. They are what we expect because we're listening to dead rabbit radio two gray aliens
They do have a bit of a different feature. He said the eyeball they have the big large head
long skinny arms
giant black eyes, but he said the eyes were
Wrapping around the side of the head like an insects eyeballs
So a little more of a sleek design than your average gray alien
He doesn't have time to take in the craftsmanship
Of these aliens the aerodynamic nature of their head
He runs back to the car. He wasn't far to begin with but
Any any distance from your car is a mile when there's two gray aliens approaching you at 2 a.m
In the middle of nowhere
He he realizes in his soul that all they want is his girlfriend
It's all they want
He realizes that all they want is his girlfriend
So he tells karen get in the back seat lay on the ground
Throw that blanket over you and don't move
She doesn't know what's going on. He doesn't take the time to explain
He's not like they're kind of like gray aliens, but different eyes. He just go get in the back seat
They're coming for you
She crawls into the back seat and throws a blanket over her and now he's sitting
In the car his girlfriend
Hiding and there's an alien on each side of the car now
He turns his head and he's looking out the window
little fire
Illuminating
the landscape
He said the aliens looked like they didn't know how to get in the car
They they were trying to figure out how to get in the car and he knows
That he's really not in danger. They are there
For his girlfriend. He said the aliens were doing this motion like they were waving their hand over the window
expecting it to just go
They're going to be able to get in
He goes the aliens were standing there and they were like waving their hand
And they were doing it again and they were waiting for the window to simply roll down or recede or disappear
That's not how that works at least here on earth
And then he hears a voice in his head
Open the door
And of course, that's the last thing he wants to do. He knows they don't know how to get into the car
He's not going to
He knows the danger
And he's just sitting there and the aliens are waiting outside in the darkness
He then gets a second message in his head
And an image as well at the same time
He gets an image of his door locks
And they're open
And he hears a voice in his head go
The door is unlocked
Hit the switch
Lock it
You will be safe
He looks over at the doors. They're locked
The doors are unlocked. You are in danger
Hit the switch and lock them. Hit the switch and lock them now before they get inside
And he sees in his mind the switch popped up
But when he looks at the door the switch is locked
You're in danger
The car is on fire
Peter
The car is on fire and he needs to get out right now
And in his head
He sees a flame
Begin to creep through the car
Peter the car is on fire. You need to get out right now
The car is burning
He has an image in his head
A flames consuming the car
Peter get out. The car is on fire
Peter starts to get lightheaded
The next thing he knows he's standing outside of his car
His girlfriend is gone
He is all alone in a field illuminated only by a small fire. The next thing he knows
The sun is up. He's driving home
His girlfriend is in the backseat
That might be one of the most terrifying alien stories that we've talked about on this show
We've talked about a lot of good ones, but this one shows the true scope
Of a gray alien's power
The true mental might of one of these creatures
I talk a lot of trash about how you can wreck these things physically. You can just totally annihilate them
But this is truly alien, right? This is this has nothing to do with physical strength
Total manipulation of really reality at that point, right?
First just giving him a simple order to open the door. We've seen UFO abductees simply do what the aliens say
When that doesn't work
Trying to trick him
The door is already unlocked. You have to hit the button. You have to lock it and he fought that
And then the fear of fire. It's one of the few innate fears that humans have
And then the two time jumps is also very terrifying
The one time jump where he's out of the car and his girlfriend is gone and then a second time jump where he's driving down the road
Now as far as I know the story has never been followed up. We this story obviously could be fake
But the story's never been followed up. We don't know if any of the
This is a case if this was me. I would 100 go to a hypnotherapist to try to get some
Try to get some clarity on this
Maybe maybe right it's quite terrifying, but it shows that level of power that these beings can have
I don't think I've ever come across that story where
We have that sort of mental combat between a human and an alien and really the alien winning
Absolutely terrifying story
To be honest, it's such a
Mind-bending story
I'm at a loss of words
How do you fight something that powerful?
Maybe you can't
I think your only hope is that they wipe all your memories
They're obviously capable of deleting
Certain pieces of memories. So why would they allow peter to remember the event at all?
Maybe they wanted him to remember the sheer panic
As he saw the figures walk up to his car
Maybe they wanted him to remember the fear
That enveloped him as he stood out in that dark field
The car empty
His girlfriend gone
Maybe they wanted him to be filled with terror
So he would tell the message of their power
So that all humans would know no matter what we do no matter what we think
They
Can make us
Open the door
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio
Twitter is @deadrabberradio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy truth-fram podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]