Is your dog spying on you?
Why British men suddenly can't have erections and we take a deep dive into the murky world of giant fish today on Dead Rava Radio.
Hey everyone, it's Jason Carpenter back again for another episode of Dead Rava Radio.
Hope you guys are having a good day. Still fighting this stupid sinus infection.
But you know what are you gonna do? I got some medicine and I'm gonna record this and edit it and get it out for you guys.
And then I'm gonna go to bed. I got a long week ahead, but I wanted to get this done. I like doing this show.
Hope everyone's having a good time. I know I always say that, but it's sincere.
So,
went to the fireworks yesterday watching the fireworks on 4th of July.
And you know what's always interesting to me is
subcultures.
Subcultures I find interesting and especially when they're based around some sort of job. So,
I'm watching the fireworks and I turn to a friend of mine and I go,
"How do they practice for this?" Like there must be some place out in the middle of the desert where like,
they shoot off fireworks to test them out and to make sure the arrangements look good and things like that.
But it's and which is probably true. I didn't bother researching it yet.
But and then I thought, you know what throughout the year,
you have those scenarios where it's like the young guy who wants to get into the firework business or,
you know, he shows up there. Maybe he doesn't have any other career prospects and he shows up to the fireworks
launching pad and there's like the old gruff guys like, "This is a business for kings.
This is a business that was handed down from the
Chinese to us." And you have those weird
economies. You have those weird like the young guys trying to break into the business and the people have been doing it for the longest time.
You have the people who to them it's just a job
and it's something they do to pay the bills and then you have people who like have great pride in the fact that
they're one of a long line of firework artists. I'm sure there's an actual name they use like a pyrotechnician
or something like that.
But I always think that's fascinating that you'll have these little subcultures that if I went and talked to them and said,
"Hey, so how do fireworks work?" They'll give me like a brief overview, but when they're talking to each other, they're gonna use all this slang and jargon and
maybe they go all to the same bar and it's called like the pop-off or something like that or Rockets Red.
It's the name of the bar they all go to and they're, you know, shooting back whiskey and talking about, "Oh, yeah,
I lost these two fingers in the fireworks show of 77 and all that stuff."
But yeah, I mean, I'm sure that there are
big test sites for fireworks and it's funny talking about the subculture of the people who set them off.
You know that there's the people who designed them and the people who,
you know, not only designed them, but like
advancing the technology forward. The people who manufacture the fireworks we have now and then there's like people in a laboratory
going like, "How can we make fireworks 44% more efficient the last longer?"
So on and so forth. I saw an article that some
places are using lit lighted-up drones instead of fireworks and you know, I can kind of see the allure of that.
There's no, you know, fire threat, but I don't know. I'm not a huge fireworks guy, but I do like, I do like
catching them. I really don't go out on my way to watch fireworks. Anyways,
so today's a weird episode because actually all the stories kind of have something in common and that's bones
and really I'm like forcing it to be in common. They don't have a lot in common.
First thing I wanted to talk about and this is actually like if you know me in real life, if you had a conversation with me for more than
10 minutes in real life and trust me, I'm a real person. This this isn't an act.
I've been quoting this article. It's been out for probably a couple weeks now, but I just find it so fascinating and what's fascinating too is I
don't think the article gets the main
issue right.
So they did, this is from the Mirror in Britain. This is their
newsletter, not newsletter magazine
newspaper. The headline is
"Men in their 30s hit by impotence epidemic is half
suffer from erectile dysfunction." Of course, this is a study and they, you know,
study 2,000 men.
They have to extrapolate it out, but half of men under 30s have impotence issues. That is mind-boggling.
I talked before on a previous episode about how as I got older and I was taking a bunch of nicotine, using a bunch of nicotine,
it was causing blood pressure issues with me.
But to be
in their 30s and not being a chemical thing,
that's just alarming. That's a, you know, it's a blow to a man's self-esteem and
it's a blow to them being able to have a steady relationship because women are gonna have a hard time
being sexually satisfied if you can't get it up. It's just the truth.
So
they asked them, obviously, the follow-up question was, "Why do you think you have impotence?"
And 49% of them said stress and then 24% of them said, you know, too much drinking and then there's some other reasons in there as well.
But I don't think either of those are really the issue. I mean, obviously, that's what they're saying.
So they said nearly half,
four in 10 minutes said it was stress and then 36% was anxiety.
Or no, 29% of it was anxiety and 26% of it was boozing.
I think it's pornography.
Now there have been studies done as well. I'm gonna link all of this in the show notes, but there have been many studies done
showing that pornography
can lead to impotence in men.
There's actually a term for it. It's P I E D, not pied. Well, it is pied, but it's porn induced erectile dysfunction.
And what it is is that when you start off,
you basically train your brain
and your body
to react to pornography.
I'm looking at a video of a hot woman and I'm masturbating to it.
And I'm creating this feedback loop. The dopamine rush is, you know, amazing whenever you have an orgasm, masturbation or not.
But what happens is when you start watching pornography and then you end up watching too much of it, you end up overusing it.
It becomes a crutch. And we do have young men say then when they go to be with a woman or a man, whatever,
but when they go to be with somebody,
it,
they can't get it up.
Now when you're watching pornography, I can click through, I can have 12 videos on my screen and I can pick which one
that I want to watch and I can find a great one and watch it for two weeks.
But then eventually the novelty wears off. I have to find another one. It taps into our
our caveman brain every time I'm watching
pornography. I'm basically finding a new mate and I'm spreading my seed. I'm doing all of these tricks.
But when you're with somebody real and they're,
it's not, they're not as sexy and you see the, you know, the blemish under their left armpit and they have a, you know,
now they smell and stuff like that.
And they're not a perfect 10 that you can't just skip past to the good stuff. You have difficulty. I actually
don't watch porn anymore. And it's not because of that.
I just am not a fan of it. Now obviously when I was in my, when I was growing up, yeah, it was great.
It was this whole new thing. But you get to a point and for one, listen, man,
I don't want to watch another dude being in a check. Like if some, if there's sex going on, I want to be the one involved.
Is you get old? I don't know if it's just me, but I kind of had that realization. I'm like, well, I'm not watching this other dude
being this chick.
Like that, it's, that's not fulfilling to me anymore. I think maybe it was the novelty of it at first and you're seeing all these beautiful women, but
you know what I mean? I wouldn't want to watch it in real life.
Like someone's like, hey man, come over to my house and watch me being my wife. I'd be like, dude, that,
no dude, you invite me over to your house and I'll bang your wife and you can watch. Or we can bang her together.
But I'm not going to come over and watch you bang your wife, dude. That's weird.
So, and that's really what pornography is. It's you're just watching an act, but you're, you're chemically your brain thinks you're there.
So that's a little bit of a
public service message. Guys, if you're listening to this, stop watching porn.
Stop, masturbation, fine. Use your imagination.
Read a book if you have to and imagine that. However, don't watch porn. It's going to mess you up if it hasn't already.
You got to get out of it.
So it can cause a lot of addiction issues and it can cause physical and mental issues when you need it the most.
You don't want to get with the girl of your dreams or any girl for that matter and not be able to get it up.
It's super disappointing to you.
It's super disappointing to her and it actually makes her feel bad.
So stop watching porn.
But I'm going to go ahead and link both of those articles and
there's actually
some science articles on the P I E D stuff and then you'll have the other article for the British thing.
There's books out there like
Your Brain on Porn and stuff like that. You can do further research on that. Now
going from boners
to things with no bones
and I don't know if maybe they do have bones. I don't know. Invertebrates. Do invertebrates have bones?
I know they don't have spines, but I'm do they have like skulls?
Because that's a bone or teeth is a bone really anyways. Anyway, so the segue doesn't make sense.
But so I was always told like I watched them a lot when I was a kid or any movie with a giant animal giant insect and people go
You know insects can't animals can't get that big
You know why not?
And they're like well because they breathe through their like an ant breathes through its skin
And if it got giant it wouldn't be able to breathe or something like that somebody told me that
when I was a kid
And so they kind of you know took the fun out. Was it them? It wasn't them with the giant ants
So I was always told that you know animals have kind of like a fixed size in their genetic code
That's not true
That's not true animals
Can really get as big as possible
In the right conditions now. I'm going to put a little asterisk next to that
It's just kind of invertebrates
So you can't put a puppy in this environment and it's going to be like this giant like
Falkor size dog
but
It's called deep sea gigantism or abyssal gigantism and basically don't know what causes it
But in areas that are super cold
Things get bigger
So greater pressure on top of them
And a really really low temperature can cause normal like a squid can become a giant squid down there
A sea spider can become a giant sea spider at the right levels and it's the same sea spider
But what happens is I mean it's kind of like a breakaway species
But what happens is it gets I read the article of like once so I could be off in this but
I read it twice
But anyways the point is is that if you go down a certain depths you live longer because it's colder and maybe it like slows
In heartbeat, I don't know but anyways like the longer you live
The more food you can eat and the more food you can eat the bigger you get so imagine them like
Uh
Like the fat people version of other animals like
On up in the coastline you have like just the normal sea spider and he's like hanging out and then like if you dropped
1200 feet you can meet his cousin who's just like oh, dude. That's my cousin down there
And they're like why is he so big and you're like, well, he he's been alive like
Five times longer than anyone else in my family. So he's eaten like a ton more
I just think that's interesting. So I'm wondering if you went to
Certain parts of the world like if you went to Antarctica and started like finding like went under in the ice caves
I wonder if there's like giant
Giant monsters down there. I guess this kind of thing. I mean, I don't expect you to be able to crawl into a cave in Antarctica and find
The giant penguin
That's a little ridiculous, but I mean
What if you went far enough down and there was a
You might be able to find a giant penguin
I wonder how penguins do get pretty big
But like if it was in the water and its heartbeat was slowed down and it's just like oh, you know what?
I'm gonna live to be 100 years old
But hey, yeah, wait a second. How come redwoods can get so big if there's a limit to how big stuff can get on land
Could you technically have?
Giant land animals, I guess you had dinosaurs. So I'm gonna say yes
I'm gonna say yes
I'm gonna say the only reason why we have the invertebrate
Keyword on these things is because they're mostly underwater
These things get pretty big and they have pictures. I'm gonna link this wikipedia article and we're gonna go ahead and move on
To our last story because my entire face is swelling up from sinus pain. It's gonna be a short episode
So
Every so often of course you read something online
You're like that guy's crazy and that happens all the time
But sometimes you read something online and you go not only is that guy crazy, but that guy's dangerous
That happens sometimes so I found a guy today
And this is what he posted
There's a picture of a little puppy
Don't know. I'm not gonna nothing bad happens to the dog
But there's a picture of a puppy
And he writes i'm pretty sure my new puppy is a synth assigned to watch me. He watches all the time
So a synth is an artificial life form
Now there's people who believe that they're being gang stalked or the government's
Spying on them. That's where a lot of the ideas of the tinfoil hat came from back in the 70s and the 80s
The government satellites flying overhead can't read your thoughts if you have the tinfoil hat on that's evolved to modern times
Where it's not necessarily spy satellites
There's a group of dedicated people following you around so when you're walking on the street the mailman spying on you
You always see the same guy on the same bicycle right by around the same time of the day
Sure, it could be the time he gets off work and he's coming home
But to these people that guy's a cia agent or working for deep state or whatever spying on him
And this is a very it's a very egotistical paranoid belief and and it's again
It's interesting because when I was talking about the transabled people, I think that was an episode 10
This is another gang stalking is something that was it's a
Like a precursor or a side effect to schizophrenia or other
Uh mental issues and it was very very very rare
For the longest time but since the internet since the explosion of the internet and other people are reading about these things
It's blown up. There's now gang stalking support groups and and I kind of want to do a whole
I think I've thought about doing a whole episode on gang stalking
But I almost feel like it's going to be something that comes up
Fairly regularly because it's a key component into a lot of conspiracy theories
It's fascinating and um, there's actually one
gang stalking
Hey, let me let me talk about this dog real quick
Before I go off and I'll just say this so well gang stalking will be something we talk about in the future
I'm going to make a note and I know also. Yeah, so okay
So this guy believes that his new puppy is a synth sent to him watch him now to who he hasn't stated yet
I'm still monitoring this thread and unfortunately on this website the threads disappear fairly regularly
So I can't really link you to it. You'll have to take my advice for it, but
You have to take my word for it. I guess I should say but anyway
So someone also says so do you so you have a cyborg dog? So what and they're kind of like toying with him
And he goes I don't think he's a cyborg. I think he's a synth with all reconstituted or cloned the live
Parts genetically modified to do the bidding of a computer without the actual computer parts. That's what a synth is
Looks perfectly normal, but I know and sometimes his skin looks fake
So he got this dog and he thinks that it's fake
And he said that the dog has some sort of mind control
Ability that's preventing him from getting rid of the dog
Someone then respore someone responds in the in the thread here
You're going to be tempted to kill the dog, but remember don't kill the dog let the dog live
And so he this person is trying to basically talk this man who's having a psychotic breakdown
Not to do anything to hurt the dog and a bunch of other people jumped on as well
And they said the dog you're you're you're that's not true. The dog's fine. The dog's fine go out and play with your dog
Your dog's a puppy wants to play with you and such and such now
Unfortunately this well, this is for a chance. So it's an anonymous board. Nobody knows
Who who's post seeing this?
And so, you know, it's not like we can track this person down now the person does say I'm I would never kill the dog like that's not
That's not what I'm thinking and the reasoning why is because if he hurts the dog then all the other synths
all the other clones will come after him
so
Fair enough no one wants to see the puppy get hurt and if it takes that delusion like oh, I better not hurt that dog
Otherwise the army of clones will come after me. Hopefully he'll just get rid of the dog. These are the you know, this this person is
You know a renter or a homeowner
most likely have a job
Talk to him drink coffee next to him pass him on the street
It's weird to think that you know, there's a lot of people there are there are people out there who suffer from depression and
anxiety and things like that and those are kind of you know, we just understand that those are
fairly common problems in a modern society
And then you know, you meet people or you hear about people like this
Which is a full psychotic break to look at a dog and think that dog's spying on me
And the reason why I can't say stop spying on me does it's controlling my mind
And the question is is what's the solution to this?
How would you deal with this in a
How would you deal with this on a personal level?
If a friend of mine told me I think my dog spying on me
After I got done chuckling and going wait, you're serious and they go. Yeah, I think my dog is made up of other parts cloned parts
And I think it's spying on me and I my first inclination is like this other person
Well, you're not going to hurt it right and they go no no no
I'm not going to hurt it because then all the other clones will come after me
I'm just you know keeping and I think it's just kind of observing me. It's not going to hurt me
It just wants to know what what I'm doing
How do you deal with that?
I mean you could get the authorities involved
You know, you could I you know, you could say well, you know, why don't I look after the puppy?
I'll quote unquote run some tests and then just they could take the dog
But yeah, it's interesting because I think
There's these people someone with this level of delusion has felt it fairly rare. But if you you start talking to people you'll mean people have
weird thoughts
Like that maybe not this bad maybe not this bad, but
Well, I'm sure the puppy's going to be okay. I'm not really worried about it. I'm more worried about him as a human
Um, because you know, I don't think you'd hurt the puppy again
The if the delusion is he'll be attacked by clones if he hurts the puppy
That's a good crazy delusion because we don't want him hurt the puppy, but at the same time. I hope this guy gets help
I've noticed sometimes when I record these episodes
People come from certain websites to listen to them and stuff like 4chan in particular
When I was doing those episodes on
The rapper who an x the rapper x
xxx tentation. I think it's how you say it
The conspiracy theorists would come to watch the videos and things like that
So maybe this young man will watch this video and or listen to this podcast and say, you know what? Yeah, maybe I should go get some help
But you know, then again, there's always the chance that he'll just the fact that we're recording this podcast about something
He posted is just that gangstalking is real he may
He may think that because how do how could I've written this and
Two hours later it's being recorded on podcasts. I'll tell you why because I don't have a life
and I troll
Um, the paranormal board. Well, I hope you had a great night tonight. Um, again, we're just cutting it
We're just making a short episode because I want to make sure I do this every single day
If I miss an episode I want it to be because I absolutely can't record something
I want this to just be my practice. This was episode 21. So we're still going strong. I hope you're having a great time
Let's go through this again. Uh, dead rabbit dot com
If you want to email me a dead rabbit radio at gmail.com
You want to email me about ghost stories conspiracy stories anything like that that'd be great
If you want to use a different name, just let me know everyone I've talked about that I've
Said I know this person. I know that person. They're all fake names. They're real people but fake names
So I usually use fake names anyways
Twitter handle is @jasonocarpenter if you want to get ahold of me there
I am going to go and
Drink some ambasol. I'm not going to do that. I actually found out you can
Die from ambasol or ambasol whatever you call it
Stuff for a toothache
You can die from an overdose and I've been like oh man, but I think it's like I think you have to take a ton of it
I think it has to be like a tall like you have to cover your body in it because I remember just eating this stuff when I was a kid
You know my sinus infection gave me a toothache that that sucks. I got a whole thing going on
but I got a doctor's appointment tomorrow, so
I should be up and running again friday and be healthy and then we're just going to keep going
So I hope you guys had a great night. I had a great night as well despite the pain and the stuffiness
I will see you again tomorrow and we will do the story how to create a conspiracy which I've been wanting to do but it takes
A little more patience on my part and a little more talking and I just haven't had had it in me to do that
So we're going to do that at friday
I hope and then the steven king killed john lennon. We're going to retouch on that because i'm reading that book
Have a great day guys. Thank you so much for listening to the podcast
It means a lot to me and I see your downloads and
It's great. So have a great day guys
[Music]
[MUSIC]