Are YouTubers really ordering mystery boxes off the deep web?
And was this very podcast responsible for the shutdown of the Sunspot Solar Observatory
today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
There is a beautiful rainbow right outside my window.
Absolutely beautiful.
It's even darker than it was just a couple minutes ago.
It's amazing looking.
Still kind of drizzling outside.
You know, I think it's interesting when you look at the story of Noah.
I think most of you are familiar with it, but the general gist of it is that God had
to wipe out humanity.
He told Noah, "Listen, your family's pure.
Build this boat."
And they're going away for 40 days and 40 nights.
The flood destroys everybody else.
At one point, a rainbow is created.
And that rainbow is created in its God's word, its God's pact, that he would never destroy
the planet again with a flood in particular.
But I mean, it was basically like a symbol of a promise between God and man that, you
know, he would no longer, you know, rain down billions of gallons of water on them.
What I think interesting, so when I read that story as a kid, you're like, "Oh, you know,
that's beautiful."
And as an adult, I remember thinking logically, does that mean there were no rainbows before
the flood?
Does that mean that before the great flood, no one had ever seen a rainbow?
Because it particularly makes the rainbow that symbol, that promise between God and
man.
And it's just kind of an interesting, I mean, here's the thing.
I meet people who go, "Oh, you know, I just can't logically believe in God or I just can't
logically believe in any sort of figure like Christ figure or Muhammad or whatever.
And I just can't believe in the afterlife and stuff like that."
Fair enough.
I'm logical enough that I don't believe in true love, but I can still appreciate a Britney
Spears song.
I can still appreciate a romantic movie.
There's a lot of stuff that I'm like, "Yeah, that just doesn't happen in real life."
That's, you know.
But I still appreciate it.
And I think that there's a lot of interesting stories and parables and lessons in all of
these religions that can be appreciated.
Even though you may not buy into it, lock, sock, and barrel, there's still some nice
stories there.
There's some not-so-nice stories.
Like when that, he was a prophet of God, some teenagers were making fun of him, so he's
sick to like 10 bears and they mauled the kids.
That's a weird part of the Bible.
So yeah, I just think it's kind of interesting.
I mean, logically, yes, rainbows existed before the Great Flood, but in the narrative, in
the structure of that story, if it's taken at face value, they didn't.
So what happened when it rained?
How did the light reflect through the water and all that stuff?
Just kind of an interesting note.
You know, I watched a lot of Shark Tank and Dragon's Den, and I think those shows are
great.
I think they're great because I think it inspires people to get up off their butt and try to
make something.
The whole show is basically people who have been working in their garage or have been
sitting in their living room and drawing notes and staying up late and drinking the coffee
and making those sacrifices throughout the day, and they build a product, they start it,
they go from just being like a soccer mom or a guy with like, he already has a job, he
doesn't really like, so he comes up with this idea that he thinks will make the world better.
I think it's fascinating.
I am always inspired by that show to come up with inventions.
I have an invention of my own.
It's called baby weights.
Baby weights are biodegradable weights.
So a woman is pregnant.
A woman has a baby.
So we'll figure it's maybe like three, you're three months into pregnancy, you don't want
to push the kid, right?
She would swallow, she's going to swallow the weights.
You swallow these little, they're like maybe two of three ounces.
She swallows them.
Or I don't know if a woman swallows something, if it doesn't go into the baby place.
Like they get food, right?
Like when a woman eats stuff, does it, chicken wings fall into the womb?
You know, to be honest, I don't know much about female biology, but I also don't know
much about male biology.
But like when you eat something, does it just like nutrients shoot into the womb or does
like the piece of, there's a hot wing flown around in there, a couple of nuggets.
Anyways, so, okay, you slice the pregnant woman open and you can, oh no, no, no, even better.
Can't you like go in through the vagina and like, and like, well anyways, somehow you
attach these little weights to the baby's arms and legs.
And so when they're like moving around in the womb and kicking, it's slowly building
up their strength.
You could even probably like put one on their neck to help like build core strength because
they're always in a ball, but then they're like unraveling and stuff.
It's like doing sit-ups.
And then what happens is the weight slowly dissolve and then you get a few more crammed
up in there and they're a little bit heavier now.
And so now the baby's like, you know, like curling five, six ounces.
And that's a lot for a baby.
Put them on their legs.
So when like they're like cycling and stuff, come out.
The baby's totally healthy.
The baby will have the most developed muscles of any baby ever.
Baby weights.
Now, I haven't put a patent on that yet, but I trust my listeners not to steal that idea.
Okay, so anyways, we're going to go ahead and get started with the episode.
We have a lot of cool stories for you today.
Now I do have to say some of you may have noticed that I did not come out with an episode
on Friday and there is a very good reason for that.
And it ties into our second story and my paranoia.
So we'll save that for a bit, but let's go ahead and get started with this.
So there's been a new trend on YouTube and what it is, it's YouTubers of all stripes,
all sorts of channels are doing this.
They're buying mystery boxes off of the deep web.
The deep web is a quick overview.
Most of the time is spent on the Surface web.
You're hearing this podcast or you're downloading it from the Surface web.
That's Facebook and Google and email and going shopping at Amazon and all that stuff.
That's just kind of everything that you can just do on the Surface.
Then when you step down a level to go to the deep web, that's when you need Tor.
These are basically servers that aren't indexed, I guess is the best way.
These are servers that are connected to the internet.
They're connected to a internet, but you need a special browser access them because they're
not they're not indexed.
I don't know if I'm explaining that right, right?
Because I'm just trying to get it real quickly because that's not the point.
The point is it's basically like a hidden internet or it's like a hard to access internet.
It's generally where you have stuff.
We've talked about this before like Silk Road, internet hitmen operate on the deep web.
A lot of horrible stuff like child porn.
It's all down there.
Well, not all down there, but I mean like there's stuff of that on the surface web,
but generally speaking, it's where you would go to indulge in a criminal activity or enterprise
with less risk.
It's not zero risk, but less risk.
It's basically like the moss isley of the internet.
It's just kind of this horrible place.
It's like where all the bad stuff happens.
So there's been this YouTube trend of people being like, "Oh, I bought this $250 box from
the deep web and you open it up and I watched a couple of these videos.
That's how I figured out about it."
And they're like wearing gloves and they have the box cutter because you don't know what's
going to be in the box.
It could be like a ton of drugs.
It could be a bunch of like bloody panties.
You don't know.
So they're sitting there with the gloves on, slowly opening the box.
The creepy stock music is playing in the background.
And they're like, "Oh, what is this?
This is a baby doll, but it's head's chopped off.
Here, let me set this to the side."
And they're always wearing like a little camera.
So we're from like their point of view and they're like, "Oh, I see something else.
It's a USB drive.
We'll put this into the end of the video.
Keep watching.
Like and subscribe.
Put this USB down.
Ooh, what's this?
It's these Polaroids and they're like a creepy forest.
Oh no."
And like builds this mystery.
And then the one, I saw one where a guy like puts in the USB drive and then he's like, "Oh,
what's on here?"
And it's just like a picture of like three guys standing in a room.
And then there's a knock at his door and he turns around.
He's like, "Oh no, someone's knocking on my door.
I'm just gonna just pop this mystery box."
Then he turns back and his computers are all glitchy.
And then people who were previously just standing in the room are looking at him.
Now obviously when he turned around, the camera turned around and that allowed anyone else
able to, you know, hit the mouse and move to the next thing.
These mystery boxes go anywhere from $250 to $10,000.
I just dropped $10,000 on this mystery box.
You don't know what's in it.
Watch this video.
Like and subscribe.
It's fake.
I'm not saying that there's not mystery boxes online.
There are these weird memes that pop up that I dismissed completely and they're real.
This one isn't.
I was actually able to track it down.
The earliest reference to this.
On July 2018, there was a story posted on Wattpad, which is a self-published free site that
you can publish your stuff as an author.
It's a really good website.
I don't read much stuff there because again, the gender and the age range really isn't
for me.
It's really for young women.
A lot of the stuff is like Twilight fan fiction.
But anyway, so the earliest mention I could find of this was in July 2018, there was a
short horror story called I bought a mystery box off the dark web.
So what did the story is?
Is that the character in the story buys a mystery box off the internet and in it is
some photos.
There's a bag of Xanax and it has a little note saying, "You'll need these.
Trust me."
And she begins kind of going through the photos and what the photos are are basically of her
neighborhood.
And she's kind of freaking out because she put the order in and then like a week or
two passed or whatever.
She sees some photos and they have dates on them.
And then she sees a photo of the house and she's like, "Wait, that's my house."
She sees a photo of her kitchen.
And then she's seen like a photo of her sleeping.
She's showing just all these creepy photos.
And then the note that said, "Trust me, you'll need these with Xanax."
She flips it over and it has the next day's date.
She's like, "Oh my God, what am I going to do?"
You know, I mean, it was a good story.
It's a good idea.
It's creepy.
And to show that it's a good idea, it launched this trend.
Rachel Nilsson is the author of this.
Now this story on Wattpad only has 98 views.
Yeah, 98 views.
But it was reposted to Reddit's forum, NoSleep, which is a collection of short horror stories.
I go there very often.
I'm subscribed to that.
I check them out.
And I don't know if she posted it on Reddit or if someone stole it from her.
But I think that's where it took off was on Reddit, not necessarily here.
But this is the earliest version of the deep web box, or the dark web box, however you
want to call it.
There is a video from December 2017 that I saw too called Unboxing a Deep Web Credit
Card.
It's just a video of a guy opening up a letter that has a credit card in it.
So we had that in December 2017 and then this story in July of this year.
And now we have this big thing.
No one's doing it.
I'm not saying there's not mystery boxes on the deep web.
There's mystery boxes you can buy on eBay.
But these YouTubers aren't buying them.
They're getting a bunch of creepy stuff and they're putting it in a box and they're sealing
it.
I mean, and whatever, dude, it's clickbait.
Like there's so much stuff on YouTube that is just fake clickbait stuff.
Anyways, all the Gold Digger videos are fake.
So I mean, they're just following the trend.
You know, kids watch it.
And kids are like, oh my God, that's so spooky.
Mom, dad, can I borrow $10,000 to buy a box on deep web?
So again, like, they're out there.
These YouTubers, the things that are unboxing aren't them.
I don't recommend really buying anything from the deep web because you're going to get
scammed.
The chances of someone sending you the proof of their murder is incredibly unlikely.
The chances of you losing $250 is extremely likely.
So how are they doing it?
These kids have bitcoins or something like that?
So but yeah, all the news articles I've read about this, when I was researching this was
like, it's a dangerous new trend.
Kids are buying deep web boxes and they don't know if they're going to get bottles of acid
or drugs or aborted fetuses.
It could be all three.
And the articles are taking it seriously because it's clickbait for them.
I clicked on all those articles.
Other people are clicking on those articles.
Parents watch out for new trend.
It's not happening.
It's really not happening.
People probably have bought these boxes, but it would be garbage if there's anything in
there.
Again, no one's going to send you the soiled panties of their 18th victim to Judy in Charlottesville.
It's just ridiculous.
But it makes for good YouTube, so you'll continue to see that stuff.
We're going to go ahead and move on to our next story.
Now, the episode that was supposed to come out Friday is done.
It's absolutely done.
I sat on it though because what happened?
It's a good episode.
I really like that episode.
And I'm going to release it tomorrow, so it will get released.
But I wanted to do this one first.
So what happened was I had gotten communications from a couple different people.
Veronica was like, "Hey, are you doing the story about this?
I shouldn't make this sound like that."
Veronica said, "Jason, are you going to do the story about the solar observatory being
shut down?"
And my friend Mitcham was like, "Hey, you know, have you seen this?"
Like they shut down.
Mitcham was actually the first one to got a hold of me.
He was like, "Hey, have you seen this?
They're shutting down this solar observatory."
No one knows why.
And I'd seen it on 4chan.
I blew it off.
I was like, "It's not a big deal.
I just kind of, you know, what's going on with the solar observatory right a bit."
I was like, "That's nothing."
And Mitcham was like, "Yeah, yeah, you know, this is going on."
So I kind of went back and took another look at it.
I did start looking at it and I'm like, "Okay, there might be something here."
And then I come home from work and there's probably seemed incredibly minor to you.
But again, I have a slight paranoid streak.
I come home from work and there's a note in my mailbox saying, "You have a certified
letter.
You need to come pick it up or, you know, we'll read the liver on such and such date
or whatever like that."
And I'm thinking, "Who the hell has sent me certified letters?"
And I go, "It's either one of two things.
It's either some birthday money that somebody doesn't want to get lost.
My birthday's coming up in about two weeks."
Or I'm getting sued again.
It's one of those two.
And so I'm like, "What?"
And I start, I'm like, "It could be..."
And those are the two main ones, but I'm thinking it could be something else.
It could be something else.
I started to get concerned.
I'm like, "Because as much as I talk about myself personally on the show, I go, "I don't
give out my personal email."
My mind kept going back to the podcast.
I'm like, "I don't give out my personal address on the show, but it wouldn't be difficult
for anyone with any sort of skill to find out."
So I went down to the post office.
I said, "Hey, can I pick this up?"
He said, "No, it's a little too early.
You have to wait because it was a Friday."
You know, the mail truck's moving around, stuff like that.
You have to wait until Monday.
And I go, "Can you guys at least tell me who it's from?"
Or like, "What it is?"
And they're like, "We can tell you it's a letter, but we don't know anything else
than that."
And I'm like, "Oh, okay."
The reason why that prompted me to not release that episode was because a lot of people are
talking about the solar observatory being shut down.
And what they forget is the post office in the town was also shut down.
So I'm thinking, "Did someone try to send me a letter from there?"
And again, you're like, "Jason, come on.
That's ridiculous."
But let me explain why.
There's basically just a few reasons why this solar observatory was shut down, or this
area was shut down.
One, it's absolutely nothing that's been blown out of proportion to the media.
It's possible there were no FBI or Black Hawk helicopters or anything like that.
It's just a solar observatory got shut down and the media blew it out of proportion like
they always do.
That's one option.
One option is there's some sort of contaminant spill.
There's some sort of mercury in the area.
There's some sort of radioactivity in the area.
There is just something going on that they needed to shut down.
That one I'm a little suspicious of because if it was just a chemical problem, you wouldn't
necessarily...
Let's assume that the FBI has been there.
I've heard that there were Black Hawk helicopters there, and we're going to table that for a
second.
Let's assume that the FBI actually physically was there.
They wouldn't really investigate a mercury poisoning, or they wouldn't investigate any
toxins in the water or black mold infestation or sentient soil or anything like that.
You'd see CDC out there.
You would see people in biohazard suits that were there to clean up a contaminant.
There's the other option that there is some sort of a criminal activity going on there
in that area.
So escaped convict, meth lab, overall drug running operation, arm smuggling operation.
This is in New Mexico.
I'm not saying that all New Mexico people smuggle drugs and make meth, but you know
what I mean?
It's kind of in this wilderness type area.
It would be a good place to cook.
So they could have cut...
They said, "You know what?
We know someone's in this area.
We're going to shut down 50 miles.
You guys just happen to be in it.
The workers leave, sunspot, solar observatory, people get out of here.
FBI's coming in.
We're going to do all this stuff."
And that would...
They would use helicopters, not necessarily in Blackhawks.
I think that's a bit of an exaggeration, but could be someone doing an operation in
the solar observatory that's criminal or in the post office that's criminal and they're
doing their investigation.
Generally in that case, they wouldn't evacuate the people if they're trying to investigate
those people, but if there was a dangerous criminal on the loose or some big operation
out there, there's the option.
People have said that the solar observatory detected a magnetic storm, detected alien
spacecraft, whatever it is.
I've heard stories that multiple observatories across the planet were shutting down.
There was four of them and that story's been debunked.
That story's not true.
So really only the sunspot, solar observatory in New Mexico that we know of has been shut
down.
We don't know what.
But I had another theory, a very ego-driven/paranoid theory, more paranoid than ego-driven, if
I have to be honest.
Golf rumors.
When I did the episode on golf rumors, we covered them.
We're saying some people thought it was the same worshipping group.
Other people thought it was the psychic camera thing.
And my suggestion was it's related to the golf, the global oscillations at low frequency
device or instrument on the SOHO satellite, which is the solar observatory healistic object
or something like that.
It's a satellite in space that is just detecting issues with the sun.
And the golf instrument is able to penetrate the sun, or not penetrate the sun, but it
is able to read inside the sun and it can figure out all this stuff.
And I said, I think that golf rumors is part of this.
I think that the rumors are things that have been spread around in these observatories where
they have detected things with the golf instrument and they've talked to each other and they
have tried to say, there's something going on with the sun or near the sun or something
like that.
And that's the rumor, not necessarily that it's true, but the readings coming back from
the golf instrument are not what people expected.
So that was my suggestion for what golf rumors was.
I thought, what if someone mailed something and see, and this is a thing, if someone in
the observatory used the post office to mail me something regarding that and they tracked
it to that observatory.
What if that episode on golf rumors, which again was always said, use extreme caution,
don't research, and me just blathering about it on a podcast and some guy heard it in New
Mexico or Gal, you know, and goes, oh, he knows, he knows the truth.
I tried a letter dropping in the mail, FBI descends on the solar observatory.
Shut it down.
We got investigated.
So I held off on that episode that had nothing to do with golf rumors or the solar observatory,
but I go, you know what, if the FBI is going to come knocking at my door, you know, let's
just take a breather.
So here's what happened.
Saturday they read, I signed the little slip on the note.
Saturday they redelivered the letter to me, the certified letter.
I opened it up.
I owe the state of Oregon $70 for past tax dues.
Okay, fair enough.
Not getting sued.
That's good.
Wasn't some birthday money.
That's sad.
But it's $70.
It wasn't someone mailing it out from the solar observatory.
However, I still think that's what, not me, forget me.
I think that it's not a chemical contamination because the FBI necessarily wouldn't investigate
that.
The criminal activity there, I don't see the FBI needing to shut down because FBI has
gone into urban areas, all sorts of areas, and they're not like, they're not like, shut
this hotel down, Arby's, close for the winter, you guys, get out of here.
We got to stop a crime.
Like that's just not the way the FBI works.
My suggestion, what I think happened, and I think that I was on the wrong endpoint, but
what I think happened was someone at that observatory was doing something and they were
mailing stuff out of that office, whatever it was, ricin or anthrax or secured documents
or anything like that.
And they did.
They said, you know what, everyone clear out because we know all of your names.
They'll probably know all of the people who work there and they're watching them, but they
want to see what information is coming out of that area from that observatory to that
post office.
That's what I think happened.
I think it's a criminal matter, maybe a terrorist or espionage matter, but I don't think that
it's aliens or Bigfoot or solar flares or golf rumors, maybe golf rumors, but I don't
think that it's anything super 40 and I don't think it's anything super weird.
The thing is, is that, and the thing that's a little frustrating is that we're never going
to know and no one's ever going to trust it.
If the FBI clears out and the observatory opens again, oh, I have another theory too,
but if the FBI leaves and the solar observatory opens again and they go, it was just, we had
a leak in our lines and the FBI wanted to check it out.
And or if they're like, oh, no, no, you know, it was totally legit.
We had a leak in our lines or there was some mercury in the water or no one's going to
believe it.
If the FBI is like, oh yeah, there's a dangerous area, a dangerous criminal in the area and
so on and so on, no one's going to believe them.
This theory is going to be running around for the next five years.
People are going to be like, well, you know, they shut down that observatory.
And then with the golf rumors thing, which I do now, the more I think about it, I think
that is the most logical answer to what golf rumors really is, is that it refers to the
golf instrument.
They're not the observatory that that information is fed into.
I had to look that up.
That information, I believe, is fed into a observatory or a computer system on the East
Coast, not a New Mexico.
I mean, is it possible that they did, that maybe that was the source of the golf rumors?
They got that instrumentate, they got that information and they were leaking it out.
I mean, it's possible like .001% possible.
They didn't mail me.
Thank God.
I don't want the FBI banging on my door.
I also have another theory.
I think it was probably something super minor and now it's a publicity stunt.
The observatory is open to the public.
You know when they reopen, they're going to be mobbed by people and it's just like,
oh, it's just a learning opportunity.
They never fuss up to that.
They never admit that.
But it, you know, did you ever know this observatory existed?
I'm sure people in the area were vaguely aware of it.
And after this happens, there are going to get so many people going up there.
So you know, it's possible that it was a minor thing and they just said, you know, well,
let's say shut a couple more days.
It could have been two FBI agents walked up there and they said, you know what, can you
guys shut this down?
We're going to run a train.
Oh, I didn't even think about that.
Maybe they're just running training exercises up there and they don't want people to know
that.
You know what?
That's I bet you anything.
That's it.
I bet you anything.
The FBI ran training exercises up there.
When my dad was a minister, we had a church and this local SWAT team asked, Hey, can we
run a training exercise in your church?
My dad's like, Oh yeah, dude, that's totally awesome.
Go ahead.
And we didn't, we weren't, no one is able to go to church that day.
It was a Tuesday, so it wasn't a whole horrible loss.
But you know what I mean?
Like they don't want you video.
They would clear that's what it is, dude.
It's a training exercise.
And the FBI wanted it.
Yeah.
That's the answer to that.
I'll bet you money.
FBI was running a, like a building to building, like, because it's a perfect area.
The observatories oddly shaped like any, that's why the church worked because it's such a
weird configuration.
The SWAT, you know, if you go into an office building, they're all kind of laid out the
same, but churches have weird architecture and weird corners.
It's not necessarily about functionality.
It's about form.
So the SWAT team could like learn weird maneuvers in there.
Learn how to maneuver in non-normal or non-traditional environments.
Observatory would be great for that as well.
And you would have the post office there, which would give them like, that would be
where they'd set up.
And then they could go into the wilderness and practice stuff as well.
I almost guarantee you that's what that is.
It's a training exercise.
Damn.
You know what?
I could have started off with that and saved everyone 10 minutes.
Hey, it's not about the destination.
It's about the journey sometimes.
Yeah.
And we'll end again.
They'll never admit it because what'll happen is they'll want to do it again.
They'll want to do it again in another location and then people will go out there and they'll
be flying drones over it and stuff like that.
They're just going to go do these training exercises and I'll bet you money that's what
it is.
Golf rumors?
Probably not.
I still really like that episode.
I think that was one of my funnest episodes to research.
And that is the Solar Observatory story.
Oh, and I want to say, I want to say right now that today.
I got a YouTube comment from Ryan ML88.
And they're like, do you think that the Solar Observatory closure could be due to your golf
rumors episode?
And I was like, spoiler alert, dude, I've been prepping that.
We're going to go with this angle.
We're going to, I'm going to research this and stuff like that.
It's like nine in the morning.
He's like, hey, everyone, this is what Jason's next episode is about.
But no, Ryan, good looking out because yeah, I didn't respond because I wanted to get this
episode out, but I'll respond to your YouTube comment now.
Yeah, that was kind of the angle I was looking at for a while and it's petered out.
But again, I appreciate that people are listening to the episodes and enjoying the episodes.
And it means a lot to me.
And I read all your comments.
I think you guys have seen that.
I read all your comments.
I get back to you guys and a couple of the upcoming stories we're going to do our stories
to that were emailed to me by a couple of you.
Hero, Clovis, we're going to do that.
We're going to do Heliocentrism.
That's coming up in a couple of weeks, but Hero, Glovis, I think is this week.
It's weird.
Just people take photos of weird cult stuff they find around their city or, you know,
flyers that are posted up around their college campuses and they're like, hey, Jason, do
a story on this and they'll take a picture of some cult like meet us up and light candles
and I love all that stuff.
Feel free to send me that stuff.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com.
You can send it there.
That's our email address.
It's also available on facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
You can also hit me up at Twitter @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)