fast food, it's all around us. Everyone loves it, it's super nutritious, and it's
good for you, it helps your bones grow. But did you know that there are actually
several conspiracy theories surrounding fast food? First off, we're gonna find out
what's really in a McDonald's hamburger. Secondly, that might not be true, but we'll
get another story about something that's in a McDonald's hamburger, and then we
will take a look at probably one of the grossest conspiracy theories out there,
involving food. And this one has a surprise twist ending today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter, I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Now,
one of two things are going on. One, if you're watching on YouTube, you actually see me in
the middle of a city right above the cafe square, and a guy in a business suit is
riding by on a skateboard. I'm going to try to do video, but don't worry, loyal
podcast listeners. I'm not gonna be doing a bunch of episodes where I'm like, "Hey,
let's watch this clip," or "Hey, let's do that," so because I hate that when I listen
to podcasts, when I have to use another alternative method. However, if you do use
YouTube, now you see me and the guy in the business suit on the skateboard. Let's go
ahead and give a shout out to one of our legacy Patreons, Bonkelman. Everyone give a
round of applause to Bonkelman. He comes walking in, he has a little like, "Soon on,
he's right in an skateboard." Awesome, Bonkelman. You're gonna be our captain, our
pilot this episode. If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. Just help
get the word out about the show. Really, really helps out a lot. So, Bonkelman, just
yesterday we were at a top secret McDonald's in the middle of the Pacific Ocean.
We were never able to wrap up that mystery, but while I was looking into that, I found
all these other fast food conspiracy theories that I wanted to talk about today. Originally,
originally I was gonna do a whole week of these, but today we're just hanging out.
We're just hanging out on the couch. Bonkelman walks in, everyone's like, "What's up?"
And he has the keys to the Jason Jalopy. He's gonna take us for a drive. We're
going to McDonald's. A lot of McDonald's, a lot of McDonald's stories, and they're
all bad. So strap in if you own Stock McDonald's or if you like eating there,
because these stories get gross. Bonkelman, I want you to drive us all the way out to
the deep south. Bonkelman's driving us out to Atlanta, Georgia. And as we're headed
out to Atlanta, go ahead and hit that time travel button. We are headed out to the
year 1978. We're driving through Atlanta, Georgia. We see people out on the street
corners. That's normal. People are allowed to walk. People are allowed to leave their
homes. Back then, at least. It's Atlanta, Georgia. We see people on street corners.
They're holding signs. Down with McDonald's. Down with McDonald's. They're
chanting. We're like, "What? We're driving through the neighborhood." "Boom! McDonald's
sucks." We're like, "Huh?" I mean, it's not the best fast food, but I definitely want to
say it sucks. It's a couple levels above Arby's, at least. And then we see a guy.
He has like a little like chain, right? We're ever thrown on him, right? He's like
an environmentalist guy, but his chain's not around. That's what environmentalists
they just walk around covered in chains. They're all Jacob Marley. You know how
environmentalists will chain themselves to trees? Well, this guy is
chained to the earth. He's chained to the dirt. And he's like, "McDonald's ain't
getting none of this dirt." We're like, "What? Why do they want the dirt?" And he's
like, "Oh, you don't know?" We're like, "No, we don't know." And he's grabbing handfuls of
mud. We're starting to think it just might be his fetish. He doesn't care anything
about the environment. He's like, "I just live laying in mud and being chained up."
He's playing with mud and he goes, "This mud contains the ingredient, the main
ingredient in McDonald's hamburgers." He's like, "Okay, maybe not the mud itself.
Maybe I'm going too far with this setup." But he reaches in the mud and he pulls
out a big handful of earthworms and they're squirmy. They're all like gross
and bloated and stuff. He's holding them right in front of our face like an
old-timey 3D movie. He's like, "Ah, this is what they put in McDonald's hamburgers."
And he's holding the worms out in front of us. This is a really interesting
conspiracy theory because this is one where we have dates and times for how
this story started, which is really rare. Like, people still can't decide on the
origins of Bloody Mary. There's a lot of people can't really decide on the origin
of the white lady who gets in your car because she died during prom and she's
hoping to get home or something like that. I always thought that one was kind of
lame. But you know what I mean? Like, we have these old urban legends, little kids,
little kids push your car. That's just when you have a lot of kids and your
car breaks down. That's where that urban legend started. Some lazy dad was like,
"Billy, Johnny, get out and start pushing this car." But you know what I mean? We have
all these urban legends. It's rare when we can figure out where they started from.
This one started on August 15th, 1978. I got most of this information from
Snopes. They were able to really track this back to get the story. August 15th,
1978, Wendy's. Wendy herself gets a phone call and someone goes, "Hey, one of my
neighbors said that your food has worms in it." Wendy's looks side to side. She's like,
"Uh-oh." They found out. She's like, "No, no, no." That's not true. So that was to the end of the phone call.
So basically, Wendy's first in August of 1978 started to have this rumor spread
about them that worm meat was used to fill out the burgers. Nowadays, someone
tweets something and it's like either a big thing or doesn't catch off. It
depends what the bots want, right? There's really no humans left on Twitter.
It depends on what the bots want to push. But someone can make a legit complaint
and it never gets any traction. And someone makes some sort of claim that
Wendy's burgers are made of worms and what the bots decide will be popular is
what's popular. But they used to not be that. There used to be a time where you
could, I guess you could still do it today. Phone still exists, but before
Twitter, where am I going with this? The point is, is that back in the good old days,
you could make a phone call to Wendy's corporate and within a couple weeks,
Wendy's had to put out a press conference. They had to come before the
people of the South. This was just a regional thing, but it was catching fire.
Wendy's by September 15th, so a month later, held a public press conference to
say there are no worms in our burgers. And people are like, "Uh-huh, okay."
That's all we just want to know, Wendy's was a real person and she showed up. So,
that was kind of the end of it. But of course, I'm talking about McDonald's
conspiracy theories because very shortly afterwards, the conspiracy theory
changed. Now it was worms in McDonald's burgers. I assume the story shifted
because a Wendy's shaped silhouette was walking out of the, walking out of like
an alleyway one day and reporters walking on the street, meaning "pspsps" come here.
You know that thing about worms in my food? I mean worms in Wendy's food? That was
lie. It's all about McDonald's. So anyways, the rumor starts with McDonald's now.
So for whatever reason, McDonald's got hit even harder by this thing. Part of it
could be that, so at September 15th, was when Wendy's disputed it a month later.
It quickly switched to McDonald's. It took them until November 23rd to
address it. But the people at McDonald's were kind of scratching their heads.
They're like, "This doesn't make sense. We don't have worms in our burgers." And
what's funny is that there, Wendy's was basically just like, "No, we don't have
worms in our burgers. That's the end of it." Ray Kroc, the founder of McDonald's, I
know he bought the company from two other guys, but Ray Kroc is kind of the guy
who made it into the juggernaut it is today. When he found out about this rumor,
he actually addressed the rumor himself, because reporters are asking about it. He
goes, "No, and I'll tell you why we don't have worms in our meat. Worm meat is very
expensive." He said, "We get slabs of meat so cheap." He goes, "Worms actually cost
the more." They're, I guess, harder to catch. I guess you need to be six years old
and have a little shovel. You have to wait for a rainy day. Imagine if you had a
wait for a rainy day to slaughter all those cows. They're harder to catch.
They're more expensive to process. You have competition. People are trying to
buy them for bait or that suspicious bird-shaped shop sitting on the edge of
town and there's a bird wearing a giant trench coat. He's like, "I have more worms
for me." But anyways, the McDonald's got hit really hard. You had some
franchisees of McDonald's lose up to 30% of their business due to this
rumor. Because who wants to eat a worm burger? I'll answer that in a second, but
who really wants to eat a worm burger? You're not. Most people would answer no.
It spread out of Atlanta. It started to get into Ohio. This rumor was getting
really, really popular back then. Eventually, on November 23rd, they held a
press conference. They said, "We don't have worm meat. Rake croc runs on stage."
He's like, "You know how expensive worms are?" I looked into it. I was gonna make
worm burgers, but I couldn't. They're like pushing them off stage. They're like,
"Dude, you're not healthy." He's like, "What? What?" I mean, they look tasty, right?
He's a bird. He's a bird in a trench coat. Rake, squawk. So anyways, the rumor
dies down. And then, like, I don't know, a couple weeks later, a month later, a new
rumor starts. You see, McDonald's hamburgers, McDonald's hamburgers have to
have meat in them. But what is meat? People are asking each other on the street.
They're like, "Literally, I don't know what's meat. I've been eating clay this
whole time." 100% beef is how they list their hamburgers. These rumor mongers
were saying, "If you took cow eyeballs, it's out of a cow, right? Everything that
is... everything comes out of a cow's beef that swallows a tungsten rod. It's beef
now. It's all beef. So they're taking cow eyeballs and squishing them up. I told
you this is gonna be... you're eating a big mac right now. You're like, "I can do the
worms." But this is gross. They're taking out cow eyeballs and squishing them up.
And McDonald's again disputed this one, and they go, "No joke. This was their
answer for this." Do you know how expensive eyeballs are? They said eyeballs are one
of the most expensive parts of a cow. Because McDonald's is buying their beef,
but the eyeballs are being sent to research laboratories. You can get, what,
50 pounds of beef, but each cow, no matter how big or small they are, they only got
two eyeballs. So those are very, very valuable to research people. And then
they're squishing them. They're turning them into mayonnaise. They're like, "Mmm, so
delicious on my McDonald's hamburger." So there's your visual. There's your
mayonnaise visual for the day. Then... I'm not just gonna list off conspiracy theories,
but I thought these three were the funniest. And then we'll get into some
creepy ones. And then people started saying, "Okay, okay. Are eyeball plans in
the world? Do you have a laboratory?" Wendy's is there, and Jack and the janitor
from Arby's, that's their highest rank and associate, and Colonel Sanders is there,
and they're like, "Dang it. McDonald's is impervious to our lives." So they didn't
believe the eyeball thing. Arby's is right down the stuff. He's like, "Mmm, eyeballs in
my sandwiches. That'll make them taste even better." So one more rumor started
up about McDonald's. They do say that they come from a hundred percent beef. This
one's actually kind of clever. Someone really had it out for McDonald's, maybe
because they were the cock of the block. They were the big boys. But they said that...
Oh, so it said 100% beef. 100% beef on these burgers. They were saying, the
conspiracy started, that they weren't 100% beef. They were worms and eyeballs and
all sorts of tungsten rods, all sorts of stuff. That McDonald's was actually
buying their meat from a company called 100% beef. So they could say, "Our
burgers are 100% beef." And it would be true. And McDonald's is like, "That's
that one. It's a little clever, but it's not true. We actually have all of our
stuff graded and everything. It might be D's and C's, but it's a grade, baby." So
anyways, all those conspiracy theories popped up all relatively around the same
time. But then you have the creepier ones.
Bunkleman, let's go ahead and hop in that Jason Jett. We're gonna leave behind
Atlanta, Georgia. We are headed out to a research facility in the middle of Brazil.
Bunkleman lands his jet in the middle of the rainforest. We're walking around.
We're hacking it with our machetes. Chop, chop, chop. We're sending stuff on fire to
make it super easy. Oh, my arms cramp. And I just burn a path. Burnin' it up. We
find a secret facility in the middle of the Amazon jungle. It's not super
secret because there's a giant golden arches on the top of the building. And
they have a sign outside that says, "Over 60 billion dissected." And we're like,
"Huh?" And so we have key codes. We beat up some dudes. We took their key cards. They
didn't even work there. We just wanted to beat them up. Then we had to beat up
some other guys. We take their key cards. We're able to access this secret
Brazilian facility. This story popped up. It was super popular in March of 2000,
which again is an interesting one we can find. I guess nowadays because so many
rumors are spread electronically, we probably could track it back easier.
This one I actually found on a website that I stumbled across. I was
researching something else. There is a Portuguese website. So it's a Brazilian
website, but it's in Portuguese. It's called Quatro Cantos, which means four
corners. It's all about internet legends and conspiracy theories. And it's, there's
super bizarre stuff on there. In March 2000, this conspiracy goes around. It was
really popular in Brazil. That there is a secret research facility somewhere in
the world. And inside it are the cows that McDonald's gets its beef from. It's not
fair to say that they're cows. It'd be better to say that they were cows at
some point. It's a real philosophical question. When does a cow stop being a
cow? So we walk into this research facility and we see this abomination just
laying there. It has no limbs. So it's just a big old torso laying on a table. But
you can tell from the way it's undulating that it's alive. Actually, the other thing
about it would kind of look like a worm. Kind of look like a bill grub. It's kind
of just has no bones. Bones just get in the way of that delicious meat. Instead,
it just has cartilage to keep it. What do bones do? Bones keep the body together,
right? It's not like the super glue, but you know what I mean? Like, if I didn't
have bones, well, here's the thing. If I didn't have bones in my arms, my arms
wouldn't work. But if I didn't have arms, I wouldn't worry about it. So my question
is, like the rib cage, if you got rid of the rib cage, if you took me and turned
me into a legless, armless, genetically modified monster, and would I need a
rib cage? I think you would only need a spine. But like, why don't you just get
rid of all of it? I guess scientists know. I mean, I don't know. Maybe scientists
know all this stuff. But they're like, Jason, of course, you need to have cartilage
in your cow monster. It doesn't have any bones. It just has underdeveloped cartilage.
It has no eyes, no tail, no fur, so it's just as big as a worm. It's a giant worm.
And its head is the size of a baseball. So a tiny little head has no eyes. It
doesn't say anything about not having a mouth, but they do just lead tubes into
its stomach, and they pump food into it, and that's what keeps it growing. It's like a
balloon, like an organic balloon. And then eventually they slaughter it. So
that's gross, right? Like, if you... it's one thing, like, the way that we treat
animals for industrial slaughter, it's pretty... it's barbaric. I'm not gonna
sugarcoat it. It's barbaric. I was a vegetarian for quite a few years because
of that. It just got too expensive. Like, at a certain point I was like, well, I do
not like supporting the industrial slaughter of animals, but at the same time I
need to eat. Otherwise, I will starve to death. So I ended up switching. Now I eat
canned raviolis and stuff like that. So it sucks. Like, I totally get it.
There's... it's... I understand why they do it, because it's industrialized and
stuff like that, but that's... it's still pretty barbaric. I watched that
documentary once about that girl who had autism, and she always had a hide-and-
under-a-blink it. And then there's one of those movie synopses that I, like, barely
remember the movie. Like, what are you talking about? Her name was like Angus
Truman, or Truman... I don't know. Truman Angus. She was named after what she loved
the most, eating cows. She actually... she had suffered from autism, so she carried
around this giant blanket everywhere and had to hang out in this box that, like,
squished her. It's a saw movie. Ah, I'm getting them confused. No, she had, like,
this box that was all cushioned. And she loved cutting animals up. She loved the
slaughterhouse. That was her favorite job. But what happened was she would go to
these... she would... that was what she was getting her degree in, and she would go to
the slaughterhouse, and she... see the cows, like, totally freaking out and getting
slaughtered. And she's watching this, and she goes, "There's a better way to kill
these cows." She wasn't, like, the super environment... I'm sure she cares about the
environment on some level. I'm not saying she's, like, peeing on the ground. Take that,
Earth. But she also was like, "I understand, like, I'm in the slaughterhouse of
business. I know how humans need me. It's really good for them. But there's a
better way to kill 100,000 cows a year," was her thing. I'm not saying don't kill
the cows. I'm not saying really kill less of them. But we can make them more
comfortable on their last moments on Earth. So she invented... it's a really
interesting movie. I wish I could remember the title of it. Angus McDuff. She invented
this thing where the... can I at least look up her name if you're gonna tell us this
intriguing story. She set up a slaughterhouse that the cows would get
hugged as they walked through the slaughterhouse. So it's not like there
would be workers going like, "Oh, like, rubbing and scratching their belly." It was
the way that the slaughterhouse was built was before the cows... before the cows
were basically just like, "It's time to die!" and a guy would chase them around with
the chainsaw or something. It wasn't that bad, but they'd like shoot them in the
back of the head and the cows would be freaking out. They could smell the death.
They could smell the cow poop. They could smell all this horror going on in front
of them and they're being herded in to this building where you can... there's so
much blood you can smell the iron oxide in the air. She says, "We're gonna kill them."
But what if we build like little huggy things for them so they're walking
through and the sides are like comforting them as they go. Playing lullaby music.
Aww. And she actually got the... she got like some rich investor to build one of
these. I think there's a couple of them now. She actually did go about changing a
lot of things of how people were slaughtering animals. I always thought it
was an interesting story. Not so interesting that I would look up the
title for you. I'll put it in the show notes. I'll look it up later. But that is
the story of the slaughterhouse woman. But where are we going with this? Oh yeah!
So anyways, you have cows being horribly butchered and so you could see
someone going, "Listen, what if we can remove that horror element from the
cow's life by not killing cows?" Or basically like, "No, they're not a
cow. They're a genetically modified tiny little brain organism. They would
basically have the personality of an amoeba. They would just sit on a table
and we feed them food and they plump up and then we chop them up." And you can
imagine other CEOs looking at the scientists and being like, "That is
brilliant, my friend. That's horrifying but brilliant." That's not all though,
because also going around in this same email, it's not just that you're eating
disgusting genetically modified cow guts with no bones. You're like, "Oh, that's my
favorite part." Eating this gives you AIDS. So that should be the deal breaker,
right? We could have moral questions all day long about whether or not to
eat this cow mutant, but it gives you AIDS and Alzheimer's, which is a terrible
combination of stuff. So basically what this theory says, not only does McDonald's
treat cows so horribly they've created a cow monster to get meat from, really the
bullet point here is eating McDonald's gives you AIDS. That's really the thesis.
That should have been the first sentence, because other people could have been like,
"Oh, you know, maybe cows don't need AIDS. Maybe those are overrated for cows."
Just start it off, eating McDonald's gives you AIDS and then you go, "Gentlemen, now
that I have your attention, read the rest of this email." But Bonkelman, let's go
ahead and hop in that carbonar copter. This episode might run a little bit long,
but I do want to cover this one. Bonkelman, call in that carbonar copter. We
are leaving behind the Brazilian rain... Previously was the rain force. Now it's
a beautiful clearing where you can build all sorts of stuff. We are leaving
behind the Brazilian parking lot and we are headed out to the Netherlands.
[Demonic mumbling]
Flying over. We see a little research facility, a lot of research facilities in
this show. So we land at this research facility and we see a big sign on it and
it says, "Research facility keep out" and then underneath it says, "A division of
PepsiCo." We're like, "Oh, that's kind of weird." So we're walking around and we see
a bunch of protesters outside this research facility and they're like, "Burn it
down. Burn it down. Burn it down." We're like, "What's going on?" And they go, "Guys,
listen, you will not believe this." Inside that facility, they are using human
fetal tissue and putting it inside Pepsi. You know that boy we're both drinking
Pepsi's were upset. What'd you say? They go, "Yes, human fetal tissue is used to
flavor Pepsi sodas." This one is so weird because I'm telling you, because I'm
telling you the reaction that you're having right now is the same reaction I
had. 100%. Let's get into this. People have been protesting boycotting, really,
boycotting Pepsi over this. This controversy broke out in 2011 when a
website called naturalnews.com, which is exactly what it sounds like. It's a
website that does a lot of holistic stuff, fringe science stuff. They said Pepsi is
using a line of fetal tissue called HEK293 to flavor their sodas. HEK293 is a
group of cells that were taken out of a embryos kidney, embryonic kidney. They're
actually from a child who was aborted back in the 1970s in
Netherlands. That's what they use with some fetal tissue. They'll use it for
scientific purposes, stem cells, things like that. So HEK293, this is the
story that was put forth. HEK293 was a clump of kidney, kidney, embryonic kidney
cells that were then sold to these research laboratories and they were
using it as an additive in the flavor of the Pepsi's. And so this started to take
off, this rumor started to take off really back in 2011 when this article was
ran. People started looking into it, people started calling up Pepsi, people
started boycotting Pepsi, and supposedly this company in the Netherlands, known as
CenoMix, was the one who was doing this research for Pepsi. So think about
everything we've talked about. We've talked about worms in hamburgers, we've
talked about eyeballs in hamburgers, McDonald's has had a rough go, we talked
about that AIDS cow that basically you McDonald's you get AIDS. We get to this
story in 2011, some things never change, right? What's interesting about this story
is in 2012 Pepsi came forward and said, you know what, we know you're boycotting
this because you guys say that we're working with CenoMix and they're using
fetal tissue to work with our drinks. We as of now are going to stop our
partnership with CenoMix, please call the boycott off. It was true, in a sense, in
a sense it was true. So the story was that fetal tissue was being used as a
flavor additive. What the truth was, was that fetal tissue was involved, that
was not an exaggeration, it wasn't being added to each can of Pepsi. They were
using it to taste thousands of flavors a day. Look at this quote here, this is from
Forbes. A tiny company called CenoMix has been working to use this new
technology to create food additives. CenoMix has isolated receptors found on
cells that detect taste and added them to the HEK cells. This allows them to test
thousands of potential taste additives to see whether they may taste sweet or
savory with a speed that would be impossible with human taste testers.
CenoMix has announced collaborations with Pepsi, Nestle, and Coca-Cola. So they
weren't using it, they weren't like dripping it in with an IV into the Coke
batch. They were using it to create the flavors in the first place. They could
just run diet, I'm sure nowadays you could do a lot of that stuff computer-wise.
I think computers like "bwack, bwack, bwack" face a gross face and they're like
"get rid of that line or sell it to Arby's." It can taste thousands of
different combinations faster than a human can. So they actually were using
this. I find that fascinating. It's gross, it's totally gross, but I also find it
fascinating because this is the one conspiracy theory of this, that it was
off the mark. They weren't actually using it as a flavor additive, but they were
using it to design their flavors in the first place. So that is the story of, or
multiple stories, of fast food conspiracy theories. I think it's really
fascinating. Oh, and to its credit, Pepsi said, because again, they really came
clean on this. They could have just said, "No, it's not true, it's not true." They
said, "Listen, the Pepsi that you are drinking right now at the press conference
that does not have fetal tissue in it, fetal tissue never ever touched that
drink. We use it to design flavors, but it's not actually in the drink." So it's
again, the story evolved to be extra gross, but I think it's fascinating to see
the evolution of conspiracy theories, to see how long they stick around. When I
read that, I read it on some wacky website where they said, "You know that
Pepsi uses fetal tissue?" And I was like, "Well, that's dumb." And I started looking
into it because that's what I do, even if I think something's dumb, I'll actually
study it to see if I'm right and to see and kind of dissect it. Because I love
how these things work, whether or not I believe in them or moot. I don't believe
in the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, but I'll watch two hours of that show a day
because I enjoy the story and everything like that. But so I looked
into this and Pepsi was like, "Yeah, kind of." And they ended their contract with
them and stuff like that. But I find that very, very fascinating. And I think we're
about to get a whole new bunch of conspiracy theories out there, guys. I
think that with everything going on in the United States, you have like the
election and then you have the votes getting disputed and you're gonna have
these lawsuits and you're gonna have... Strap in, guys, because this next... I
predict... I don't think there's gonna be a Civil War. I think that's the... whatever.
But I don't not even think we're close to that. But I think the next five years is
going to be... it's going to be the golden age of conspiracy theories. We're gonna
see both sides... we're not both sides. We're gonna see every single side issuing
conspiracy theories about other people. Some will grow. Organically, some will be
boosted by the bots of Twitter. Some will die off. The real question is, will we be
able to talk about them? Will things get so gummed up by algorithms that if you
talk about this conspiracy theory, you talk about that conspiracy theory, they
take it down. I actually got hit with a hate crime strike on one of my episodes
recently. It was... you can check it out. There's nothing in it that was even
close to that. It was the episode about the woman magically disappearing in
Paris. So the lady vanishes. It was episode like 550, 553 or something like that.
Got hit with a hate crime strike against my YouTube channel. There's nothing in
that episode that even comes close to that. Or any of my episodes really for
that matter. They're coming down hard on conspiracy content. And I think the
conspiracy content is going to grow and the hammer is going to keep striking
down. There was a time where Pepsi or McDonald's would just come out and go
"That's not true!" and everyone would go "Yeah, that was kind of dumb. Eyeballs do
cost a lot." And everyone goes home. We're entering an age where even saying
something like that could get your Twitter account banned. So golden age of
conspiracy theories is coming up. Will we be allowed to talk about them? Who knows?
I just figured that's food for thought. As I'm pointing at the camera, that's the
only... those are the only jokes. That's the only joke that you won't get if... well
you got the joke anyways, but I'm pointing at the camera. Dead Rapper Radio at
gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
Dead Rapper Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime
podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it
today. Have a great one guys.
[Music]