A young boy out camping with his friends and family tells them a bizarre story of a past life.
And then we travel back to the year 1971 and visit a movie theater in San Francisco.
A man has made a movie and it is premiering tonight. But the movie wasn't made to entertain people.
It was made to catch a serial killer today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I just ate a bag of Halloween candy.
My tummy hurts. I got a little bit of sugar in me. I got a lot of sugar in me. I'm all
super bloated now. Anyway I'm just like laying there like pearl from Blade. I'm in just in front
of a bank of computers right now. I'm just hitting buttons lazily. And while I'm doing that one of
our legacy patreons happens to walk and he's like why is it so dark in here? Why is it so spooky?
What happened to you? Alexander Nesticoe. Alexander Nesticoe one of our legacy patreons.
He's like can I turn on the light? Yeah yeah just it's blinding. It blinds me.
Ugh I feel so bloated. Alexander has the privilege of pushing me around in a wheelbarrow for the
rest of this episode. He is going to be our captain, our pilot, and our wheelbarrow pusher this episode.
If he can't support the patreon I totally get it. Just help spread the word about the show.
That also really helps out a lot. Alexander, whom you got your back brace on? Push me, push me young
man into the Dead Rabbit Row vote. Then prepare to row me across the Pacific Ocean. We are headed
to Russia. I'm just laying there and we're rowing out. We're headed to Volgograd, Russia,
and it's the year 1996. And we walk into this maternity ward and there's a little baby in a
box. Not a box that's grim. A little baby in like a little crib. You know like they have lines of
cribs in maternity ward. You've seen them in movies or maybe you've been in one. We've all
been in them actually but we were babies. But maybe you've been in one recently. I don't know.
Anyways, the point is that we're in a maternity ward and we see a little baby dude just kind of
going me making baby noises. And we look at him and we're like that's an interesting looking kid.
Like I figured that kid, I figured that kid has something to do with this story obviously because
I'm talking about it. And we follow the kid home. This sounds grim but it's not. We follow the kid
home. His name is Boris Kipri Yovanovich and he's only been alive for two weeks. That's crazy dude.
A little baby. He's been alive on this planet for 14 days. I mean that happens all the time.
So that's not so amazing but it's actually pretty amazing when you look at a baby you're like dude
you just, you like just came out of a human and now you're like chilling here. Like babies are
trippy. Babies are super weird. But this whole segment is not about how weird I think babies are
because I just find them so bizarre. Little baby people. This baby is weird for other reasons.
So we're hanging out in this dude's house and we see this little two-year-old Boris and he's
just sitting there and his head is perfectly stable. Now you're like Jason where are you going with
this? My head's perfectly stable. Everyone's head is perfectly stable. And you're right. However,
not when you're two weeks old. Normally it takes a baby two to four months to be able to develop
the neck muscles so it's perfectly stable. But little Boris here, his neck, he's looking around.
He's scanning the room. And that's weird. That's a whole story. Okay so our next story. I was joking.
He's this little dude. He can hold up his head. His mom realizes there's something odd about him
because that's not normal. By the time he was 18 months old he could read and draw. So he's like
drawing pictures of stuff. They don't say how good of an artist he is. You have sucked. You've
been terrible at it. They're like oh that's really cool. He can draw. Are you going to hang this up
in your fridge? No, this is awful. This is horrible. But it's cool that he can draw. Not that he can
draw well, but he can read. He's reading Dr. Seuss books and stuff like that. But wait, how could
he talk? Could he talk at 18 months? Is that when babies talk? Anyways, the point is is that I
guess you're not supposed to be able to read or draw at 18 months. They also notice as he was
getting older he would know a lot about stars and star systems and constellations even though
they never really told him anything about that. He's like me draw you a picture. They're like
don't draw us a picture. We know what you're talking about. He's like but I like drawing. They're
like hiding the crowns from him. He draws these abominations. So when Boris is around the age of
seven, his family and family friends, they all go camping. They go on this little camping trip.
Boris is sitting there throwing pine cones into the fire. Everyone's just kind of sitting around
having a good time. Boris tells this story to the people closest to him. A little seven-year-old boy
turns to his left with a super strong neck, turns to his right 180 degrees perfectly, and goes now
that you have all gathered here, my friends and family, I want to tell you who I really am.
I'm from Mars. Well, I used to be from Mars. He's throwing another pine cone into the fire for
dramatic effect. He tells them this story thousands of years ago. Mars was once populated by an
advanced civilization. Boris is flying a little space car, leaving behind one gilded city for the
next. The entire planet was beautiful with civilized cities popping up here and there across the
landscape. Boris was only 14 years old when he was trained in the art of warfare. Boris looks to
his left with his alien neck, looks to his right. He's flying with a fleet of Martian jet fighters.
He said that Martians would live to be incredibly old, but they only looked as old as a 35-year-old
human. The way he's describing it is not like they were great aliens or anything like that.
They appeared to be humanoid, however they had one big difference between humans and Martians.
But everything else, he didn't talk so much about alien biology. They're very, very human-like.
They had these vast cities. They would age to about the age 35, and then they would stop aging,
but they would live much longer than that. They had mastered the way to stop aging because they
didn't breathe in as much oxygen as we do. A lot of times their vehicles had a tube inside of them
that you would get in, and it was pure carbon dioxide. You would breathe it in and then expel
oxygen, or maybe you didn't have any oxygen. Maybe they just loved carbon dioxide so much they just
went, "Oh!" and they held their breath for the next 500 years. But I don't think they even had much
oxygen on Mars even back then. They would breathe in primarily carbon dioxide, and that's what kept
them young and long-lived. He turns to the people next to him at the fire, and he goes, "You see,
oxygen is poison. That's what actually causes humans on earth to get old and die. It's oxygen."
On Mars, we didn't have that problem. He said that the Martian race had actually mastered
interstellar travel. They used portals to go through these things. However, they had two
types of vehicles they could also use to fly around. One was the flying saucer. That was used to
travel from planet to planet and from star system to star system. But the triangle UFOs people see,
those are scout ships, small distance ships, Mars to the moon, moon to earth, things like that.
You never see a triangle in deep space. But he wasn't really skilled in either of those things.
He was trained as a jet fighter, as a Martian fighter pilot.
He's still flying over the vast landscape of Mars with a battalion headed towards an unknown target.
He said that even though they appeared to be human, the one trait that they had different
were that their fingers were incredibly long. They had actually evolved to be able to use their
spacecraft more efficiently. Now, let me pause the story for a second. That's not how that works,
right? Generally, you would build a vehicle. We don't build space shuttles and be like,
"Hope you're an octopus, dude." They're like, "What?" They're like, "Yeah, you wouldn't be able to pilot
the shuttle way better if you were an octopus." "But I'm not an octopus." "Yeah, but if you were,
maybe you'll evolve at some point while you're flying the space shuttle. Maybe that'll work."
But whatever. Whatever. I mean, he's already reincarnated from Mars. I thought that was out of
everything the most unbelievable part of the story. But anyways, they were normally humanoid people.
They just had really long fingers. Pushing all these buttons and stuff like that. They were able
to do that. They could have just built one with no buttons, voice command, but they did it because
they're Martians. So why is this advanced society that has mastered interstellar travel that is
far older than anything on Earth? All of this would have happened when I said thousands of ago.
I'm talking like 10,000 years ago, long before humanity was even thinking that there were other
planets out there. They just saw twinkling lights. The jet fighter battalion is flying through ridge.
It crests the mountaintop and sees their rival country in their crosshairs. Boris, 14-year-old
Martian, flips on his weapon systems and opens fire on the city. People are running up. All the
babies are holding their neck up looking. These ships are flying over the city. They're coming
back for another run. Martian alarms go off. They sound just like Earth alarms, but they're
backwards. There's a bunch of wolves running around too. That city's Martian fighters are
getting up in their ships. They're getting blown up while they're even trying to take off their
runway. Extra long fingers just flying all over the place from people getting blown up.
Boris and his battalion struck a devastating blow into their rivals territory. They head back
for victorious celebration. But all wars have to come to an end. They either end with peace treaties
or the fact that there's no life visible on Mars today. It ended like this. The rival city states
of Mars had amassed their own nuclear weapons. And Boris, all of his friends, all of his family,
all of his countrymen died in the nuclear holocaust before we even fashioned the first spear here on
Earth. Boris is sitting around the campfire poking at it with a stick. He tells this story to his
friends and family. I find this very fascinating because on the one hand we've talked about people
who say they reincarnated. I always talk about that guy who said he's from Atlantis and things like
that. This is an interesting story because he tells this to his friends and family. He's not
telling it to a reporter. He's telling it to people he trusts. And people laugh at him at the campfire.
He's a seven-year-old boy telling the story of this great Martian war. He's also telling this story
in 2003. So talking about triangles and saucers, obviously those UFOs have been seen for decades.
And by 2003 the Iron Curtain had fallen and we started to get a lot of UFO reports coming out of
the Eastern Europe and they started getting our reports as well. But for a seven-year-old to
know that stuff, it's not impossible. Now there also is a thing we have to look at of retconning,
is that someone could easily tell the story today and say, "I was seven years old when that first
happened." So it could be completely made up. It could 100% be completely made up. But
continuing with the narrative, he tells this story to his friends and family. People are kind
of chuckling at it. They don't really believe him. It is unbelievable. And that should have been the
end of it. But what happened was when they go, when the vacation's over and they go back to town,
people start making fun of him in town. The friends and the family who probably should have just kept
it to themselves, they thought it was kind of wacky. It's not like they went back to town and go,
"Hey, this kid told us this weird story. They were actively making fun of this kid
for weaving such a bizarre story." And so for a while, he didn't want that mockery. Nowadays,
like there are photos of him. He was born in 1996. So what would that make him right now?
That'd make him only about 24 years old. So still, that's right. That's not,
math is right, right? I'm not from Mars. I'm not really good at math. But
he's only about 24 years old. Now again, he could be retconning it. He could obviously have come
up with the story two years ago and built this whole backstory. But I think it's an interesting
setup. We take the narrative at face value where he wasn't out to get any publicity. He was just
kind of felt comfortable to share this story. That's not even the end of it. There's a couple
key interesting factors here. One, he said that there's a way for us to avoid the same fate as
the Martians. He said that the Sphinx, I know this is where it starts to get kind of goofy again,
right? That story in and of itself, the reincarnated Martian story, I find fascinating. But then he
says, the Sphinx has some sort of super secret tech in it. And there's a lever behind one of its ears.
He doesn't, and this is where it starts to get interesting again, right? You kind of lost me
when you introduced the Egyptian mythological part because that's so tropish. That's so generic. But
anyways, he said that behind one of the Sphinx ears, there's a lever or a mechanism that if you press
it, this thing will open up and it will help us from destroying ourselves. And he also said the
Great Pyramid of Giza has something in it as well that will help us, but he doesn't know how to get
that one. So the question you would ask, and the question people have asked them, so what's in the
Sphinx, bro? Like, you know how to access it. What's in there? And he goes, I don't know. I just know
like there's a button behind its ear or something like that. I'm like, what? So wait, you know there's
a button there, but you don't know what's in it. He's like, no, I don't know what's in it. I just know
that there's something to do with it. And they go, okay, what's in the Great Pyramid of Giza? He's
like, I don't know. I have no idea. Now this is interesting because I've used this before as well,
and it could be a crutch. I'm not for sure, but if you're making it up, the answer would be simply
easy to make up. I actually have more respect for people who go, so you're reincarnated from
Atlantis. What was the monetary system like there? Do you remember that? And that guy who says he's
half Atlantean or from Atlantis or whatever, if he went, uh, I don't remember. I don't remember
ever spending money. I was a really young kid. Like, do you remember how money worked when you were
seven? If you died when you were seven, that got dark quick. And someone from the future asked you,
how was money in the 21st century? You'd be like, what? I was seven. But there's always an answer.
Oh no, monetary, there was no money. Everything was perfect. Everything was super good. And you
just got up and like seashells fell into your lap and you ate seashells and everything was built
out of seashells and da-da-da-da. When people are making it up, they have an answer for everything.
If you took someone, if you took someone who was seven years old, or he was 14 when all this,
when he died in Mars, but if you took someone who was 14 years old now and teleported him 10,000
years in the future, and they asked him, hey, so who won the election? He's like, there was an election?
What are you talking about? I don't even know what you're talking about. I'm seven years old. Ask me
about Fortnite. They're like, what? What's Fortnite? So you would be limited to the information you'd
have access to. I think it's more interesting when people who weave these tales say, I don't know.
I don't have an answer to that question. But there's also two other interesting things coming
from this. This is going a lot longer than I thought it was going to go, but one, he says that
he's a reincarnated alien. So that opens up a whole host of things, because you almost want to think
like reincarnation, if it exists, is a localized phenomenon. Like I may die and become a grass
hopper and then become a cow and then become like a lily pad. But it's weird to think that I may die
and become a cow on some alien planet a billion miles away. Or you die and then you're reincarnated
as an amoeba on a meteorite floating around in the middle of nowhere. It's weird to think of
reincarnation past the bounds of Earth. So that even opens up a can of worms. Like is reincarnation
geographically based? Is Mars close enough that if you died on Mars you'd get reincarnated on Earth?
There's a whole bunch of interesting questions there. But then oxygen is poison. Now again,
he's seven years old. If we take the story of face value and he told his story when he was seven
years old, oxygen is poison is actually on the conspiracy theory iceberg. It's been around for
a while that people believe oxygen actually kills you. Alexander, grab that wheelbarrow and then
call in that carbonicopter. You're gonna push me onto that carbonicopter, come heller high water.
I am now on board. We are headed out to the underground. Helicopter's flying. Alexander,
I'm taking up the whole thing. Everyone's pressed up against the window. Alexander though is able
to fly us away from Mars and he sees this cave in the middle of a mountainside back on Earth.
Helicopter's flying through this cave system. We land in the middle of this cave and we see
a bunch of people walking around. A bunch of young, healthy, fit people. And then there's us.
And then there's us. The world's most sugary man pushed inside of a carbonicopter. Roll me out like
Violet from Willy Wonka. And then the rest of you just get off with free will and legs that work.
Everyone jumps back off the carbonicopter and we're looking at all these people. They're super
fit. The dudes are wearing tank tops and shorts and the girls are wearing tank tops and shorts.
It's a beautiful society. Everyone's super healthy. And then one of these people walk up to us and
they just they're beautiful and they go, "Whoa, what are you guys doing here? You guys look like
a bunch of circus freaks as opposed to us. Look how great we look." And I'm like, "Hey,
don't talk to my buddies like that." Secondly, how do you look so good? And they go, "The secret is..."
And then we realize it's probably been about, I don't know, 45 seconds a minute. And there's no
oxygen in this cave. Yet somehow we're able to survive. We are in the headquarters of
undergroundwellness.com. And they are one of the supporters of the belief that oxygen is poison.
It's on the conspiracy theory iceberg. We'll save this Zodiac Killer story for tomorrow because I
want to spend some time on this. I didn't know that last segment was going to run so long. So if
you're a huge fan of the Zodiac Killer, shame on you because he's a lame serial killer. They're all
lame. But he's one of the lamest. We'll get into that tomorrow. But let us breathe in this pure
carbon dioxide and we feel ourselves getting stronger. We feel our bodies becoming healthier.
Our vision clears up. And then all of a sudden we're standing there and overclosure gone now.
We're wearing shorts and tank tops. We're like, "What? This is weird." Oxygen is poison. Goes like this.
95% of the oxygen we breathe in goes to the mitochondria. That's the powerhouse of the cell.
So you've got a little cell inside you and inside the cell is the mitochondria. So when you breathe
in, you're fueling the mitochondria in your body. But only 95% of the oxygen you breathe
actually goes to fuel the mitochondria. The other 5% becomes this thing known as free radicals.
There are little dudes inside your body, little mohawks, little pierce steers and they're walking
around and they've got little bats and they're beating up the apple stands in your body. They
float around in your liver. They're like, "Hey, nice liver here. It would be horrible if I started
bashing stuff up." And they're like, "No, please. It's the purple dragon gang. They're back." And
they're kicking over stuff in your liver. 5% of all the oxygen you breathe and you breathe a lot of it
becomes free radicals and they just float around in your body and they start beating you up from
the inside. The free radical, again, I'm not saying, this is the last time I'm going to say this,
but everything from here forward, I don't believe is true. So the free radicals in this theory,
they're walking around, they're pushing over old ladies inside your body, and that's what causes
parts of your body to go haywire. It gums up your system, damages your DNA and can be one of the
causes of cancer. It can actually also burn through your membranes to cause Alzheimer's, Parkinson's,
Lou Gehrig's disease, stuff like that. So this is what the underground wellness
oxygen is poison conspiracy people believe, that 5% of all the oxygen you breathe is actually doing
damage to you. They also say, one of their theories is this, one of their theories is this, when someone
is completely deprived of oxygen, let's say you're completely deprived of oxygen, whatever scenario
it takes, your body's there, your head's not chopped off or anything like that, but you've suffocated,
you have no oxygen in you. What they do is they take you to the hospital and they give you oxygen
and brings you back to life. Now generally, if you've been without oxygen for three minutes,
it starts to cause brain damage and you can become brain dead. Everything else is fine,
but your brain is dead. People who believe oxygen is poison believes that brain death is caused by
giving you oxygen. So if you have no oxygen and you're turning blue, instead of putting a mask
on somebody and spraying a bunch of oxygen in their face, you need to slowly, slowly give them
a little bit of oxygen. And they said, if you slowly raise the oxygen level, they'll turn out fine.
So you could be three to four minutes with no oxygen and super blue and stuff, and then you give them
a little bit of oxygen, give them a little bit of sweet sweet oxygen, you'll be fine. They also say
that breathing can make it harder for you to breathe. This is an interesting one. Oxygen makes it
harder for you to breathe. I remember looking at that and I was like, what? When you have COPD,
what happens is the membranes, little bubbles inside your lungs, they fill up with air and then
they deflate and that helps filter out air and it just kind of helps you breathe in general.
COPD is where the sacs in your lungs, they're a little tiny bubble sacs in your lungs
start to get distorted, they start to get big and puffy. It's like a balloon. If you blow a balloon
up and then you open the little hole nozzle thingy, all the air will rush out. But you know how if you
take a bigger balloon and you blow it up and you let it out, the bag will hang and there'll still be
some air in the bottom of the balloon. Does that make sense? Like if you have a little balloon,
it'll all immediately go out, but the bigger the balloon, you blow it up, it'll sag down
like clam chowder in a paper bag and there will still be some left. That's what COPD is.
Your little sacs in your lungs don't completely deflate anymore. They're bigger and so only some
of the air comes out. If you get enough of those semi-inflated bags in your lungs that are technically
still full of oxygen, it makes it harder for you to breathe. There's less lung capacity in there
because more of it's taken up by all of these little bags. Yes, you can make the claim oxygen
makes it harder for you to breathe, but you see all those steps in the middle there? Oxygen itself
does not cause the sacs to expand and distort and get grody and not work. That's not oxygen doing
that. Those are other things going on in your body because otherwise then everyone would have COPD.
But it's not. So you can make the claim oxygen makes it harder for you to breathe, oxygen causes
cancer, but that's you're missing so many steps in the middle. It's the same thing as saying walking
causes you to fall off cliffs. Yes, I would say probably 99% of all the people falling off cliffs
were walking at some point and they fell off the cliff, but then you can't say well walking kills
you because most people who die were walking at some point right before they died. That's the same
logic there. Watch now there'll be a conspiracy theory about everybody who walks. It's the same,
it's the exact same thing. Doing A causes X, but there's so many steps missing there, but there's
a huge group of people who believe this. Now we're in the underground caves because when I read that
this was on a website called undergroundwellness.com it's just one website. There's tons of people who
believe this. I imagine I was like oh dude these people believe this so much they're actually
hiding underground in giant oxygen depleted cities. No, it meant underground wellness like
these are the medical tips. Your doctor doesn't want you to know. You're that doctor, he just
wants you to become brain dead and blue. He's a big fan of the Smurfs. He's a big fan of Eiffel
65. He wants you to get blue bro, but here at underground wellness we teach you the stuff
that they don't want you to know. Like oxygen kills you. Another weird thing they always say,
because I read a couple sites on this, they always make a statement similar to this.
How does oxygen kill? The same way metal rusts and a half eating apple turns brown
by a process termed oxidation or oxidative stress. Yes, oxygen turns steel brown,
steel can survive 1400 degrees Fahrenheit, I'm not steel. And I understand like there are things
steel can do that I can't and there are things that I can do that steel can't and I can do a
way a lot more than a half eating apple. I understand in the mind they're thinking whoa
if oxygen can destroy something as hard as steel, imagine what it could do to me because I'm soft
and fleshy. That's not the way that it works. It's observational science, but it's based on
a bad observation. It's a bizarre comparison between the two. But this theory is very popular.
It's one of those things like sun gazing. I will say this, these people don't
seem to be saying well that's it, no oxygen for me. This is a weird one because there's no
fix for it. People who believe in sun gazing are like yeah you look at the sun for like
what was it like 10 seconds the first week and then 15 seconds then don't do that by the way,
but they have this thing. It's supposed to open your third eye and all that stuff. Ormus where
you like pee in a cup and you separate the gold out of your urine. I covered that one a long time ago.
You drink it for health benefits. Like you're not healthy, but if you drink the ormus that'll
make you healthy. There's no fix to this oxygen thing. I guess you could probably hang out in a
chamber like a Michael Jackson S. Khyperbaric chamber that might help you, but there's really
no fix for this one. It's like telling someone you're going to die from breathing and then people
go what can I do to stop that and they're like well you stop breathing but that's just going to kill
you quicker. This is a weird one because they're telling you something's going on, but as far as
I could tell there's no long-term fix for it. I think it's just limit your oxygen exposure.
This sounds fake, right? This sounds like something someone made up in 1952 was a joke. The world's
first troll. The world's first. I'm going to make up a conspiracy theory and see how many people can
buy it. So he makes up the idea that oxygen is poison, but people still talk about it today.
But what is so weird about this whole combination of things is I've heard oxygen is poison for the
longest time. It's actually not hard to research. I didn't cover it on the conspiracy theory iceberg
because it wasn't obscure at all. I'd been hearing it in and out of the conspiracy theory
circles for a long time, but I researched this stuff and I researched this stuff for fun.
How in the world did a 7-year-old boy in Russia know about this conspiracy theory? It's not impossible
that in 2003 when this kid told this story, it's not impossible that he'd come across us at some
point, but it's so it's such a bizarre detail in his story of Martian colonies and it's almost a
throwaway line. It's not even integral to the plot of the story. I was born on Mars, there was this
great Martian war. We want, I forgot to, one of the things was like we're here. Some of the Martians
have been reincarnated on Earth to prevent Earth from having a nuclear holocaust. We're here to
help change the world and stuff like that. So you have this narrative thread and then just in the
middle of it, oh by the way oxygen's poison, that's how we are able to live so long. We would limit
our oxygen as much as possible and we actually, when we were traveling long distances, we'd be in
only carbon dioxide environments. It's weird that this boy crafting this story throws in an element
from a hippy-dippy underground wellness conspiracy theory. They didn't invent the conspiracy theory,
but it's in that holistic realm. Oxygen is poison. That this boy in Russia telling the story
plucks that detail out of the ether and puts it in to explain why Martians live so long. Now I
don't think oxygen is poisonous. I do think, I don't want to be controversial or anything,
but I do think oxygen is required for a life on this planet. Please, please don't unsubscribe. I
know it's going to piss a lot of people off, but I do believe that you need to breathe in oxygen
and expel carbon dioxide to live, but there are a lot of people who would disagree with me on that
or would disagree with me at least on how much oxygen we actually need. And that's fine, we can
have those disagreements. We can have those disagreements until you're blue in the face,
but all that aside, I find it so fascinating that it's also a part of this boy's Martian story.
I guess we will actually know the truth someday on this one. Just buy a couple tickets,
fly out to Egypt, get an incredibly long ladder, and start digging around on the Sphinx's ear.
According to Boris, what's in that Sphinx will save the world. Now he believed that he was one of
the people who would usher in a new age, but who knows? That person may be you if you find that
switch behind the Sphinx's ear.
Bye guys!