Did the elites of the world try to control a secret nectar and keep it from the masses?
And then we cover a disturbing story.
A story about drug addiction and body horror.
When a young couple begins smoking meth, they just use it as a supplement for their sexual
activities.
But soon they find that meth is not only transforming their personalities, it's melting them from
the inside out.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have a great weekend.
I hope you guys have either some cool stuff to do on the weekend or nothing to do on the
weekend.
Cause on my days off I like to do nothing.
I just want to sit.
I just want to kind of just sit and absorb media and not move.
That's my day off.
But some days some guys going to be like, "Hey, hope you have a great weekend white water
rafting."
I'm like, "What?
No, I don't like that."
Next thing I know I'm like, "Uh, curse you Jeannie."
Let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, Camp Counselor Steve.
Camp Counselor Steve.
Thank you so much for supporting the show.
You're going to be our pilot, our chauffeur this episode.
I guess that's probably not a compliment.
Hey, great.
I donated money to this dude's show.
Now I'm his chauffeur.
But thank you so much.
You can't support the Patreon.
That's fine too.
Just help get the word out about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
So Camp Counselor Steve, let's go ahead and hop in the Jason Jollopi first.
We're going to take a little drive.
Cars driving, little dotted line across the map.
We are going to, it's a little more than a dotted line.
We're in ancient China.
So again, Camp Counselor Steve's like, "Oh man, I think I left my front door open.
I thought we were just going to be gone for a minute."
No, we drive all the way back to ancient China.
There once was a deep kept secret that the elites didn't want us mere mortals to know.
And so we're walking through the snow.
We see this old Chinese dude.
I don't know.
He may have been in his 20s, but old has in the sense that this is ancient China.
This is like 2 BC.
He's taking a bunch of snow and he's like thrown in his backpack.
He's like, "Hope this stays snow by the time I get down.
Otherwise, my journey is for naught."
He walks back down to the emperor and the emperor's like, "Do you have my snow?"
And the explorer throws his back down.
Actually, he's probably more polite than that.
He's like, "Here's your snow."
He gives it gently to the emperor and the emperor's like, "Yes.
This is what we must keep from the mortals."
When George Washington became president, there was a little bit of a time jump there.
Camp counselor Steve was like, "What?
We just magically appeared in old timey colonial clothes?"
"Yes, we did."
When George Washington was president, he said, "I want to have a lavish party."
And these people are writing down notes like lavish party.
And he's like, "And I want it to have the secret."
And everyone's like, "Mm-hmm."
And they all wink at each other.
At the same time, a lot of confusion.
People thought they were being flirted with.
But no, they were like, "Hmm, the secret."
"Shhh, secret."
When he died, he spent $200 on this secret concoction at the time, which would be like
5,600 in today money, right?
Which he really still isn't even that much.
And I was like, "$200 in George Washington?
That must be like 100,000 a day."
And I was like, "Oh, just 5,600."
That's like a car.
That's like a used car.
Nice flex, George Washington.
But when he died, they found tools that he used to personally make this concoction.
It had been passed down.
It's not like the ancient Chinese emperor was like, "Hey, George Washington, here you
go."
It had been passed down through the ages.
And at one time or another, the masses started to get just the taste of this.
But it was so expensive to make.
The ingredients were so rare, really.
I mean, other than the snow on the mountain.
It was really hard for the commoner to get it.
So what was that ancient concoction?
Well, my friends, bing!
Now we're standing in a ice cream shop.
You're like, "Jason, are you just telling us trivia about ice cream?"
No.
Well, yes.
But there's two reasons why I'm doing this.
So we're standing in this ice cream shop and there's a guy behind the counter.
It's President George Washington.
He's been reincarnated as a soda jerk.
Those are the guys who would put ice cream and stuff and then put a little soda in it.
Hand it to us.
So we're drinking ice cream sodas.
It's really interesting, at least to me.
Ice cream, I was out having ice cream with Sabine the other day and this is how I am.
I go, I'm like, "Lick.
Lick.
Lick."
And then I go, "I wonder when ice cream was invented.
Like I can never shut my brain off."
Sabine's like, "I don't know."
Like probably when people had access, you would need ice, which was hard to get for
a long time, like mass shipping of ice and butter and stuff like that.
And I go, "Hmm."
And I went home and I looked it up and I found from the International Dairy Foods Association
I found all this information.
I found their one-sided information.
There's some insider.
He's going to email me later.
He's like, "Oh, you don't know half the truth."
And starts sending me all these diagrams.
It was invented in the 2BC and that was just basically those gross snow cones where they
would take snow and then put honey on it and they eat it and stuff like that.
And it went like, the Romans had it and in the medieval ages they had it.
And it wasn't until about the 1500s that we actually had ice cream where it was like
milk.
Milk were its actual dairy product.
Before that there were a bunch of losers that just had to eat ice with gross toppings
on it.
The 1500s they were able to add the cream and the sugar and all that stuff.
But even then it wasn't even available to the public until 1660.
And it was still very expensive.
Like the chances of, there were people who lived and died that never ever tasted ice cream.
Now to be fair, there were people who lived and died that you haven't done a lot of things.
But ice cream just seems so normal, right?
It seems like something that everyone should do.
When a baby's born, here you go.
Entire generations died without even knowing that ice cream existed.
But anyway, even when it did exist people couldn't get it.
So here's one more bit of ice cream trivia.
I thought this was interesting.
Because again, we're talking about conspiracies, right?
We're all at this ice cream shop.
And then we're drinking these ice cream sodas.
It's soda water with ice cream in it.
And the door gets kicked open.
We're like, "Ugh!"
And it's a bunch of religious leaders.
And then at that point we look at the clock and that doesn't tell us anything.
So we look at a calendar and it's Sunday.
And these religious leaders go, "You shouldn't be drinking that stuff."
They're like knocking it out of our hands.
And we're like, "Whoa, whoa, we don't want any trouble, clergy."
They have leather jackets.
What happened was in 1874 you had the religious community thought you should not drink something
so rich and sinful on a Sunday.
But these places are super popular.
I mean, George Washington's working at one for crying out loud.
That's a good sign.
So people were going seven days a week to be drinking at these soda shops, these ice cream
sodas.
And the religious leader said, "No one should do anything so sinful."
And that delicious, that creamy, delicious soda, "No, I must resist.
I must resist."
You can't drink that on Sundays.
So then the ice cream, the ice cream, the Illuminati got together and they go, "We'll
show them."
They created the Sunday, which was just scoops of ice cream.
It was syrup on them, like chocolate syrup.
And that is why that's called a Sunday.
Eventually they changed the Y to an E, how it's spelled today, because the religious
controversy had ended.
But that's why it's called a Sunday.
Because it was basically a, "You can't tell us what to eat."
Technically they did because they stopped serving it with the soda.
The religious problem was specifically with the soda and the ice cream.
So they started serving ice cream, no soda, with syrup on it, and that was called a Sunday.
Oh, and one last bit of trivia.
During World War II, so you know this is the second one, right?
During World War II, you had the different branches of the U.S. military.
They had a war.
They had an internal war.
So not only did you have the World War going on, you had this internal war.
Each branch of the military was trying to figure out the best ice cream bar.
Like they wanted to be able to serve their men like the most toppings available.
As like they're like, "Sir, sir, we need to get these fuel lines.
We need to get the Germans have blown up our transportation lines."
She's like, "Shut up!
Do we use the chocolate sprinkles or the multicolored sprinkles?"
They're like, "Ah, general patents, slapping soda jerks."
They had this huge war over who could serve the best ice cream to the point that in the
Pacific front, where we were fighting the Japanese, there was a floating ice cream bar.
Now, I don't think it was just like one dude.
I don't think it was like a dingy.
I think it was probably like a pretty sizable boat.
I don't know if it was all ice cream, actually.
They're like, "Sir, sir, protect the ice cream."
Like Kamikaze playing crashes into the ice cream bar, just gets stuck in the ice cream.
The pilot gets out and starts eating some.
"No, they've taken our resources."
I don't know if it was, they dedicated a single destroyer to serve nothing but ice cream.
It's shooting out chocolate syrup.
I think on one of their existing ships, they just happened to have an ice cream bar, but
it is true.
They did.
Each branch of the military would get in fights over who could serve the best ice cream bar.
And George Washington wipes a little tear away from his face and he goes, "I always
knew being reincarnated as a soda jerk would make me proud to be an American once again."
And he's just floating over the Pacific battle and planes are blowing up, but the ice cream
is safe.
The reason why I wanted to tell this story is one, I found it very fascinating.
I found all that ice cream stuff fascinating.
Secondly, because this next story is gross.
This next story, "Enjoy your ice cream now," is what I'm saying.
"Enjoy your light-filled, happy memories of George Washington, transparent George Washington,
revenue ice cream, and your time in the Pacific eating ice cream as war is raging around you."
Think about those happy memories as we move to this next story.
Hey everyone, I'm back.
I'm back.
I can run in around the corner and everyone's like, "What did I even know you were gone?
You were just eating ice cream with us."
I actually took a break after I recorded that story.
I went for a jog.
I started doing intermittent fasting.
I've moved away from the keto because I think I've kind of hit the limit of what I can lose
on that.
I can eat fast.
I only eat between noon and 6 PM.
I can go up to 8 PM as my official window, but I'm usually eating dinner pretty early.
I'm jogging.
You can just eat a bunch of ice cream.
That's the cool thing about intermittent fasting, as opposed to keto.
If I want ice cream, as long as it's the right amount of calories and stuff, I can treat myself
to some ice cream.
And Camp Counselor Steve paid for all of our ice cream, so we're good.
I can eat as many calories of ice cream as I want as long as someone else is paying for
it.
So, Steve, let's hop in that carbonicopter.
We're done jogging.
We're leaving behind the ice cream stand.
George Washington's ghost is waving to us.
We're headed out to an American city.
And in this American city sits an apartment complex.
We're going to land on the roof.
We're going to enter this apartment complex.
And in this complex, we are going to meet a young couple.
"Hey guys, what's up?"
And they wave back to us.
We don't have the real names of these people.
So we'll call the woman Brittany, the husband Tom, and the son we'll call Barrett.
So if those are the real names, it's just the shot in the dark.
This story comes from a website called AeroWid, which before I found out, I've always had
a fascinating, I don't use like hard drugs and I used to smoke weed and stuff like that
way back in the day.
But I always have a fascination with drug stories, with the effects and how people are
going through it.
Particularly bad drug stories.
I don't want to hear about, "Oh yeah dude, I took LSD and everything was normal."
I want to hear that, right?
I want to hear about like really trippy horror stories, right?
Horror stories involving drugs.
There is a website called AeroWid, which I'm sure a lot of you guys are familiar with.
It's a very, very popular website.
It doesn't seem to be as active as it used to be, but I used to, "Oh dude, I used to
just consume it.
I was just like this monster.
Give me your horrible experiences.
Let me eat them."
Any drug you can think of, this website, it's very informative and has a lot of harm reduction
stuff to it.
But it also has reviews.
Basically right, and you guys know I love reading reviews.
What's better than a Yelp review?
A Yelp review for methamphetamine.
So AeroWid has all of these experiences or trip reports a lot, I believe is the technical
term.
And back in 2007, there was a trip report posted on there called "Skin."
And I remember reading it.
I don't know if I read it right when it came out, but I read it about 10 years ago.
I read it a while ago.
It's almost iconic.
You either have red skin or you're going to hear it now.
Because this story is 100% pure body horror.
We're walking through this apartment complex and we see this couple.
We see Brittany, Tom, and Barrett.
We just kind of wave to them.
They wave to us and they go into their apartment.
This New Year's Eve 2006.
I'm assuming they were casual drug users because if someone came up to me and said, "Hey, you
know, meth makes sex feel really good."
I'd be like, "Fine, fact of the day.
Go about my business."
But Brittany, because I'm not a psychonaut, I'm not someone who wants to go and explore
drug use and stuff like that.
I'll read the reviews, right?
I'll read the reviews.
But Brittany and Tom had been hearing for a while that methamphetamine makes sex feel
so much better.
For them, they said, "Hey, let's try it.
New Year's Eve, let's smoke some crystal meth and have sex."
Because we hear so many good reviews about it on Yelp.
So they do.
They smoke meth and Brittany says, "The sex was amazing."
It was just exactly what the rumors were.
When she woke up to go to work the next day, she had a little bit of meth left.
Smoke that went to work.
But when she comes home from work, there's a gram of meth.
Her boyfriend went and copped some more.
And that would be the beginning of them smoking every single day for about two months.
And when I say every day, multiple times a day.
They may have started off just smoking it in the morning, but as the story progresses,
they're smoking lots of crystal meth.
By the time three weeks pass, she starts to notice something wrong with her skin.
It's brittle.
It's like paper almost.
Now, it's not falling apart, but it just feels like it's lost some of its firmness.
But that's not the only thing.
That's not the only thing that's going wrong with this young mother.
Her body's starting to swell.
This is happening at the same time she's severely dehydrated from her continual use of meth.
Because we're three weeks now, if her using it constantly.
Her and Tom are using it constantly.
So she's extremely dehydrated.
She's drinking tons of water, but she can't urinate.
Or she urinates so infrequently, she realizes, wait a second.
All this water I'm drinking has to be going somewhere and must be making me bloated.
So she begins taking a diuretic to help flush the water out of her system.
But it's not working.
She's continuing to use meth.
She's continuing to drink a ton of water.
And every day she swells just a little bit more.
And then one day she notices something when she wakes up.
She kind of pushes down on her arm.
It's not just bloated anymore.
Underneath her skin, her muscles begin to feel doughy.
Not even really her muscles.
She said it was like in between her flesh and her muscles was a layer of play-doh.
And she could actually squeeze her arm or squeeze her leg.
And she could feel clay underneath.
Brittany and Tom continue to smoke meth.
She's turning into a putty from Mighty Morphin Power Rangers, but that's not going to stop
you, right?
They continue to smoke meth.
And then one day, eventually at a certain point you would just stop wanting to wake
up, right?
Because every day she wakes up something disgusting happens.
One day she's looking at her arm and she sees black little pieces of dirt on her skin.
So she brushes it away.
It doesn't really think much of it.
I need a shower.
Brushes it away.
But she continues to see these black dots.
When she talks to Tom about it, she says, "Can you check?
Can you see what's going on?
Like I don't...
I got this stuff on my arms.
I got it on my chest.
I don't know what it is."
She takes her shirt off.
She asks her husband to take a look.
It's on her back as well.
And when he touches her, he can actually press more of this black byproduct out of her skin.
Now she has it too, she discovers.
He's getting it too.
Now they had this massage oil around because these guys were total freaks, right?
They basically love sex so much that they're like, "Let's do a toxin to make sex feel better."
Not saying if you have a massage...
There's a massage artist out there.
What do they call it?
Masseuse?
They're like, "What?
I have massage oil.
I'm not a freak unless you come over, Jason."
And I'm like, "Ugh."
But not everyone who owns massage oil is a freak, but every freak owns massage oil.
How's that?
So they realize if they push on the muscles, the black dust, the black flakes will come
out of the pores.
So there you go.
This has to be a toxin.
Okay, if anything to do with the meth we're smoking, let's not stop smoking that meth.
Let's continue to smoke meth, but we'll give each other massages at night.
And Brittany would lie down and Tom would crawl on top and give her a back massage and
he could just push.
Ugh, work those muscles and this black, unknown substance would come out of her pores.
She would do the same to him, give him a massage, and she would massage this toxin out of his
body.
They got to the point though where they didn't necessarily have to push on it.
Whatever this substance was, it was also heat activated.
If they got really hot and sweaty, they'd be outside working, they'd look at their arm,
there'd be a black grime coming out of their skin.
Taking a hot shower, standing under the water, this black dust would just pour out of them
into the drain.
Now obviously there's something wrong with their bodies, right?
So what's the worst thing that they can do?
Let's get someone else involved in this horrible disgustiness.
This apartment complex has a sauna and we're sitting in the sauna, we've got our towels
on, I'm eating ice cream, eating ice cream in the sauna, I've got to eat it quick before
it melts, and Tom and Brittany walk into the sauna.
We're like, hey guys, what's up?
We've been a couple of weeks since we've seen you.
Is everything okay?
You look a little off and they're like, oh no, no, we're fine, we're fine.
We just come into the sauna because it's hot in here and their eyes shift side to side
and we're like, yeah, we know it's hot and it's nice, but what's that smell?
And they're like, what?
I don't know, it smelled like that when we came in here.
As they would sit in the sauna, this black substance would just come out of them.
The sauna opened their pores up enough that they would begin to leak it.
It made the sauna have a stench of ammonia.
Now this is a communal sauna, remember?
This is a communal sauna.
They would use the sauna for an hour at a time, four times a day, if not more.
They would just sit in there and sweat and let this toxin come out of their body because
they knew whatever this was, it shouldn't be inside of them.
It shouldn't be inside of them.
They wanted to get it out as quickly as possible.
It's February 2007.
It's been two months since their first hit of meth and this is their life now.
Brittany has lost 20 pounds.
Tom has lost 30 pounds.
One day Brittany's sitting in the sauna.
She wants this black ooze out of her.
That's on her calendar for the day.
Her blackberry ding.
Get black goo out.
And she's like, oh, I almost forgot.
I almost forgot about this disgusting illness inside of me.
Brittany goes into the sauna by herself and she's sitting there.
That heavy hot air surrounding her body, she notices something coming out of her skin,
which shouldn't be notable, right?
That's kind of the flavor du jour.
But this time it's not this black substance.
It's a white grayish goo leaking out of her.
Before it would just be black flakes that you could kind of squeeze out.
It would be like if your arm was perpetually dirty.
This was like Crisco pouring out of her body.
Her pores would just open up and this gelatinous ooze.
She said tablespoons worth.
This wasn't a nice sheen.
It didn't look like she just got out of the shower or the sauna.
This was a slick, slimy substance.
She said it was just coming out of her.
Out of everywhere.
She said it was like, quote, "Plato through a garlic press."
Unquote.
This episode sponsored by Plato, by the way.
She could just see it lift up out of her skin.
Tablespoons worth.
Just Crisco coming out of her.
She lost eight pounds in one hour in the sauna that day.
Now she thinks that it's the fat coming out of her body.
When you lose weight, the fat is secreted through your urine.
But remember, she's not able to really urinate.
And even then, I don't think the fat's just like, "Well, I don't have anywhere to go."
They jump out your pores.
I think the fat would cause some medical problems.
But I don't think if you put a plug in your pee hole and then said, "I'm not eating."
You would basically just be, you wouldn't be Plato in a garlic press.
You might just die.
Your kidneys might just not function.
But anyways, she at this point thinks this Crisco, it's sponsored by Crisco too, this
Crisco greasy substance coming out of my pores is me burning fat.
The swelling is even worse now.
She'll wake up in the morning and she can feel how bloated she is.
Her skin is bruising.
Whatever's building up inside of her is pressing so hard against her skin, it's threatening
to rip it.
It's busting blood vessels.
Her head begins to swell.
The thin layer between her skin and her skull begin to fill up with whatever this was.
She said if she brushed her hand through her hair, by the time she got to the back of her
head, her hair was soaking wet.
She could push out this white gray ooze just right out of her scalp to the point of drenching
her hair.
Her body was full of it everywhere at all times.
On top of that, there's psychological problems going on.
She says she would be up for 3-4 days.
That's why I'm thinking they were smoking a lot.
Because if you just smoked once in the morning, you're going to be buzzing for a while.
But to do that actual 3-4 day meth head thing, you have to keep re-dosing.
She's up for 3-4 days and she said she'd sleep for about an hour and then she'd be good to
go.
To the point where when she was at work, she had a job this whole time surprisingly.
Hopefully she didn't work at a sauna.
She had a job at this whole time and she said she'd be at work.
She was customer service and she would be talking to a customer and the next thing
she knew, she'd wake up.
She would have micro sleep.
She would fall asleep in a heartbeat and then wake back up and the customer would be like,
"What?"
She's like, "Oh, you must have noticed I was asleep.
Better brush my hair back."
How do you keep a job when you're leaking flu?
How do you do that?
It must have been a job at an ice cream shop.
It must have been super cold all the time.
She's like, "Oh, you want butterscotch, eh?"
She puts over to get the ice cream.
Goose falling out of her hair into the ice cream.
Here you go.
Kids are like, "Yay!"
Eventually, they go to the sauna.
Her and Tom go to the sauna and someone's standing there and is like, "Uh-uh, you're banned from
the sauna."
They're like, "What?
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?"
And they go, "Well, it might just be a coincidence, but every time you've been using it an hour
a day, four or five times a day, and every time you leave, the next person who would come
in would be choked by the smell of ammonia."
"What?
That's not us!
Ma'am, you smell like ammonia right now.
What?
Uh-uh, no, I don't."
They're plugging the guy's nose, see?
Take a big whiff.
You can't smell anything.
They were banned from the sauna, so that was their big way of helping to get this goo out
of them.
Now, they're restricted to only using the hot showers at their apartment.
One day, Brittany is taking a shower alone, that hot, hot water on her skin and she can
push the goo out.
"Ugh, get out.
Ugh."
But she falls asleep in the shower.
She'd been up too long and her body just gave up.
She actually falls asleep in the shower.
And when she wakes up, she's laying there in the bathtub.
The hot water had been pouring on her body for who knows how long.
And there is a puddle of this gray, white liquid surrounding her body.
While she was asleep, it just began pouring out of her, leaking out of wherever it could
come out.
She turns the water off and weakly gets out of the shower.
And that's when she realizes that the position she was in caused all of this Crisco-like,
fat, Play-Doh fluid, this thick, white gelatin to coalesce in her abdomen.
Imagine if you had like a bag, 'cause I don't have to give you an imagination thing, but
I'm gonna, anyways.
Imagine you had a bag of gravy and you held it up by both ends of the bag, how all the
gravy would just settle into the middle.
She was that bag of gravy.
So she gets out and she can feel all the goo that had been in her extremities in her chest
had leaked in to her abdomen.
And it's extremely painful.
It's congealed in there, it's all stuck, and she can feel it in her pelvic region as well.
She has this intense need to urinate.
Whether it was to expel the urine or to simply unplug something, she didn't know, she didn't
care, she had to urinate.
And she sat there and she pushed and she pushed and she pushed and then a hard chunk that
had congealed in her urethra.
Bleurgh.
You like that sound effect?
Comes out of her and splashes into the toilet water.
After this shower, and again we don't know how long she was in the shower for, she doesn't
know either.
Whatever substance was inside of her was completely melted loose.
Before she could sit in the sauna and would come out of the pores, she could push on it
to get more of it out.
Now it's coming out of her eyeballs.
It's coming out of her ears.
It's coming out of her nose.
It's coming out of her vagina, but that's preferable to where else it's coming out of.
She could feel it in her throat.
She said sometimes she could spit it out of her mouth.
She'd spit out speckles of this fluid, but sometimes it was so thick she just had to
swallow it.
She would feel it start clogging up her throat.
She tried to spit.
She tried to cough, but she couldn't.
She had to swallow it down.
It's no longer limited to her pores.
It's now loose in her body, coming out of every single orifice that it can.
She's lost a total of 50 pounds since December 31st.
It's March.
She begins having this delusion because she knows that this is not normal meth behavior.
Nobody would ever do meth ever.
The sex is really good, but eventually you turn to Play-Doh.
No one would ever do meth if this was true.
She begins to have this delusion.
She believed that her drug dealer wasn't giving them methamphetamines.
He was giving them something else.
It had the same initial effects of meth, but it was highly addictive and had these horrible
body-altering side effects.
She believed that the drug dealer would actually sell this meth and he would smoke it and get
addicted to it and couldn't stop using it.
She believed that at some point after enough time had passed, the drug dealer was going
to break into their apartment.
She imagined herself being chained up in a basement with his past customers.
Each of them with a meth pipe being held to their lips, forcing them to inhale.
And then the drug dealer would come down each night and he would scrape the goo off of their
skin, dry it out, and sell it as a methamphetamine.
She believed the liquids and the black dirt and all of that stuff coming out of her body
were drugs that were then to be sold to other people.
The drug dealer was actually transforming her into a recreational drug.
This delusion haunted her.
It was really the only thing she could think of to be rational of anything that's going
on.
On being turned into a drug, but the whole time she doesn't stop smoking.
She wakes up her eyes crusty with goo.
She's at work trying to concentrate but swallowing tablespoons of an unknown liquid before it
can choke her.
All of this ends when the drug dealer gets arrested.
Before she can score any more meth, she crashes for 3 days.
And apparently the husband didn't really try that hard because when she woke up 3 days
later he goes "I couldn't find any meth."
She said that "I know this must sound like meth psychosis, but after I was sober I was
still cleaning this stuff up out of my bathtub.
It's been weeks since the last time I used and I'm still cleaning up my bathroom.
I'm looking at it now.
I haven't used meth in a while.
I can still see the physical proof of this.
So this isn't meth psychosis."
There were some issues in the story where Tom began physically abusing Brittany and where
Brittany began neglecting their son.
At one point she says "My son went a whole day.
I forgot to feed him."
So the house was chaos, where before it wasn't.
That's how quickly this drug destroyed that life.
Let me read you the ending of this story.
"My husband and I haven't done any drugs at all for four weeks and things are slowly
going back to normal.
My son is happy.
He has his mother back and his daddy plays with him again.
I'm happy because I'm not so afraid anymore.
Not afraid of my husband or of dying painfully in the near future.
We're happy because we've nearly paid all the bills we neglected and have cable TV again.
We are happy because we resemble the normal, healthy family we once were.
But I still want it.
I can't sleep tonight because I want it.
I wrote this in all honesty, mostly to help myself, to remind myself why I don't want
it and I still want it."
So we don't know if she ever stayed away from methamphetamine.
The story was written in 2007 by unspun was the user's name, but we don't know who wrote
this.
We don't know what city it took place in.
So it's possible, hopefully, right, that she was able to write this out and it reminded
her of why she should never do meth again.
And she goes back to it.
She may be checking that post even today when she gets something in her head and goes, "Oh,
you know, I really like the energy.
The sex was good."
She may have to return to this post to remind herself why she should never do meth again.
Or she may have never done meth in the first place.
This may have been something else.
Because there is nothing else in the meth literature that I've ever come across that
even comes close to this.
It's possible that even if she didn't want to start smoking meth again, it would not
have any of these effects.
But there's also another option that that drug dealer, like all drug dealers do, eventually
gets out of jail.
And he comes to her apartment when she's alone with a little sample of his drug.
Without Tom's knowledge, because she knows how much he loves the happy family dynamic,
she begins using again.
Just here and there, nothing serious.
And then she goes missing.
One of a hundred thousand people that goes missing every year in America.
If Brittany ever did start smoking that drug dealer supply again, she could be, right now,
13 years later, in some basement somewhere.
Barely alive, a skeleton of the woman she once was, as a man slowly scrapes her skin,
her bruised, parchment-like skin, getting every drop of fluid out for his next batch.
And while she sits in that basement, she doesn't think about her husband, she doesn't think
about her son, she doesn't think about the pain of her skin being pressed against, all
she can think about is when will she get another hit of her drug.
Because even in the end, she still wants it.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[Music]