A woman realizes her nine-year-old son is missing and her worst nightmare begins.
A Russian man gets a mysterious message on his iPhone, causing him to change his life
forever.
And then I'm gonna tell you a personal story.
Something that happened to me on my birthday seven years ago.
It changed me profoundly.
It filled me with a sense of permanent fear.
It was the night I met an angel.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I'm recording this episode on October 3rd, but it is officially my birthday episode October
4th.
Joker comes out.
I've probably already seen that by the time you're listening to this maybe.
And October 7th.
New season of The Walking Dead.
Tell me that is not an amazing Jason-filled weekend.
I also got a birthday card from my mom.
I'm gonna open this real quick.
I'm gonna open it today early.
It says, "Happy birthday son."
Real original mom.
Thanks.
That's at the top.
"Can't look at you without feeling a surge of pride."
She put a little exclamation point there.
"Can't hear your voice without smiling."
She actually listens to the podcast now.
She'll listen to one episode.
I'll get into that later.
"Can't remember you growing up years without a little tug at the heartstrings."
"Can't let your birthday go by without reminding you how very much you're loved."
My mom likes to underline words that are like special.
And then, "I love you son very much.
Praying God's best for you.
Love always mom.
Happy birthday.
Enjoy your special day."
And then she sent me some kizash.
Mabola.
Thanks mom.
You listen to this episode?
I don't know.
She listened to the military episode, the military special.
And she said, "Yeah, it was really interesting.
It was really funny, but I didn't like that comment you made about the Joker doing something
in a cake."
Because I talked about the Joker with masturbate in someone's cake.
She goes, "Yeah, I didn't really like that part because I'm a mom."
But I love you mom.
Thank you so much for your birthday wishes.
I always appreciate it.
So let's go ahead and move on to our first story.
This episode is probably going to be long because it's birthday special.
So first off, let's hop in the carpenter car.
All of these stories today, I'm going to say this too before we get started.
All of my stories today, I personally choose them.
And I always personally choose them.
But these ones, I think, give me a sense of joy and excitement.
So let's start off with the story of a missing child.
So we're going to hop in the carpenter copter.
We are flying out to St. Cloud in Minnesota.
It's September 21st.
We're flying over this giant race.
It's giant 5K, 10K race.
So it does both.
But you have the 5K, which is the shorter track, and then you can keep running and going on
the 10K.
And then we're flying over in our helicopter.
People are getting blown away by the rotor blades.
Last night I had a dream there was a horrible plane crash.
And I found a foot from the wreckage.
And then I found a computer that could convince you to kill yourself.
It was really weird.
The computer would communicate with you by playing songs.
It's kind of like Bumblebee, but you could just look at the track file for the song,
like Blame It on the Rain.
And you'd be like, well, the weather's not that bad.
It was weird.
And we were trying to hide the computer from the government because if the government
didn't got it, they would make people kill themselves with it.
I don't remember.
But anyways, if there's a plane crash soon, stay away from computers.
We're flying over the 5K.
And we're watching this thing.
Now there's this little boy.
It's creepy that we're watching this dude.
Let's land.
We land and we get out.
We're standing in the crowd.
There's this nine-year-old kid named Cade Lovell.
And he runs all the time.
He runs home.
He runs to school.
He runs around the house.
He just runs.
He's a runner, right?
And so he's like, mommy, mommy.
I want to do the 5K.
And she's like, yeah, sure.
Last year, you actually won the 5K, remember?
And he's like, yippee.
So he's this little jock kid, right?
And so he wants to run the 5K.
And the mom's totally fine with it.
But you got like thousands-- or it's St. Cloud, Minnesota.
You got hundreds of people here, right?
And the 5K starts.
And Cade Lovell takes off running with all the other competitors.
And the mom's waiting at the finish line for him.
She's like, has this orange tang and a camera or cell phone instead because it's the year
2019?
And she sees a bunch of slow kids.
Now comparatively slow kids.
But she's seen a bunch of kids come and she's like, that's weird.
Where's Cade?
He's like the fastest of all these guys.
And it wasn't just kids running the 5K.
She's seen elderly people across the finish line before her son.
So she starts to get worried, like any mom would.
She's like, bear attack?
Wasp attack?
What happened to this kid?
Or more likely, he just fell and stripped his knee?
Or more sinisterly, that somebody took him?
So she begins trying to ask people, hey, have you seen Cade?
Have you seen my son?
Have you seen like a nine year old boy run around?
Nobody has seen the kid.
She basically starts running through the craft.
She grabs a runner's number and puts it on her chest, starts running the 5K.
She's like, Cade, Cade.
And eventually the race officials begin putting out the word, hey, we're missing a nine year
old kid.
So everyone's looking for this kid.
And that's when it gets back to the mom.
We think we just saw your kid, but he's in the 10K.
Mom's like, what?
He's only supposed to run the 5K.
So she goes to the 10K finish line.
She figures there must have been some sort of mistake.
She goes to the 10K finish line and she sees her son running all by himself and she's like,
poor Cade.
Like he totally would have won that 5K, but look, he got blown away by all those adults.
He's running all by himself.
Super sweaty dude.
He's all a panicked across his finish line.
And the judges are like, congratulations to Cade, winner of the 10K.
He actually was a minute ahead of every other runner in the 10K.
And so the mom finally was asked him, hey, what happened to you?
Like how'd you start running the 10K?
I was super worried.
And he's like, yeah, I was worried too.
What happened was I was coming up to the corner where you're supposed to get away from.
So it starts off the same, but at a certain corner it becomes a 5K.
And if you keep going straight, it becomes the 10K.
And as I was running, some woman kept going, keep going, keep going, keep going.
And she was pointing ahead and she was like an official volunteer.
She had on like the neon yellow shirt that they give out.
She's pointing ahead, keep going, keep going.
And he goes, I got confused where I was supposed to go.
So I just kept going.
And then I won the 10K.
I love that story.
I don't know.
I think the first off, I think it's hilarious that a kid can be that easily confused.
And then smoke everyone.
Oh, and the reason why he beat all the adults, I also thought this detail was hilarious.
The reason why he was running so fast, because he was scared.
He was scared because he didn't know where he was supposed to be.
And he knew his man.
He said this in a couple of interviews.
My mom gets really mad when she gets scared.
And I figured if I'm scared, my mom must be terrified.
So if I don't get back real quick, my mom's just going to get madder and madder and madder.
So he just started smoking these adults, dude.
Running as fast as he can.
He ended up, his time was 48 minutes, 17 seconds.
And he's just like straight up Terminator running after a truck full of Sarah Connors.
And he gets the finish line and she gives him a big old hug.
And then he went home and took a bath.
I don't know why they included that in the article.
And sat on the couch or something like that.
And then he started running with his friends.
So that's the story of Cade Lovell.
I love that story.
I thought it was hilarious.
This next story is another story I just came across.
That's the story of a man receiving a, true story, of a man receiving a mysterious message
on his iPhone.
This story is currently being litigated in court.
Well, it's currently about to be heard by the court.
Let's hop back in.
Let's hop into Dead Rabbit Durgible for this time.
So we're going to take a slow leisurely journey over to Russia.
Mother Russia.
And there we meet a man named D. Razmilov.
We'll just call him D for short.
And that's actually all I have is just an initial.
He's currently suing Apple.
He walks in the courtroom.
Dun dun.
But you know, it's so funny.
The other day I was looking through the newspaper and I saw the TV guide listings and I'm looking
at all the shows and I was like, I miss TV.
Like I miss actually like turning on a TV and having it play shows and advertisements.
It's really weird.
I have a sense of, because I don't watch my TV.
The reception out here sucks even for a Nintendo and I'm not going to pay for cable.
But I remember just so much of my childhood and adulthood really.
Just getting home from work, turning on the TV and just having it play and watching shows.
Like even shows like Two Broke Girls or just like garbage sitcoms.
I miss.
I miss that stuff.
It's super bizarre because nowadays I'll just be like, oh I want to watch a horror movie.
I'll just like find something online or watch it on Netflix or something like that.
Like before you just turn on the TV and then you'd like be reading a book and you'd look
up and you're like, whoa, Fallen's Plane starring Denzel Washington.
This is dope.
And then you'll watch it for about an hour and a half and then you'll go back to reading
a book.
Yeah, I miss that.
It's really, it's a weird nostalgic thing.
Anyways, so that was the People's Court song.
That's why I got into that one.
The D walks into a court in Russia and he goes and he says, your honor, here's my case.
I want to present to you guys.
And the judge puts on his little glasses, his little reading glasses, picks up the paperwork
and he looks at it and he goes, is this serious?
Like is this true?
You know, this is a joke, right?
And he's like, nope, no it is not, sir.
So what happened was Dee bought an Apple iPhone and that was his first mistake.
His second mistake was he downloaded a cryptocurrency app.
So he downloads an app onto his phone that was approved by the Apple store, by the iOS
store, whatever it's called.
And he's using the cryptocurrency app and he gets a message and it says that he's, it
says that he's received, this is 100% true.
I was looking for it and I'm like, is this from Prov?
There is something?
No, they are actual, there's a court filing on this.
This guy gets a app and he gets a down message on the app sending him 69 gay coins.
That's the actual terminology.
It's not that they were coins that happened to be gay.
It was like, you know, you have bit bucks or what's the real one that people always freak
out because it's not worth anything anymore.
The opposite thing, the stuff, it's by the, invented by the Japanese guy who doesn't exist.
Everyone always talks about it.
It's a leading Bitcoin, Bitcoin.
So anyways, he gets these gay coins, just one word, gay coins, right?
And there's an English message included with the 69 gay coins that he got and it says,
do not judge, do not try.
I have no idea what that could mean.
Honestly, I've tried thinking about it, but, and this is plausible the way he came up with
it, but he saw that as meaning, don't knock it till you try it.
So like, don't judge it until you try it.
Just the terminology so where do not judge, comma, do not try.
So apparently Yoda is sending out gay coins from a gay bar in Dagobah.
So anyways, Yoda send that out.
Dee gets this message, don't knock it till you try it.
So this is what, imagine you get that message.
If you got this stuff, if you got 69 gay coins from an anonymous user, hey, and all they
said was don't knock until you try it, what would you do?
I would go, these coins, my first assumption would be these coins must be for some other
sort of app saying, hey, don't hate the game until you try it.
Try out gay quest.
Put in a gay coin and you get like an extra man on gay quest or something like that.
I would assume it was something like that.
Dee here said, I thought, this is an actual quote, I thought indeed, how can I judge something
without trying it and decided to try same sex relationships.
So this guy is suing Apple because he says that Apple made him gay.
Here's another quote from him.
"I can say after the passage of two months that I mired an intimacy with a member of
my own sex and can't get out.
I have a steady boyfriend and I don't know how to explain it to my parents.
After receiving the aforementioned message, my life has changed for the worse and will
never be normal again."
So he gets this message, he gets a gay coin, he gets 69 gay coins and a message saying,
don't knock until you try it.
He then goes, yeah, sure, why not?
He goes out and starts blowing dudes.
What?
That's such a huge leap of logic.
Then we fast forward two months.
He apparently likes it.
Because it for two months has a boyfriend, which is very, very quick time to settle down
dude, you gotta play the field for a bit.
Get some message, two months later he has a boyfriend he can't break up with.
He can't break up with his dude.
He's keeping this lifestyle from his parents.
I'm assuming he's keeping his boyfriend in the dark about this lawsuit and then he goes,
my life is totally screwed up, I will never be normal again.
And I can almost guarantee after he filed this paperwork with the court he went back
home to his boyfriend.
So he's making choices to stay with this guy and I wonder if he still has 69 gay coins
in his account.
So apparently some people are so easily persuaded that if I showed them a picture of a balloon
and said don't knock until you try it, they will bang the balloon.
And of course it's easy to say this guy was probably gay or had gay leanings before he
got the app.
But who knows.
I think I could see someone going yeah you're right, don't knock until you try it.
And then going out for a weekend and banging a couple dudes and being like yeah it was
okay but it wasn't really for me.
Versus you're dating another man and then you go I need to sue Apple.
The whole story is hilarious to me.
And you could say maybe the app did brain wash him, maybe there is some computer conspiracy
around here that Apple wants to turn people gay, maybe.
But my favorite part of this story, he's suing them for pushing him towards homosexuality,
suing them for moral suffering and harm to mental health.
He's suing Apple for 1 million rubles.
Which in real money is $15,300.
So first off, how much is your sexuality worth to you?
Like if somebody forced you to change who you're attracted to, is that truly only worth $15,000?
But also, how busted does your economy have to be?
How absolutely ruined is your monetary system that 1 million of your money equals the same
amount that an 18 year old kid working in McDonald's for a year makes?
How bad is your economy?
Because when you read 1 million rubles, think about how much room that would take up in
your house.
Versus the kid I order a Big Mac from and he can't even get my order right.
I did not know Russia's economy was that bad.
Someone's like I'm a millionaire whenever I read it now about these Russian oligarchs,
these Russian billionaires I'm thinking, they probably make as much money as like a contractor
in America.
But anyways, the moral of this story, the moral of the first story was if someone keeps
telling you keep going, keep going, you can do it.
Don't stop, stop.
Because if you don't, if you keep going where they want you to go, your mom's going to
be mad at you.
That's the moral of the first story.
The moral of this story is 1.
Leave Russia because their economy sucks.
2.
Be careful what apps you open because there may actually be a secret app out there that
can change your sexuality.
And if they do, you'll only get $15,000 for pain and suffering or in Russia's case 1
million rubles.
Let's go ahead and you know what?
And actually I want to go ahead and do a Dead Rabbit Recommends right now.
Now I'm only going to be able to get away with this one on my birthday.
I know that.
It is a horror movie in a sense and you guys are going to be like I'm never watching that
Jason.
I'm never going to watch that.
A couple years ago, Disney Channel made a movie called Disney's Zombies.
I watched a lot of that stuff.
I watched a lot of it back when I was a babysitter.
I watched Sweet Life of Zack and Cody and really got into that.
I remember once, I think I told you guys the story, I went on a date with a Mormon girl,
but the dad wouldn't let us actually go on a date the first couple times so I would just
go over to her house and her mom would make me cookies and we'd sit on her couch and we'd
watch television with the dad.
I'm in my 20s at this point.
I'm like 24, 25.
I think she was like 19 or something like that.
But anyways, the point is, is that I remember the first time I went over there and I sit
on the couch and the dad's like you know, you guys can't go out.
You guys got to sit down and watch television with me.
I was like yeah, fine, whatever.
I'm eating cookies.
I really don't care what we're doing.
I'm sitting there.
I'm eating cookies and they put on this Disney Channel.
I think he was doing this to like get rid of me.
He turns on the Disney Channel because they were Mormons.
So they had like 15 kids.
They put on the Disney Channel and there was a bunch of other little kids running around
and he turns it on and I'm watching it and within five minutes I was laughing so hard.
I don't remember what the movie was.
It was something to do.
It wasn't a switching body one.
I don't know.
It was some scientific gadget that had been created.
I was laughing so hard I was spitting cookies out of my mouth.
I thought it was hilarious and I remember after the date I said hey, I got to go and I remember
watching more Disney Channel movies after that and a lot of them are actually pretty
funny.
Most of them are kind of weak but a lot of them are pretty funny.
One with the kids who built this machine that allowed them to go back in time and they were
driving.
They wore the clock stoppers.
They would wear these special suits to hide their identity and they'd go back in time
to prevent kids from getting embarrassed.
It was interesting because they were basically vigilantes but it's in a high school and it's
a Disney Channel movie so instead of fighting crime they're fighting kids getting spaghetti
on their dress.
It really well put together a story and I've watched a lot of those.
So I was excited and I love zombies and I enjoyed Disney Channel movies so I was like
this is going to be a train wreck.
Descendants I don't like.
I don't like a lot of the newer stuff but this movie is going to stink.
So if it's a musical about zombies and humans going to high school together.
Train wreck.
I'm going to get it in.
It might be one of the most bizarre movies I've ever seen.
Like structurally it's weird.
You have what's weird about it is you can it's well it's a well made movie.
There's like and I have a low bar for that but there are things like establishing shots
and you're introducing characters in the right order because I watch a lot of bad movies
so you notice when that stuff is missing.
Characters have clear motivations but what's interesting is that character will start off
with their character arc and then they will come to a realization and then they'll make
a different decision than you would have made.
And that happens constantly so you don't understand why the characters are doing what they're
doing but when you step back and make sense for the character everyone comes to a cross
road in their life and if someone was watching you and they'd go oh that's weird I would
have made a different decision but we're so used to seeing the right decision made especially
in a movie especially my main characters that it would be like if Luke saw Aunt Baru and
Uncle Owen burned and he's like eh and just walked away and you would have a different
movie at that point.
You would have them go no no no you gotta come back and he's like nah I'm fine and then
he would be a true reluctant hero.
That's this movie like in a nutshell it's it's basically a basically a post-racial society
where all ethnicities get along but humans hate zombies and zombies are very leery of
humans.
And all zombies by the way there's references throughout the movie to them eating people,
eating people's brains that you know I don't trust zombies one of them ate my uncle or bit
my uncle's ear off and stuff like that.
Zombies live in a ghetto, the humans live in this beautiful pastel colored neighborhood,
it's musical numbers galore and then subplots that involve things like allegory for steroid
use which is completely goes into the weirdest direction possible.
There's an illusion to like a school shooter slash school bombing that totally just goes
in a bizarre direction.
The Disney Channel movie by the way gotta keep reminding you of that.
Absolutely bizarre and then by the end of the movie I remember watching the end I've
only watched it once I think the magic will leave me if I watch it a second time because
I've watched it and I just like I have no idea I felt like I was stoned watching it.
And when it ended the credits are rolling and I'm like what just happened like nothing
happened the way I thought it was going to happen.
Even the ending dance number I was like what?
Absolutely mind boggling great great movie.
So if you're looking for something it's horror because there's zombies and it would be scary
if you were six.
If you're looking for an unusual movie to watch this weekend see if you can track down
Disney zombies you can get it on DBT but it's just a really bizarre movie.
And I don't you know the couple of the other movies I've recommended are kind of like
those quiet horror movies you just kind of want to watch alone.
You don't want to watch deep down with a bunch of buddies because it's just kind of a weird
solo movie.
That's what this movie is too.
This isn't a movie you want to put on in the background at a party.
If you really want to appreciate it you kind of want to put it on and watch it because
so you can put like just weird dialogue choices.
It's just so bizarre.
There's a black coach who and I don't want to keep talking about it but there's this
black football coach the main zombie Zed wants to join the football team black football coach
and when they're talking about him joining the football team and they show the coach
I go oh it's going to be a thing like I understand the struggle like my uncle tried to get in
and my great grandpa tried to get into Louisville and you and you couldn't couldn't play but
I understand.
No the coach is like I don't break barriers I follow trends I'm not going to take a chance
on anybody I'm not that type of guy.
So he actually acknowledges in a way the remember the Titan story he acknowledges that it would
be groundbreaking for him to have someone of a different race on his team but he's flat
out refusing to do it.
It would have been one thing if he says no son you're not good enough you got to get
better but he acknowledges the fact that there is like racial animosity between humans and
zombies and that's why he won't put him on the team.
And you had a black coach delivering those lines and I'm like what is going on with this
movie.
So bizarre I don't like to use the word post-racial a lot but that's almost the only way you can
describe the setting for this movie it's absolutely bizarre.
Again he didn't have to acknowledge the race and I wouldn't have even thought twice about
it but the fact that he started saying no you're a different race so I won't put you
on my team even though I'm a different ethnicity and I used to not be able to even be in a
school I'm not going to break barriers that's not the type of guy I am.
And then the zombie starts doing basically steroids and the coach lets him on the team.
Absolutely bizarre movie.
And actively defends him from investigation.
So weird man.
Okay let's go ahead though and move on to a story.
A story that I actually mentioned I mentioned it quite a few episodes ago I think it was
like season 4 finale something like that.
And I actually was planning on saving this one until the end of the show.
I thought you know what I'm not going to tell this story until I cancel the show or until
the show ends.
But then I thought about it and I thought this is actually the perfect time for a couple
reasons.
One it happened on my birthday.
Two it happened seven years ago on my birthday and with the whole time reset conspiracy that
we talked about a couple episodes ago which is hilarious now that it's passed people online
are like how come my life didn't reset because it was fake dude like you have to get a mental
filter for this stuff.
But I thought it's been seven years it's on my it's story takes place on my birthday.
Let me tell you the story I had moved up the previous year so we're in Hood River in the
sleepy little town of Hood River Oregon I moved up here in October of 2011 it is now October
2012 and I'm up in my bedroom looking down at Wasco Street the creepiest street in the
world and I'm just I like I do a lot of birthday stuff by myself like this year this year I'm
going out to go see Joker I did get a couple of my local buddies Ir Bardo he listens to
the show and then my buddy Jacob we're all going to go see Joker.
But a lot of times I spend birthday I spend a lot of time by myself and I do I really
enjoy it and so that birthday I was spending by myself at night and I am super excited
because I saw that the new horror movie VHS is on television and I was like that's weird
I didn't even know that movie was released yet but it was on like Shutter or it was on
some horror channel so it's like oh that's awesome so I'm going to watch VHS I'm going
to stay up I'm going to goof around online then go to sleep probably like 2-3 in the
morning and so I'm sitting in my big comfy recliner and I turn on television it's probably
like 9 or 10 o'clock at this point I turn on television I start watching VHS I was really
really into this horror anthology movie I used to watch a ton of horror movies a ton
of them I'm watching it and I watch the first segment I go oh that's pretty good it's about
like a vampire succubus or something like that and then I'm watching the second segment
and it's about these honeymooners this young couple who are on a road trip and there's
this mysterious woman following them and then they murder the boyfriend and it turns out
the two girls are lesbians and that's kind of the end of the horror story but I'm watching
it and this point is probably like 9.30 10.30 I don't remember when it started but I'm watching
it and they get to the scene where the man sleeping in bed and it's all like first person
camcorder this short story and they plunge the knife right into the dude's neck and he's
like blood's dribbling out and it's just this long shot and I remember being unusually
disgusted and disturbed by that now here's the thing there if you've been on the internet
long enough and if you're probably in a certain age range you've seen I hate to bring this
up because you guys probably be like damn it Jason I forgot about the video most of
us have seen that video though of that Chechny and soldier getting stabbed in the neck with
by the Russian it's a real video with dudes laying on the ground and the guy sticks the
knife right in his neck blood gushes out the VHS killing looked pretty similar a lot of
times special effects people will steady snuff not snuff videos but steady videos of people
actually night but I don't think I'd seen that video years ago and it was like ew and
then just went on to whatever I was doing eating spaghettios and watching Chippinels
Rescue Rangers whatever it was and I think if anyone's spend any large amount of time
on the internet eventually they come across gross stuff like that other than just answering
their email and going to Facebook if you're ever like just clicking on news articles and
stuff you see people get smashed into cars and get chewed up by escalators and all sorts
of stuff so fall down elevators all that so anyways I'm watching VHS though and I see
that scene and I really disgusted me and I didn't really I just felt like that's that
was too much it's too much I think I was 36 if I'm so it's I'm gonna be 43 so seven years
ago would be yeah it'd be 36 and I was like what like I thought it was weird that I had
that type reaction to it but I shut the movie off shut the movie off and I said I kind of
fiddled around on my computer stop watching him so this all happened on October 4th this
story this story here happened on October 4th so my birthday and so I end up going to
sleep and around 4 or 5 in the morning I don't even know if I could classify a time to this
right I'm laying in my recliner and I wake up now what's interesting about the story
and to be fair this would be something I would use to debunk anyone telling a story like
this there is no proof that I'm actually awake could 100% be a dream however the stuff that
happens after it makes me question that I'm sleeping in my recliner as I usually do a
sleep on couches and recliners and I'm sleeping on my side and I wake up I'm looking out my
bedroom window into the dark street of wasco and I see in the middle of the street so probably
a good I don't know 40-50 feet away I see a little glowing light probably about 2 inches
tall it was like maybe a little maybe about 4 inches tall because I'm kind of making it
with my hand it was like this glowing ball of light and I could perceive something in
the light like a figure a figurine so at this point I think I'm still dreaming and in real
life I was like oh I must be dreaming this isn't real and I see this little light start
to get closer and move very very slowly towards me but what was weird out of this is there
multiple weird details but as it's moving closer to me it doesn't change size so if
it's something's really 4 inches and it's 40 feet away as it's getting closer and closer
to you it will get bigger that's just the way vision works and distance but as it got
closer and closer to me it stayed 4 inches tall I'm just laying there with my eyes open
looking at this thing it's floating closer and closer and closer and closer to me and
then and right when it gets to basically outside my window it goes and I'm standing in this
white room it was I was I don't even know if I was standing I was just in a white room
and I just heard this and standing there it's so weird I can't even use terms like in front
of me just you were aware of this was an angel it was how I would perceive an angel it was
a blonde haired woman in white robes now I should have explained this part of the beginning
because some of you guys know this and some of you guys know the reason why I brought
up the angel story a long time ago I was talking about where I was fighting shadow people or
something like that and what I did and it was this I don't know how I came up with this
idea or why even thought it would work but apparently it did it's I think that was the
demon the shadow people was it the demons around us no it wasn't that episode sorry guys should
be more prepared but anyways go back just listen every episode it's ever have a radio
you'll find it I talked about where I took a part of my soul and like it sounds so cringy
when I talk about it but basically like removed a little piece of my soul and made it into
a like a thought weapon like a psychic weapon because I figured if my soul is indestructible
and blessed by God then therefore anything from my soul should also be the same so if
I can meditate on taking a piece of my soul out and turning it into a weapon a sword then
it would basically be the equivalent of punching someone with your soul or stabbing someone
with your soul so I did that when I was in my early 20s and I also did the same thing
and made myself like a little shield because I was I used to be ten toes deep into hunting
ghosts trying to summon demons and punch them in the face and all sorts of just nonsense
right not that hunting ghosts is nonsense but thinking that you can summon a demon and
then kick into the nuts is the height of stupidity but anyways so I I encountered shadow people
and all sorts of monsters and gobble and stuff like that so I figured I needed some sort
of defenses so I took a little piece of my soul and meditated on it and did work on it
and all that stuff and over the course of weeks I made this thought sword it wasn't
real it didn't actually exist I wasn't walking around with a hill time like at the ren fair
this was something that I made out of my my atolpa weapon and I had a shield too so that
existed and I always would use that it was basically I guess another it'll be like a
security blanket it was very very odd deep very odd thing it does sound very cringy when
I talk about it but let's jump back to the present I'm standing in this white room I'm
in a white room there's this angel in front of me and she's holding a toy wooden sword
and a toy wooden shield and then she gives them to me and she takes the sword and shield
that I made so as she's handing me this toy sword and this toy shield made of wood she's
taking away these things that I had made 14 15 years ago out of meditating and visualizing
a piece of my soul coming out and forging it and doing all of this work she takes those
from me and gives me the toys of a child pretending to be a war and she basically takes like two
chunks of my soul and then she's right next to my ear and she's standing there and she
whispers into my ear I can hear and then I'm laying there on my recliner and the sun's
coming up I remember I told that story to Lana and she goes what did the angel say and I
go I don't know I don't remember I tried remembering immediately what the angel was
saying to me whispering in my ear I have no idea and I've gone over that event a lot and
you're like well that's weird Jason just had a dream we're just getting started well we're
almost near the end we're not just getting started but I've tried figuring out what that
encounter meant over the years it terrified me so much I didn't want to be alone on my
next few birthdays I was afraid it was going to come back and you go Jason what's so terrifying
about that well ever since then I've had this really weird thing where I've become people
who know me especially when I was younger knew I'm fairly empathetic but nowadays it's
almost paralyzing sometimes when I'm reading the news I kind of mentioned this in the military
episode when I was talking about the ISIS soldiers getting blown away I said guys listen
I know these people have families and mothers and fathers who love them and first loves
and stuff like that but they're bad guys and then I go on to proceed how the British dude
just blows their heads off with a shotgun I cannot read any sort of news account or hear
any sort of story or even watch a fictional horror movie or action movie or whatever without
completely empathizing with every single person in that movie and that's not a superpower
other people can do it but for me since that encounter it's become tenfold when I read
an article about somebody getting killed whether or not they are the bad guy like let's take
those ISIS soldiers for example and I had that comment and it sounded like a throwaway
comment but that kid his mom was cradling I can picture all of this stuff the mom cradling
the little baby boy him getting his feelings hurt at school one day and kind of throwing
rocks against the car and then someone out getting in trouble his first kiss his first
love when he feels the sun on his face his favorite comic book and then bam shotgun
to the head as he's trying to build a suicide vest that happens to me all the time I'm not
visualizing and I'm not hallucinating but I just my my empathetic feelings are an overload
right now so the point where even when I watch like an action movie and terminators just
like gunning down security guards I'm like oh my god they have families those people
had lives just like mine they had hopes and dreams and aspirations they had first loves
and breakups and they sat in the living room crying in the dark one night with spaghetti
or stains on their shirt every human goes through those things it's a super bizarre but I've
also been instilled with a sense of dread and fear that I've never had before in my life
have I don't want to say no fear there were certain things I feared I wasn't a fan of heights
I wasn't a fan of water but I would go into rough neighborhoods and start trouble and
I wouldn't have a problem someone says you got a problem I say yeah you like I had no
problem being an open jerk and courting danger at any point in my life until that after that
I have become a different person less reckless and and people could go well that's a good
thing you're maturing but to me it feels like such a core part of my identity is gone because
I used to just not care at all when I keep saying fearful I don't really think that's
right fearful and being less reckless are good things my anxiety attacks are have been sky
high since then like anxiety attacks I've never had before have been happening since this
encounter like I just feel like I'm constantly under threat from something I wake up basically
with an anxiety attack and for the most part it hasn't gone away since so when I say fearful
I'm meaning more like that I'm not scared of the spooky spooky why I'm scared of the
spooky spooky woods but it's not like a fearfulness like a Scooby-Doo it's more of just like this
every muscle in my body is constantly tightened waiting for something that won't come so it's
more anxiety than fearfulness and it's not a good level of oh I'm gonna be careful it's more like
I have to be careful otherwise I can die at any moment it's that level of anxiety slash fear
primal fear not spooky spooky fear now it's possible that this is all just stuff that's
normal with growing up and since I'm growing up for the first time this is something everyone goes
through but it feels like such a core part of my identity was lost that night and an additional part
was added on i.e. just being too tuned into people I talk a lot and when I say oh yeah I read a lot
of true crime I used to read a lot of true crime that's the reason why I stopped I just couldn't
I couldn't enjoy it anymore because I'm reading about these victims and I can't help
but seeing every point in their life it's sucked all the entertainment value out of people being
murdered for me and it's funny because I always wondered what the symbolism was of me getting the
toy sword and the toy shield and it's funny because I know what it is I know I knew what it was then
and I always tried finding an alternative answer because I don't like the answer and that's the
funny thing a lot of times when we analyze stuff we have to be honest with the answers we get
the reason why those things were taken for assuming any of this is real again assuming it's totally
not a dream and it just happened it happened at a time where I had this big awakening and I was
turning 36 and I assuming any of this is real I was given those items and taken the the the sword
and shield that I made were taken away from me and I was giving these toy sword and shield
for one of two reasons actually I've always I've always thought maybe it's because God is saying
that I don't need any of these fancy weapons any of these fancy thought forms to fight
demons or monsters that God's power over darkness is strong enough that even a toy sword and shield
can destroy them you don't need this mega blade that you built out of your soul that's the answer
I want to believe but I don't think that's what it meant I think I think that what that shield and
sword represent is you're a little boy you're a very very little boy and if you think that you're
ready for what's coming you deserve little boy toys if you think in any way shape or form you're
ready for challenges that may await you with these things that you built with your brain if you think
any of these things will do you any good you're a dumb little child who deserves dumb little toys
you know I want to say this too this isn't an ARG this isn't a fake narrative that I'm building
up over the course of the seasons or anything like that I want to be clear on that as far as that
story is that story ended that night there is no follow-up where I see like a dark shadow in the
corner and he's like you think you're ready for me none of that like all of these stories are
fairly self-contained I don't want you to think oh great he's building up to some big narrative that
at the end if we donate to his patreon you can fight gall orth or whatever no these are all just
kind of independent moments in my life but I but I think that that's why I got the toy sword and
shield that I think I think of myself as kind of this big bad warrior guy but I'm just a little boy
and it's funny because that's the first time I've said that out loud and now that I think about it
that would make me fearful if I thought I was this big bad rough street fighter tumbler dude
because I've gotten in a few scrapes but none of that is there's nothing that has happened in my
life that's preparing me for what may come in the future and that would make you fearful actually
I never thought about that having being told that you're not ready would make you fearful so I wonder
if those two things were connected yeah never really made that connection because I've only told
this story to maybe like three people told it to Lana I told it to Jenny I think maybe only two people
if it was a dream it was a life-changing dream and people have those and people may say Jason
you're actually a better person now because you're less reckless I'm definitely a different person
than I was October 3rd 2012 to October 4th 2012 I'm different my thought patterns are different
the way I look at the world is different the way I look at myself is different
could just be a normal factor of aging could be that I was visited by an angel
and other people I have encounters with angels near-death experiences and stuff like that I've
thought yeah what if I had a near-death experience what if I had a heart attack or something and
this was my second chance I don't know people's personalities tend to change after near-death
experiences but other people have told me stories I've read stories about people seeing angels and
their lives changing for the better but I don't really look at it as the better I just feel different
the empathy is almost crippling people will tell me a horrible story and to them they're like
isn't that awful and I'm like yeah that's the worst story I've ever heard in my life I don't
tell them that because I know people tell horrible stories because they have to get it off their chest
but I don't go oh my god why'd you tell me that horrible horrible story but it just
affects me where as before I totally would have forgotten about it again might be a normal thing
of aging the being less reckless is most likely a normal form of aging the angel visit could have
just been a dream but all three of those things have oh and I forgot to tell you the actually
there's one more piece here we'll end on this this could easily be debunked as well but I've
tried very very hard to debunk this part so I said I was watching VHS on my birthday and I go
that's weird didn't come out yet VHS it was released on video on demand on august 22nd okay
it was released at theaters for a limited run on october 5th according to the internet it was
never shown on cable television unless you did your video on demand it was not shown it wasn't
even released until the next day now to be fair they could have been some special run on shutter
they wanted to show it the day before and got permission but that is not listed at all that
I could find on the internet so to make this whole story even weirder I watched a movie on a cable
channel the day before it was released at the movie theater and it wasn't I didn't do video on
demand it was on shutter it was on just a station I turned on the tv and I watched it I almost forgot
that detail again it's just a whole weird thing so happy birthday Jason seven years after meeting
an angel I gotta admit I gotta admit my birthday still make me a little nervous
because I don't know what's going to happen if it comes back
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and
true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today
have a great weekend guys and happy birthday to me woo happy birthday Jason yeah I am giving you
guys all high fives yeah yeah okay I'll see you guys next week