Did John McAfee kill himself or was he whacked as so many people seem to claim?
Then we meet a man who's out in the wilderness waiting for some of his friends to arrive.
Instead he is greeted with a glowing orb shooting sparks in all directions.
But the story gets even more bizarre when this hovering egg
hatches today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
*Music*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got three days left until my vacation.
That's more for me than for you.
Um, I have to take a vacation every 50 episodes just to keep the whole noggin joggin the noggin joggin.
And we're past 50 episodes. I think this is episode 709.
708. It's a lot of work. This show takes a lot of work.
I mean my break, but I got three more episodes to do. Three more episodes are really cool content for you guys.
I'm telling myself that. Don't give up Jason. Just three more episodes.
First off, coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our legacy Patreon supporters. Give it up for Medusa Buzzcutt.
Wooo! Everyone give a round of applause to Medusa. Medusa, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. Just help spread the word about the show really, really helps out a lot.
And even though I am taking a three week,
very, very well deserved break. I'm actually traveling going to the tropical country of Medici to help overthrow General DeRevello.
But um, before now that they know that I'm coming now that they know to send the Bavarian tanks after me, while I'm on vacation,
I will have a special on July 18th. We are doing a July 18th Alien Invasion special. That is the day
that some dude predicted seven years ago he predicted aliens would invade July 18th. So we're coming up to that.
So get your strawberry ice cream ready. Subscribe to my YouTube channel because it's going to be a YouTube livestream.
I don't know exactly what time it's going to be yet because that is I haven't worked those details out, but July 18th Alien Invasion
special brought to you by a quiet place part two. And if you don't listen to the YouTube, if you don't want to watch it live,
that's fine too. I'm actually going to upload the audio to the podcast.
So if you guys just want to sit and listen to it at your leisure,
that is, that works too. So no, you have to listen to it live. After words, the aliens are going to destroy the planet.
You want to be with me while that's happening. Medusa Buzzcat, I'm going to give you the keys to a new vehicle.
I just invented since I'm going to go on vacation soon. I'm going to toss you the keys to the Carpenter Cruise Ship.
This is our festive, this is our festive cruise ship.
We're all going to be lounging around on decks, sipping my ties, playing shuffleboard while Medusa Buzzcat has an actual job.
They have to be the captain of this ship. They now control a crew of about 100 people. Guys, kickback, relax.
Let's take a trip across the ocean. We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We are heading on out to
Barcelona, Spain.
Come up with a sound effect real quick and go, "What noises do cruise ships make?"
The sounds of hundreds of elderly people having fun. Or, you know, the horn.
You're like, "Oh, that's what that sound was. I thought you were constipated."
We pull up in the Carpenter Cruise Ship. I already forgot the name of it. Totally forgot the name of it.
I'll forget this vehicle exists after this episode. We pull up in the Carpenter Cruise Ship. We disembark in Barcelona, Spain.
The reason why we're in Barcelona, Spain is because
I'm sure most of you guys are familiar with this news. John McAfee, rogue outlaw,
inventor, programmer, businessman.
He's a very hyphenated individual. He's done a lot in his life. John McAfee, who's most famous, I think, for the McAfee antivirus.
He
died.
I think we can at least say that. He died. There's actually, we can.
There's some people who say that he's not dead, that he's faking the whole thing, but just a quick quick overview.
John McAfee was in a Spanish prison
and he was being held for tax evasion, tax charges.
And what had happened is recently he, it was successful. United States was trying to have him extradited to the United States to
stand trial for tax evasion.
He's been being held by the Spanish authorities until the stuff could get figured out.
It was figured out. The U.S. won the extradition battle to actually have him sent over to the United States.
And then he has found hanging in his cell. He's dead.
Again, there's some people who say that he's faking the whole thing
because he definitely had the money to kind of bribe officials and stuff like that.
There are some people who're saying that he's faking the whole thing, but that's another conspiracy.
That's another conspiracy. We might look into that if it continues to grow, but right now the big conspiracy theory about John McAfee is
did he hang himself
or was he whacked?
Was he hung by people who are trying to keep him silent? This is a really fascinating conspiracy theory, but not in the way people think it is.
This is this is fascinating. Here we go.
John, this is the reason why people think John McAfee didn't kill himself. One, he said is
late as December of last year. I will never ever ever kill myself.
And then he got a tattoo on him that says whacked is like the dollar sign and it says whacked and he's like
if they come after me, it's because I got whacked. It's because I know too much and they're trying to silence me.
And then he's found hanging in his cell.
So the immediate reaction was oh dude, the people who got Epstein also got John McAfee.
Like he knew too much and they had to silence him. So they hung him
and he tried warning us. He said he would never ever commit suicide. He had this tattoo called whacked and
after he died, there's been all of this chatter about a dead man switch with
dead man switches. Basically, it's kind of what it sounds like. Let's say I have a dead man switch. I might.
I might. I might, but let's say I do have a dead man switch and every week I have to enter a code into my computer.
But if one week it goes by and I don't enter that code,
my dead man switch is activated, which in a electronic sense would be
tons of emails start going out with all sorts of encryption keys to high level
politicians and high level journalists and things like that.
So as long as I'm alive, the information that I've gathered that I've told people I will keep secret is secret.
But once I die and that code goes a week without being entered, all of this information starts flooding out into the
information place. What is that? I don't know. The information's fair. It gets out. Your secrets get out.
So after he died, there was a dead man switch that started going off apparently and like one of the codes was
Epstein, so that kind of brought into it or
So a lot of people are hanging their hat on that.
He said he was never going to kill himself and he dies and it looks like it's suicide by hanging.
And then this dead man switch goes off. But if that story is correct,
if that if the dead man, so this is what I don't understand about the dead man switch thing,
he wouldn't be able to activate the dead man switch constantly in jail. Anyways,
so the dead man switch would have had to have been run by someone on the outside, which could do it
whether or not a dead man switch works when you die.
And I guess you could have a dead man switch and someone else hits the button.
It's not really a dead man switch. It's kind of a live man switch who waits for you to die.
But anyway, so all this information and I wanted to report on this earlier. I actually had done a segment on it
last week and I you're like, really? I didn't hear that part. I edited it out. I took it out before
I released the episode because we didn't have enough information really. And the dead man switch
had just been activated. We're just seeing this information drop. And in that segment, I said,
I really don't think anything's going to come of this. And here we are a week later and the dead
man switch is still being investigated, but there's been no massive Epstein level bombshells.
Nothing's really been dropped like that. And that brings me back to my main argument with this.
I believe that John McAfee killed himself before you shut off the podcast. I have a reason why I
think he did that that no one else is talking about. And I'm a little I'm a little perturbed that no
one else is talking about it. But I think that John McAfee killed himself. But let me explain.
Let me explain this and then I'll get to why I think him killing himself is far more interesting
than the whacked tattoo and the Epstein connection and the dead man switch, which has not revealed any
major bombshells right now. First thought, this is really sad to say, and I'm not saying this
to be mean or anything like that. But first off, suicide is not it's super interesting. I was doing
a bunch of research on this for a topic a while ago. Suicide committing suicide is a
it's not something that everybody does. I was always under the impression that any single person
put under enough stress can kill themselves. And that's partially true. But some people are far
more inclined to kill themselves. We don't know if it's genetic. But we do see that it runs in
bloodlines. It runs in families. Let's say that someone kills themselves. And then 10 years later,
their niece kills himself. And then four years later, her brother kills him. You know what I mean?
Like we'll see it run through bloodlines. There are people who suffer such extreme, extreme events
that they take their own lives. But like 95% of people who kill themselves are predisposed to
suicide. I actually think I did do a subject. I'll see if I check their notes. I think I covered it
more on an episode. But yeah, it is there are people who just predispose to killing themselves.
It's rare. It statistically is rare when someone has no connection to committing suicide,
suicidal ideation, anything like that. And then event after event after event after event happens
to them and they kill themselves. That's not the statistics. That's what we see in movies. And that's
the story that we think is true. 95% of people who kill themselves are actually predisposed to
suicide. His dad killed himself. So when I saw that, I go, well, that that's a huge that is a huge
I'm not saying that just because I've had a friend whose father killed himself, right?
I'm not saying that that is the Oh, well, I guess he killed himself then, but that is a signifier.
And you can't deny that you can't deny that because suicide is a we don't know if it is genetic,
but people are kind of leaning that way. Doesn't mean if someone in your family has killed themselves
that you are going to kill yourself. Just means there's a higher likelihood of it.
So we have that, which I did read that and I go, well, that is that is a pretty big thing. But
the other thing is McAfee was never ever and I've followed McAfee for a while. Like I remember
he first came out on my radar when he was under under suspicion for murdering his neighbor. He was
living in Central America, South America. He murdered his neighbor. And I remember following
that case and he beat it. He was there and never able to prove that he murdered this guy. And he's
always been a almost ran. Like you could almost sense like him and Elon Musk and Jeff Bezos,
they all want to be this Hank Scorpio type character. If you don't know who that is,
it's this character from The Simpsons, who's this seems like a super congenial billionaire
inventor philanthropist, but he's also a supervillain. And it seems like they all kind of saw that
episode and they kind of patterned their life after Hank Scorpio. But John McAfee always seemed
like an almost ran in the conspiracy theory community. He people knew who Epstein was
after his first arrest. Like Epstein, maybe if you were really deep in conspiracy theory and you
were connected, you knew a lot about him before it came out, before he got connected, all this
up. But after his first arrest, he was arrested twice. A lot of people don't know that. And he
beat the charges. You have that going on. He was a huge threat, right? He knew about everyone. He
knew about tons of people who have been named and a lot of people who have not been named.
A lot of very, very powerful people that have not come out during this whole Epstein Me Too scandal.
He has all that info. So Epstein was 100% a target. Who would John McAfee know? John McAfee,
apparently like mingled more with like common gang members and stuff like that. Like apparently he
was, I read this story that he was dating this woman and the local mob was trying to get her to
poison him. But she's like, no, I don't want to. She could be making that story up. We don't know.
He didn't get poisoned. But so he did have like he was probably pushing people's buttons,
but he was nowhere on the level of an Epstein threat where he's hobnobbing with presidents.
He's hobnobbing with royalty. He's hobnobbing with Hollywood. John McAfee looked unkempt in
every single photo I've ever seen him in. So while he may have been a threat to some people,
him getting extradited to the United States, how are they really going to lean on this guy? Now,
to be fair, behind the scenes, I said no one really knew in the general community what Epstein
was up to. Until that first arrest, it's possible that John McAfee was super connected to all these
world leaders and this stuff would have come out. But we have no hints of that. Even when I'm reading
this stuff about the Deadman switch, which now it's been a week and we're not seeing these bump
shows, there is never like, oh and he was tied to this politician and high level politician. I'm
sure he hobnobbed with some state representatives or something like that. But not for a while,
the guy always looked dirty. But here is the thing and this is what I find so interesting
that no one else is talking about, at least that I've seen. The main thing John McAfee is
knowing about in the conspiracy theory community, we talked about him before on this show, I believe,
is quantum immortality. He very, very famously during an interview with Vice or Vanity Fair or
somebody when he was in his tropical home, this was years ago, he played Russian roulette with
a revolver, obviously you don't do it with a bow and arrow, you don't do it with a semi-automatic,
playing Russian roulette and he's saying, he's going through the spiel about quantum immortality,
quantum suicide and he goes, there's one bullet in this gun, I will never die, I'm gonna put this
gun in my head and I'm gonna pull the trigger and the bullet will not go through my brain because I
cannot exist in a timeline where I don't exist, I will shift to a timeline where I do exist,
I will continue to exist. Very, very famous interview and the reporter sat there and the
guy clicked the gun, maybe more than once, I don't remember, but it was to prove that he had no fear
that he would just slide into another timeline. When he first died, I saw people saying, oh no,
we're in the worst timeline now, we're in the timeline where John McAfee died and I thought
that was an interesting comment, but then they didn't continue on the thread, this is what I think
happened, honestly, this is what I think happened, I think John McAfee killed himself, but in his
mind, he was just sliding to an alternate reality where he wasn't in jail or where the extradition
trial hadn't worked, I think that's what happened, I think that he didn't kill himself out of utter
despair, he didn't kill himself out of unending torment or pain or anything like that or an
underlying mental illness or all of those put together, he believes in quantum suicide, he
believes the fact that if I die in this reality, I'll shift to another reality where things work
out for me. The problem is, is that quantum suicide, quantum immortality, it doesn't,
it's a theory and it does, it's a theory, it's interesting from a sci-fi angle, but it doesn't
hold any water whatsoever, when I did the episode on it, it was probably about a year or two ago,
I did this episode, this was my, this is my problem with it, let's say that it, let's say that it
works, right, that means that no one ever dies, the thought process is, is that you can't perceive a
reality where you don't exist, so as a concept of quantum immortality, we've all had close
brushes with death, whoa, I should have died there, but I didn't and it does feel kind of weird and
we've covered stories like that, like do you die or do you shift to another reality, interesting
theory, the problem is, is that we all get old, we see that around us, we felt our own bodies
getting older, so if you can put a gun to your head, don't do this, but if you put a gun under
your head and you pull the trigger and in this reality, your brain spray all over the wall,
but you go to a reality where the trigger doesn't pull, where the bullets have dud,
where the gun turns to cheese in your hands, whatever, interesting theory, but what happens
when you're 95 and you're bedridden and you can't die, you're hooked up to all these devices and
you have a heart attack and you shift to another reality where you're hooked up to all these devices
and you're still in this bed and you have a heart attack and you're shifting to another reality where
you're 95 years old and you're still in this bed and you have another heart attack and you shift
into this reality, like that would be hell and that it could, you could be like, well,
I'll just work out, I'm going through all these quantum realities, I'll keep working out, I'll
be fit, fine, you're 107 and you're in bed hooked up to all these machines, you go, I want, do not
resuscitate on myself, okay, fine, you're in the ER and they say, well, we can't resuscitate you and
you die on the operating table, you shift to another reality where you're on that operating table,
you die on that operating table, like it would just keep happening over and over and over and over
again, of quantum and let's say that you're 95 and you shift to a reality where you did take
better care of your body, now you're no longer hooked up to all these machines, you're 95,
you're sitting at home surrounded by your family, well, guess what, you're still going to turn 96
soon and this is forever, you're just going to keep getting older and maybe you shift to a reality
where you're slightly more healthy and you live a little bit longer, but eventually you're just
going to be skeletal husk, having stroke after stroke after stroke after stroke after stroke
and shifting each time you do, that's hellish and the idea of quantum immortality, it's interesting
when you're 33 years old and you almost get hit by a car and you go, whoa, I mean, I should have
died, maybe I died in an alternate reality, that's not an interesting thought when you're begging
for death, so I personally think John McAfee killed himself on two levels, one he could have just
been predisposed to suicide and he wanted to go out a legend, now people are always going to be
talking about him, if he had just died or had an aneurysm or something else that happened to him,
people would have been like, people would have totally forgotten about him, he is now like
Forrest Finn, he has etched his name into conspiracy theory content, people will mention
McAfee next Epstein, conspiracy people will, normal people aren't talking about this, people
aren't making mugs that say McAfee didn't kill himself, nobody really cares because he wasn't
as big as a character in real life, I think as he thought he was, but there will be a core
contingent who will hold McAfee up to Epstein even though I don't think that's true, also why would
you want to be held up to Epstein? He either killed himself because he was unfortunately predisposed
to suicide and put all these breadcrumbs out saying that he would never kill himself and got
the tattoo that said whacked and know that well if I kill myself I'll just become famous like
Epstein became famous because most people didn't know who Epstein was really until
the controversy over the second arrest and then him killing himself shortly after, or this guy
said well I believe that if I dial just shift to another reality so I'm just going to hang myself
and shift to the other reality and while that is an interesting theory on a sci-fi level I don't
think it works in reality, I mean who knows right we don't know what happens after you die but to me
if quantum immortality, quantum suicide is real that is a very very hellish and dark future to
think you're just going to be perpetually alive and getting older no matter what you do or no
matter what fate does to you you just shift to another reality where you're slightly more alive
than you were before. John I wish you the best wherever you're at obviously it's tragic that this
happened see that's the thing even tax evasion charges what he would have done some Wesley
Snipes time would have done like six years and would have been out the it's an interesting story
it's a tragic story that it ends I wish him the best wherever he's at if the quantum suicide
thing works obviously that's the best case scenario he is still somewhere else I guess the best
case scenario is that he faked his death which we do have to keep that option on the table but
Medusa Buscutt we are leaving behind Barcelona Spain we are headed out to Newton Falls Ohio
Medusa Buscutt takes us out to Newton Falls on the carbonic after we're specifically headed to
the Ma O'ning river it's a warm summer night in 1972 it's 10 p.m. Terry Osnick is standing at the
Mahoning River he's there to meet three friends I've never been to this place I very rarely
leave the state but if you guys are familiar with Newton Falls apparently there's two this
sounds pretty spooky and dope there's two cemeteries and then there's a river and then there's a bridge
that goes from one cemetery to the other so that's kind of cool right like you can go you can visit
all these dead people then you're like hey I wonder who died over there and then you walk
across the bridge but then I would think like the river is good you know go and do and it's water
stuff and you figure it start eroding everything and then eventually like bodies would be rolling
down the hill so like that you're like Jason we planted people the Newton Falls the Newton Falls
people the Newton Falls City Council listen to this podcast all seven of them they're like we
planned it out a little better than Jason I know you imagine like this spooky spooky cemetery from
a Bernstein Bear book but no it's not there's like stuff or maybe their eyes are shifting
side to side they're like uh-oh he knows our secret maybe it's all yeah why would you have a
river going through cemeteries super spooky and let me back up cemeteries aren't normally built on
whether or not they're spooky or not I don't think the city council of newton falls like we should
put it here but oh no that's too spooky water has a really big thing with attracting ghosts when you
look at all sorts of lore all over the world we see water especially running water and ghosts
highly connected and then bridges too anyways he's there to meet his friends I don't think they're
gonna hang out there and discuss water erosion tables I think they're just meeting up in the
middle of nowhere but Terry Oz and Nick is waiting there to meet his three friends and he
hears his buddies crossing the bridge he looks over at him and he's like waving he's like hey guys
over here I'm over and I'm over the less spooky cemetery this one all has 50 less ghosts is this
friends are getting possessed over there no he's looking at his friends they're crossing this bridge
and he sees in the sky a glow he's looking into this glow and inside of this glow in the night
sky this I have to figure out another word for glow there was I want to say glow of the rest of the
episode he looks up and he sees in the illumination a round shiny ball and it's shooting off sparks
it's about 30 feet above his friends and he's panicking obviously he's like what no this is
supposed to be downtown today oh no he's looking at this effinessent we're just gonna start making
upwards at a certain point but I know this is a real one effinessent orb floating above his friends
about 30 feet above his friends and he is panicked he doesn't know what to say and he gets this feeling
that it's scanning him as he's standing there in the darkness he feels like it is reading his
soul he said like it knew everything about him in an instant whatever this was could figure out who
terry ozinek was and terry ozinek was probably trying to figure out who terry ozinek is his entire
body is enveloped in terror and his friends look this is something you only see in movies right
you don't think people do this in real life his friends see him shaking his friends see him in pure
fear and they're like hey terry what's going on and he's like oh i'm gonna oh he doesn't know what
to say he doesn't know he's run out of words to describe glowing he can't even focus in his brain
to warn his friends what he's seen so he just takes off running right he just leaves his friends
he goes running in the opposite direction of this bright orb in the sky his friends begin to chase
after him they still don't know what's going on but they just see their friend had been startled by
something they are they are in two spooky cemeteries on a cursed bridge so they go chasing after him
as he's running away from this and his friends are running behind him terry stop hold up what's
wrong buddy he turns around and the shiny shiny orb is gone it's been replaced by what he can only
describe as a dragon in the shape of the scottish flag it's not flat it's not a rectangle but you
know what i mean like those old classic european type dragons it almost looks like as lion feet and
has like the long neck and he says he sees this dragon in the night sky it's hovering there and
just all around it sparks shooting from its body him and his friends quickly leave the scene
now his friends never saw this thing they left the scene because he left the scene
and because he was so terrified they knew something was wrong they didn't they thought
something might have been wrong with him chasing him down make sure he didn't get hurt
but he told him this story after things calmed down after things calmed down after he's in the
emergency room and they're giving him all the xanax he's like oh man you guys won't believe what i
saw in the doctor the doctor's like oh we might want to keep him here for a while he tells them
that he sees this orb in the sky it gave off a light and then the scottish dragon appeared
and the friends believe him because they know he saw something this story is really interesting to
me obviously i'm telling on the show and i'm telling boring stuff but it's because the story is so
visually weird the glowing orb we come across that all the time we come across that so often in UFO
lore i don't cover it when i look at stories and it's like lights in the sky i don't cover it for a
couple reasons one it's really hard to just talk about lights in the sky on a podcast unless you
can see it and two it can be anything it's so mundane it can be anything but when you have this
is what is so interesting about the story i talk about this all the time on the show so i'm not
going to spend too much time on it but i talk about the lore what we expect from UFO stories what we
expect from ghost stories sometimes they blur we covered one earlier i think it was late last week
about four ghosts and an alien breaking into this woman's house weird but it's more than weird but
sometimes they blur but when you see a glowing object in the sky you assume you're gonna automatically
your brain is going to catalog it with certain things so you're gonna go that's a UFO so you're
gonna expect gray aliens you're gonna expect reptilians pleiadians humanoids we've covered
stories robots and all sorts of stuff but there's a certain you wouldn't expect a leprechaun to jump
out of it and if you're in a haunted house you're expecting to see a very you know maybe get some
evp recordings temperature drops stuff like that maybe you'll see a full body operation maybe you'll
see some hot victorian babe floating down the hallway you would be terrified i mean that would
terrify you too maybe not the babe but imagine if you're in a haunted house and you're getting no
evp readings and you walk into a room and there's a gray alien peeking around the corner
like that because it's so unexpected leprechaun jump out of UFO would just be kind of cool
but being in a haunted house to see an alien in there it's just the image is creepy because
you can imagine the broke down old haunted house and you see that gray alien in the darkness
it's not supposed to be there this story it starts off with the UFO what was the Scottish dragon
and then you start to think was it a dragon like because it scanned him did it pick something that
it thought he would be afraid of did it pick something that he thought he would be in awe of
did it pick something that terry could recognize instead of undulating geometric images folding
upon each other which the brain couldn't process it chose an image that terry could process because
it scanned him but why would it choose something so awe-inspiring that would instill him with fear
he said the sparks looked like it was hot metal being stricken at a forge it was just pure raw
fury in the sky and we do have it at a place you know going back to the whole spookiness of the
place two two cemeteries a running river that really is asking for paranormal activity any body
any moving body of water if you live near a river sorry guys but any moving body of water does seem
to attract this type of entity or this force or creates a gateway for it who knows why so does
this have something to do with paranormal activity at the graveyard that has something to do with
extraterrestrial activity is it both is it neither i love this i love stories that leave you questioning
stories that have such an answer as the alien congress did this and they came down to tell
us to shut our nukes off yeah i mean i think i've become jaded you're like jason that's
groundbreaking july 18th the aliens might say that i'll be i'll be like oh boring as the aliens
are coming down they're giving us cures all these diseases i'm not gonna matter their hands i'm like
do something weird guys do something weird for my podcast you know what i mean like that part of the
like here's the thing and i've said this before when you listen to this podcast this is paranormal
400 a lot of the stuff out there is 101 or as far as like college classes go you got you do have to
learn about the mary celeste and the bermuda triangle and basic bigfoot stuff and roswell
that's all of a good ground game but when i cover stuff on this podcast and i'm not bragging about
the show this is us this is us as a community i'm not just saying that i do this if you listen to
this podcast you've graduated past roswell and betty and barney hill you know you learn that stuff
when you're younger but when you're listening to this podcast we cover the weirdest stuff out there
and then sometimes it just gets so weird even for us you just kind of got to step back and go
what is go what is the actual event here what is going on when we cover the alien invasion
of casablanca where these alien arms these robots show up and start beating up school kids you're
like what is this but at the same time we know in the lore that aliens like to interact with humans
they like to kidnap humans they have these ships and all of this stuff is appearing in this story
as bizarre as the story is i'll put it in the show notes it's one of my favorite
things i've covered on this podcast this one doesn't even have that there's no conflict there's no
entity that we can identify it's just a glowing orb and then a giant dragon shooting out sparks
and that's it and the puzzling stories to me the ones where you just go i don't know what that is
are my favorite they really are my favorite because you just are stuck and you don't have
all the answers you don't have any of the answers you don't even have the questions really just this
bizarre event that happens and that's what i love about doing this podcast is sharing these type of
stories with you guys so the next time you're looking up into the night sky waiting to see a UFO
or cutting the lock on a long abandoned cemetery gate or simply staying up late in your own house
trying to record an EVP be careful be careful of what you look for you may be thinking you're
going to run into a run-of-the-mill ghost or see an orb in the bright sky but you may come across
something that is beyond all understanding that breaks your brain down into a state of madness
terry took off into the darkness engulfed in fear but he had three friends to chase after him
to calm him down to keep him safe what happens if you see something you can explain
and every nerve ending in your body panics at the same time you may want to know the truth
you may search the night skies for answers but are you truly prepared to face the madness
that may come with those answers dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead rabbit radio dead rabbit
radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every
day i'm glad you listened to it today have a great one guys
you