Did a demon possess a man and cause him to rampage through a maternity ward?
And then we travel to Pakistan to take a look at the story of a young woman who left her
house to go hang out with a friend.
But when she came back home later that night, the entire family knew there was something
off about her.
And their suspicions were confirmed when a demon's voice came out of her mouth.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garbiner, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing.
We got a lot of stuff to cover today so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of the original Patreon supporters.
Everyone get on your feet and give it up for Cantillions.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Come on in buddy!
Come on into Dead Rabbit Command.
Cantillions, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
And I gotta say this, for those of you who do support the Patreon, I appreciate it so
much.
I really, really do.
I don't make a lot of money, I don't make a lot of money in general.
And with the Patreon money man, today I went grocery shopping and I was able to buy some
new thermals and I got myself a new little sweater and some food.
Some food and some beef jerky and stuff like that.
Your Patreon donations, they're being spent on not lectures, they're being spent on necessities
and I really, really appreciate those of you who can financially support the show because
it means a lot to me.
It really does mean a lot.
Now if you can't support the Patreon, I'm not shaming you at all, I'm not one of those
podcasts, there's a lot of podcasts that do that, that shame people who don't give them
money.
It's one of the weirdest things in the world, I've stopped listening to podcasts when they
do that, a lot of them do.
If you can't support the show financially, trust me, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio, tell your friends, tell your families,
print out some of the flyers we have in the show notes, get the word out about Dead Rabbit
Radio, that also helps out so much and I appreciate that as well.
I appreciate all of you, whether or not you support me financially or not, or whether
or not you even spread the word, honestly, I still appreciate you guys for taking the
time out to listen to some fun stories.
Cantillions, let's go ahead and get this episode started.
I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the bunny bicycle.
Hope you can support an entire way to a bicycle flying through the air towards you.
Let's hop on the handlebars, as Cantillions pedals us all the way out to Odessa, Texas.
Weak, weak, weak, weak, I probably should spend some of my Beijing on money to oil the
wheels of this bike.
I'll put a baseball card in it next time, maybe that'll be a better sound effect.
We're headed all the way out to Odessa, Texas.
It's October 3rd, 2022.
And we're in the Odessa Regional Medical Center.
That's where this story takes place.
One of us fell off the handlebars.
We're taking you into the ER.
And while we're there, it's about 6.30pm, while a doctor is tending to your wounds.
There's better news.
There's better news than injuring somebody.
Going on in this hospital, Marcus McAllen Jr. is about to be a daddy.
Marcus McAllen Jr., him and his girlfriend have gone to this hospital.
He's in labor.
And he starts kind of walking around the area.
He's just kind of pacing.
People think, "Okay, you know, he's about to be a dad.
He's probably super nervous."
But then he walks up to the nurses station and he grabs a nurse by the arm and he says
something unintelligible.
"Nurse, let go of me, let go of me, weirdo.
You gotta leave.
You can't be over here if you're gonna be grabbing the nurses."
He then begins to run up and down the hospital hallway.
The nurses are like, "What in the world is going on?
Like, they've seen people at all levels of stress up in this area.
This guy is running laps, basically.
What is this guy doing?"
And then there is a woman standing there and she has her newborn baby in a little carrier.
And she's waiting to get discharged.
The nurses observe all this stuff.
The nurses are keeping an eye on Marcus because he's acting so weird and they actually see
this happen.
They go, "Marcus begins to stare at the baby.
He's staring at that baby that the new mom is holding in this carrier."
And he begins walking right towards the mother.
The nurses notice how focused he is on them.
They're very, very nervous about what can happen because he's already so erratic.
And then the mom, I don't know if she did this intentionally.
I don't know if she knew Marcus was coming for her.
I think she probably would have just left.
She goes, "I'll check out tomorrow.
I'll check out tomorrow.
I'll discharge myself."
I don't know if the mom did this on purpose or just because she was moving about, but
the mom kind of turns her body so now she's blocking the view of the baby?
And it's like a light switch gets shot off and Marcus' brain.
The nurses say once the view of the baby, he couldn't see the baby anymore, he literally
just turned around and walked away.
He leaves the area.
The nurses are like, "Okay, whatever in the world that was.
The guy was running up and down the hallway.
Why was he staring at that baby?
I don't know.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]