The discovery of bones in a trailer home lead to some unanswered questions.
A drinking game gets out of control when it involves a power drill, and then we cover one of the most
disturbing topics that we've ever talked about on this show. John Sharp and his spear gun. Today on Dead
Rabbit Radio. Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. Saying that, hold on a
second I'm gonna pop some ibuprofen. And some Sudafed while I'm at it. One more second. And
I'm gonna wash it down with a delicious cup of diet cranberry sprite. You know what's funny I'm
actually do drink that and as I was listening back to the last episode we did about monkeys don't
exist I thought you know what they're gonna sue me because I was equating diets cranberry sprite
with Hans the lunatic. Okay so ibuprofen a little bit Sudafed. Oh I dropped the Sudafed the smallest
of all my pills. Oh there it is. Why do they make pills round? They're like let's design something
that people need to stay healthy and let's make it in the most rollable form. So if they drop it
it rolls and clicks all the dust underneath their chair. I guess I really should just dust under my
chair. Who dusts? Okay who dusts under their chair but I've never dusted in my life. I think
dusting is the dumbest of all cleaning activities. I've never dusted anything. Maybe for a dramatic
effect I ran my finger over a dust line but that's it. I don't ever dust. So before we get started
it was funny I was looking at this so like I said I've been working a lot that's where the episodes
are a bit shorter this one might be around actually revolving around normal length but oh and I do
have to say this real quick. Last night's episode monkeys don't exist took forever to record the
monkeys don't exist story I actually did three takes the first one I was just kind of like
and then the monkey guy he doesn't believe it and these videos are fake isn't that wacky oh my god
look at all of this stuff that this guy doesn't believe in and I'm recording it and I felt myself
zoning out thinking oh my god this might be the worst episode I've ever recorded that's not
true I actually know the worst episode I ever recorded there was an episode a long time ago
I almost quit I hated it so much I'll talk about that some other time but I hated that episode
but anyways I started to zone out and then I was like cut and I started it completely from scratch
and I was going on again like each take was maybe 15 minutes and I'm like I could care less about
this topic like I felt the topic was super interesting but my delivery was so bad and I was
honestly thinking this might be the end of Dead Rabbit Radio like if I maybe I'm just working
the three jobs maybe I'm just too tired mentally tired to do this type of show anymore and I sat
there I stopped recording for a long period of time I just sat there silently in front of the
mic and I thought I'm gonna come up with a narrative to it where and then that's when I invented the
idea of haunts in your bedroom and it turns out to be one of my favorite episodes but yeah after
I got them recording it I was laughing really loud when I was editing that you laughing at your
own stuff is pretty indulgent but yeah I was like okay so I think I'm gonna use that narrative
device I'm gonna use it sparingly but there are there are other conspiracies that I've had on the
doc that were just lists of lunatic facts and I was like it would be lame if I just read these
facts off I didn't I couldn't figure out a way to deliver it so I just kind of like Bamagara's
afterlife is one of them that I've had research for a long time but I'm like there's no it was just
it will just be me listing stuff off but I've created this narrative device and I think that'll
pop up especially with that one because it works but where was I going with that oh yeah yeah three
jobs so I was mentally tired yesterday but part of part of one of my jobs is I kind of have to be
up on my first aid I kind of have to know how to like field dress wounds and stuff like that the
jobs are they're they're mundane working class jobs I'm not like a special agent or anything like
that but so I've been reading up on first aid now I have a I have an app on my phone that's like
the offline survival guide which makes sense because if you're trapped in the wilderness
you're not gonna you're like oh I wish I knew how to make a tourniquet if only I had three bars like
you want to have it just stored on your phone and I found a neat little tip it's only half a tip
though if you have a large blister you're not supposed to pop it because then you have to treat
it as like an open wound and again they're assuming you're out in the middle of nowhere if you're like
at home well you still probably shouldn't pop it but especially if you're out in the middle of
nowhere so they said if you had a large blister this is so gross if you have a large blister and
you don't want to pop it but you want to make it smaller what you do is you take a needle a sterilized
needle and sterilized thread which I don't know how you sterilize thread you can't really
spoil it because then it just gets all but anyways you take a needle and a sterilized thread
and you stick the needle through the blister and it's big enough to put a needle through it's not
just a tiny blister you put the needle through the blister and you pull the string all the way
through and then you take the needle off so you just have this string hanging out of your blister
and the string so gross the string soaks up all of your blister juice so your blister gets smaller
because it's going like the threads absorbing it now that was the end of the tip and I thought well
when do you pull the string out like do you just leave it in there forever the rest of your life
do you just have a string hanging out of your blister like at what point eventually you're
gonna have to pull it out eventually it will then become an open wound and think about it yeah I know
having blisters suck but you know what is secondary to that walking with something in your shoe like
if you're walking down the street and you have a rock in your shoe it's very annoying with this tip
not only do you feel like a string in your shoe but it keeps getting bigger and gooey like your
shoes all I guess you don't have them at both feet but I mean you have a string and then eventually
becomes yarn because it's so full of pus I guess pus is in a blister right some sort of goo some
sort of human made liquid I would I would totally throw those strings at people too just to let you
I'd go to like a like a Michaels and I would pull it out and hide it in the yarn section and old
women are like oh I'm never seeing this exotic yarn old women are like it smells like taquitos
this must be from Mexico my I had a sister who used to work for a podiatrist she said sometimes
people take their shoes off and they smelled like microwave to taquitos because they were so
diseased let's go ahead and move on with the episode I hope none of you were eating taquitos
just now I know it's very popular to listen to dead rabbit and eat a taquito but the first story
comes out of our batch of new news just quick overview if you're just into the show new news
are articles from 2004 that I saved in a folder called new news and forgot about until I found
them on a computer I was junking let's go ahead and look at the first one though first one new news
so this story of course takes place in the year 2004 and in my notes I just wrote Alabama maybe
so I don't I couldn't really figure out what state it was from because the story was so old it was
hard enough for me to even track down the current article because when you have I was downloading
web pages these weren't bookmarks so it wasn't like I could go back to CBS news and even if I could
for the most part that page would probably be purged because some of them would say this page
is available blah blah blah but I did find this one I was happy enough to find the article this is
weird so there's this a 10-year-old girl named Stephanie Ogden and she has this imaginary friend
and her imaginary friend is a black girl in a white dress never got a name that we know at least
maybe she just called her I don't know what's a good name for a go I'm really gonna get detracted
I'm not gonna get sidetracked I'm not gonna get sidetracked okay so she's hanging out with this
ghost girl this black girl with a white dress they were hanging out for the past five years so
Stephanie met this girl it's weird she doesn't have a name though am I wrong they don't even say
it in the article the she was hanging out with this imaginary friend for five years so you know
they're hanging out that's a long time too they're hanging out there she said the mom said whenever
Stephanie wanted a soda she would have to get two sodas one for her and one for her imaginary friend
I don't know check the diabetes on that girl she's probably lying but anyways the parents were like
you don't know kids have imaginary friends it's not a big deal but what happened in in in today in
the year 2004 what happened was they were doing some renovation on their trailer home
they're and so they were pulling up their floorboards and they find a pelvis
pelvis bone on actual pelvis they find a pelvis bone and a leg bone and they're like oh my god
like what's going on here and then they continue to well I'm sure they called the cops then but as
they were continuing to do renovation they find another bone and what's weird is that the bones
when the police investigated it they said it looked like a rat had been carrying them around
underneath the trailer home like it was part of the trailer home itself it wasn't like they
lifted up the floor and they saw a bone in the dirt it was yeah underneath the installation the
insulation you know the pink fuzzy stuff and so the cops are like it's weird because we see that
like a rat had been moving around playing them like a xylophone but the cops said it's also weird
other than the rat moving them is that the people are up late at night they're all where's that xylophone
music coming from the the cops are like I'm marking this girl's death the cops are like we can also
tell that there's some sort of like there was dirt on them so at some point they believe that these
bones were buried and then brought or at least sitting outside for a good amount of time and then
brought into the home and they go well the rat could have brought them into the home which is weird
because the brats don't eat bones or somebody could have left it at left the person outside to decay
and then put them put them in the home or they could have buried the body and then dug it up
through it underneath the floorboards which doesn't make much sense and the cops were like here's the
thing this trailer home has had multiple owners and it's been across multiple states and these are
obviously human bones but we don't know we will never be able to track them down like this could
have been anyone who ever owned this trailer home it could have been in any of these states it could
have been unrelated to the trailer home and a rat was like oh dude these are awesome and he brought
them into his house actually here's a question where's that rat where the rat must still be in
the trailer home what rat is big enough to carry a pelvis bone but so the article was making it
out to be they didn't interview the rat the article was saying that maybe the imaginary friend was the
ghost of the little girl who previously had those bones now that's a creepy like story obviously you
have these bones underneath your floor and your daughter keeps having this imaginary friend who's
humanoid it's not like puff the magic dragon walking around the backyard drinking the second soda
diet cranberry sprite but he it's creepy enough to have bones under your floor but then to think
like this ghost girl was kind of like talking to your daughter for the past five years and also
I was the daughter like hey mom hey dad you know my imaginary friend she's really cool we go to
school together we play forts and her pelvis is under the floor but yeah so I mean it could be
connected it could not be connected we have to you know I you know what actually it's 14 years later
Stephanie Ogden is now 24 years old I'm gonna see if I can try to track her down and find out more
about this dude I didn't think about that we have basically a time machine in our possession the time
machine being an old folder of links this girl's old enough now so Stephanie Ogden of Alabama maybe
get ahold of us get ahold of us if you're one of my 1100 subscribers on youtube wouldn't that be
crazy but let's see if we can find her and ask her if she still has this imaginary friend or what
happened to the rat these are all questions I need to know no I'm curious I'll I'll uh I'll see what
I can dig up and we'll go on to the next story next new news so I'm sure this already got an old
for you this one is a story of levels so it's the year you can guess it's 2004 we're in Perth
Australia we're in Perth Australia there is an unnamed man and an unnamed party of people now
generally unnamed you you have to take the article with a grain of salt but he's saying he wants to
remain unnamed because it's super embarrassing but again you have to take with a grain of salt
this 20 year old man is hanging out with his buddies it's 2004 Chumbo Womba's blasting on your
radio that actually I'm not sure even then I think that song came out 99 they're like why are you
playing this old song um 50 Cent is killing it with Phil and the blank top song they're like man it's
gonna suck that there's not gonna be any more Star Wars movies ever I bet you they could tell the best
stories if they just made more Star Wars films these guys had it all they had the future ahead of
them and our why is this guy unnamed too I can't do stories with unnamed people this guy's name is
this guy's name is uh light bulb so no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
this guy's name is uh light bulb so no no no no this guy's name will call him we'll call him Serge
that's kind of a cool name we'll pretend he just got 21 years old just got he's on break from
American Gladiators so Serge here so Serge made him name don't sue me real Serge from American
Gladiators if you've ever competed in that show Serge here is hanging out with his other 21 year
old friends it was one it was a 21st birthday party for somebody else not Serge and Serge is
there with Nitro and Tank and Flame on and they're like let's all have this drinking game and they're
like yeah that's awesome so one guy pulls out a drinking helmet with a jug on it and they're like
yeah dude we'll just pour liquor in here and it'll drink it in the hose and someone's like no
it's kind of laying that's not how it's not how gladiator rolls so let's take this this pretty
benign jug with the hose coming out into your mouth which isn't that but sounds more like a
saw trap so let's take this jug and let's let's kick it up a notch let's kick it up a notch so
they attached a pump to the reservoir where the liquor is going to go in at this point that all
the gladiators are getting a little curious maybe a little apprehensive maybe a little apprehensive
and some guy goes oh that's that's a cool pump but we need something to power it and they're like
what do we get like double A's triple A's dude breaks out a power drill and says we're gonna
attach this power drill to the pump and turn it on and it's going to push all the liquor straight
into your stomach with that absolutely insane and dangerous idea cheers rose up through the group
they started doing it put a hose in your mouth fill the little reservoir it wasn't reservoir it's a
bucket basically with beer and then they turn on the power drill and the liquor would just be pumped
right into your stomach first guy does it totally fine second guy does it totally fine six people
do it all in all no problem so surge steps up and he's like yeah i can do this puts the hose in his
mouth turn someone turns the power drill on now surge surges quote later much much later said
and i'm paraphrasing the first part but he was saying that he knew something was wrong
when he started to throw up quote red stuff unquote surge that's known as blood it's not
generally called red stuff and that's exactly what happened he began vomiting up blood and alcohol
and basically fell down his friends rush him to the hospital in their gladiator mobile it's
they're in those big balls that they all have to run in they're like hurry up get him his body's
like flipping anyways they get him in the hospital they get him to the thunderdome med take him in
there what happened was the force of the liquor going into his stomach was so intense it ripped a
10 centimeter i don't know what that is in in real measurement but a 10 centimeter rip in his
stomach so all the beer and all the cheap food and all the weight gaining supplements and the
creatine powder all of that pushed into his body and the doctors are basically like this dude's
toast there's no way this guy's gonna make it but you know we get paid by the hour so they open them
up i don't know if they get paid by the hour but they open them up and they were able to kind of
vacuum everything out and they had to give him a ton of antibiotics and i think it was like a week
or two but he was in a coma such and going all that stuff imagine all okay i just imagine getting
a rip in your stomachs bad enough but then to imagine like the taquitos you just ate or those
20 chicken nuggets and all that stuff just hitting your liver they're just like bumping around in you
i the stomach acid would burn that'd probably be the only thing you would feel but i think you
would also just like i said you have a pebble in your shoe that's irritating imagine having 20
chicken nuggets just hanging out in your body they're out of your stomach they're just chilling
you have these little lump shape you have like a little boot shaped um lump pushing against your
stomach i probably he probably didn't care what his stomach looked like he was dying but the moral
of the story obviously is this don't engage in stupid drinking games but i think the bigger moral
of the story is why doesn't everyone just use english measurement what is it called imperial
why do people still use stuff like centimeters and kilometers i don't get that these articles
from other countries are irritating just use inches bro it makes you seem taller kind of i mean if
somebody says i'm 300 centimeters tall you sound no matter how many things no matter how big the
number is before centimeter you sound tiny you sound absolutely tiny just say inches or feet
something guys get on board get on board for the sake of this podcast and the sake of the
fact that i could use google and easily you know what here let's find out how big 10 10 centimeters
is because i do have the internet in front of me it better be impressive though because i'm gonna
be upset otherwise where's my phone oh i have a like on tinder okay let's see here this better
be impressive or i'm gonna be mad 10 centimeters in inches it's three inches that that's a sizeable
gap i want to see how tall i am in centimeters i'm five i mean six no i'm five foot 11.5 in centimeters
let's see that's 181 centimeters that makes me sound like a tiny person if someone ever asked how
tall you are and i said oh i'm 181 centimeters what makes me sound lily pushin lily lily um
lily yeah it's a lily pushin pushin the little people from gulliver's travels you know he went
to other places in those books like he went to the tiny place and then he went to a place where he
was tiny and then he went to a place full of like hot air balloons or something i don't remember what
the third or fourth place was but nobody does everyone just remembers that he was a giant and
there's tiny people running around and i barely remembered that he was tiny but anyways he would
have 108 tell me 181 centimeters doesn't sound tiny tell me that um do i have time to do the spear
gun story considering my rant on centimeters i don't think i do i don't think i do you know here
okay oh i'm gonna be completely honest with the spear gun story the spear gun story i actually
have a full episode a 20 minute episode recorded of the spear gun story and it is so creepy and
disturbing that i recorded it a couple days ago and was like i'm not gonna release this i you the
sound of my voice towards the end i'm just like and i had that was an episode that i enjoyed
recording from a technical standpoint and from a storytelling standpoint but it's so grizzly and
early in the podcast we did more we did some darker stuff and as the podcast has evolved i've
kind of moved away from that the spear gun story is far darker than anything we've covered before
i think so i know there's a lot of people who are like oh i listened to that episode while i was
eating Cheerios it was no big deal i didn't yeah that's fine but for me it was disturbing and
just a sheer inhumanity of it so you know now that i've pumped it up i think what i'll do and it
will actually it is a recorded episode and i am running out of time this week so i'm going to
just use this as a teaser for that story and i will release that one tomorrow because i thought
i was like i'm just gonna do a quick overview of it but i'm just gonna i'll release the episode
that i recorded i'll edit it up and to be honest that helps because like i said i'm short on time
this week to have recorded a full episode to not release was making it difficult but i'm gonna
have to go in and put an ending in it or something some in the movie the episode just ends i was just
like i'm done but it is a very interesting story it's and but i'll warn you now if you're not into
it's not super gory it's just so inhumane um if you're not into that just skip it just skip the
next episode because the whole episode is just going to be that 20 minute story so i know i said
it in the beginning but i'm gonna leave it in there as a i don't even want to call it a teaser
because the episode's such a downer i thought about re-recording it with a big smile on my face
just so the tone was lifted a bit but um we're gonna go ahead so actually that works out for me
because that means i don't have to record an episode tomorrow but see now i feel bad because
basically i've spent the last five minutes talking about let me give you an other interesting new
news story how's that i don't want you to feel like you just had to listen to how the sausage was
made for five minutes and it was kind of out so let's give you another new news story here
let's go out on a good note let's go out on a happy note so what do we got what do we got this was
something i was going to talk about later but i think we'll find a good one for you here
um here's one this is a funny one the year 2004
we're in the country of Bahrain which if my geography tells me right it is
uh the middle east the mess i don't know why it's based on that it's the middle east okay
predominantly muslim country now everyone's chilling in the mosque and they're getting ready for
their sermon and everyone's just kind of hanging out doing the thing and this dude walks up big old
beard kind of moving towards the podium like they're going to deliver a sermon and the cleric
who's in charge of the church or the mosque i guess is the technical term but the cleric who's
in charge of the mosque notices this stranger he's never seen before start to walk up to the stand
to deliver a sermon and the cleric goes hey hey are you here to to do a sermon and the cleric's like
yeah i'm here i'm here to do a sermon i'm here to speak to these these fellow muslim people
here in this mosque and the cleric he said in a he said in his quote his voice was strangely soft
and his beard slipped as he spoke so imagine this big dude comes walking up and you've never
seen him before and you're like hey man what's up and they're like oh nothing and then every time
they move their fake beard is moving farther and farther down her his face actually you know
nothing about the story isn't funny it's kind of horrific but in a different way what happened was
so the cleric realizes that this is a woman with a beard on and she wanted to give a speech because
her brother got arrested or was being prosecuted or persecuted one of the two for something that he
may or may not have done and she went she was going to deliver this impassion this story's
horrible this isn't funny jason this woman was going to deliver this impassioned speech on behalf
of her brother but once the cleric realized that it was a woman he's like no get out get out you
because they have to in strict muslim countries the women and the men are separated well and that
she wasn't wearing a burqa or anything like that that would have been a bad disguise she has a full
burqa and a beard and anyways a bunch of guys showed up in the overpowered her sorry i thought this
story was gonna be funny here the image of a woman in a beard try it came off as something from like
kids next door or like someone wearing a really bad disguise like a really bad sanisuit was how
i envisioned the story when i read it but now as i'm reading it out loud it actually is quite sad
that this woman broke all these rules to try to get her brother free and then she got manhandled
she was surprisingly strong it took five men to get her out she did get arrested she did get
bailed out of course this was in 2004 so i don't know what happened afterwards hopefully her and
her brother are out doing fine man that story was not a fun story either yeah i just imagined it more
like a bad sanisuit and then i realized all of the cultural and sexual and religious implications
in that otherwise a slipping beard story now whenever i see a santa with a bad beard i'm like
i'm gonna be reminded of this episode and it's christmas time so that's gonna happen a lot
well thanks for bearing with me this was a weird episode it was kind of off the cuff
because i made that change in the end but we will do the speargun story tomorrow i'm not trying to
hype it up too much but it is an interesting story but again i have no problem if you guys give it
deadrabbitradio@gmail.com is going to be your email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio
twitter is @jasonlcarpenter deadrabbitradio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast
you don't have to listen to it every day but i'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys