A supernatural thief on the run from the law.
And then we visit a town in England that seems to have a taste for fire,
fear, and the souls of children today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too. We have a lot of good stuff for you today.
[music]
So I wanted to start the story off with the tale of a photo that I happened to find
while I was out walking today.
Now, of course, talking about a photo can be difficult about on a podcast.
And I'm going to start off by saying that this story is 100% true,
because you could be thinking, "Oh, Jason's just larping.
Jason's just trying to set up some narrative going on with the podcast."
But today I was-- and it's 100% true.
I showed the picture to Veronica earlier.
I kind of had to explain to her why the picture was more worrying than normal.
But it could be a totally logical explanation for this.
So let me actually go get the picture here.
[music]
It's not like I can actually show it to you or anything, but--
So I found this picture. It's on one of those little instax,
Fuji film instax thing.
It's basically the kid version of an old Polaroid camera,
like I had when I was a kid.
So it's a little picture. It's probably about two inches by an inch and a half,
a pink border on it.
And in the picture, what I'm going to do too,
just so you can have a frame of reference,
is I'm going to take a photograph of this picture,
and I will put it up on the website.
So if you go to deadravid.com, you'll see a copy of the picture.
And if you're listening to this on YouTube,
you're probably looking at a photo of it right now.
So let me explain to you a little bit about it.
It's funny because I didn't plan on talking about this,
so we'll see about those other stories.
But the photo, you're going to see black smudges on the sides.
That's not dirt or anything to make it look any creepier.
It is the ink coming off of the back of the picture.
The little film has been slightly removed.
When I found this, it was raining.
So it wasn't in the best condition,
but all the dirt isn't to make it look spooky.
That is just ink.
I got ink all over my hands when I picked this photo up as well.
I had to carry it with me.
But if you're not looking at the photo right now,
let me explain it briefly to you.
The camera is tilted slightly.
So the camera itself is tilted slightly.
So it gives it a look as if someone
wasn't looking straight on at their subject,
but they're holding their camera at a,
I don't know, 60 degree angle.
In the picture, we see what looks to be an apartment.
The apartment looks fairly,
I don't want to say abandoned
'cause that makes it too creepy,
but you can see that the blinds are kind of a skew.
They're not lined up right.
The only thing we see in the photo is an oven, a stove,
I guess whatever, that thing that you put food in.
Cabinets, the top of a chair,
presumably a kitchen chair,
a couple of knickknacks on a windowsill.
And what appears to be a young woman cowering in fear
of whoever's taking the picture.
So my first instinct obviously is that
this is a staged photo some kids are messing around.
And that is very likely.
There's actually three scenarios here.
One is that this is a staged photo
and these kids are messing around
and they either lost it
or they left it there intentionally.
It was raining.
So again, if someone was going to put this out there
to be like, ooh, let's do some spooky stuff.
You may want to have waited until it wasn't raining
or put it somewhere where it wouldn't get wet,
but again, it just adds to the creepiness factor
that it was sitting out in the rain.
It was sitting face up, I walked right by it
and looked down, picked it up.
The other option is this.
So there is a famous, if you're into true crime,
you most likely have seen this photo before.
Let me actually get some more info on it.
Again, I didn't plan on doing this part of the show.
I showed it to Veronica and I was going to save it,
but I was just looking at it on my,
put it on the top of my fridge and I said,
"No, I'm going to do that story now."
So let me get some quick information for you here.
So there is, if you're into true crime,
you've come across this photo.
It's a very famous photo.
It's the last photo of Regina K.
And who Regina K is?
Sorry, it's the last photo of a woman named Regina K. Walters
and I'll also have this photo on deadrabbit.com.
All the show notes are going to be in as normal.
So if you forget the website or whatever,
you can still locate this stuff.
But I really think you should check it out.
There is a photo of a woman named Regina K. Walters.
She is, it was chilling the first time I saw it.
It's actually still quite chilling, but.
It's a photo of her standing on what looks to be
an abandoned barn or a house that has been partially destroyed.
She is standing there, her hair has dyed black.
She's wearing different clothes than she had on
than when she was kidnapped.
And she's cowering in fear in front of the camera.
And the camera is tilted about 60, 70 degrees at an angle.
So that's what made me a little more suspicious of the photo
is that it matches this very famous true crime photo.
So the first option again is that it's completely made up
and it just coincidentally matches one of the most famous
last photos of a victim that it's pretty iconic again,
if you've in true crime, you've probably seen it.
The second scenario is that it is fake
and it happens to, sorry, the second scenario
is that it is fake and the people who took it
were making it match that photo in the first place.
That was kind of the point.
They go, oh, that's a creepy photo.
Let's do that.
Let's do this sideways thing, this angle.
The third option, the least likely of all the options
is that it's real, that this young, unidentified woman
was really cowering in fear that the photo was staged
as some sort of fetish or warning or trophy.
As of now, there's been no reports of missing women
in my area.
So, and it's a small town.
So it's not something that I'm super concerned about.
I just think it's an interesting item.
So we're gonna go ahead and we're gonna hold onto this.
And again, I want to 100% assure you
that this is not a LARP, this is not an ARG,
this is not some fictional narrative
that I am building up for the podcast.
This is 100% true.
And I understand if you go, Jason's just mucking about.
Like, I get that you would think that.
I know that I did the four short story episodes
a while back, but those were completely different
intro music, completely different tone.
They were labeled as such.
I may continue to do this, I don't know.
They still get hits, but I don't know
if I'm gonna keep doing that.
But this is 100% true.
As far as my part of the story of finding the photograph,
I can't verify that the photo itself is not fake.
But if it is fake, I had no part in taking the photo.
I had no part in planning the photo.
I had no part in anything like this.
It was just laying on a rock as I was walking by.
And I'm not so famous in my area
that someone would be like,
"Oh, Jason Carpenter walks by here.
"Let's leave him a photo and get on his podcast."
So, yeah, really weird.
I took it, I showed it to Veronica.
She thought it was weird.
I showed her the backstory and showed her the photo
of the young woman who was also missing.
The dude who did kill her, I just looked that up.
He's in prison.
He's like in his 70s.
So I don't think he's kicking it around in my neighborhood.
But so yeah, weird.
I'll keep you updated.
I'll tell you this right now.
There's probably no ending to the story.
I'm probably not gonna come back a week from now
and being like, "I was being chased by guys in cloaks."
Or, "This woman went missing."
To be honest, it probably is just a weird series
of coincidences, but I will keep you guys updated.
I wanted to go ahead and share that story with you.
It's kind of different than what I normally show.
It kind of falls into my personal experience,
ghost story type things.
And I kind of prefer to cover stuff
that I can show you articles and verify,
but I'm gonna post the photo of the photo.
And I'll post a copy of the other photo
of the young woman that I think this photo is emulating
and we'll go from there.
Okay, so let's go ahead.
I didn't plan on doing that, but I was like,
'cause that actually just happened today
where I found the photo.
And I was like, "Oh, we'll do it later."
But no, I'm glad we did it today.
So, and I know no one's gonna believe me, but anyway,
so let's get, and that's fine.
That's fine.
I don't, yeah.
It's good to be skeptical, even of me.
Never heard to be skeptical of anybody.
So, but it is true.
So anyways, okay, and we're back.
Actually, I took a bit of a break there.
I talked to it.
This next story I went on for like 20 minutes talking about.
I think it's an interesting story.
I don't know if it's 20 minutes interesting.
And I said it'd be easier for me to just rerecord it
than to have to edit it down.
So I do think it's definitely an interesting story,
but I talked about it way too long.
What we're gonna do is we're going back in time
to the late 1800s.
So we're after the Civil War, we're in the United States.
We're in the South.
And there was a man who was known as Railroad Bill.
So Railroad Bill is half factual, half legend.
Maybe the legends are true.
I don't know.
We'll explore that in a bit.
But Railroad Bill was just a normal dude.
Well, he's a little more than normal
because nobody knew anything about him.
He just kind of popped up in the area.
We don't know anything about his childhood
or where he came from.
And even people there, they weren't too familiar
with who he was.
He went by the name of Morris Slater.
But even then it seemed like
that may not have actually been his real name.
People stories go that he originally started off
as a circus performer
and ended up getting a job at a Turpentine company,
which I guess somebody has to manufacture Turpentine.
Turpentine is paint remover.
It's most popularly known as the dip that Judge Doom
put shoes in.
I'm sure a painter will be like,
"No, it's more popularly known,
"popularly known as paint remover."
But anyways, worked at a Turpentine company.
He also enjoyed riding the rails.
So there was a rail company back in the day called Louisey.
They weren't really good with names back then.
This railroad company was called,
this railroad company was called Louisville
and Nashville Railroad.
So again, like, yeah,
you're just kind of describing what it is.
He hitches a ride on the rail.
The breakman on the train finds him
and picks him up and throws him off the train.
And from this event, railroad bill vowed vengeance
on the train company.
But anyways, then this breakman throws him off the train
and he like falls into the dirt.
And most people's first reaction would be like,
"Whoa, I'm glad I didn't get mangled horribly by the train."
Railroad bill's first reaction is to pull out his rifle,
which he somehow kept a hold of.
If I was throwing it off a train,
I wouldn't then be like,
"And take your rifle with you."
But anyways, railroad bill takes out his rifle
and opens fire on the breakman.
Train just keeps on chugging along.
From that day, railroad bill vowed vengeance
on the train company.
Now getting thrown off a train
isn't the easiest thing to endure,
but railroad bill made it his life mission
to go after the train company.
Actually quit his job at the Turpentine company.
He's like, "You can kill tunes on your own."
And formed a gang that then hijacked trains and robbed them.
And what they would do is they would put one guy
on the train, they would hide a guy on the train
and be like, "Tip one, don't get thrown off."
But they would put a guy on the train.
And when the train would kind of be out in the middle
of nowhere, the dude would open the door out
and throw all the goods out of the train.
The story goes that railroad bill would then get the goods,
get the contraband.
Is it contraband?
Well, he would get the stolen property
and then give it to the poor.
He hated the railroad so much,
he's like, "I don't even want to make money from this.
I'm just gonna give all this stuff to the poor."
So the people in the area saw him as like a folk hero,
as a real Robin Hood type guy.
He also, this is why, the story is true crime-ish,
but the reason why I'm covering it,
I came across this in that great book
that I love, National Jerk Crew of Haunted Places.
There'll be a link below if you wanna buy the book yourself,
and which I highly recommend everyone doing.
And it is affiliate links,
so when you buy something, I get a little bit,
but still, I highly recommend everyone getting this book.
He had, the rumor goes that he actually had
the power to shape shift.
And he could assume either the form of a big black dog
or any inanimate object.
Now, if I had a choice between becoming like,
yeah, being a big black dog helps you run around
and menace people, but if I can become any inanimate object,
I would just become a $100 bill.
And then have my buddy, which back then was a ton of money,
have a buddy buy stuff, and then the hand over the $100 bill,
and they don't notice the little picture of the guy
like, "Winking" at the get, at that,
is a accomplice going, "Wink!"
And then after they get the goods,
he can turn back into a human and run out the back door.
That's how I would rob stuff
if I could turn into inanimate objects.
But anyways, I wonder if you turned into a stage coach
and people were inside you, would that be comfortable?
They're like, it's just like an eight month ride
through the wilderness.
But anyways, so, well, if you turn into a stage coach,
is that inanimate?
Technically, the coach part is you'd have to get
some wheels put on you.
But anyways, so railroad bill could turn
into an inanimate object or a big black dog.
And that's the legend.
The reason why that legend grew
was because they could not catch this guy.
First off, there was a $350 reward,
which again, is a ton of money back then.
And as his crime spree progressed, at one point,
okay, at one point he was fell asleep
behind a water tower along these train tracks.
These train employees found him.
They grabbed his rifle, they grabbed his pistol,
and then woke him up.
They're like, "Get up, get up, railroad bill,
we're assuming 'cause you're by railroad."
Railroad bill jumps up, sprints 100 yards,
pulls out another gun he had hidden
and starts a gun battle.
And the dudes weren't prepared for that.
They had to hide in this little shed
and he's like shooting in the shed.
(imitates gun shooting)
And the other guys are like, "Pfft, pfft, pfft, pfft,
shooting."
And around that time, this is just luck,
this isn't supernatural, a train pulls up to the water tower.
Railroad bill jumps in the train,
hijacks it to make his getaway.
But he hated the train company so much,
he drove the train about 200 yards, stopped it,
got off the train and started another gun battle
with the people in the shed.
And he kept shooting at them until he ran out of ammo
and then just took off.
Eventually, more law enforcement got called in,
a sheriff was killed.
At that point, the reward was raised to $1,250,
which in today's money was $34,000.
So everyone was out looking for this guy.
You had Pinkerton detectives, you had vigilantes,
bounty hunters, law enforcement, railroad officials,
just normal dudes or shotguns.
He ends up getting cornered in a swamp
and a hundred men are on his tail.
Now these are all different groups.
So some of them are gonna be expert trackers,
some of them are just gonna be moonshine people.
Not like they're made of moonshine,
but you know, like people who drink a lot of moonshine.
It's much easier to evade one group of people
that are working as a group than it is to have to outrun
basically a hundred different battle plans.
Every group's searching for him on his own.
For five days, he evades them in the swamp.
And that's again why people are like,
yep, told ya, he's a shapeshifter.
I can imagine like these hillbillies
walking through a swamp looking for this dude.
And there's just this giant tree there
with like these cartoon eyes,
just like looking at him and he's like (laughs)
and then once they leave,
he turns back into a human and runs away.
Or he like turns into a frog.
I guess it's not an animated object.
He turns into a frog that doesn't move.
So that's an animate.
It kind of probably pushed in the boundaries there.
But anyway, so he does all this stuff.
He eventually does meet his end.
He's at like a convenience store, like an old timey shop.
And two different teams of vigilantes
come at the same time and they riddle him full of bullets
and he dies.
And you go, well, that's proof that he's not a shapeshifter.
However, I will argue that maybe he's simply shapeshifted
into a dead body to keep everyone.
That's an animate, right?
And then afterwards he jumped out of his grave.
Actually, I know for a fact that's not true
'cause his body was on display for so long
in so many different cities that judges had to say,
you can't, you have to stop displaying this guy's body.
He was that big of a local legend, that big of an outlaw.
The people loved him, law enforcement hated him.
Whether or not he was a shapeshifter
is definitely up for debate.
I'd like to think that he was.
I think that makes the world more interesting.
He should have shapeshifted into a bulletproof vest
at the end, but anyways, so again,
he was such a local figure that they're actually,
I believe it was in the 20s, they wrote a ballot
for railroad bill, little ballot.
And I'm going to sing a part of it for you.
Now I can't play it for you because copyright,
even though it was in the 1920s,
the only recording I have is copyrighted,
but the lyrics themselves are not copyrighted.
Railroad bill up on a hill,
light and cigar with the $10 bill.
Now, before you criticize the lyrics,
again, this is an old timey song.
So it's not like these guys are coming out
with their A game.
This people are like, damn, he rhymed hill with bill
and bill again.
But anyways, railroad bill up on a hill,
light and cigar with the $10 bill.
Railroad bill took my wife,
if I don't like it, gonna take my life.
Not only is he a shapeshifter,
not only is he a train bandit,
not only is he a, well, not modern day Robin Hood,
but not only is he an American Robin Hood,
he also cucks you.
Yep, so that's the story of railroad bill.
Now imagine that story I just told you,
it expounded to 20 minutes
and you'll understand why I cut out a bunch of stuff.
And also I went on too long talking about that.
I can't, I didn't have room to talk about our next story.
So let's go ahead and move on to our next story here.
We're going to England.
We spent a lot of time in England.
We spent a lot of time in South America
and we've spent a lot of time in England.
I'd like to do some more like Australia,
Eastern European stuff, African stuff.
We spent a little bit of time in Africa.
Crazy Cryptid Week was there,
but now we're back in England
and we're going a little bit back in time here,
which tends to happen.
I don't know, every time I go to England
I get caught in some sort of time warp.
1920s.
Now in Gillingham, England,
which is in the states,
they don't call them states over there or whatever.
They call them like, the cities are called shires
and the states are called counties or something like that.
But anyways, in the shire of,
and someone's like totally like,
no, that's not true at all,
but in the shire slash town of Gillingham,
in the 1920s, they had the Gillingham Fair
and one of the highlights of the Gillingham Fair was,
they would build this three story structure
out of wood and canvas.
And you're thinking, that seems incredibly dangerous.
That seems very flammable.
Uh-huh.
So they built this three story structure
out of wood and canvas
and it was for a firefighters demonstration.
And they had this thing.
It's called the bridal party rescue.
I don't know if that's what it's actually called,
but that's what we're gonna call it.
They had this event that was a bridal party rescue
where you had two firefighters
who would act as newlyweds.
So they'd go up there.
I don't know if they put on tuxes and wedding dresses
'cause they're both dudes 'cause this is the 1920s,
but anyways, they go up there
and they have a bridal party
and they're in the structure.
And this is out of fair.
So people are watching this.
Like you have this huge crowd watching this event.
And then you have flares go off and smoke go off
and everyone goes, oh no, help me, help me,
firemen of Gillingham.
And the firefighters come
and they bring out their ladders
and they rescue the people out of the structure
and everyone claps and they're like,
oh, these are very efficient firemen.
And then they start a real fire
and they burn the structure down
and they just put it out with their hoses.
And everyone would be like, yay.
There's nothing else to do back then.
I mean, like that was the highlight of your year
when you got to see that happen.
And went off without a hitch, quite a while.
But eventually there was a hitch.
So you know where this story's going in 1929.
So now we're on July 11th, 1929.
It's fair time.
Everyone's like, oh dude,
are you gonna go see the canvas structure burned?
Oh yeah, totally, man.
Of course I'm gonna see the canvas structure burned down.
That's all I'm gonna do this year.
So they go out there.
And for this bridal party this time,
you had nine boys and six men.
So you had two of them or the bride in the groom
and the rest of the people were pretending
to be the wedding guests.
And for what, and this is where the story goes weird
and we're gonna explore this more.
But for whatever reason,
the smoke bombs and the flares, they don't go off.
Instead, the second stage starts.
So this people are in this building.
You have a total of 15 people here.
The fire starts.
Now that's supposed to happen
after everyone's out of the building.
Again, it's three stories.
It's 40 feet tall and it catches on fire.
Now it doesn't take a rocket science to know
that canvas and wood are incredibly flammable.
The building just ignites.
Now the firefighters on the scene, on the ground,
who were there to be there to do the mock rescue
and then put the fire out afterwards,
they realize immediately what's going on.
They just flameshoot out the building.
They look at each other, drop their tea and crumpets,
grab their gear and start trying to put out the fire.
But the audience thinks that it's part of the show.
They're like, man, special effects
have gotten really good this year.
Normally there's just smoke coming out of the windows,
but look at those flames go.
The audience is cheering at this fire.
The people in the building are screaming for help.
They immediately know that things have gone sideways.
'Cause some of the adults in the building are firefighters.
They immediately begin screaming for help
and the audience is now even clapping even harder.
They're like, this is the best performance
those people have ever given.
Normally they're just like, help me, help me.
But these guys actually seem like
they're crying for their lives.
This is amazing.
The crowd is cheering them on.
Firefighters are probably just like, shut up.
Actually, the firefighters probably didn't even hear him.
They're just blasting this thing with water.
And the audience continued to applaud
until the first boy jumped off the top of the building
on fire, smashed into the ground.
And the audience is kind of like slowly stopped clapping.
They're watching this and then another boy
jumps out of the building on fire,
crashes into the ground.
Of the people who were there,
so there was 15 people in the building,
of the people who were there,
13 of them died at the scene.
Horribly burned, choked out on smoke.
Two of them leapt to their deaths on fire.
Two were severely injured and then they died later.
So out of the 15 people in the building, all 15 died.
They don't know how the fire started.
They don't know who started the fire.
They don't know what happened at the event.
They just know it was this horrible tragedy.
Basically the city shut down.
There was this huge funeral.
They're all buried in the same location.
So I read about that event.
And I was like, that's just a tragic event.
But what's weird, it is weird that all this time
we don't know who started the fire.
Like you think that would be one detail you would know.
Cause there's someone's job was to start the fire.
Cause they're firemen.
They're not like mucking about.
They're not just like throwing matches and stuff
waiting to go off.
They're very controlled to burn.
But no firefighter was ever accused
or brought to trial or anything like that.
The fire just started.
And you go, okay, just a tragic coincidence,
technological failure, whatever.
22 years later in the same town,
Shire of Gillingham,
there was a bus and a street light.
Out of all the street lights in the world
that could have went out,
one street light goes off.
A year old bus drivers driving down the road.
This bus driver worked for a company
called the Chatham and District Traction Company.
They needed a, somebody's invented a time machine
and go back in time and teach people how to name stuff.
The Chatham and District Traction Company,
which you can actually shorten district traction
to distraction, oddly enough.
Street lights out, bus drivers going down the road.
Now normally it wouldn't be a huge issue,
but something else was going on in the street.
And also the bus driver did had his side lights on,
but he didn't have his headlights on,
which was actually at the time totally legal.
You didn't have to drive their headlights on.
And this was later, obviously,
and that's why the street light being out
and him not having headlights on is an issue.
While he's driving this bus down the road,
there is a march.
There is a parade of 52 young kids
of the Royal Marines Volunteer Cadet Corps
between the ages of nine and 13,
marching down the street in their nice little uniforms.
They're dark uniforms, that doesn't help.
He doesn't see them with the street light being out
and him not having any headlights.
He plows into them.
The bus driver didn't even know he hit him.
It was a double-decker bus and they're little kids.
So it's tragic as that is.
I mean, it's be hard to see.
He runs over him and he doesn't even realize
that he has hit anything until he started
to feel the car wobbling like he was driving
over loose stones, which would have been bodies
caught up in the wheels.
Witnesses at the scene say, "We don't believe that
because the minute he impacted them,
you just hear it screaming everywhere."
They believe that he knew much quicker
that he had hit these kids
and for whatever reason kept going.
Out of the, I mean, okay, now you're driving
a bus down the road and there's 52 kids marching
in the intersection.
You have to have, this is school shooter numbers
of the damage he did.
Like I imagine if a bus hits a bunch of kids
at a certain point they're gonna start moving
out of the way or if he hits a broadside,
he's only gonna take out a chunk of them.
Out of 52 kids, 24 killed, 18 injured.
So more than half of the kids in that group got ran over
or maybe a couple got trampled.
At the time, it was the highest loss of life
in any road accident in British history.
I saw both of these events and I thought, yes, coincidence.
Both of these events relied on just a little problem.
And we see that with a lot of stuff,
like plane crashes, they can say it was just
this one instrument or this could have been prevented
if just this one little piece was in place or whatever.
But it seems chilling that both of these events
separated by 22 years in the same city
with mass loss of life of a lot of kids
both happened through happenstance.
They both happened by sheer bad luck.
Him not having his headlights on, like I said,
that was legal at the time.
So they didn't, that probably wouldn't have made an issue.
But the street light going out and him running over
the kids and then the light, the fire,
mysteriously being set before it was supposed to
and nobody was ever held accountable for that.
I was looked at these two things and I thought,
this sounds very like Derry, Maine.
This sounds very like a Pennywise type situation.
And I started, no, again, a lot of times people go,
man, you're really skeptical.
But I don't always start off like that.
So with this, I go, they were 22 years apart.
Let's see what happened 22 years after the bus accident.
Let's see what happened 22 years before the Gillingham fire.
Like I tried to look for some sort of pattern,
some sort of Pennywise style pattern.
I couldn't find any, to be fair.
But it does seem in that short amount of time
that all these kids were killed,
it really does give the two stories a connected,
really creepy vibe.
And not only were mass amounts of kids killed,
but the way they were killed was terribly brutal.
Is it possible that the town of Gillingham
is powering itself from the torment and death of children?
If I wanted a liable lawsuit, I would say definitely.
If I wanted to be skeptical about it, I'd say no,
they're just two tragic events in the same area.
And you can look all over the world
for tragic events in the same area
and they may meet some sort of pattern.
But there's a part of me that thinks
that there's something a little more creepy going on there.
I have no proof of that.
And it hasn't been replicated.
I can't prove it.
I just get it, it just gives me a creepy feeling,
a creepy hunch that there is something there.
Or more importantly, there was something there
that made these events happen.
I have no proof of that whatsoever.
At all, just a hunch.
But sometimes a hunch is all you really have.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarvin.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
(upbeat music)