A woman has a terrifying experience that we can all relate to. Is it possible that you can create
superfood by sucking on a seed and then for the first time in human history, the dead speak today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Let's go ahead and say thank you to
our newest Patreon supporter, Michael Hunt. Michael, thank you so much. We really, really appreciate
you supporting the Patreon. It means a lot. You're going to be piling us around this episode. If you
can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. I totally understand. Just help get the word out about
the show. That really helps a lot. We have now reached back our numbers where we were pre-lockdown.
When the quarantine happened, we took a dive in listenership. So I'm very, very happy with the
people who stuck around and now we're back to where we were. I think people are just trying to get
like mentally there and people who commuted to work, who listened to the show or were at school,
listened to the show. But it seems like we've gotten everyone back. That's awesome and handsome.
So thank you so much for you guys who are sticking with the show. Again, you don't have to listen to
it every day. You don't even have to listen to every episode, honestly. If you just listened to
an episode every once in a while, that's totally awesome. I would listen to every episode. I think
the show is pretty awesome. But if you, you know, people tell me, "Oh, I didn't listen to the last
episode. I don't care. Listen next one." Or the one after that, "I don't matter to me." Anyways,
Michael, we're going to give you the keys to the Carpentercopter. We are headed off to Cat,
this is a disgusting name of a place. Cagged with, what does that even mean? Cagged with,
it's in the Shire of Cornwall in England. So we're flying our Carpentercopter over this little town.
Everything's just muddy and gross and all the people are dismal and depressed and they're like,
"Oh, I wish I lived in a cooler town. Wish I lived in like any town. I wish I lived in Stinkville.
I heard that place smells so much better than Cadg with." Anyways, there's a little cottage here.
This is from the year 1988. We don't have a lot of details from this. It's from that. Think about
a docs.com website, which I absolutely love. I'm going to spend the weekend really pouring over it.
This is referenced in a magazine and we've talked about this magazine before and I've never
been able to find out exactly what it is. It's in the names hilarious though. The magazine is called
Pancake Perspectives. Now they've shown up twice, so I guess it's like a paranormal, but I don't know
why you would talk about pan-- why you would have-- I mean, I guess Dead Rabbit Radio is not, that doesn't
make you think we're talking about ghosts and conspiracies, but I'm not a food. It's not, you
know, it's not like flambé, podcast. You'd be like, "What you would-- you expect pancakes?" If it's
called Pancake Perspective, maybe it was a magazine about pancakes. And first of all, often they just
told a ghost story. I don't know. But anyways, let's land the carpenter copter. We're going to put on our
little booties so we don't actually touch the disgusting ground of Caggwith. We're going to
take a look at the story. There's a young woman she spent in the night at a local college out of
towner. She's a toony. She's just hanging out and cagged with. I would assume lost on her way to
a cooler named city. But anyways, she's in this cottage late at night. She gets up. It's windy.
Rainy. And just generally inhospitable, aka the weather in England all the time. She's like,
"Why does this wake me up? It's always like this." She's walking around this cottage late at night.
She looks down a long hallway. So you know this story's going to be good, right?
She looks down a long hallway. Which at first off, I have a question. How long can a hallway be in
a cottage, right? Whenever I think of a cottage, I think of like a Thomas Kincaid picture. It
doesn't even look like there would be a hallway. It looks like it's just, you walk through the door,
it's just one big room. And then there's like an eight foot tall wizard sitting by the fire.
And that's a cottage. I don't imagine, Gandalf wasn't really eight feet tall, right? That's just
something I made up. The hobbits were small. The hobbits were normal size. And he was the giant.
He was a normal sized human, I believe. Maybe it was Hat that made him look so big.
But anyways, there's nothing to do with anything that we're talking about. I imagine
cottages are just kind of one room. I've never been in a cottage. I've never been in a cottage.
I've been in a mansion once. I'm just okay, never mind. I'm not going to go on a segue of the different
domiciles I've been in. Yeah, you like that word? So anyways, this cottage apparently has a hallway.
They might all have hallways, but that's the most mad. You're like, Jason, get to the part with the
monster. You're stuck on the part of a hallway in a cottage. You do episodes about people who turn
into monsters all the time. Anyways, anyways, there's a hallway in this cottage. And this young
woman, she looks down the hallway and she sees something. She doesn't register at first. She does
a double leg. There appears to be, it's really hard for her to kind of make out what it is,
but there appears to be a man in a black robe at the end of the hallway. That's spooky.
Spooky for multiple reasons. And the reason why I like this story, we can really break into it.
But she looks down the hallway, man in a cloak, a hood on. She's like the Nazgul.
He's hanging out at the back end of Frodo's cottage. Then her mind clicks in and realizes,
whoa, that's not just a figment of my imagination. There is actually someone down there. And at that
point, the phantom, the figure raises its arms up. So it's almost like, you know, like,
you know what raising your arms up are, even if you don't have arms, you know what it is.
But it's like, it's like his arms are going up. So there, you know how you can do them in front
like a mummy? He's not doing that. He's doing side to side. I don't know how else to describe that.
I'm holding my arms up now as if you can see me. Side to side. Which again, how big is this
hallway? I don't want to get too much into the hallway. Now, not only do we have a long hallway,
it's apparently wide enough that I don't think I've ever been in a hallway that that's big.
You're like, Jason, you're not a giant. Jason, I know for a fact you've been in hallways
you can stretch out arm to arm. I don't think I have. I mean, it gets like hallways of like
office buildings and stuff, but I wouldn't really consider those hallways, right? I'm not just like
knocking over cubicles, but like a household way. I don't even, I don't think I've ever been in a
hallway that's big enough to fit two people going down the hallway at the same time. You're like,
Jason, that's 100% not true. I'm basically arguing with myself. Michael's just like taking off in the
carbonicopter. He's like, I'm out of here. This guy's nuts. You're like, wait for me, wait for me.
No, you get stuck here too. I don't think I've ever been in a hallway that wide before. But anyways,
I might have. I might have. The point is, is that there's a hallway in a cottage and it's big enough
that a man, a grown man can put his hands out like he's flying, which is interesting because that's
what he starts to do when his arms go up and they're horizontal side to side, you know, like one
know what it is. I assume you guys are smart enough. You have enough of a vision dictionary
in your head that you know what I'm doing. He's holding his arms out like a cross. Okay. He's
holding his arms out like a cross and then he hovers a bit off the ground and now she's terrified
from the beginning, but again, your brain's trying to make sense of this stuff. And then he
flies super fast like a jump scare. He's flying down the hallway at her and she runs and she
jumps in bed and she throws the blankets over her. And then she says she hears like wrestling,
wrestling noises. They're like, get him up, get him up. Cowls and not cattle wrestling,
not cattle wrestling. Like stuff. He has maracas. He comes down the hallway. He has one of those
Andy's rain instrument. That's what the rainstorm was. He was just practicing his instrument.
Anyways, this is a Friday episode if you can't tell. Point is she hears him wrestling above her
sheets. She's hiding underneath the blankets. It goes away. Goes away. So interesting story.
It's spooky, right? Like all of us have looked down a hallway, cottage or not. All of us have
looked down a hallway and they're spooky. Hallways in and of themselves are spooky, right?
And then I'm reading the story and I thought it's weird that she jumps under the covers. There's a
natural inclination to jump under the covers, right? I'm not that guy. I don't jump under the covers,
but I also, because I mean, if I see something late at night, I don't like run away from it.
I'm not super buff, tough dude, punching ghosts in the face, but I'm not. I can't actually know
what that's funny. I can't, all the experiences I've had where I've seen stuff or felt stuff before
I was going to bed or heard stuff before I was going to bed, I just kind of go about my normal
business. I think it's interesting that people have, we have a tendency to throw blankets overhead.
I've never done it, but I was starting to look into that. Why do people, when they're scared,
tend to cover themselves up with blankets? And there was the answer that that's what kids do,
because kids basically say, "If I can't see you, you can't see me." I think maybe a baby would do
that, but by the time, well, they don't have the muscle to like pull a blanket up there weak.
But like once you're like eight or nine or whatever, you know that's not true. Like every time you
blink, you don't think the universe disappears. Other people said, "I think this kind of works
well that being under a blanket," I don't know how true this is, but it just made more sense than the,
"I can't see you, you can't see me." Being under a blanket, you replicate the mom's womb,
which I mean, your mom was had a pretty wooly womb. Your mom's womb was made of microfiber,
but because you're like encapsulated and capsule, there you go, Misty, encapsulated
in something, you feel like you're in your mom's womb. And then I thought a tunnel is like the
vaginal canal. So maybe that's why it's holes are so spooky, because really, I guess that's what I'm,
that was a long way to get to this. Holes are spooky, right? I'm not saying vaginal canals
aren't necessarily spooky. I guess it depends on what injury you're in. If you're in them,
they suck because you're, this is your first time, right? Like I'm talking about being a baby. I'm not
talking about sex. I'm talking about like, if you're in the womb, right, you're just chilling for
nine months. That's all the reality you know. And you hear voices. You don't see nothing, right? You
hear voices off in the ether. Every so often, you get a tasty twinkie to eat on. And then that's a
reality to you. That's not, that's only thing you know. And the next thing you know, you're,
"Ugh!" You're getting like squeezed through something that you definitely can't stick your arms out
both sides and fly through. Like you're getting squirted out, like mustard coming out of a tube.
And then you land into really bright, loud, colorful reality. And it's like a shock. What? I
didn't know any of this stuff existed. I've always thought that's what death is like, that you have
no con, we don't really con. A baby's probably like, "Oh, I'm sure there's something out there. Like,
I hear something. Like, there's something out there. Like, I, but I don't know what it is. I'm
hearing these voices and stuff like this. I'm hearing, I don't, the baby doesn't speak any language.
The baby's not a dummy. We are chasing babies to the definition of a dummy. But baby's flowing
around. Oh, I can hear stuff and stuff like that. But then the second that they pop out, it's a,
it's a, they don't know what the color white is, or they don't know what's like really like,
what sound it, well, they know what sound is, but they don't know like the beep, beep, beep of like
the doctor machine or like hands. They've never like been held before. This stuff is new stuff.
I think that's what death is like. Like, this is the only reality we can even come close to
comprehending. Anyone who tells you otherwise, trying to sell you a book or get you to join their
cult. And then you pop out of this one, boop, and then you're in a, you're like, "Whoa, I didn't think
any of this stuff could have ever been possible. I had a little baby brain. Even though I was 90
years old and I experienced all this stuff, I had no idea. Just like a baby who's one month old
in the womb, little tiny peanut dude versus a baby that's going to come out in 30 seconds. They have,
still have no knowledge of what's on the other side at all. That's a long way of saying that maybe
being under your blankets is like being in a womb. Wholeways are spooky because it's, it reminds us
of popping in and out of the vaginal, well not in and out. You only come one way out of the vaginal
canal. I personally think the reason why we hide under blankets, it's a monkey behavior.
Yeah, it's animal behavior. You're hiding from a predator. So if it's not a blanket, we'd be like
scurrowing into a burrow or hiding under a bunch of leaves or something like that,
painting ourselves with bark, all sorts of stuff, right? So, so did this story happen
was she really pursued by a ghost down the hallway? Maybe, right? We've just covered
weirder stuff. I just think it's interesting that it had the motif of spooky hallways is something
we can all relate to. I think everyone who's ever spent any time, anywhere around a hallway,
especially when they were young, they find them creepy. And now at night, you're walking
through your house and it's dark and there's a hallway. It's creepier than just a dark living
room, I would say, right? Unless you have a giant hallway that you can put your arms out,
and then maybe there's enough space in case something was coming after you, you could get away.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story. We are going to go ahead that with that story.
I just told you was a literally one paragraph long. I don't know how it blew up to be whatever
20 minute long story it is. But let's go ahead and Michael fire up that car. Let's call Michael back
in. Hey, Mike, we're done. We're done. He's like, are you don't being crazy? Yeah, yeah, we're done.
Bring back down the carbonicopter. We are headed off for a little tour, actually. This story kind
of takes us a couple different places. And this was actually a suggestion from another Patreon
supporter, Lori. Lori Snyder, thank you so much for supporting the show. Thank you so much for
leading me on to the story. Now, this story actually cost me $4.95. I had to buy a copy
of Fate Magazine. So you guys better appreciate this story. Cost me more money than the past
20 episodes put together. I never spent any money on these shows. I had to pay $4.95 for this.
There's a section in Fate Magazine. Fate Magazine is pretty good. They've had eras where it's been
kind of tabloid-ish. I don't know where they're at right now. I've only read this first part of
this issue. Lori was like, oh, you got to do a story on this. They have a section called I Seen
It in the Papers. I don't know what that's a reference to. I don't know if it's all like little
news clippings. It's bizarre. We're going to talk about some of these stories that are just,
it's like little news nuggets from Fate Magazine. Fate Magazine is like a paranormal
magazine like 14 times. They've been around since like the 50s or the 60s, old school.
This is the newest issue though. There's a cult in Russia called the Ringing Cedars Anastasianism.
Anastasianism. So Michael, take us down to this cult compound. It basically looks like that movie
Midsummer that I didn't bother watching because I didn't like what was that other movie they did
about the person with the head chopped off hereditary. Whatever. A bunch of people dancing
around, maypole, wearing old-time dresses. This is a cult in Russia. It's gaining a lot of membership
because it's a return to a simple life. Everyone needs to have a house. Well, everyone needs to
be in a family. It's very family. It's kind of nationalistic, but it's also a return to nature.
They said every man should have a house on about a hecca acre, hecca acre of land.
And that's your love place. And I did like this. That's stupid. That's dumb. But I did like this.
The idea that what you put in the universe gives back to you. I believe that. And they have this
thing that you put love in the universe. It creates a loving universe. If you put hate in the
universe, it creates hate. That's, I think that's fairly standard. And you might, I don't necessarily
know if you can affect global change, but you can definitely see changes in your own life. People
are very bitter and angry. Tend to have very bitter and angry lives. You very rarely see a bitter and
angry person and everything go right for them. You will see optimists, and I know them. You'll see
optimists that have a lot of unluck, like that's not a word, that have a lot of bad luck. You'll
see that, but they just keep on going. But a bitter man will have good luck and can never see the
bright side of it. And so at the end, the bitter person has, I think, a more miserable existence.
They may seem more comfortable with what they're surrounded with. Their job, their family, but
their family ends up hating their guts. Anyway, you know what I mean? Like, you have to put positivity
to at least get it back in your universe. So I agree with that. The rest of this stuff is dumb.
They believe that you create like you. It's very, I'm a fan of the family unit as well. It doesn't,
not everyone has that opportunity, but I'm a fan of it if it can work for you. But
they're vegans, so I'm done with that one. And not only vegans, they're the raw vegans. So they
only eat like corn husk and grass whispers. Like they don't eat nothing. And all their clothes are
made of natural materials, because yes, mine are made of quantum molecules from the fourth dimension.
Everything's a natural material. I mean, unless you're wearing, unless you're a sheep and you're
wearing your own wool, whatever. That's not, whatever. The point is, is that this is the reason
why Lori sent me this. She's like, Jason, I want to hear your views. I want to hear your, right after
you said you have to be positive. I want to hear your very critical reviews of a religion you found
on Wikipedia. Love Lori. That's not what she sent the story for. You're allowed to be negative
every once in a while. Just don't let it override you. Or when you're doing it, it should be for
entertainment purposes only. Well, Lori sent me this. She goes, so there is a belief there's a
conspiracy theory. It's hard to really decide how you'd want to call it. A cuckoo theory would be a
good way. That you can create superfoods by sucking on seeds. This corn kernel. Don't eat it, Billy.
You're supposed to plant it. Oh yeah. Is that how you plant corn? Do you take like a corn, a
cobb of corn, right? Are all the kernels the seeds? Like could, what's weird about that is basically
shouldn't the whole world be corn at this point? Because if a corn cob is nothing but seeds and
each basically like, let's say I had a baby. I have me and a woman. We have a baby, right?
That's how that works. That's what I've heard. I don't know. I don't have one. Maybe I've been
lied to by the mainstream media. A corn, corn grows, right? And then it has a ton of seeds.
And then birds come and eat the seeds and some of them just kind of fall out on the ground.
And then the birds poop out the corn everywhere. So shouldn't there be corn? Like if there weren't
humans, would there be a plant out of the corn? Would there be a statue of liberty? But instead
of holding a torch, it's a corn cob. And instead of just a statue, it's just a giant corn cob.
Like why don't we have plants that override, why isn't the world nothing but sunflowers and corn?
Because like a zucchini, actually that's interesting because like stuff that grows in the
ground, what happens then? Do like gophers eat it and poop out the seeds? I know that citrus,
I've talked about this a long time ago, citrus trees wouldn't exist if humans disappeared,
they'd be gone in like 20 years. Because we created lemons and limes. Birds are like,
"Blech, that's gross. We're not pooping out those seeds." Bugs don't like them. The blood orange,
like there's an old orange that's actually a real citrus thing. But like lemons and limes we created.
The mongols created, it's all genetic engineering. But anyways, yeah if corn is nothing but like an
apple has what like six seeds? Well I guess the apple tree has like 20 apples, but still like so
that's still only 120 seeds, right? But corn is nothing but seeds. What else is nothing but seeds?
Watermelons too? But again, so I'd have to be a bear and I eat a watermelon then I poop out.
What's really Jason? Why is it always about it? That's how it's transferred, right? It's poop.
Birds? Because it's a little bit of fertilizer. So a bird eats the sunflower seed and then flies
and then poops it out and then it's all like a little fertilized and then it just grows, right?
That's how that works. Anyways, what am I talking about? Oh yeah, sucking on seeds. So anyways,
you suck on the seed. Let's get back to the story that I actually planned for. It's Friday episode.
Lori sends me this story. So I go and I buy "Fate" magazine, issue 735, 495 by the way.
This episode costs me money, so if you enjoy it, it has that story in there. In that section I've
seen it in the papers. You suck and this is the logic, there's no logic behind it. This is one of
the dumbest things I've covered in a while. So you know how a banana shares 50% of DNA with a human?
It doesn't by the way. That's 100% not true. That's the same way thing when they say you only use 10%
of your brain. It's not true. It's an old saying. It's people say it over and over again. It doesn't
make it any more true. Banana does not share 50% of its DNA with the human. It shares like 1% or 2%.
We all evolved on the same planet, but that means like we have the same amino acids and stuff like
that. It's not actual, it's not half human. It's not half human. If you rearranged it, you wouldn't
be like, "Hey, Mon, I'm banana Mon." Hang on, I don't know why I made him Jamaican, but anyways,
the point is that it's not true, but because people are stupid, they believe that. Now there's this old
idea that humans have deficiencies, which is true. Humans have vitamin deficiencies, and depending
on which geographical region you're in, if you're in a place with tons of vitamin C,
oranges everywhere, then you're not going to have a vitamin C deficiency, right? But if
everything's super like spooky and dark, you might have a vitamin D deficiency. So anyways,
with the idea is this. You take a seed because it's half human and you go, "Mmm,
I mean, you don't have to make love to it. Maybe you just lick on it." Actually, there's two
different ways to do it. In Europe, you stick it under your tongue. This is how dumb this is,
by the way. There's no science to it. And even like a shaman or a witch would be like, "That's
pretty stupid, even for our standards." You take a seed, you stick it under our tongue,
not our tongue, we don't share one. You take a seed, you stick it under your tongue,
then you look up at the sun and the sunbeams imprint your DNA on it. That's dumb. They imprint
your DNA on it, and then you spit it out and you bury it. And what you've told the seed is,
"I'm missing vitamin K and I could use a little more sodium in my diet. I don't have enough."
So when the tomato grows, it basically will grow with extra vitamin K and a little more sodium.
It'll be like, "This is nice and salty tomato right out of the ground. Gross. I'm allergic to
tomatoes." The end. That's the idea behind this, and that's what ringing seeders do. A couple other
groups do it. And the East, apparently, Eastern cultures, this is a thing too. People have been
doing stupid stuff for thousands of years. You take, a little kid takes a seed, because the kid's
the one who actually is going to be more vitamin deficient, they got to grow big and strong.
They suck on the seed, imprinted with their DNA, and then it grows and they're like,
"Oh, just what I need. I needed this specific potato to be able to." Which was dumb, because one,
how many seeds are you sucking on, bro? I think this was probably some dude made this up because
you had a seed suck on fetish. Because what happens, man? You don't grow just one potato.
Isn't a potato itself a seed? You're trying to fit it in your mouth. The idea is this.
I guess if you had just one farm for you and your family, it might work. But what if you have more
vitamin deficiencies than your kids do, and they're eating the seeds you were sucking on,
and they're like a super hyper and stuff like that, because all of a sudden they have all these
extra vitamins. You're like, "Jason, that's not how vitamins work." It's a Friday episode.
The point is, is that it wouldn't work on any sort of scale whatsoever.
Especially like, again, you don't just go, "Oh, the harvest is in. We got one corn,
one cobbocorn, one tomato." You have farms. So how long are they sucking on these seeds for?
Your neck would get tired just looking up at the sun all the time. So we're going to stamp this
false, busted, dead rabbit radio. Bust this myth. That's a new thing I'm doing. I'll probably never
do it again. But, Lori, thank you for the suggestion. The reason why I wanted to talk about this one,
that was interesting because it's just kind of a stupid practice. This section of
"Fate Magazine," which I love about "Fate Magazine," they have usually like a ton of stories in each
little book. They have two other stories. This is weird. One is like a paragraph long.
"Extraterrestrial." We all have heard that word before, right? You're like, "No, I haven't. Explain
it to me." Well, extraterrestrial is the idea of spacey. Why am I even... I don't need to explain
it to you. The point is, is that you know what an extra... I've completely lost my mind. You know
what an extraterrestrial is. This little blurb in this magazine said, "Some people," which basically
just means "me," the person writing it, "some people say that extraterrestrial actually means
more land." Because "extra" means more and "terrestrial" means land. You're like, "Okay, that's... I guess
that's a fun word game, right?" Like, sure. But when you say "extrajudicial," you don't mean, "Oh,
there's just going to be extra courts involved." No, it means that you're doing something outside of
the court system. Like, "extra" doesn't simply mean more. "Extra gum" doesn't mean you have extra gum.
It just means that's a brand of the gum. This episode's sponsored by extra gum. The idea of
whatever, so that's just weird. But then underneath... So it's a paragraph long. That's the first
sentence. "Extra-terrestrial" actually means more land. And it doesn't. It doesn't at all.
Then it says... This is actual quote from this article. "Many..." There's not many people who
do this, right? But whatever. "Many theorize that this is a subliminal message that there is more
land out there that we are unaware of." Yes. So all of this time, whenever you hear people talk
about extraterrestrials, they're actually... It's subliminal. We know that... What is... What does
that even... More land where? Who's the... Who... Who are these many people who whenever they're like,
they walk by an ET poster, they're like, "Yeah, I want to go there someday, too." People are like,
"What is... You know..." Pointing at the... You want to go to the movie theater? This movie hasn't been
in the theater since 1983. No! Pointing very slowly at the word "extra-terrestrial." I want to go there.
Do you know how to get there? What? Is this like a phone home joke? No! That goes on for like 30 minutes.
What is that even... Many theorize that this is a subliminal message, that there is more land out
there that we are unaware of. What? On Earth? I don't understand this! Absolutely hilarious. This...
This... That was worth $4.95. I really love the seat-sucking story. That was definitely good, too,
but that statement alone was 100% worth $4.95. That many people believe that the word "extra-terrestrial"
is a secret hint to us that somewhere out there, it could be outside your door, it could be
billion light years away. There's extra land we don't know. Okay, sure, probably, but again,
"extra-terrestrial" does not mean more land. It never has. It never has, but that's not even the
best part. Lori really hit the trifecta on this one, and this was all from two pages of this
magazine, okay? Two pages of this magazine. Lori straight up pulled a hat-trick on this one,
so you got three crazy stories. Fire up that Carbentercopter one last time this episode, Michael.
We're headed out to... Back to Britain, actually. We're going to Leeds. Little town, Leeds. It has
a museum in it. I know that much. It's... The whole town is just one giant museum. All the people just
stand there. Everyone's behind glass. The very safety are in this quarantine. We land, and there
we meet a bunch of scientists, a bunch of nerds sitting around, and they have in front of them
the mummified remains of priest Nessiamen. Nessiamen. Nessiamen was a Egyptian priest. He was a scribe,
and he wrote like on his thing... Well, he didn't write it. He was dead. He was being mummified,
but people carved on his esophagus that his life wish was to speak after he died,
because to him speaking, especially speaking your name, was the ultimate
oneness with God, that people were still talking about you after you died. So basically, Marilyn
Monroe is the equivalent of Hercules at this point. That was his goal. So these nerds are
sitting there on their computers, and there's this mummy just chilling out in their lab,
and they're like, "Are you ready to run the diagnostics, Timothy?" And Timothy's like, "Yes,
I am. I forgot your name, Mark. Yeah, I forgot." And so they take this mummy, and these nerds are
all running these tests. Now, elsewhere, this dude is like pitching this business thing, right?
He's like, "There's this huge narrative now. There's this guy. His name is Tony,
and he's like... None of these names are real. By the way, as far as I know, Tony goes,
"Listen, we are on the cusp of one of the biggest breakthroughs that mummy technology has ever known.
We are going to change the world of the bandaged and decayed." There's a fat cat corporate weasel
sitting with this cigar. My grandfather didn't get into this business to spend a bunch of money
doing mummy stuff. So get to it. And the guy's like, "Okay, we want to see that mummy right there.
We want to take that mummy. We want to give him the ability to speak." And the fat cat investor,
smoking his cigar, he's eating an apple, spitting out seeds, creating new apple trees in his office.
He's pooping them out. I don't know where that even came from. I gotta end this episode.
Okay, the fat cat goes, "Fine. I'll give you all sorts of money and all sorts of time.
I want to see what you can do." Then none of that happened, okay? None of that happened. I just think
it's funny that somebody wasted a ton of time and money and effort to do what I'm about to tell you.
Okay? All of that was my bizarre way of letting you know. Somebody thought this was a worthwhile
endeavor. They spent grants and college funds and all sorts of stuff. Money from colleges,
I mean, not their scholarships. A bunch of money went into this. This is the end. This is the
actual story, okay? Forget Tom and Timothy and Mark and the stereotypical corporate guy whose dad
invested in mummies or whatever nonsense they came up with. These guys took this mummy. This part's
real. This part's real. This mummy named Nessie Oman. That's true. He wanted to speak after death
and all that stuff. So they go, "He's a perfect candidate for this technology." They put him in
a CT machine. They take a scan of his vocal cords, his throat, his mouth, all that stuff.
It was all grody, obviously. He'd been dead for 3,000 years. But they were able to take all this
information and then they put it through a 3D scanner. They go home for the weekend. It takes
a while. They come back. It's ready. Now they have a 3D replica of this dude's vocal cords,
right? Which, come on, they're decayed, but whatever. They're somehow, maybe it's just
the way his bones were or something like that. They took that. Then they reconstructed his tongue
because parts of it were missing and everything like that. So eventually, long story short,
they replicate his voice box. You're like, "Jason, it's called a throat and a mouth."
They replicate that and they go, "Well, we've spent a ton of money and a ton of time and all this
stuff, but we have finally done it. We have finally created the ability to hear what this guy sounded
like." Which in and of itself is pretty awesome. You're like, "Jason, that's pretty dope actually
that you can do that and we can find out what people have to say in the old times." And while
they're doing this actually, someone came forward and complained about it. Here is a quote. This is
just adding to the ridiculous. Here's a quote. "Kara Kuni. She's an Egyptologist at the University
of California Los Angeles. She says, "When you're taking a human being and using so much inference,"
is that a word? "Inference?" Inference? Inference? It doesn't matter. "When you're
guessing what, when you're putting stuff in that you don't know." Like how to pronounce a word.
"When you're taking a human being and using so much inference about what they looked or sounded like,
it can be done with an agenda that you might not even be aware of." She's for mummy rights.
She doesn't think that she thinks, I don't know, is it deceased to imitate a dead person?
I don't really. So basically she's going, "Well, what's your agenda? Do you have a hidden agenda when
you're trying to give this mummy a voice?" And the scientists are like, "Yeah, we want to hear what a
mummy sounded like. We want to hear what this guy sounded like 3,000 years ago. What would be your
agenda?" That quote is the equivalent of many people believe. There is a journalist writing an
article and they're like, "Well, I do need a counteractual point." So they probably caught,
allegedly, allegedly, don't sue me anybody. I must, allegedly, the journalist calls up a friend,
a close friend, and go, "Hey, you want to be in an article?" Yeah, sure. I need a negative quote.
Oh yeah, yeah, I can do that. Allegedly, that's what happened. It's possible that she actually
does care very deeply about the rights of 3,000-year-old mummies being given a voice,
even though that was their last wish. She may actually have problems with that. She may have
like power to the power posters and it's just like a picture of ash she's fighting for the people
who have rotted away. Anyways, now you have controversy. Many people are up in arms about
this. You have controversy. You have money. You have time spent. You have technical brain power.
You have a CTE machine that was used. There was some guy who really needed it. He's like, "No,
I'm dying now." And they're like, "No, we're too busy scanning this mummy. Go home." He's like,
"No, kick him down the stairs." The point is, is that you have all this time, money, effort,
everything for this. That is, that was the, that is the result. So yes, let's hear it again.
That's it. That's not a Minecraft villager. That's not any other number of cultural references or
jokes I could make. That's the sound of a 3000. That's all they got. So they hooked, they built
this huge thing and then they just like had a way to like make it make a vowel sound. That's,
if you're gonna, I was, it's so funny because I'm reading the article. I read multiple articles on
this and then I had to find the sound clip. You imagine, I don't, okay, here's the thing. Maybe
it was my expectations, but I was expecting Hall of Presidents from Disneyland, right? Where it'd
be like, "Oh no, Moses, not more frogs!" Like they actually would make it say something, right?
No, I can, I, I, here's the thing, dude. I, allegedly, allegedly, I could get a ton of grant
money, take a scan and then just go into a microphone where I can imitate, uh, there,
I imitated that. Uh, maybe that's a little like it because I'm not hearing it right now. Uh,
how much time and money went into that? And again, I, I could just make, you're like, Jason,
science, science isn't about whether or not you can make it, you buy your, like that's not,
sign, you're like, Jason, you can, you can create a whirlpool, you can create like a little whirlpool
in your bathtub by pulling the drain. We still need people to steady whirlpools in real life.
We still need people to steady momentum, things like that. Yeah, yeah, I guess, but still, that was
disappointing. And I think it was equally disappointing for you considering the amount of buildup that I
gave it. Now that story makes sense. I wanted you guys to feel like I felt when I was reading all
those articles. I'm like, "Oh dude, is he gonna be like, "I've risen from the grave!" Like they could
have made him say so many mummy-like things, not, "Come on, that's ridiculous!" Come on, science.
You let me down. You let me down once again. But guys, have a great weekend. I hope you enjoyed
this Friday episode. I promise there was no Benadryl or Nyquil involved in the making of this
episode. I think it's just been a long week. Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be
your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadratvoradio. Twitter is @deadratvoradio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Be safe, be kind. I love
you guys, and I'll see you on Monday. I'll see you on Monday.
Bye.
[MUSIC]