A ninja, a ninja attacks a US base on US soil and nobody seems to care.
Such a bizarre story.
So insane.
Then I'm outraged, I'm outraged people aren't talking about that story.
And then we travel to Oregon to have a good night out drinking at a local bar.
Everything is going according to plan until it's time to go to sleep.
And then we take a look at a brand new conspiracy theory from the twisted mind of your favorite
podcast host Jason Carpenter.
A lot of times we've talked about people like Hans Wormhat and other conspiracy theorists
who believe that NASA is trying to hide proof of God from us.
We always laugh at these conspiracy theories, but the other day I looked up at the night
sky and had an epiphany.
What if Hans is right?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are having lots of fun.
Hope you guys have some cool plans for the weekend.
I bought a heater that oscillates.
That's how exciting my life is right now.
You know what?
I love it.
I've always seen myself moving up here from California when I moved up to Hood River.
I always saw this as this was Sam going back to the Shire.
I'm retired baby.
I'm done with all of the crazy adventures.
I'm done.
I buy an oscillating fan on Amazon and it gets sent to me and I'm like, "Whoa, this
is a heater with remote control and it oscillates?"
That's the most exciting thing and I love it.
I don't need car crashes.
People coming after me.
I just need an oscillating heater.
You get to that point in life and it is a good point in life.
And another good thing in life is our Patreon supporters.
Coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now, a long time Patreon supporter.
Give it up for George Clooney.
The George Clooney.
You didn't know he's the word of the show?
Come on in George.
I call him Georgey for short.
George, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
I could buy a lot more heaters but I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show really, really helps out a lot.
George, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Grab onto George's hips.
Oh wait, actually before we do that, we got some Fan Art Friday.
We're just going to hold on to his hips for the rest of this segment.
Fan Art Friday.
Look at this awesome art I got from Madison Merritt.
It's the classic Dead Rabbit Radio logo but Madison's own take on it.
Really, really love this stuff you guys are doing.
That's so awesome.
Really, really love it.
Thank you so much Madison.
So George, we're going to go ahead and keep holding onto your hips.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed all the way out to the Mojave Desert in California.
[breathing]
The reason why we're going out to the Mojave Desert, this story absolutely boggles my mind.
So let me start by giving credit.
Mason on the Patreon Discord sent this over to me so thank you so much for that.
I got all of my information because it's really only coming out of one source right now.
It's Stars and Stripes which is the official newsletter for the Milit Armed Forces.
These articles have been written by Chad Garland.
September 18th, 2021 we're in the Mojave Desert.
We're specifically at the In-Yokern Airport.
What's going on?
It's 1 a.m. and currently this airport is being used for training exercises by the 160th
Special Operations Aviation Regiment aka the Nightstalkers.
It's an elite helicopter unit.
They're training here.
At 1 a.m. the Staff Sergeant leaves the Admin Building.
Smoke a cigarette.
Get a little relaxation from all those other knuckleheads in that building.
There's 26 guys in total here.
While he's outdoors he's smoking a cigarette.
His name is not released for security reasons and I will also assume embarrassment reasons.
As he's outside smoking a cigarette he turns around and there's a ninja standing next to
him.
Full on Ninja Garb carrying a katana and he asks the Staff Sergeant "Do you know who
I am?"
I don't know.
I don't know if he had a voice changer but we will pretend that he did.
Do you know who I am?
Staff Sergeant's looking over at him and he's probably thinking "Ninja?
But I mean specifically I don't know."
So he answers "No."
And then the guy goes "Do you know where my family is?"
Staff Sergeant's like "Are there baby ninjas around?"
That would be really cool if they were hiding in the bushes and underneath street lamps.
But he says "No."
He doesn't goad on the armed ninja.
He goes "I know, I don't know where your family is."
The ninja then begins to slash at the Staff Sergeant.
Cutting his knee and his leg.
Staff Sergeant starts running away.
Gets to a fence.
He's over it.
The ninja is in quick pursuit.
See he doesn't even make sound.
I didn't have to do sound effects.
He doesn't make sound when he's running.
The Staff Sergeant breathes heavily.
The ninja does that non-noise.
Staff Sergeant gets into the admin building.
He goes "Guys, you will not believe what's out here right now.
A ninja."
He didn't let him guess because he knew they would never guess.
They're like an elephant.
He's like "No, a ninja."
He locks all the doors.
He's calling 911.
There's 26 Special Operations Soldiers in the hangar.
Verse 1 Ninja.
We've been lied to, ladies and gentlemen.
I've seen many an episode of G.I. Joe which let me know that if you took 26 Joes and put
them up against Storm Shadow, to be fair this is a cartoon, but the Joes would win.
Maybe Storm Shadow is going to take a couple of them out.
You don't want to be that guy, but it's a cartoon.
They're not really dead.
Shipwreck just gets his shirt kind of torn.
Now I guess we've also been watching movies where one guy with ninja skills comes in and
kills a bunch of faceless goons, but these are U.S. Soldiers.
They're not faceless goons.
We're not the faceless goons.
The other guys are the faceless goons.
Troops from Belarus trying to take down Owen Wilson.
Those are the faceless goons unless you're listening to this podcast in Belarus and you're
my favorite listeners.
This one ninja keeps 26 Special Forces Operators at bay.
Now to be fair they're Special Forces and helicopters, but still they should know how
to fight like hand to hand or chair to sword.
They are in this building hiding from a ninja with a sword and he begins throwing, first
off he begins punching the door, which their hearts must have just stopped at that point
because after the first fist punch hits the door you have to think, does he know a ninja
way?
Does he know a ninja way of punching a door off of the hinges?
But he punches the door a couple of times.
That doesn't work.
He's punching windows, which works and then he picks up a big piece of asphalt and throws
it through the window and again people think this wasn't a real ninja.
We'll get to the ending of this story.
That's how stories normally conclude, but people think he's not a real ninja.
He is able to take a large piece of asphalt, throw it through a window and hit a man.
In the building.
That skill.
That skill because when you think about it when you're trying to shoot a hoop, shoot
basketball that's already a little difficult, but he's shooting basketball with not a basketball
with a giant piece of asphalt.
It's going through a window and he's still able to throw it accurately enough that it
hits a captain.
Now the soldiers, even though they're soldiers, you're like Jason you're going really hard
on these guys.
This ninja did have a sword and I get it.
I've had knives pulled on me.
It's not a fun experience.
But what do these guys do in the battlefield?
Again, they are helicopter operators so maybe they don't know how to fight hand to hand,
but I thought that was kind of required.
I thought like if you joined the military you had to know how to swim and shoot a gun
and like roll around on the ground and go no and screaming the air and stuff like that.
But apparently those rules don't apply to the 160th.
They are just hanging out.
They don't have any guns in there.
They're on training.
They don't even have like an experimental helicopter.
You don't have nothing.
What were they training with?
The police show up and they shoot him with some non-lethal rounds and I really hope that
he tried blocking them with his sword.
I don't know.
It doesn't say for sure but the rounds were useless.
The non-lethal rounds did nothing to this guy so I'm sure the police officers left it
out of the report that it was so weird.
We pulled our guns and then all of a sudden reality became split screen and it was a close
up of my eyes and a close up of his eyes and then I shot three times and he just moved
his sword around noiselessly.
Is that a word?
Quietly.
He moved his sword around quietly.
It moved like a whisper through the night sky.
It moved like a whisper through the morning air and then the non-lethal rounds just seemed
to be chopped in half.
They don't say that.
They did pull out a taser and they finally subdued him with a taser.
That story I'd seen when I was on my vacation and I was like, "What?
This is insane."
But I wanted to wait because I wanted a key piece of information.
When the story was first released they said, "Authorties are not saying who this guy is."
I thought, "That's really the crux to the issue, right?
If this guy is a ninja and he's actually from like a ninja clan, this is huge.
This is huge.
Geopolitical ramifications."
And then there was a follow-up article to this whole thing.
They did announce who this guy was.
Gino Rivera, 35-year-old man.
And I'm like, "Now I just have even more questions, right?"
I was thinking maybe it was an actual ninja in the military.
Can't up this guy's family or something like that?
He was on some sort of collateral Arnold Schwarzenegger-esque revenge mission.
No.
There's some guy named Gino Rivera, not a ninja.
Just some dude who's now in jail for attempted homicide, brandishing a weapon.
He's got a whole slew of charges, right?
Embarrassing the US military.
You go, Jason, I think you're going a little hard on the fact that a dude shows up.
How would you like it if a dude showed up at his sword at your workplace, right?
And I wouldn't, right?
It'd be pretty rude.
But I'm not a trained soldier.
I'm not a trained soldier, but if I was a trained soldier and some guy comes to me
with a sword and he's like dressed as a ninja and he goes, "You know where my family is?"
I'll say, "Probably burning in hell.
Why don't you respect my back?"
And I just turn around, right?
I'm just going to throw him off of his game and I'm going to hear that sword whistle
through the wind.
And I'm going to put my hands up.
I'm blocking.
I'm going to catch you with my hands right before it hits my skull.
I could have done it earlier, but I wanted it to be super dramatic.
And then I turn around somehow.
I don't know.
I haven't worked at all physics, but I turn around.
My head spins around like the extra system.
I'm staring at him and I look at him and I go, "My turn."
And then I flip the sword up and I catch it.
And then I keep it because it's a cool sword and I want a sword.
I take it to my car and I put it in the trunk and then I come back and I walk back to him.
And I go, "My turn still."
Because he's not doing anything.
And then I kick him in the shins a couple of times.
And if it's that easy, if I could do it, well, actually, to be fair, I don't even need to
get made a thing.
The police did it.
The police showed up, shot a couple of non-lethal rounds at him, tased them and it was over.
So I don't know.
I don't know.
I think I just think military are trained to fight and this guy came to fight and they
ran away and they hid.
So that's a little just embarrassing.
And more to the point, what in the world was this guy's motivation?
Where is his family?
Were they really missing?
Was this guy actually on this revenge quest?
Was he like a self-trained ninja or an American ninja?
Maybe?
Who knows?
They're not telling us anything and they weren't telling us this story at all until it leaked
onto Facebook from people who knew about it and then Stars and Stripes covered it.
And then it was in the mainstream news very, very briefly.
US base infiltrated by a ninja who attacked servicemen and then they ran and hid and he
continued to attack him until he got tased.
That's a story.
That's a national news story.
What in the world is going on?
George Clooney?
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're leaving behind in Yoki Airport or whatever the pronunciation was.
I moved past that page.
We're leaving behind that.
The troops are like, "Thanks for the tips on self-defense."
I'm like, "You got it, guys."
I'm wild.
I hope you never try that.
You can't get your sword before it hits your skull.
We're giving you the keys to Jason's Lappy.
We're headed all the way out to Oregon.
George Clooney is driving us all the way up there.
We're watching Batman and Robin for the 15th time.
And finally, we get to a little pub in Oregon.
Now, I got this story from a friend of mine.
It actually happened to her not too long ago.
It's a very, very interesting story.
But for the sake of privacy, I'm going to be changing some of the names and things like
that.
Because it's a weird one.
It's a weird one.
Talking to my friend Molly, she listens to the show.
She shared this story with me.
Her son works at a bar, not in town.
He works at a bar in another town.
And he thought it was weird when he went to get the job.
The interviewer, the boss, asked him, "Do you believe in ghosts?"
Because this bar the business owner explained is haunted.
It's a haunted bar.
There's three ghosts who regularly hang out here.
Now, even people who believe in ghosts, I believe in ghosts.
But if somebody told me this is a haunted bar, I would be like, "Oh, that's really cool.
I no longer want a job here.
Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
That's super spooky.
I'm a little stressed to work in a haunted place, but you would think, oh, you know,
is it like, and then at midnight, sometimes you hear a clock chime 12 times.
Like, there's different levels of ghostly activity.
Sometimes when a train goes by, a glass mysteriously falls off the bar.
We don't know what causes it.
Molly's son is working the bar one night and he sees a full body apparition of a ghost
walk by, which despite what the movies would have you believe is the rarest type of ghost
encounter.
Most paranormal encounters, ghost encounters are fragrances, really in this order, fragrances,
noise, hearing something that you shouldn't hear creaks.
That actually in yesterday's episode, I'll put that in here.
Yesterday's episode when I was talking about Baby X, or that was Wednesday's episode, I
was talking about Baby X.
I'm going to play this clip for you here in this haunted closet.
It sounds like a footstep every time I mention the age of the victim.
It was a three week old infant.
It was the body of a three week old infant.
That's not me.
I was making sure I was perfectly...
When the first time I heard it, I go, "Is that me?"
And the second time, I did it again.
So just weird.
Again, I have ghosts at home.
I don't need ghosts at work, but most ghost encounters go like this.
Fragrances, smells, perfumes, cigar smells, noises, voices, and then seeing something.
And even then there's that degree of seeing the mist fly by versus seeing a discernible
figure.
And that's the most common in movies because it's very visual.
That's the least common you'll see in real life.
So her son sees a full body apparition.
The family goes out to visit their son who's away.
He's working at this bar.
And they go to the bar.
They're visiting him right now.
They're not like, "Hey son, we're in town, but we're going to Applebee's."
They go to the bar.
They're hanging out.
They see him.
And they have a good time.
Molly has a good time.
They tip their son very poorly.
They're like, "Oh, it's a horrible service son."
That night, Molly has a dream.
Molly is in a house and she's taking care of a little girl.
Little girl in a white dress.
She doesn't recognize her.
Cute little girl.
She's just there to take care of her.
And she gets the girl settled in this room.
And there's a baby monitor in the room so she knows that she can move about the house
and do other things while this girl is safe.
And she goes upstairs and she hears on the baby monitor what could only be described
as demonic voices.
So Molly runs back downstairs to check on this little girl.
And when she goes to open the door, it's locked.
She fights with the knob.
She's trying to get this door open.
She's banging on it.
She's screaming.
She's panicked.
She knows something evil is on the other side of this door with this girl who she's supposed
to protect.
And when she finally gets the door open, the little girl was no longer in the room.
Instead the room was full of dogs.
She doesn't say how many of them.
I don't think it looked like Oliver and Company.
I just imagine three really vicious type pit bulls whatever.
They're barking at her.
She goes right when she opens the door and she sees these three dogs or however many dogs
barking at her.
Get ready for their big musical number.
She sees another door in the hallway open up out of the corner of her eye and she turns
and she looks and she sees the little girl run out of that door and run down into the
basement of the house.
Now she immediately thinks this little girl's panicked.
She's freaking out because of the demon voice because of the dog and she somehow got away.
This little girl is now running down to the basement.
I have to go get the little girl.
We got to get out of this house.
I have to save the little girl.
And as Molly begins to run down the basement herself, she notices something.
The little girl is running too fast.
She's moving way quicker than any human should.
Molly is now halfway down the stairs and she stops.
She's looking into the blackness of the basement.
The darkness has swallowed the little girl in the white dress up completely.
Molly is standing on those stairs and she comes to a very, very powerful conclusion.
I cannot go down these stairs anymore.
I cannot enter the darkness of the basement.
And then she woke up terrified, terrified of that dream.
Later on, Molly told her son about the dream.
I had this dream when there was this little girl and then as she's talking about her dream,
her son stops her and goes, "Was the little girl wearing a white dress?"
She goes, "Yeah."
Her son goes, "That's one of the three ghosts that are trapped in this bar."
The night she went to the bar is the night she had that nightmare with the little girl
leading her through the house, trying to get her to go into the darkness.
And Molly's a legit person.
She's not someone who would try to pull a prank.
She's a fan of the show.
She listens to the show.
She's a friend of mine.
She wouldn't be telling me a tall tale.
Could have just been a dream, right?
Could have just been a dream.
Could have just been a coincidence as girls in creepy white dresses, this kind of thing.
Could just be the dream.
Imagine if you visit this place and the ghost girl attaches itself to you.
Could it attach itself to Molly?
Because she's a mother.
And attached itself to Molly because she's a mother and sensed the mother's love and
knew that it would be a weakness.
I wouldn't follow no one down to the basement.
Are you kidding me?
But Molly did.
And at the very last moment she caught herself from going down into the darkness.
What was waiting in that darkness?
What was that little girl's plan?
And you see Molly was able to tell this story to her son who works there and he goes, "Oh,
you know, that's one of the ghosts that's at this place."
And it leaves Molly with this kind of idea that was, is, how would this be classified?
Did this ghost follow me home?
Was it somehow able to attach itself to me?
Was it just, I was in a spooky place and something, I just had a weird nightmare.
It's just not even connected.
But think about all the people who go to that bar who don't have a son working there.
Who go home and have a weird nightmare and would never ever put two and two together.
They don't know that the bar's haunted.
They go there for some fish and chips.
Later that night, woman's laying in bed.
She has a nightmare.
But a young girl she can't rescue from demonic forces.
Only to find out that the young girl herself may be a demonic force.
But then think about the people who do continue into the basement.
The dreamers who don't have that logic kick in at the last moment.
Who aren't quick enough to realize, wait, no human can move that fast.
If Molly had not realized that detail, she would have continued down into the basement.
Are there people out there who have visited this bar?
How did that dream and walked into the basement?
And when they woke up, who were they?
Were they the same person who wakes them and goes, well that was a weird dream.
Or is this bar and this little girl a demonic infestation?
Ghosts tend to stay in a very localized environment.
The place that they died, the place that they loved the most, the place where they have unfinished
business, demons roam.
Demons leave.
They have a base of operations, but have soul will travel type of thing.
What is the little girl at this bar in Oregon?
Or was it all just a dream?
We will see.
That'd be cool to do an investigation there.
Now you guys see why I left the business name out and they don't want to give this
city because they basically blasted that business.
I'm sure they serve lovely food.
I'm sure the staff is great.
But if you go there, you may be possessed by the demon of a little girl.
You may have a dream and you may wake up and your soul is gone and a little girl is piloting
your body.
And nobody wants that except for the demons who work at this bar.
George Clooney, I'm going to go and attach the keys to the carboner copter.
We got enough time because this last story is pretty short, but it's pretty brilliant
in the literal term.
I'm going to attach the keys to the carboner copter.
We are headed all the way out to the middle of nowhere.
And when I say the middle of nowhere, I'm talking like we're on a mountain top.
There's not a city or a town or anything to be seen for miles and miles and miles and
miles.
We're just enjoying each other's company.
Molly's taking a nap.
She's like, "Don't let her get possessed.
Don't let her get possessed."
We're hanging out there.
We look up at the night sky.
The other day I was walking through town here, I was hanging out with my friends Sabine.
And I said, "When's the last time you've seen the galaxy?"
Now she's a real rural girl.
And rural, I can't really say that word, but you know, country girl.
She grew up more country than I did.
She's gone camping and stuff like that, stuff that I just don't like to do.
She doesn't have stuff.
So I expected it to be a fairly high number.
She said five or six.
And I was kind of shocked.
Like five or six, really.
She's like, "Yeah.
I've seen the galaxy one time.
45 years old, I've seen the galaxy one time."
I didn't even, I mean, I guess I'd seen pictures of it.
I'd seen it in movies.
I'm not talking about, I'm not talking about like the galaglactic map of Star Trek or something
like that.
But when you're in a place with zero light pollution, you look up and you see the galaxy.
It was truly awe-inspiring.
I remember we were on the way back.
We had just seen the Sacramento Kings play against the Phoenix Suns in the playoffs.
We were driving back and we had to pull over to go pee.
It was me, Justin, and Hal.
We got out of the car, drained in the main vein, leaking the lizard.
And I looked up.
It's sort of like two or three in the morning.
I looked up and that was the first time I had to be like in my late twenties.
And I'm still using terms like drained in the main vein.
I looked up and for the very, very first time in my life, I saw the galaxy.
I thought all of that stuff was like camera tricks, like exposures held for the long.
I didn't know you could look up and see the galaxy.
It's beautiful.
And I haven't seen it since.
It's been around 20 years since the last time I saw the galaxy.
The other day when I was walking down the street, I asked Sabine how many times have
you seen the galaxy?
She said five or six times.
I just kind of thought it would be more.
But I said I have a conspiracy theory and it really had just popped in my head when I
was looking up at the sky.
And you see like a couple of stars, right?
Maybe if you're farther away from town, you see a couple more stars.
But when you're in the middle of nowhere, you see the Milky Way.
And it's totally, if you guys don't, some of you probably have no idea what I'm talking
about because you've never seen the galaxy.
You have to go into the middle of nowhere.
We're walking down the street and I said I have a conspiracy theory.
Just all kind of popped in my head.
We talk a lot about Hans on this show.
He's back by the way.
He announced his retirement, but he's back.
He's doing stuff again.
Nothing super hilarious.
Right?
Just the same old, same old.
But his big thing is that NASA is trying to convince us that God isn't real.
NASA is behind everything.
NASA has orange chairs because orange is satanic color.
And NASA is behind faking monkeys because monkeys make us think evolution's true.
And if we think evolution's true, don't believe in God.
It's hilarious.
And he's not the only person who thinks that.
A lot of people think NASA is the super satanic group.
It was started by Nazis, to be fair.
It was started by Nazis.
But the idea, I've always said, what would be NASA's stake in trying to keep us from
believing in God?
Or what would be really any, how could you do that?
How could a group actually erase existence of God?
A couple of days ago I was looking up in the night sky and I said, I have a conspiracy
theory.
Sake pollution is being done on purpose because if every night every person on the planet
looked up and saw the glory and majesty of the galaxy we live in, you could not deny
there was something greater than us.
We look up at stars under these twinkling little lights.
But when you see the galaxy, you see the galaxy, you see just splendor.
I wanted to do a bunch of research on this.
I wanted to try to match up places with low light and places with high levels of religion.
I wanted to take a look at how light pollution is growing over the years and how belief in
a deity has fallen.
That research I spent maybe like an hour trying to pull up some numbers and I couldn't because
it was one, a bunch of other stuff to do.
I had to read about a ninja fighting US troops and two, it's a lot of work.
So I decided to be like every other conspiracy theorist out there and just make this claim.
But here's my claim.
The world would be far more religious and I would say, I'm going to take a guess here,
this is anecdotal and this is just.
If you look at parts of the United States that don't have a lot of light pollution,
I'm going to gamble that they're more religious than the coastal cities that have tons of light
pollution.
I think that's a fair, but is that, and that was the other thing I was thinking about doing
all this research, but at the end of the day, is it causation?
Could you actually show something or could you show the rise of technology just merit
a decline in religion and the rise of technology creates more light pollution?
So there was all that.
Brad, I could have done a ton of research and it would have been inconclusive anyways,
but the conspiracy theory is what if putting our conspiracy caps on, what if there is a
conspiracy theory to make people not believe in a God when you look up and you see the
majesty of the universe, bright and for every single night, how can you deny a creator?
But if you look up and you just see five twinkly lights and 10 of them are man made, you're
seeing planes fly by, you might see a couple of satellites.
It's far easier to go.
We're just on a big old mud ball, floating through the darkness, but we're not.
We're in the Milky Way.
We're in this beautiful gem.
We live right in the middle of it and we used to be able to see it from the time that humans
developed the capacity to identify what was in front of them, to comprehend something beyond
their physical body.
In that moment, until what?
The 1880s?
When those first lights started going up, you saw a little less of the night sky.
But by the time we're talking about the 1960s and 1970s, light pollution is out of control.
So from the beginning of mankind to the 1950s, what is that?
Until 70 years ago, when you watched that sunset, you saw the galaxy.
You saw what we were a part of.
And again, there are two people listening to this show.
One person who knows exactly what I'm talking about, who has seen the galaxy and goes, "It
is awe-inspiring."
And then a lot of you are just like, "But it's just the night sky."
It's not.
Those photos that, again, I thought were total time-lapse photos of the night sky, those
cannot even capture the beauty of it.
And so the question is, obviously the obvious answer is just the acceleration of humans.
We build bigger cities, more lights are going up, we have high rises and all that stuff.
It's just a normal thing.
But what if there is a group that wants to deny that God exists?
And this has been a strategy that they've been laying out for decades.
Fill the world with lights.
Cut them off from the universe.
Make them think we're just on a ball of mud in a darkness.
And when you look up, you see a couple satellites, you see a couple airplanes, and oh, look,
there's the North Star.
Look at that little bright light out there.
There's the Big Dipper.
And it makes you think it's people like Hans Wright.
Now, I don't believe that monkeys don't exist thing.
But are there groups that are actively trying to erase something that would, when you see
it day after day or night after night after night after night, makes you realize that
you exist as something smaller of a glorious creation?
And whether or not it's an organization on earth of men and women who are actively doing
this, or it is some, I mean, who's the person who mostly doesn't want to disbelieve in
deity, right?
A Satan, a Lucifer, a demonic presence.
That this is his plan.
Cut us off from the most beautiful view in creation.
It's easier to tell us that it doesn't matter when we die, we just disappear into the darkness
that surrounds the planet.
It sounds so demonic to want to cut a people off from God.
That's kind of the definition of demonic.
That's the definition of a satanic plan.
You know what the name Lucifer means?
It literally means a light bringer.
The story of Prometheus who stills to fire from Mount Olympus and gives it to the humans.
Gods were angry.
That fire was a tool of the gods.
He'd given it to these commoners.
But what if that fire was the first time that the night was no longer magnificent?
Even by the roaring fire, the galaxy looked a little less holy.
Is there a conspiracy theory to hide the wonders of the universe from us?
And is that conspiracy theory man-made?
Demonic?
Or both?
Who knows?
It's just the thought I had the other day.
But I'm a 45 year old man who's only seen the galaxy once.
Before a thousand generations before me, my ancestors saw the galaxy every single night.
Doesn't really seem fair to be robbed of such a beautiful view.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend guys.
Bye.
[MUSIC PLAYING]