Will the world end on July 27th? And just when you thought conspiracy theories couldn't get any
dumber, we delve into Jewish swim lessons today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. Hope you guys are having a great day. I am. You know what's funny? I was listening back
to the previous episode of the Ageless Travel one. I was like, "Oh, I'm so excited to
find all this stuff." And I realized that unless you knew about the Ageless Travel conspiracy
theory mystery before it, you're like, "What is this lunatic talking about? Why is he so happy
about this?" But I know the fanbase of the show is kind of split, and it's crazy to think there's
a fanbase, but the fanbase of the show is kind of split in two. They're the people who are really into
collecting information on wacky conspiracy theories. And there are other people who just
like hearing the occasional odd story. And I hope that kind of played into both of those.
But again, I definitely had a lot of fun researching that. So we do have a couple good
stories for you tonight. One story I think is going to be entertaining just because of how
frustrated I was once I found out exactly what I was looking into. Actually, you know, it's funny.
I think both of these stories kind of frustrate me on different levels, on different levels.
I don't like end-of-the-world prophecies. I think they can be fairly dangerous to people who aren't
of a level mind. And that's the blood moon thing. And then the Jewish swim lessons, when we get
into that, that's just, that's enough. That's enough of that. It's interesting too. So, you know,
on this podcast we talk about conspiracy. It seems to be mostly conspiracy stuff,
secondly, some paranormal stuff, cover a little bit of true crime. And I do think those things
kind of intersect. Another subject that I like to talk about, we haven't talked about much on the
show, is weird science. It's like high science, like kind of a cutting edge of things. I really
like that topic. Killer robots, you know, nanobots. I was watching a video today about something
called graphene. It's supposedly this super light, yeah, super durable material. And I was like,
"Okay, I've never heard of that before. That's really good." You know, the thing though that I
come across a lot is transhumanism. So transhumanism is the evolution of mankind. The next stage is
not going to be a biological evolution, but it is going to be a technical evolution. You know,
so we're going to have things like bionic eyes, robotic legs. I don't know if necessarily exoskeletons
count. That might be like a bridge, but you know, it's kind of like a Johnny Mnemonic thing, where
you have like a chip in your brain, you plug a port, you have like a port on your neck, and you
stick a cable in there, and you can, you know, download the internet, internet in like a minute,
into your brain, which sounds like a nightmare. Like honestly, I don't want all that information
in my brain. The one thing, it's funny, they always talk about these transhumanism things,
like to reach the next level of ascension, we put this little chip in your brain, and it will allow
you to, you know, maximize the use of your brain or whatever nonsense, or you know, they can do this,
you know, electronic hearing. You know what I want more than anything that no one's ever talked about?
I want a robotic butthole. That would sell me on transhumanism. You tell me you want to put a chip
in my brain, I'm thinking, what about the privacy implications? Is it something that can be hacked
into? Does it send out some sort of signal? Is it a tracking signal? You tell me, hey Jason,
I'm going to put a valve where your butthole used to be. So whenever you have any like problems going
to the bathroom, like you got the flu, or you're having just general issues,
there's like a release valve. It's like a bionic butthole. And because it gets sore,
it gets sore when you have diarrhea. And like you don't want to, you're like, I don't want to say
you don't want to wipe. You obviously have to wipe, but it gets sore, and then you got to get those
soft baby wipes, the medicated ones sometimes. It would totally prevent hemorrhoids, it would
totally prevent a lot of issues with IBS. I think you might need to have like a robotic
intestine for that. But yeah, and it's just like a little valve and you could hold it forever.
You're like, oh man, I really need to go to the bathroom, but we're like 50 miles away in the
woods because we went to Ong's Hat and got lost. Oh, I don't have to worry about it. I have a release
valve that'll just stay locked. And then eventually you find a bathroom and you just hit a button and
it all comes out. And there's no like pressure, nothing. That's what needs to be done. You know,
and that's the thing, a lot of times with high science, there's a lot of like hoity-toity stuff.
They always want to, especially transhumanism, they kind of blend the quasi mystical with the
technology and talk about like, this is the next evolution. No man, just give me a robotic butthole
and call it a. I'm totally fine with that. Totally fine with that. You get the key, you know, I'm on
that keto and one of the side effects when you started off, because I went off of it,
because I had to go to a party and, you know, I wanted to enjoy myself, but one of the,
one of the side effects when you first started is what they call keto flu. So you have a bit of
diarrhea and it hurts, man. It hurts after, you know, like having diarrhea for the third time in a
day, you're like, oh man, I'm sitting on the toilet the other day and I was thinking, I wish that I
just had like a little button I could press and it just came out. So work on that transhumans.
I think you'll win over a lot of people if you can make it more mundane. No one wants to chip in
their head except for a bunch of nerds. Nobody wants that. So we're coming up to the, to the red moon,
blood moon, blood moon, not red moon, we're coming up to the blood moon. So whether it is it's a
lunar eclipse where this, I don't have to explain a lunar eclipse to you, but anyway, so the moon
is turning red. So this was a big deal back in 2014 when they were going to have four blood moons.
They had one in April 15th, one on October 8th, and then April 4th to 2015 and September 28th to
2015. And people are saying this is going to be the, this is how they always get away with it.
The headlines always say the end of the world, the end of the world. And when you talk to the
prophets, I'm doing air quotes and you can't see that because I'm on a podcast, but when you talk
to the prophets, they go, oh no, no, no, this is the start of the end times. This is just the
beginning. So nothing will change. You will notice exactly nothing. There will be no difference from
today versus tomorrow because it's just starting. That's always how they get around this because
if you, you know, when you have people who go, nope, the rapture is taking place this day and
the next day passes and there's no rapture, then you have egg on your face or egg lists on your face,
but, or sack on your face. Sorry if you didn't give those references. Those are all from the last
episode. I shouldn't assume everyone listens to every episode, but you say, oh no, no, no, it's
just the start. So anyways, these, this prophecy, this bunch of prophets came out back in 2014,
2015, saying that this was the start of the end of the world. There was a book written called
Four Blood Moons explaining the whole thing by I think a minister named Hagi Hagi. And he,
it was a best seller. People were spending this, spending their harder under money
buying this stupid book, making him a millionaire. And then nothing happened, but again, it's just
the start. And now we're back to this again because we're having another blood moon. And again, this
is another sign that the world is ending. So now this is a different minister. His name's Paul Begley,
Begley. And again, he's saying July 27th is not the end of the world, but it is a sign of the
end times because you are already in the end times. Well then, if we're already in the end times, why
do we need a sign? The blood moon is a natural event. It looks scary. And I know in the Bible it
says that the sun will go as black as sackcloth and the moon will turn blood red. And that's part
of the prophecy that's listed a couple different times. Here, here's the thing. Those are really vague
prophecies for a reason because you're not supposed to know when the end of the world is coming to.
A lot of the prophecies had to do with the destruction of the temple in Jerusalem. The
Bible itself is, the Old Testament is a religious history of the Jewish people. And it is a cornerstone
of their faith. They don't call it the Bible, but the Torah. Then the New Testament is basically the
sequel where Jesus shows up and says, "Forget all the old rules. Just follow me. I'll get you in
heaven. You guys are cool. Let's do this." Now, Jesus also talked a lot about the end times. A
lot of people misconstrue that because he talks about the end times are going to happen in his
generation. And honestly, I was confused by that because I thought, wait a second, Jesus saying the
end time is going to happen in his generation. I'm obviously not in his generation. But again,
when I've the more looked into that, in reference to the basically end times of the Jewish people
and the destruction of the temple and all of these things. So a lot of these events pointed
towards historical things that were historical to us. It was the future to them. The reason why
this stuff is dangerous is because people, not you guys. I get that the people who listen to
this podcast, I think I have a very smart audience. And the reason why you've stuck with the show
is because I'm not telling you, I'll tell you which ones I think are true, which conspiracies I
think are true, but I'm not going to present the Titanic conspiracy. Actually, no, I did
think that one was true. I'm not going to present all these conspiracy theories to you and say,
"Oh, no, you got to believe this. You got to believe that." I think you guys are fairly smart. And I
think that as you listen to the show, you kind of know the angle of it. If it's debunkable,
it gets debunked, no matter how interesting the story is. But there's a lot of people out there
who aren't like you. The majority of people aren't like you, where these things terrify them.
Terrify them. These prophecies can be life ruining to us. It's a funny story. Oh, those crazy nutbags
thinking the world's going to end. So there was that minister, Harold Camping, who years ago
was trying to tell people. He believed that on May 21, 2011, so we're talking way far back, really,
he believed that the rapture is going to happen. And people are freaking out about this. One man
spent $150,000 of his money buying billboards, telling people to repent. And you may think,
"Well, that guy's an idiot." And he is. But that's the problem, is that he was an idiot with $150,000
and he wasted it on the—not saying that trying to convert people to your religion is a waste,
but trying to tell people it's the end of the world and it not happening,
it's just foolish. Now, him spending his money is really the least of our worries.
You have incidents like this, when people are selling these into the world things,
it terrifies people. I remember listening to Coast to Coast AM back before 2012. I think I actually
had downloaded some of the podcasts or some of the recordings they had after the event.
And George Norrie was taking phone calls and he was getting calls from people being like,
"Oh yeah, me and my buddies are out here. We're having a good time. We're just going to drink
and see if the Mayan gods show up to stomp us all." And George Norrie would be like, "Well,
you know, have fun." And he'd get in call. "Oh, I don't believe in any of this stuff,
but it sure is fun to hear about it." And George Norrie's like, "Oh, that's great."
Someone else called up and said, "You know what? Since this is the last night alive,
I'm going to start doing heroin. I'm going to shoot up a bunch of heroin,
because what's the point?" And I've always been curious about it.
George Norrie's like, "Don't—that's not a good course of action to do." "Oh, you know,
I'm not—I don't know. I probably won't do it." And it could have been a troll call,
but it could have actually been a legit thing. You think the world's going to end and you've
always been curious about heroin. Why not? Another caller said that he was feeling so close to the
universe because he knew the universe was going to end and he could feel space and time bending
as the world was about to be destroyed by the Mayan gods, that he felt himself drawn to his roof
where he was then going to fly away. And at this point, George Norrie's getting a little panicked,
because basically what the guy is telling him is that he is going to accidentally commit suicide.
And he's like, "No, don't do that. Don't do that." Whatever, you know, George Norrie, he gets a lot
of crazy people on his show, and he always—the one thing I like about Costa Coase is that he's
generally very like open. He kind of lets people say what they want to say and doesn't question them
too much. He'll ask questions, but he doesn't question their beliefs too much. But you could
tell at this point he was like, "No, I have to do something. Like this guy might actually jump off
of a building." So, how many people killed themselves in the run-up to 2012 because they were scared?
There was a small increase. There was like 2,000 extra suicides in the year of 2012,
than there was the year before. I think it was like 38,000. I had looked it up earlier,
and I think in 2012 it was 40,000. So, you know, that's just the United States. And you know,
people at one point, the government of, I believe it was Mexico, had to block off access to a mountain
because they got wind that a cult was going to go up there and kill themselves on December 21st,
the day that the world was supposed to end. So, these things, yes, they sell books and
they're clickbait, but they can really cause damage. They can really cause damage. That's why
I hate stories like this. I hate stories like this. No, the world is not going to end on July 27th.
No, the start of the end of the world is not going to happen on July 27th, and we're not in
already the start of the end of the world. Whenever someone brings this up, you just got to be like,
man, like, you got to call them out like you would call out a flat earther and just ask them to back
it up. Well, my minister said, and to be fair, most ministers think this is nonsense. What I think
is interesting was we had 2012 and that was a Mayan prophecy, and we have a lot of prophecies
about Christian, the end of the world of Christians, but there was a story I read a long time ago,
and I don't know how true it is, but so there is the Muslim version of that, of the end of the
world mythology story. And when Ahmadinejad, President Ahmadinejad of Iran, when he was first
elected, he went to a well and he wrote on a scroll and him and the other people around,
he dropped the scroll down the well. And what apparently that ritual is, it's to summon their
version of like the purging force of the planet. It was basically summoning up some sort of mystical
force to help Iran purge the world of the non-believers and to accelerate the end of the world.
Christians do it too. They're always trying to build the temple because Jesus can't return until the
third temple is built, so there's always constantly a right-wing Christian's trying to raise money to
rebuild the temple. It's odd that these people want to accelerate the end of the world and ISIS is
the same way. The ISIS ideology is to get the Western nations into Iraq that didn't really work
out for them, to have the Western nations move into Iraq and just get annihilated by them. And
through all that bloodshed, they would, it was a religious cult that had state power. That was the
odd thing about ISIS, and I'm talking about them in the past tense because they are pretty much
past tense of this time. They would be the equivalent of Westboro Baptist Church took over
one-third of a country. That was what ISIS was. We'd always think of them as this terrorist force,
but they were a terrorist force with the end of the world doomsday cult. It was basically Waco
Meats, the Westboro Baptist Church, Meats Al-Qaeda. And that's what made them dangerous,
but they've been annihilated for now. They may pop up with another name or something like that,
but they're just getting destroyed, which is good, which is good. And we didn't have to send
in tons of troops. We have things called airplanes, which they pretty much lack. So don't worry about
the blood moon, and I don't really think any of you were. I just had to vent about that because
that really makes me mad. Another story that makes me mad. And I guess it really shouldn't make me mad,
but this is again, this was one of the requests I've been getting. What are Jewish swim lessons?
What are Jewish swim lessons? It took me a while to find it, and after my success of finding about
Aiglis Travel and the Belray Surge and the Despair Code, I'd been pretty much batting a thousand
up until this, and I did find it. So I mean, I guess that's okay, but it was okay.
So the Jewish swim lessons is three little words. It's on the conspiracy chart. It can be traced back
to a poll thread on 4chan. So that's the politically incorrect board. So you can kind of see where this
is going. It should be kind of implied with the Jewish swim lessons, but I'm going to go ahead and
read this to you. Well, because I can't even, I couldn't say anything this stupid myself. While
on the Poconos, I noticed camp after camp or Jewish, over 70% by my sincere estimation in northeast
Pennsylvania are Jewish. I started pondering what the reason was because Jews do not seem to be very
interested in normal outdoor sports, nor do they seem to spend their resources very often on amusement
parks and things along those lines. Okay, disclaimer, I don't believe that Jews have a problem with
outdoor sports. That's a weird stereotype. I think that's someone who's never met Jewish
person. Don't they, they have Olympic teams. Actually, I know they have Olympic teams because
one of them got shot up in Munich. But anyway, so according to him, not me, according to him,
Jewish people do not like sports, even though they play every single sport available. So he goes on,
and so he comes to that conclusion. First off, he's like, all these camps are Jewish, like 70%
of the kids in these camps are Jewish. And why Jewish kids don't like sports? What's going on?
Okay, okay, so I get it. It's a stereotype, whatever. Now he has that conclusion. Now we're
going to go into the next step. I was then telepathically connected to a Hasidic Jew.
That is one sentence I thought I would never read.
Okay, he continues, I started asking questions. I suppose you are programming the children there,
he mentally nodded, yes. How somebody mentally nods, okay, okay. Okay, so back to the letter,
back to the letter. I continued, I suppose at some point that you sacrifice a child there,
program them, and then lock it in with sexual abuses thereafter by the staff. He stated something
along the lines of bingo. I asked how could I catch them in this? The response was that the
ritual sacrifice must be real or maybe operating in a virtualized state, yet the sexual abuse is
often real. I suppose that they refer to these camps cryptically when they talk about camps,
and people presume they are referring to the Hala hoax. So I guess now he's, okay. So now he's
saying that whenever they talk about, oh, I guess now he's saying that whenever they talk about
Nazi death camps, they're actually referring to camps in northeast Pennsylvania, apparently.
Hala hoax, if you don't know, is a term, derogatory term for the Holocaust, because these people
claim that the Holocaust never happened. And then he goes on to say, interestingly enough,
interestingly enough, the solution may be to camp out on these camps from the beginning
to the end with cameras in the trees that can monitor the camps for any group programming
session. So what we have here, I'm assuming this is a man. I think people generally assume that
when people are online are their same sex that they are. But I'm going to assume this is a guy.
So what this guy is saying is that he, someone, he realized that 70% of the people who go to
the camps in his area are Jewish. Then he is hanging out at his house or walking down the street or
doing whatever. And he hears a Hasidic Jew in his head saying, well, actually, no, he starts
asking questions. So imagine that you're hanging out and then all of a sudden you hear a voice in
your head and somehow you're able to determine its ethnicity and religion. The first thing you do
is start asking questions about, hey, what are you doing with kids in those camps? And then it
mentally nods yes to your questions. And then you ask and it's like, well, we kill them, but we
don't really kill them. But the sexual abuse is real. And this guy's having this whole conversation
in his head. And then he decides the next step is to go to these camps and install cameras
all around the camp to record young boys and girls in the woods.
That's Jewish swim lessons. Because they're at the camp and they're engaging in swimming and,
I don't know, lacrosse and making bracelets to send back home. This is where googling those
three words led me to the rantings of an obviously mentally ill and racist man.
These swim lessons are used to program children. Here's my question, actually. Why would they do
it to if the Jewish people in his mind, not mine, I have to keep distancing myself from that.
If Jewish people in his mind are torturing kids, why would they do it to other Jewish kids?
That doesn't make sense. Why wouldn't you do it to people that you felt were unworthy?
I mean, I guess like Catholic priests, molest cast the Catholic boys, but they're not trying to
program them or necessarily torture them. They're just trying to get their rocks off.
This is supposedly some ritual thing. And I'm going to say right now, this isn't true.
None of this is true. I hope that goes without saying. But it's like, what's the point? And
this question gets asked all the time. I've seen it online. People have asked me about the show.
Hey, do Jewish swim lessons, do Jewish swim lessons. I found it. It's ridiculous. It's made up.
It's very racist. And this guy is out there putting cameras up in trees and
he actually gives you links to find Jewish camps in Pennsylvania. So you can be part of his
underground resistance against the quote unquote swim lessons that are really used to program
these kids. So out of this guy's post, it's posted January of 2017. So over a year ago,
out of this post came Jewish swim lessons on the conspiracy board. Out of this guy's ranteens,
it's now been solidified as a legitimate conspiracy theory. But I hope I was able to shed a little
bit of light on it for you because you'll see people go, "Hey, what's Jewish swim lessons?"
And now, what do you do? You can share my link and say, "This is what it is. It's the ranteens of
an idiot." Not the podcast host. Well, he's kind of out of it too, but it's the ranteens of this
idiot on this board and so on and so forth. You know, I always like to say this. I thank you so
much for listening to the show. You can always hit me up at DeadRabbitRadio and gmail.com.
We're at Twitter @JasonOCarpenter, at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Is there for you to follow us
on that as well? I didn't mention it last time, but again, I want to thank you, Ash Black, for
doing our logo art. It looks amazing. Like I said, it's on my phone. It's on my wallpaper.
You know, I'm trying to spread that. We're going to be putting on flyers soon and everything like
that. If you like the show, subscribe it and share it. Share the show. I've actually seen some
people already do that online. People asked, "What's Michigan Blue Hell?" And somebody posted
one of my YouTube videos about that. So thank you. Thank you for that. That's how the show grows.
That's how we keep the momentum going. This is the Daily Paranormal Conspiracy and True Crime
podcast. Thanks for listening today. You don't have to listen to every episode, but thank you for
listening to today's episode. Tomorrow we are going to be back with another ridiculous conspiracy
theory. Tomorrow we're going to come back with another ridiculous conspiracy theory. All this
week, I really like the stories we have. I really like the stories we have. The Blood Moon 1 has just
kind of fell in my lap because it's in the news right now. But you see people talking about it
just say, "Hey, how many end of the worlds have we lived through? We're still here. We're going to be
here on the 28th. We're going to be here on 2025, you know, July 28th. We're going to be here in 3000,
July 28th. The world is not going to end because there's a lunar eclipse. We're not cavemen. Just
remind them of that. I will see you back tomorrow night. I have a great night and thanks for hopping
in. Is that a good outro? I don't know. I might keep that. Bye.
[Music]