Today, we take a look at one of the most gruesome topics we've ever discussed on
Dead Rabbit Radio. No joke, I questioned whether or not to even do this episode.
Today we cover the speargun murders on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great
day too. I think today's episode is only gonna be a single story like yesterday's
episode. Speaking of yesterday's episode, the vampire sex cult of Yerba Buenae.
That one, I was listening back to it as editing it. I was laughing, which is kind
of self-indulgent when you laugh at your own stuff, but I was laughing and I was
thinking, oh dude, this episode to me, I thought it was very fun to record. It was
very entertaining and as I was editing it, I was like, oh yeah, still got to do
tomorrow's episode because this episode is probably one of the most disturbing
stories we've covered here on Dead Rabbit Radio. It definitely did very
disturbing to me and there may be people out there who go, oh that's not so bad. I
saw this movie or I read this article or something like that, but there's a
particular gruesomeness to this story that I don't think I've ever encountered
in my journeys through the internet. 100% true story. It's a true crime story.
Everything's been documented. There's no conspiracy, no spooky ghosts. This is just
a look at pure human madness. Now I will say, there's no sexual abuse or rape or
anything like that. That's not, because that is kind of its, oh we've covered that
a couple times. This is just a look, an insight, and it's just how cruel a human
can be towards another human. So that being said, I imagine for a lot of you
this will be the end of the episode. So play outro music, Dead Rabbit Radio,
Gmail.com, hit us up on Twitter, Facebook, but for those of you who want to stick
around and if you guys jump out right there, that's totally fine. I hope you
guys come back tomorrow. I'm not, I want to let you know and I've never done this
before because I think it's that haunting, but for those of you who are still
with us, we're gonna go ahead and get started here. Now quick quick introduction,
real quick introduction. I did actually have a podcast that I started back in
like 2003-2004 and I didn't remember the title of it, but I actually titled that
podcast Dead Rabbit Radio as well. And that's not a lark, but it's a long story.
I'll explain it some other time. I want to get into the story, but when I was, that
story, that podcast was more political and weird news. This one's not political at
all, just all kind of weird news. Anyways, I've recently been consolidating all of
my computers, all of my hard drives and stuff like that. I had a bunch of like
externals that I bought, you know, 10 years ago and I'm like, I never use it,
let's get the documents off here and trash it. And I've done that with a laptop,
there was just sitting in a box. And in that process, I found a folder that I had
titled New News and it was all links to articles, generally around the time
limit of probably about 2004-2005. So I was basically bookmarking stuff back
then and it's just all saved in these folders. I was actually downloading the
web pages themselves, so because I was always afraid this stuff would get
memory-hold and a lot of it has. Now, a lot of it's political stuff and I've
just been deleting that because nobody cares about the Bush administration
anymore. There's a bunch of weird news in that and you'll see that popping up,
especially right now when we're doing the shorter episodes. But one of the things
I found was this article and I saw the headline and I was like, well that's
intriguing. I don't remember that at all and I read it and it's haunting that this
happened. And I, you know, yesterday's episode I go, how could they not have made
a movie of this crazy vampire sex cult? There's a reason why they would never
make a movie of this crime. And again, you guys may think I'm hyping it up a lot,
but just wait till we get to it. Let's go ahead and jump in here. It might sound a
little bit louder right now because I just moved my mic ahead. I just need to get
comfortable. So it's 2004. Oh, and I should let you know there's probably not
gonna be a lot of jokes in this one because it's pretty grim. 2004. We're in
Melbourne, Australia. Australia is a continent. I'm sure you guys know about
that. It's full of dangerous animals and stuff like that. I have a couple of
friends from Australia actually, but it tends to be like, I think people, I
pictured it's kind of an ideal place. Kind of like New Zealand is kind of like, it
seems like a big old hobbit home. I think people look at Australia as just kind of
like, there's wallabies and kangaroos dancing around, and my crocodile done
these doing stuff. If you're over the age of 30, you know who that is. Yahoo
Sirius is dancing around. I think he was from Australia. But anyway, so just kind
of a harmless nation overall. Even though it's populated by a bunch of
descendants of convicts, it's they tend to not have like a ton of scandals like
other countries would. We're gonna travel through the country of Australia
and we find ourselves in Melbourne. We'll take the Jason Jalopy for this one
because we actually need a little bit of light, a hardiness. So we're going down
the road. There's like two umbrellas hitting each other, steam shooting out
of the back. It's just making a little ton of noise. It doesn't have, anyways,
forget the Jason Jalopy. I'm getting stuck on the description. We do end up at
the home of John Sharp. And John Sharp is married to Anna. And it's not the best
marriage in the world. There's friction, but what marriage is perfect? What
relationship really is perfect? What complicates things is they have a
daughter named Gracie. And Gracie has a thing known as hip, dip, dip,
dip, placia, dip, placia. So little baby's born, little hip, hip problem. The baby's
like, oh, you little cane. But they did have to get the baby a brace. So she, and
she only had to wear it for the first three months. Oh, sorry, first three years.
Huge difference. The baby had to wear it for the first three years. So little baby
born with a bad hip, and then they had to get a little hip brace for it for the
baby. And so eventually the baby would only have to wear it for three years, but
still it was hard. It's hard for a little baby. And Gracie was like crying a lot.
She couldn't sleep. She had a hard time sleeping. I mean, a baby's born into the
world and they're immediately in pain. That's pretty jacked up. So Gracie's
like, oh, my hip. And there was her first words actually. I shouldn't make jokes,
but I can't help it. Okay, so anyways, Gracie eventually loses the brace. Not
like she lost it, but they took it off of her. And, but the problem was, was she
still had some difficulties sleeping through the night, crying a lot. She,
she had to be fed. I don't know why, because it was just a hip thing. But she,
she had some developmental stuff. And that put a lot more stress on John and
Anna's relationship on their marriage. Hey everyone, this is Jason from the
future. I'm actually recording this as I'm editing the episode. Hopefully I don't
have to do this more than once in this episode, but I made a mistake. She had,
she did have to wear the brace for only three months. She was only 20 months old.
At some point I thought she was six for some reason. I think I mentioned she's
six several times later in the episode, but so she only had to wear the brace
for three months. She's 20 months old. There we go. That's our, that's our
pro, hopefully last clarification on this episode. Enjoy the rest of this, this
horrible, horrible story. Did I say it started off in 2004? That's not true. It
actually starts off earlier. 2004 is when everything happened. So we're actually
right now, we're in the year 2003. And John Sharp, he's in like his 30s I think.
He's sitting there and he's talking to his wife, when Danny goes, "You know what? I'm
gonna buy a spear gun." She's like, "What?" He's like, "Yeah, I'm gonna buy a spear gun. I
just, you know, want to like shoot stuff with my spear gun." The wife doesn't
really think anything of it. That conversation probably never happened,
but anyways the point is he actually did go and buy a spear gun and in hindsight
it was weird because he never showed any interest in spear fishing. And he would
take the spear gun, he bought a spear gun in two bolts, and he went out and he
would go in the backyard and he would just shoot stuff with his spear gun. He
was practicing using it basically. Crank it back, put the bolt in, pull the
trigger, shoot an apple off a kid's head or something like that. Pull the
bolt back, shoot, you know, shooting ducks and stuff. Shooting kangaroos.
Anyways, so everything is not perfect, but it's not murder my wife bad until
Annie gets pregnant again. And at that point John is like, "I can't do this. I
absolutely can't do this again. Like, we have this little girl who was in total
pain and I couldn't sleep and she's still having all these difficulties and
now we're gonna have another baby. I just flat out can't do this. Now a normal
person would either man up and say, "I can't do this but I have to do this and do
it anyways." Or just leave, just bounce, just be like, "Yeah, whatever. I'm gonna go
to New Zealand. It's only like, what, 20 miles away or whatever. I'm just gonna
rowboat over there." And just bounce. Like, those are really your only two options
if you want to be... One is obviously grosser than the other, but you can stick
around and suffer silently and just deal with it. Or you can be a deadbeat dad and
bounce out. Both of those options are far preferable to the one John picks. So now
we're in 2004. March 21st, 2004. John highly practiced with his speargun, wakes
up one night, his wife's sleeping in bed next to him. He goes to the closet, he
goes to the speargun supply room, and he receives a speargun and he's two... his two
bolts and he walks into the bedroom. His wife's sleeping there. Just centimeters
from her head, he pulls the trigger. And the first bolt goes right into her skull.
But she's still breathing. So he brought the other bolt with him. You know, you
always have to have a backup, right? Puts it in, pulls it back, thwup! Second bolt goes
in, kills her. And he's like... "Breathe as a sigh of relief, throw some towels on her
body, and just sleeps on the couch." Now, right there, that's the sign of a sociopath.
Like, you know, I mean, he might have been internally freaking out. He most likely
steeled himself to make that decision to kill her, and he'd probably practiced it.
Since he bought the speargun, I think it's pretty widely accepted that he bought
the speargun to commit the murder. To commit the murder. Can you imagine sleeping
and having a metal rod jammed through your skull? And it didn't kill her. The
first... the first rod didn't kill her. He had to shoot the second rod into her
skull as well. But you think that he... it must have been a crack shot for it to just
go in and devastate enough for the brain that it didn't immediately wake her up.
The next morning, he tries to pull the bolts out, and they're stuck. Because, you
know, it's evidence. You got a bunch of evidence. You got, you know, what are they?
Like, 12, 12 inch long metal rods that can easily be traced back. Oh, look at
someone. This wife got killed by a speargun. Who bought a speargun recently, the husband?
He has to retrieve him. He can't get him out. He can't get the bolts out. All he
can do is unscrew them. So he's holding his wife's skull and he's unscrewing it.
So the sharp tip is still left inside of her skull. He unscrews the shaft. So now
he just has the shaft. So it's basically blunt on both ends. Because the
little arrowhead, or the little point, is inside a skull. He had to unscrew them.
And he had to do both of them. And then he... buried her body in the backyard.
Shallow grave. Because he has other plans for that. He has to, you know, actually
get rid of the evidence. And then a few days after that, he goes and he buys a
brand new bolt. So again, don't want to hype it up too much, but if you want to
bounce out now, cue the actual music.
Get a rabbit radio gmail.com, is your email address.
No harm, no foul.
March 27th, 2004. John Sharp widowed, sitting in his home now. So it's what?
Six days later. So no one's really noticed the wife is dead.
The wife is gone. He's sitting in his house, it's late at night. He's drinking
whiskey and Coke. He later said he had to do that to calm his nerves. He goes and
he gets his speargun out of the speargun supply closet. And the bolt with
the tip on it goes into his daughter Gracie's room. Little kid. Little kid.
Sleeping. And he takes his speargun and he does the same thing. He puts its
centimeters from her head, pulls the trigger. Gracie immediately wakes and
begins screaming at the top of her lungs with a spear rod, a spear gun rod, sticking
out of her skull. John obviously panics. This little girl is screaming out loud.
She's just been shot in the head by her father with the spear gun. What's he gonna
do? What's he gonna do? He runs back to his speargun supply closet, gets the two
blunt speargun rods that he used to murder his wife. They don't have the tip,
they're just blunt. Loads one up in his speargun, points it at his daughter as
she's looking at him, fires again. She's still crying. Screaming. He loads the other
speargun rod up. The broken speargun rod points it at her, tears streaming down
her face, pulls the trigger again. Still screaming. He then holds his daughter
down and has to pull one of the rods he previously fired out of her skull,
reload the speargun and shoot her one last time, killing her. Jesus Christ, can
you imagine how disgusting of a human being that you have to be to do that? To
do really any element of it. To kill your child, to shoot them while they're
sleeping, to shoot them multiple times while they're looking at you, to pull a
projectile out of their body, to shoot them again, to use the same arrows you
use to kill your wife six days later and then imagine little Gracie. I hope she
didn't really know what was going on in those last minutes of her life as he's
running to and fro and grabbing extra bolts and pulling one out of her head.
Inhumanity. Inhumanity. And we can talk about stuff. We, a lot of times we'll talk
about inhumanity on a global scale and then sometimes, you know, like starvation
or death camps or mass shootings and things like that. And that's all tragic,
obviously. And then we can also look at murders and abuse and things like that.
And that's tragic as well. I honestly don't think I've come across, I read a
lot of true crime, a ton of it. And I think this is one of the most gruesome
ones I've come across. I've read other stuff that could give it a good run for
its money, but what pushes this over the edge is simply the age of the victim
and the relationship to the perpetrator. Four times in the head with a speargun.
Two of them were dull and one of them was pulled out of your head. But he's
not done. So now he has these bodies. He covers her face up because he
doesn't want to look at her because he's a coward. Shooting women in
their sleep. And this is what I always talk about, serial killers and stuff like
that. I always pick weak targets because they're weak. They're weak people.
"Oh, I'm gonna go kill 30 women. Hey, Ted Bundy. Good job. Good job. Yeah, go kill a
bunch of co-eds. Go try killing some MMA fighters and cowards." Anyways. He takes
his wife, digs her back up out of the ground, chops her body up, throws her in
the garbage, takes his little infant daughter, takes her to a dump, tosses her
in the garbage. Perfect crime. I'm sure he was just so full of himself. He
was gonna get away with it. He begins sending out emails to her family from
her saying, "I'm leaving John. I've met a nice guy in this other city far away."
And the family immediately becomes suspicious. They're like, "This isn't
like her daughter. She's never mentioned anything. She's mentioned being unhappy
with this guy, but she never mentioned another man before or anything like that."
Cops begin to investigate. He ends up being going on the news saying, because at
this point he's like, "Well, she went to this other town and the cops in the other
town are like, 'We can't find her,' so then there's a missing person's case for
this mother and this daughter." He's one of those idiots who goes on television
crying, "Please come back home and if you took my wife and kid, please let them go.
I just love them so much." Nation was all into this kidnapping. What happened to
this mother and her daughter? And she was pregnant. What's going on? "Oh, no, please,
help me find, you know." Doing the whole sob story. The cops weren't buying it,
though. Just getting really, really suspicious eventually on June 22nd, so
just a couple months later, he was arrested for murder. And that's where
we get the account of the murders. He confessed to it and he was basically
saying, "Well, you know, I was just having me and my wife were having
difficulties and I just kind of broke one night." But then his family apparently
said that he had a history or had in the past committed child sexual abuse. So the
theory, and I know I said it didn't happen, I know I kind of gave that
spoiler, I said it wasn't gonna happen in this story, but it's just kind of a
footnote in this particular story, that he had possibly been abusing Gracie,
that he had possibly been abusing Gracie and that Anna had found out. That
might have been the actual motive for the murders. And I was saying that before
with the mass shooters, like they'll go off and do this crazy stuff and be these
killers, but you know, still don't want to get known as a pedophile. You know, so
I mean, that's definitely possible. That he was molesting Gracie and
found out he had to take care of it. So gross, he still didn't have to do it.
He didn't have to molest her in the first place. He didn't have to get married if
you're a disgusting person. There's a whole bunch of stuff that's going on here.
He's in prison for life. Got sentenced to prison for life. He's in protective
custody because the inmates want to kill him. So he's basically in a cell
by himself. The end. I mean, I know it's not something that we typically cover on
Dead Rabbit Radio. Tends to be a little more jokey. Tends to be a little more
mysterious. But sometimes you are just... And again, I was reading this article that
was written in 2004. I have links below. I found actual links other than my saved
webpage, but I'm reading this article and I'm thinking, you know what's insane? Is
this is so brutal and cold and vicious and I forgot about it. Everyone forgot
about it. Like at the time when I downloaded that webpage, I am a hundred
percent for sure that I was like, oh my god, this is the most vicious crime I've
ever heard of. And then 14 years later, I'm surprised when I read the details
again. And I'm sure at the time there were these specials and these dateline
NBCs and these exposés, you know, what's going on, and people just don't
remember this story anymore. And I talked on... I touched on that on an earlier
episode about a school shooting everyone's forgotten. Where the guy
broke into the school and molested a bunch of girls and then opened fire. And
that was the worst school shooting you've never heard of. That was a long ago
episode. I think it was episode 40 something. We just get so overwhelmed by
the inhumanity that goes on around us that we forget these horrible horrible
things. And you're like, well Jason, thanks for reminding me of it. There's a
strong possibility that I don't release this episode. Or at least don't release
it when it's scheduled. I'm gonna have to sit back and edit it because it is a
heavy one. It's almost like too heavy. I don't know. Yeah, we'll see if this one
gets released.
[BLANK_AUDIO]