Does whistling at night attract ghosts?
And then we head to the workshop of Michael Minkin, a man who has finally perfected the
tinfoil hat.
If you're being abducted by aliens, he has your cure.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You know what's funny?
Because I constantly am checking the stats for the show.
I view it as if I own a small business, you're constantly wanting to know how much money's
in the register.
I check the stats of this show multiple times a day and I have different ways to do it.
I look at the iTunes charts, we're doing pretty good on there.
I look at YouTube stats, I look at the websites provider stats.
One interesting thing that I've noticed is that I get a lot of hits in Nigeria.
And it's funny because they're probably the 14th country.
I have a lot of stats for this show, this ranking list.
And they're listed 14th out of the world.
We get a lot of downloads from Nigeria.
And it's funny because I thought, is there a server farm there?
Why am I getting so many hits from Nigeria?
But because obviously I underestimate this show.
A young kid from Nigeria asked me to be his Facebook friend.
And he's not a prince.
Just cutting to the chase.
Actually did look at his Facebook profile and was like, oh, this is a legit kid.
And I'm assuming the two things are related.
I'm assuming that the Facebook and the Nigerian listens to the show are related.
But maybe they're not.
Maybe he's just some random kid who walked in and he's like, hey, I wonder who's living
in the river.
But AO, AO from Nigeria.
I have some stories for you and stories to share with the rest of you.
You can listen to the episode if you're not AO.
And I actually had prepped this before when I saw all the Nigerian downloads.
And I was like, I sat on it for a while.
But then I was like, hey, today's a good day to do this.
Now we're going to look at some Nigerian myths.
I don't think I've come across anything like these.
I don't think I've come across in my journeys through the paranormal.
Something quite so mundane/bizarre.
Like it's just both.
So first off, let's go walking through Nigeria.
I have no idea what the geography is like at all.
But we're going to be walking down the part of the planet known as Nigeria.
And like you always do, you want to whistle.
But we're not just whistling walking through Nigeria.
We're whistling at night.
We got our flashlights in front of us and we start whistling.
I can't whistle.
I can suck in.
No jokes.
I can do this.
Like that.
But I can't go.
I guess I can kind of blow out.
But mostly I actually, I remember one summer I kept going all summer long.
It was just some weird habit I got.
And my grandma's like, I was staying with my great-grandma at the time.
She's like, you better stop doing that.
It's going to be a habit.
I think it was along to the third grade.
I'm like, no, what are you talking about?
And I'd just be watching television and I'd go, whew.
And then I remember like the first week of school I'd be sitting in class and I'd go,
whew.
I'd be like, oh no, my great-grandma was right.
Who would have thought that a 70-year-old woman would know anything?
I have to break myself of that habit real fast.
I look like a total weirdo sitting in class going, whew.
Anyways, we're walking through Nigeria and we are whistling.
And that's when we hear someone from the bushes whistling back.
We're like, what?
Where's that coming from?
And you're like, I think it's coming from the bushes.
Now when you hear the whistling from the bush, the funny thing about this myth is it's none
of the stuff I would ever do in real life.
One, I don't whistle.
I've made that apparent.
I can't.
This might have worked in the third grade.
I don't feel compelled to whistle in the first place.
I definitely don't like drawing attention to myself at night so I wouldn't whistle in
the darkness.
And the other component of this myth, or this legend, is that when you hear whistling from
the bushes, you go and you investigate.
I would not do that either if I'm walking down a dark street and I hear whistling in
any street.
I could be walking through Beverly Hills if I'm here whistling in the bushes.
I won't investigate.
But anyways, what happens is if you investigate the bushes, the ghosts get you.
See the dead whistle back at you is really the point of this story.
You whistle the dead whistle back at you.
The creepy component.
So it's fairly mundane whistling in the dark.
I guess people do that.
But if they get you, I thought this part was creepy, if they get you, you then become
a lurking ghost like sitting by the side of the road with haunted eyes, just waiting
for someone to walk by and whistle so you can drag them into your hellish reality.
So every time someone loses this game, their army of whistlers gets stronger.
I always think stories like that are creepy.
People are like "and then you die" and I'm like "yeah, I could die eating a subway
sandwich like I could choke on a piece of bread or something like that.
That's not scary."
But what if when you died you then had to work in a subway for the rest of eternity?
That's scary.
That'd be pretty scary.
It would smell good.
But it would be scary.
Stories where you get sucked into the hellish dimension.
We covered the night marchers from Hawaii a couple of episodes back.
The same thing.
I don't like being turned into a monster.
Who does?
Now, I'm bought all those materials.
Let's explain a little bit about how these hats work and testimonials.
That's what you've been waiting for, right?
People who have actually worn these hats out in public, how they have dealt.
He wears it.
Several photos of him wearing this hat.
He wears it all the time.
So, here's the thing.
Aliens come down.
You know, like looking around, you're in a house all of a sudden, you're like, "Oh, no.
It's dark.
You're covering your mouth so you don't accidentally whistle.
Aliens walking up behind you."
And they're using telepathic powers against you.
See, and I've made this comment several times on this podcast.
You could wreck an alien.
I don't care who you are, man to man or man to thing.
You could defy physically defeat an alien.
It's the telepathic powers that actually take you out.
So if you can wear this hat, that's what I love about these testimonials, because there's
a lot of one-on-one alien action coming up.
When you wear the hat, the aliens can't use their psychic telepathic alien powers against
you.
So when it's like, "Ahhhhh!"
Coming up behind you, you can just turn around, punch it right in its big old gray head, punch
it right in the eyeball, dude.
It's like, "Ahhhhh!"
Falls backwards.
You basically remove their greatest tool outside of their hyper-hyper-warp-drive starships and
space-age weaponry.
Now they can't beam thoughts into your head and they can't paralyze you, so that's the
good point of these hats.
Now, they also say, or he also says, and we actually know other people have said this
too, aliens absorb nutrients through their skin.
They stick their hands in water to drink.
They don't drink it like a normal human being, because they're not.
So he says, another good defense against aliens is perfume.
Really smelly perfume.
Because what happens is when they grab onto you, it sucks the nutrients.
Basically, they're basically drinking all the time.
So if you're covered in smelly, smelly scents, they're absorbing it into their skin.
So the Axe Body Spray.
So I think the shorthand is he wants everyone to go get Axe Body Spray.
You know what, I'll tell you this.
This is one of my Jason Is Amoron story.
I consider myself not the smartest guy in the world, but also not the dumbest, pretty
moderate intelligence.
Back in the probably late 90s, I remember watching, I can't believe this.
I was watching television and I saw a commercial for Axe Body Spray.
This is the first time I'd ever even heard of this stuff.
I saw a commercial and I go, I got to get me some of that.
And the very next time I went to the store, I went and bought Axe Body Spray.
I'm not the most easy person to manipulate, but for whatever reason, that commercial looks
so cool.
I bought that.
I bought Axe Body Spray.
I think I actually bought a couple of cans of it over the next couple months and I was
like, this doesn't work.
This is, girls aren't all over me.
Like it was dumbest.
It was probably one of the dumbest decisions I've made in my life.
Like not on the level of like life changing, but I remember just, I don't think I've ever
had that experience before where I've watched the commercial and then gone out and bought
something.
Anyway, that embarrassing story is, right?
Spraying with Axe Body Spray that also helps if you don't have your hat handy, which becomes
an ongoing problem.
See this is why he says the leather aviator cap is the best because it straps underneath
the chin.
The aliens hate these hats so much, they will steal them from you.
They'll take them right off your head.
So he recommends the leather aviator cap so they can't do that.
However, if you can't wear one of those in public because you look like an idiot or a
time traveler, you can get a baseball cap or any other hat.
And there is a photo of this 60 year old man wearing a woman's bonnet, by the way.
I did not expect to see that, but so a bonnet works as well.
But the baseball cap, he says you can wear it, but you should attach string or tape it
to your head.
So you're kind of defeating the purpose.
You're in a business meeting, guy gets up, he's the baseball cap, and you're like, "Hey
Larry, you probably shouldn't wear your baseball cap here, but you definitely shouldn't have
a tie to your chin."
And he's like, "Listen boss, I'd really like to take it off my head, but aliens."
Assuming that the aliens aren't working at the building next to you, I think you'd be
fine with just the baseball hat.
But when you go home by yourself, you should switch to a leather aviator cap or tie it
to your head because they will take it off you while you're sleeping.
Because they hate these caps.
Once you remove the cap, they can actually start to use their mental powers against you.
So this was one of my favorite parts of this website.
It was just listed as directions.
Directions.
The first and only direction really should be wear a hat.
Wear one of my hats.
But he actually has a whole webpage dedicated to directions.
So here's a couple of his directions.
One, prepare for a fight.
That's an attention-grabbing direction.
He said, "Aliens will fight you for your hat," like we were talking about.
And then he goes on to say, here's a quote from the website, "Before you make one, they
may try to influence you that you don't need one."
Which is fair.
I think that's your own judgment coming into question.
And you spent two and a half hours making this hat.
You got an hour and a half left.
And you're so envelosed at to your third-eye blind tour hat that you got back in 1999.
And you think, this is a waste of time.
I can't believe that I'm actually wasting this and ruin my third-eye blind hat.
That's the aliens telling you, you don't need that.
You don't need that.
I think that's just your better judgment.
I think that you go, and there are better things I can do in my time than making this
hat and then having to wear it.
He also stated that sometimes, oddly specific, sometimes the aliens, when you're making
the hat, they don't want you to-- because they're watching you at all times, obviously.
They're aliens, right?
If you're making the hat and they don't want you to make their hat, they will kill your
pet.
So there's a story, a reader testimonial, where this woman was making these hats and
she-- her dog died.
And she took it to the vet and they said that its spine was surgically cut from the inside.
And the vet couldn't explain that.
And then she lost two more dogs.
And I'm thinking, this woman's killing these dogs.
This woman's totally killing these dogs.
And so, like, why is the alien killing the dogs?
Why isn't it like knocking down your house or killing you, taking your brain out, putting
it in a jar so they can do whatever they want to?
Like, it just isn't why your dog-- that woman was most likely killing her own animals.
But that's a bold claim.
But anyways, she's anonymous.
I don't even know her name.
So I could say stuff like that, I hope, legally.
So it's a joke otherwise.
This was one of my favorite quotes on this website, though.
And this really sums up this whole group of people, because you have people who exist
in a reality where they believe that by putting packaging material in a hat, they can protect
themselves from travelers from beyond our solar system, who have perfected light drive,
hyperdrive, whatever you want to call it.
They come here and you can put packaging material in a hat and you can defeat them, versus everyone
else who goes, "Hey, aliens might exist.
People may get abducted by aliens."
That's the camp I'm in.
But I don't think your hat's going to stop them.
This is my favorite quote that really shows the divide from the website.
They are good at manipulating your spouse to have a conflict with you about wearing the
helmet.
So basically, you have a guy who's making a helmet.
He's at home.
He's 44 years old.
Father of two kids.
He's making this hat and he wears it all the time.
And his wife's like, "Jerry, will you take off that hat?
You're so embarrassing me."
And he's like, "Honey, if I take it off, the aliens are going to get me."
And she's like, "You look like an idiot.
You're about to get fired from your job.
I heard you had tape on your hat.
When you were in a business, you had a hat on in a business meeting."
He's like, "The aliens, honey.
The aliens."
According to...
So, what basically Michael's saying is she, your wife, or your husband, is mad at you,
not because your hat is stupid and you're giving the family a bad name, but because the
aliens are influencing them to make you take the hat off.
That is a dangerous statement.
That's a very, very dangerous statement.
He makes quite a few more coming up.
So it's no longer this charming, like, "Hey, look, I think when we start off, I said,
'Hey, the guy's not trying to make money off of it.
He's making this hat.
He's not really harming anybody.'
But as we go through this website, he makes some dangerous statements and that's one
of them.
The reason why your loved ones are telling you to take off the hat isn't because they're
worried about you and they're kind of afraid of your mental decline or they think you're
getting too delusional.
It's because they're being controlled by aliens.
I'm afraid that aliens are abducting me so I'm going to go to these extreme measures
to stop them.
And when someone is trying to be rational towards me, I think you're an alien too."
That is not something you want to put into the head of someone who is possibly struggling
with mental illness at this point.
So yeah, that's just a bizarre statement to make in the first place.
But you want to know more directions, right?
You want to know more about this hat.
You need to have a locked container.
So when you're not wearing that, a lot of times the hats will disappear.
A lot of times the hats will disappear.
And most people go, "I woke up one day.
Hat wasn't on my head.
The aliens must have taken it."
Again, I know who's taking it.
It is the people closest to you who are saying he needs help.
This one guy came home and said, "My hat had a hole punched in the middle of it so aliens
didn't."
I can almost guarantee that what happened was one of his, like his spouse or brother
or whatever like that punched a hole through the hat and was hoping he wouldn't notice.
So then one day when he's like, "Yeah, my hat really works."
The guy goes, "Hey look, I put a hole in it.
The hat doesn't work."
Like those are things that people, that's kind of a dick move, but there are things
people will do to try to stop this delusional behavior, to stop this kind of insane behavior.
Again, this is different than believing in aliens or saying people who say they've had
abduction experiences.
This is full blow and delusion where you think that every single day you're being hunted
by aliens and it affects your life.
This is gangstalking with a sci-fi twist.
We had another direction, another thing.
I love this one.
There's a quote.
"Don't let the aliens lure you out of your location.
Stay where you are if you think aliens are close by.
They will make noises by banging on walls to lure you out, but don't do it.
They also may use lights outside to lure you outside."
I can imagine these people at home and they hear banging on their walls and they see lights
outside and they're afraid aliens are out there.
In fact, what it is is people are outside saying, "This is the police.
Please open up."
Or "Sir, your wife sent us here to help you."
But anyways, anyways, so there's more directions, but they're basically stuff that I've covered
already like tape the hat to your head.
Make the helmet quickly because you'll be under telepathic attack.
But let's end it like this.
Let's end it like this.
I want to talk to you about one of these testimonials, one of these stories that someone who's worn
the hat has sent in to him.
In Pennsylvania in July 2008, this woman writes in to Michael and says, "This is what happened
to me.
This is my experiences with your hat."
Here's a quote.
This is a great quote.
This is the beginning of the description of the testimony.
So this is Michael.
Michael does not ease us into this at all.
This is how the testimonial begins describing this experience.
In July of 2008 in Pennsylvania, a woman abductee who was teaching...
A woman abductee who was teaching two alien hybrids how to drive her SUV at night had
her helmets forcibly removed from her.
You can't...
That is not how...
I want to know that story.
Why was she teaching them how to drive?
Did she know that they were hybrids?
Oh, I guess I should say right now.
The whole point of these aliens, according to Michael, the whole point of aliens abducting
people is to harvest their sperm and their eggs to make alien hybrids to take over the
planet.
That's the whole point.
So all of his stories involve people getting their eggs and getting their semen sucked
out.
So anyways, that's why there's a bunch of hybrids showing up.
Now, I'll tell you this right now.
Hybrids, they're actual...
Everyone I'm going to talk about in this testimonial are real humans interacting with this woman.
I can almost guarantee that none of them are alien in any way, shape, or form.
So the two alien hybrids she was teaching to drive most likely were just her teenage
sons or something like that.
They were not 100% at all half human, half alien at all.
So she's teaching two human beings how to drive is really what that sentence should have
said.
So her hats were taken from her two times, right?
Here we go.
So, again, real people.
Real people are interacting with her.
This woman is led into a room and she goes in there and there is a hybrid hiding behind
the door.
The other hybrid leads her into the room and once they get in there, they forcibly
remove the hat from her head.
And they take the hat and never give it back.
That sounds like something that someone would do who was fed up with their loved one wearing
a hat.
A little aggressive?
Yes.
Manhandling this woman?
Absolutely.
But it almost seems like someone was just at the end of their rope that their mom or
their aunt or whatever would not stop wearing this stupid hat.
It was a delusional crutch.
They forcibly took it from her.
And then as she's laying on the ground and she looks up at him, she's like "hybrids!"
When in fact they weren't, they were people, they were other humans.
So she ends up writing Michael after this and saying "Hey, a couple of hybrids took
my hat and he's like those damn hybrids.
Here's a trick.
Here's a thing that you'll need.
You got led into that room, right?"
And she's like "Yeah, I got led into that room."
He goes "Okay, I'm going to send you a new hat for your charge and I'm also going to
send you some aviator goggles."
So now you have this woman who was previously just wearing a hat full of packing material,
is now wearing a leather aviator cap and goggles, aviator goggles at all times.
So she's fully off her rocker at this point.
Like there is no doubting that this woman has some problems.
She's wearing the goggles now, she's wearing the hat.
So what do you think is going to happen?
Some people have already taken the hat off of her.
What do you think is going to happen now?
Second time, she had recently had back surgery.
Only from the attack, the first hybrid attack, but she had recently had back surgery, right?
Michael says this in his website that one hybrid quote came up behind her going through
the wall and back of her.
So Kool-Aid Man style?
Did he like bust through the wall?
Is her grandson Colossus?
Was the hybrid able to phase through the wall?
Which I would argue, if these alien hybrids can actually phase through walls, they can
get through tape and string.
Did I mention the locked cabinets earlier?
I don't think I did.
You have to have a locked cabinet because aliens don't know.
I think I quit.
I think I moved on to another topic.
You have to put it in a locked cabinet because aliens are telepathic, therefore they trust
each other.
So nothing on their home planet is ever locked.
They don't know the concept of what a lock looks like.
So if you lock stuff away, aliens can't get it.
That's the logic he says.
If you put one of these hats in a locked cabinet, these aliens who have perfected bending time
space don't know how to open a lock because on their planet we don't have locks.
Aren't all your doors and windows generally locked?
They go through the roof, right?
So can they just reach their hand into your thing and break it?
It doesn't...
None of this makes sense.
If you think about it for a second, it just doesn't make sense.
But anyways, that's why I said a locked cabinet earlier.
Anyways, so Guy, oh yeah, breaks through the wall, grabs her.
Other hybrid, pulls her hat off.
Now if these are real humans, they're incredibly strong to break through a wall.
I think most likely someone surprised her.
But that hat's gone as well.
Now this is where we get incredibly dangerous with this guy.
Like the originally saying your loved one was an alien was bad enough.
This is far, far worse.
This is a quote from the website.
This is how he wraps up this story.
This is the first case of an abductee being forcibly restrained by very human looking
and 'cause they are human...
Okay.
By very human looking and acting alien hybrid.
So even he's agreeing that these people are indistinguishable from humans.
Okay?
That's going to be very important for what's coming up.
Forcibly restrained by very human looking and acting alien hybrids and having their helmet
subsequently removed.
If the woman had a weapon, such as a gun or rifle, she could have tried to shoot them.
But she hardly put up a fight.
He's now recommending that these people open fire on hybrids.
He is now recommending that if this poor woman who recently had back surgery had a gun or
a rifle, she could have shot both of these hybrids dead.
So we can talk all about not wanting to take money, scams, stuff like that.
He seems to be doing it out of the goodness of his heart.
But he's now recommending that these people, these delusional people who are wearing these
hats, armed themselves at all times to shoot the hybrids who are trying to take their hats
away.
And if you think that is chilling, tomorrow we're going to get into some more hat stories.
I have a couple more testimonials of people who did actually engage these hybrids.
And then we move on to the second part of the story of Michael and his hat.
He believes that not only can his hat cure autism, but autism itself is caused by alien
experimentation.
Dangerous, dangerous theories from a man giving away free hats.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
[Music]