When a young man wants to get something to eat, all of a sudden the police state steps on his neck.
What a shame.
And then we travel to Mexico to take a look at the story of a young boy who was working at a construction site.
It's a 11 year old kid working at a construction site.
And he accidentally makes a big mess of things.
After he is quickly and severely punished, he runs to the safety of a shack on the edge of the construction site.
And there he comes face to face with something that defies explanation.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend. We got a ton of stuff to cover.
So let's go ahead and get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of my original listeners.
One of the original 14 people who were listening to this podcast back in 2018.
And a close personal friend of mine.
Everyone get on your feet and give it up for Veronica.
Wooo yeah, come on in Veronica. Walk on into Dead Rabbit Command.
Veronica's moving away. Veronica's moving away last week.
We've had a great friendship over the past six years.
And she was one of the original listeners of Dead Rabbit Radio.
A longtime supporter of the show, a longtime supporter of me, and she's moving away.
She's moving away so I wanted to go ahead and put her in the pilot seat this time.
I'll still talk to her, you know, we'll still chat and stuff like that.
But it definitely sucks when one of your friends moves away, but she is on to much bigger and much better things.
She's going to have such an adventure into where she's going.
So Veronica, thank you so much for being such a great friend and for all the years of our friendship going forward.
Also, let's take a look at this fan art from Paul Iana.
Paul, thank you so much for this. This is like a military Air Force type badge for Dead Rabbit Radio.
I love it very much. I love getting all of the fan art you guys send me.
It's fantastic. So for fan art Friday, Paul, really, really appreciate it.
We do have a lot of stuff to cover. So Veronica, let's go ahead and touch the keys of the Jason Jalopy.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We are headed all the way out to Joaquin, Texas.
[Jazzy music]
On Monday's episode, you're like Jason, please don't bring that back up, please.
I promise I'm going to shut the podcast off.
On Monday's episode, we covered a guy who killed a cat in an Arby's restaurant.
And then left.
It's kind of the polite thing to do, right? You don't stick around. You've outlasted. You're welcome.
He was an ex-employee of this Arby's restaurant.
He got fired for setting fires throughout the restaurant.
Multiple fires over the period of time. They must have really needed an employee.
They didn't fire him the first time he set a fire.
He then went back a couple of months later and eviscerated a cat in the bathroom of an Arby's.
And I remember saying in that episode, I go like, at what point did this guy decide to do that?
Did he always like chopping up cats? Or was it a one-off thing? I don't know.
We never came to a conclusion. Who knew that you couldn't solve the secrets of the human mind over the course of a half-hour podcast?
And that's where this story leads us as well.
But this one has an interesting spin on it. This really has an interesting spin on it,
because Fault, this guy for whatever disgusting things you want, this guy is a monster.
He's kind of polite. He's kind of polite. Just a little bit.
In Joaquin, Texas, this is back in October 2018, a young 23-year-old man named Alexander Nathan Barter
posted a request on the Deep Web, on some hidden site somewhere out in the Deep Web or Dark Web, whatever they're calling it nowadays.
And he asked in the most polite way, because I'm telling you right now, I feel like I'm kind of disguised as a defense lawyer, even though he's already been sentenced.
There's a lot of criminals out there who would not do this. He asked for permission.
He asked for permission. It's very polite of you, Alexander.
Muggers don't do that. Muggers don't wait to see a guy walking around. He has pocket-throttle of money. He has money in each hand.
And he just bought a coffee and he can't carry it. He's like, "Oh man, I wish someone would mug me."
There's a guy who pulls down his ski mask. He goes, "Now it's my time to shine."
Most criminals, by definition, are predators. Well, he posted on the Dark Web,
"I'd like to try necrophilia and cannibalism and see how it feels to take a life. If you'd be willing to let me kill you, or in the U.S., preferably in the south, and can travel by car."
This guy must be so poor. He wants to murder people, but he can't afford gas money. If you live in the south of the United States and can travel by car, contact me.
And I imagine there was some guy in Pittsburgh being like, "Oh, finally. I found my soulmate. I've always wanted to be killed and eaten."
And then he reads the rest of the sentence. He's like, "Aww, a little teardrop. A little teardrop of pure barbecue sauce. I was born to be eaten."
So he posts this online, and the feds see it. The feds see it. Listen, man, there are law enforcement agents on every corner of the Internet.
I'm surprised people still do this. I know criminals keep changing the game. They'll move to Telegram.
I think now the big thing is a lot of them are on kick, on this messaging app, kick.
But what'll happen is then the feds swarm that, and then someone discovers another way to communicate or invent one.
And the criminals go to that, and then the feds jump on that one, and just like this chase. This guy's way behind the times.
This Alexander dude, he's living in the 2010s, man. Posting this on the dark web, the feds find him.
So they begin chatting him up. And they're like, "I am from the south, and I'm so yummy."
Whenever mosquitoes bite me, they always sit there and they rub their little tummy. "I'm so yummy, you should eat me."
And he's getting these responses. One of the things that a fed actually said, they weren't talking about how yummy they were.
The head of the FBI is like, "Get out of the way. Get out of the way. I'm the yummiest of all of us." I'll talk to him.
One of these federal agents says, "This is weird, too." Because that's what he's saying. I'd like to try necrophilia and--
Okay, that's weird, right? His statement's weird. He wants to try necrophilia and cannibalism.
But then, like, he wants it to be a willing participant.
What happens is an undercover federal agent contacts him and says, "Well, I got a treat for you. I don't want to be eaten, but my 13-year-old daughter--"
Maybe she does. I'm not gonna ask her. I'm not gonna ask her, but tell you what. Why don't we meet up at this hotel?
You can kill and eat my 13-year-old daughter. And Alexander says yes. He says yes to eating this kid.
So, remember when I said he was polite in the beginning? You're not polite now, because she wasn't in on it.
Apparently, they came up with this whole backstory where it's like, "You bring your daughter out to walking Texas.
We will tell her we're going on a hiking trip together, but instead you'll take her to this hotel. We'll all kill her and eat her."
So anyways, and then, you know, 'cause this is what the police do, they say, "We want you to bring these four items.
We want you to bring, like, a knife, some hot mustard packets from McDonald's, a camera. Like, they'll give them specific things to bring,
so that way when they arrest this guy, they could show intent."
If he just showed up, he could say, "Well, no, I didn't actually want to eat the person. I just wanted to see who would be so sick to offer their 13-year-old daughter for someone else to eat."
If he showed up with a bib and some hand wipes, he's obviously going to eat somebody, right?
So they did that, and what happened was Alexander, he gets ready for this, this is on October 19th, he steps outside of his house,
and there's a bunch of cops outside and they arrest him.
And he's found guilty of this. He's found guilty of all these crimes. He gets 40 years in prison, so this guy's 23 years old.
If you don't know, if you don't know how to do that, he cannot get out of prison until he's 63.
That's insane. Again, what he was planning on doing was insane, and I'm not saying that that's not a just sentence,
but I just can't imagine being 23 years old and making a mistake that impactful.
I shouldn't say mistake. This guy didn't want to eat a human body.
It's not just, it's not like, "Oh, it's all we made a mistake. It's a criminal act."
What if that was interesting? I don't know if this is a common police tactic.
I don't hunt cannibals professionally, but the police officer said my daughter's 13 years old.
So because of that, and I guess they said bring a camera, he got hit with like attempted child pornography manufacturing or something like that.
And which is it super interesting, because he never, as far as we can tell, the information that's been released in the media,
he never specified he wanted it to be a kid. He was looking for like a willing victim, and the police said,
"Oh no, my 13 year old daughter's going to be there. Bring a camera."
And they threw on another like, "That's a huge charge. That charge alone is like 5, 10 years."
So yeah, just weird. I guess that's a crime fighting technique, right?
You make it so gross to the jury after they get done vomiting, they go guilty.
That guy's obviously a sicko. Now I'm not defending him, right?
I've actually done several versions of this story. The first 20 minutes was me editing out to make sure it's clear.
I'm not defending the guy. I just find it super weird on that legal level.
I'm just fascinated by the whole story. And again, like, how did Alexander even get to this point in his life,
where when he's 23 years old, he decides to throw it all away. All of it.
For this weird fantasy. And what's so interesting to me, like, did his brain break? Was he always mentally sick?
Did he start watching some really, really horrible stuff online? And he goes,
"Oh, this is good. It's sending endorphins to his brain. He's constantly looking for the next big thrill."
Like, how did he get to this point? And what I find so fascinating about this, for all he knows, humans taste super gross.
Like, he put it all on the line. Imagine if McDonald's came out with a new hamburger tomorrow, called the Forbidden Burger.
And the only way that you could get the Forbidden Burger is to dip your hands into hot grease to pull it out yourself.
But it's supposedly the best tasting burger on the planet. And if you want, you could have sex with it before you eat it. Would you eat it?
Now, I'm assuming if you would, I'm assuming if you would, you would not admit it. You're not going to go on my YouTube channel and be like, "I'd order too."
But that's the equivalent of this. You don't even know if it is the best burger ever made. But he wanted to eat a person, and now he's in prison for 40 years.
Which, I mean, for the most part, is the rest of his life, right? He'll get out when he's 63 and he'll be completely flabbergasted.
Like, "Oh man, I worked up such an appetite in prison." You start walking down the street and you go to a retirement home.
"Nom nom nom nom nom." You can't get away from you if they're too old. Weird, totally weird story. Was he always this crazy or what? Who knows?
Veronica! Veronica's like, "I didn't even want to be in this show. I didn't even want to be in this episode. I'm moving away, you freak."
Veronica, you can't leave yet. Veronica, let's go ahead and attach the keys to the carpenter copter. We're headed all the way out to Mexico.
*mimics car noises*
I found this story posted online fairly recently, maybe in the past two weeks, by someone who goes by the name BUSHITOBROWN.
Really, really interesting story, and it's one that just makes us ask, "Huh?"
We're headed back to the late 1970s, and we're going to a state in Mexico known as Guerrero, and this region is a particularly rugged region of Mexico.
Apparently, like, I was trying to look at the map and read a little bit about this region. I think it's also where Alcapulco, maybe, the tourist resort,
but a lot of it is rugged mountainous terrain and it's primary populated by the indigenous people of Mexico.
And back in the 1970s, we have a young boy, he grew up in this region, he never really left this area.
He's between the ages of 9 and 11, he's just a young boy, and we don't have a name for him, we're going to call him Billy.
So Billy was working at a construction site, I hope he was closer to 11 than 9, but he was working at a construction site with his father,
and they are currently putting up the walls of a large ranch.
And Billy goes out to the shed on the edge of the construction site and he's mixing cement, and then he has to load it up on a wheelbarrow and roll it.
What's the verb for using a wheelbarrow? Push.
He had to use a wheelbarrow to get the cement from one end of the construction site over to where his father and all the other workers were,
and as he's getting close to them, he's like, "Look, I'm a big boy, I'm 9 years old, I can carry 50 pounds of cement in a wheelbarrow."
Well, apparently he shouldn't have been bragging, he should have been paying attention to where he was going,
because right when he gets up to where the workers are, he spills it.
Which I imagine cleaning up cement is quite difficult.
You're like, "Hurry up boys, otherwise we're just going to have this giant lump in the middle of this ranch."
Well, the jokes end because his dad is a real piece of work, right?
Billy's dad is just a piece of trash.
And when this little boy, who has no business at a construction site to begin with,
makes a little boy mistake, his dad hits him.
His dad straight up punches Billy and starts screaming at him, calling him a worthless piece of garbage.
Get out of here. Get out of here before you mess something else up.
So little Billy runs away, because what else are you going to do, right?
You can't take on your pops. I mean, you wish you could.
Right, but he's just not strong enough.
Well, Billy runs away and he runs back to that little shed he was previously at,
that's sitting on the far end of the construction site.
He runs and he shuts the door and he is sobbing.
He's sobbing because he's in pain, he's sobbing because he's afraid and all this.
They're just horrible situations.
And in this little shed, the shed is basically like a 12 by 12 shed.
It's a fairly small shed.
And there's like a bench in there where you can kind of sit down and then you basically just look at the wall across from you.
It's full of nails and cement and all these other supplies and stuff like that.
And Billy's in the shed and he's crying.
And he's bored, right? You're crying, but that doesn't mean that's super exciting.
He's looking down on the ground and he sees a car magazine.
He picks it up, he starts going through it, his teardrops are ruining the page.
He's like, "Oh, I really wanted to cut that out and put it in my dream journal."
"Now it's ruined. Just like the cement. Why did I remember the cement?"
He's looking through this car magazine and all of a sudden something is off.
He feels something is different.
It's not like an electrical discharge. There's no noise.
There's no overwhelming sense of fear. Just something's not right.
Billy turns to his right. Something draws his attention.
He looks to his right. Now his back, he's sitting on that bench.
So his back is to one of the walls of this shed.
And when it looks to his right, on the wall, right next to him,
maybe six inches from his shoulder, he sees a giant purple hole.
He's kind of staring at it. Now he had just been in the shed earlier this day, getting the cement.
And then he ran in the shed when he was crying. He didn't see anything like this.
He sees this purple hole on the side of the wall.
He said, the way he described it to his stepson, Bushido Brown,
he goes, "Imagine if someone took a three-foot in diameter purple piece of construction paper
and just placed it on the wall. It was just this hole, but it almost was just a solid purple color.
It was flat. It was flat against the wall. And then outlining the purple hole was this tube
that ran all around the circumference of the purple portal.
He said it was this dull yellow tubing that had I thought about it at the time, I probably could have grabbed it.
Like it actually came out of the wall. He goes, "The purple hole was flat against the wall.
There was nothing to grab onto, but as I think about this, because he thinks about it from time to time,
he goes, "I feel like I could have actually touched the yellow tubing."
But he sees this and this isn't supposed to be right.
He's been in here multiple times. He's never seen this before.
So he readjusts his body because he wants to look into this.
Because right now he's kind of seen it from a profile.
And he's kind of turning his body, he's kind of craning his neck to look and see what this is.
And as he is craning his neck over to get a better view, he sees a human come out.
Now, not all the way. It's just a man's head and shoulders kind of pop out of this hole,
as if you were looking out of a window, just kind of leaning out.
It startles him and he's looking at this guy who's leaning out of this hole, but the guy doesn't notice Billy.
This guy who's leaning out of the hole, he's looking at the opposing side.
you
(no audio)
[ Silence ]