Soybean trickery, a giant monster lurking in the forest, and is time running out for reality itself today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I hope you're having a great day. I'm having a great day. Great temperature. It took a long nap.
It's really nice out. I needed that nap because I finished recording the Bell Ray Surge episode,
The Prince of Bell Ray, probably around 11, which is normal, 11 o'clock at night, but the episode was 49
minutes long before I edited it up. Now usually what you hear is what was recorded. I don't do
many edits. Sometimes I'll take out "uhs" or certain words, you know, "mmm," but it's normally how
you hear it is how it was recorded, and I kind of did that on purpose. So if I have a 20 minute
podcast, it takes me maybe 20 minutes to edit it, listening to it back. Just keep it casual. Just
keep it casual. Last night's episode, though, 49 minutes long was way too long for the information
presented, and I found myself repeating stuff, and I went on like a five minute rant about the
Illuminati, and I was like, "ugh." So I, and to really, to get down 19 minutes, I had to take out
like two minute segments at a time. So I ended up going to bed like at one in the morning,
and I work at six in the morning. So I came home and got a good nap in. Today we actually have a,
we're going to have a really cool episode, I think. There's some interesting stories going on. One of
them I was thinking about a lot today, and I kind of changed direction on it, so I think that's
fairly interesting. There may be, you may notice there's a bit of a change in my voice, a little bit
of discomfort might be the right word. So what I've started doing, I drink a lot of soda, a lot of
diet soda, and I was like, "you know what I'm going to try to do? I'm going to try to switch to coffee.
Just drink in as much coffee as I did soda, just because it's cheaper, really, in bulk. But I like
to drink a cold drink at summertime, so I've been buying coffee, brew it up, pour it into an empty
diet Pepsi bottle, throw it in the fridge, and I'll make six bottles at a time or three bottles,
you know, whatever. And I just keep using the same coffee, and I just like put more coffee in it,
and da-da-da-da-da. So I make about six bottles at a time. I've been doing this for maybe about three
or four days. How often do you think I horribly scald myself while pouring the hot coffee into
the bottle? If you know me, if you know me in real life, you know the answer to that. It's about one
out of six. So for the past three days, and not one out of six days, one out of six bottles,
and I'm refilling them every day, for the past three days I have horribly scalded my left hand
three times. Normally I don't record a podcast right after I burn my thumb so badly it changes
color, and then just water being put on it burns as much as the original pain. I have a funnel,
I'm not an idiot, but you know, obviously I need to work on my funnel game if I have a one in six
chance of horribly scalding myself. And today it was so bad I actually dropped everything I was
holding because it kind of covered my whole hand, so I lost even lost some coffee out of that,
out of that bottle. So that kind of sucks. Now I only have four and a half bottles in there,
five and a half bottles, something like that. I have a bottle out here for me. It's really good
though. I'm thinking about learning how to cold brew coffee just so I don't burn myself horribly,
but I need to buy some cheesecloth for that. So first conspiracy today is going to be one of our
other food-based conspiracies. This one's interesting because it's happening right now. There's actually
a court case going on about it. And you know, we look at these conspiracies and they're like, oh,
you know, this evil group is trying to use cannibalism to control these politicians who will
then pass these laws that will bring about the New World Order. Those are fun, sexy conspiracies
because they get the blood boiling and they get the brain working. But the conspiracies that really
like affect people are just fairly mundane and kind of cruel at the same time. So what the issue is
is black farmers, specifically black farmers in the southwest and Louisiana, that area.
Recently, well, last year, everyone buys Stein beans. Stein soybeans. It's a great product.
They're not a sponsor of the show, trust me. They're not definitely going to want to be after
this story. But anyways, the Stein beans are very well known. They're a great product. You
plant them, they grow, they just produce great crops and they've always had their reputation of it.
Generally, you drop $100,000 on just the soybean seeds or they just soy beans. Maybe the bean is
the seed anyways. And then you buy another $100,000 worth of chemicals from them to help everything
grow. Generally, you'll get 60 to 100 bushels out of a bag of these seeds. So in this area,
you had white farmers buying these Stein seeds, planting them and going, "Oh, great crop. I got
80, 90 bushels. I almost got the max. This is amazing. Hey, Craig, how are you doing?" And Craig,
who's a black farmer, he's been in farming all of his life. His dad was a farmer, his grandpa was a
farmer. He bought his Stein seeds, he bought his chemicals, he planted them, five bushels.
Maybe 10, high end 10. He's like, "I don't know what's going on, Tom. I'm doing the exact same
stuff you are. Our farmers are right next to each other. The rain falls on our crops the same way.
I've been in it my whole life. You've been in it your whole life." Why isn't this working? Tom doesn't
know. They start talking and what happens is they meet other farmers, black farmers, who are like,
"Oh man, I'm having such a hard time with my crops. My soybeans aren't growing." And Craig's like,
"Let me guess. You bought Stein seeds." And they're like, "Yeah. How'd you know?"
They take these seeds down to Mississippi State University. They pop them on the table. "Hey,
check these out. We think there's something wrong with them. They're not growing for us."
And the researchers at Mississippi State University look at them and go, "Yeah,
there is something wrong with them. They're fake. What do you mean they're fake? They're dormant.
They would never grow under any circumstances whatsoever." They bought the seeds from Stein,
who they've always bought the seeds from. And when you buy them from Stein, and I'm assuming other
seed manufacturers, it's in a huge bag and it's sealed with a label on it to show that these
things have been certified Stein seeds coming right off to the factory. Because obviously,
fraud's been a problem in any industry. But when they opened these bags up and broke that certified
seal and planted these, the seeds were fake. The question, there's multiple questions here. One,
who, what was the end game here? Some people think it's just human greed. Sell someone a bunch of
fake seeds for $100,000. You know, you pay $10,000 for the seeds. If that $500, they're useless.
A dollar for the seeds. You can sell them for $100,000. The other one, the other conspiracy
theory that is being put forward is that this is a concentrated effort, or concerted effort,
I think it's the word, concentrated. This is a concerted effort to run black farms out of business.
The lawyer, and this will all be in the article. There's a nice audio clip from the lawyer.
And he was saying that, you know, these farmers have lost a million dollars. Like,
you invest $100,000 plus the chemicals. But the bushel, you make the money from the soybeans.
Everyone, every food company wants to buy soybeans. It's in everything. They've lost all of that.
And he's like, the point, the reason why this was done, the reason why black farmers were targeted,
was to run black farmers out of business so white farmers could buy their land.
You know, and that's always the funny thing with conspiracy theories,
is that you come to a point where the facts, the absolute facts run out. And then that's the
extrapolation. The absolute facts is that this group of farmers who were black were sold fake seeds,
and their crops failed. That's 100% the truth. And they were in certified seed Steinbecks.
The why, we know the who, what, when, where. Wait, who, what, when, where. Yeah, we know the who,
what, when, where, and how. But we don't know the why. And so that's where we go start to go off into,
you know, more conspiracy theory land. Now, Stein seed company has said, this is not true.
What they are accusing of us is not true. They're not saying it was an independent
distributor that they're investigating. They're not saying that, oh, that must have been a training
batch. They're saying it's flat out not true that these farmers are absolutely lying about the
whole thing. And again, when we talk about conspiracy theories, when you're, when you're,
the person that conspiracy theory is against is a group we don't normally trust. Which group is
more trustworthy to you, a group of small business owners, or a mega corporation. Now, to a person
who works for mega corporation, top level, they may go, oh, the small business owners. But generally,
the general population will go, oh, the small business owners are probably really did get
ripped off because everyone's been ripped off. Once you throw race into that, it kind of throws
the scales up a bit. Because now if I go, who do you trust more black people or white people,
people go, I don't like that. And but obviously that plays a part in people's perceptions of
these conspiracies. There may be people go, I don't trust black people. So the corporation's
telling me the truth. But I don't think that's likely. I think people will generally say,
yeah, it makes sense that a corporation would try ripping someone off. Racial component aside,
they may go, I bet you those guys are ripped off. I don't know if they are ripped off,
so white people could buy their land that's stretching it. Really what happens is it's
going to come down to the court case. And I hope when they file the court case,
that they don't include that part, because that is not very well linked for me. If I was a juror
and they presented me with all the evidence, and the defense goes, well, what's the motive,
why'd they do it? And the lawyer goes, human greed, human greed. Maybe it wasn't just targeted at
black people. Maybe they randomly got them. Maybe a bunch of white farmers got them too,
but don't know about it and haven't complained. And as a jurorist, I would go, that makes sense,
because corporations are really, really greedy. If they say this was a huge concerted effort to
eliminate the black farmer, as true as that might be, as true as that might be, as a juror, I'm
going to go, I believe everything else. But I mean, that's now, once you start to get into motive,
you kind of start losing me. That could honestly be why they did it. But I think a huge factor
of it is human greed. Maybe it's both. Maybe it's both. I don't know. I would be interested to see
if it was only black farmers that got these seeds, then I would say, yeah, it probably was an effort
to destroy these farms. I imagine, the only way I can imagine that is, you don't order this stuff
out of a catalog. As far as I know, you have to go to a warehouse or a convention where you
place your orders for seeds. And you have a line of a bunch of people, and there's two white farmers
and a black farmer behind them. The white farmer goes, I'll take 10 bags, and the guy puts the bags
on the table, and the white farmer comes up and goes, I'd take 10 bags and puts the white farmers
white bags up on the table. The black guy comes up and the guy turns and pulls out of a different
pile of stuff and goes, here you go. Or even if you're in like a warehouse and you get an order
online, they're like, hey, buddy, which one do we pull the stuff out? The white pile or the black
pile? Well, the name's Tyrese, so pull out of the black pile. I don't see that. I think someone
just cut labels off, dumped fake seeds in there, and sold the real seeds on the black market.
Either way, it's horrible. And either way, it is a conspiracy. One is a criminal conspiracy,
and the other one is a, like, what we would consider an actual conspiracy theory. But I
thought it was an interesting story, and it's something that I'm definitely going to try to
keep involved in, not involved, but on top of, because I think it's a, I love the stories that
are kind of happening right now, and especially the ones that involve law enforcement or any sort of
record keeping, because that way you can actually prove them. The second story we're going to talk
about, we're going to see if I can get to the big dog story. The big dog story is supposed to do on
you know what, we'll talk about the big dog story now because it's super short. I came across this
video on the Daily Star. Now, if you know about the Daily Star, it is probably one step above the
onion. It writes the most ridiculous articles. It's the internet equivalent of the weekly
world news, and that's saying a lot because there's a lot of fake news out there. This is like,
takes the cake as far as fake stuff. So normally if I see that a link takes me to the Daily Star,
I just ignore it unless I want to laugh, but this one has a video included. It could be fake,
could be, but I don't know, and it's interesting to watch anyways. It's a video of a man, you see
a dog in the middle of the woods, and then she's like a black dog laying on the ground,
and the dog's barking at this black dog, and they're in the middle of the woods, and here the
guy going like, get away, get away, like trying to get his dog to get away from it, and then you're
watching this and you're like, what's going on? The black dog then gets up on its hind legs,
and it looks like a dire wolf. It looks like, what are those things called, the wargs from
the two towers? It is one of the biggest animals that I've seen outside of CGI, and the dog immediately
reacts to it. I mean, it's huge. Now obviously you could watch it and go, ah, it's forced perspective,
or it was CGI. I don't think so. Cryptids is one of the things, I'll all say, ah, the bell racers,
I don't think happen, and there may be individual sightings of bigfoots, or UFOs, or fairies,
or whatever that all just be like, yeah, I don't believe that, but I do think that cryptids are
probably one of the more likely phenomenon. I think it's more likely that there is an undiscovered
race of creatures, or even just one remaining creature left in the wilderness, than a lot of other
paranormal ideas. Stuff like, I'm, you know, talking to the dead, seances and stuff like that,
I'm usually like, eh, but you know, again, people who are like, yeah, I was in the middle of the
woods and I saw this thing and it was like eight feet tall and it was a giant lizard, I got, fair
enough, you know, I wasn't there, but generally those type of things, I could see that happening.
So go ahead and, I'm gonna put that video on the links, it's just real crazy how this dog just,
and I don't think it's a werewolf, a couple people were saying it was this side or the other thing,
could just be a super massive wolf, but it's definitely scary. And then don't click on any
other links on that website because they will, it's just trash, it's a trash website. Unless
they want to sponsor me, and in that case just email me at deadrabbitradio.com, I will edit this
episode and take that whole segment out. So our last story we're gonna do today is interesting for
me because it's on the conspiracy list, it's on the iceberg conspiracy list. It was just three
little letters. I looked it up, I found the information rather quickly and I thought it had a
beautiful image. Thought I wanted to talk about it, just it's very short and had kind of this
beautiful imagery tied to it. And I've been thinking about it because I kind of try to chart out what
I'm gonna do for the week on this show. Past two days I was like, okay Thursday episode's about
this and I've been thinking about it. I'm like, that's kind of just a nice visual, but I don't know
how much I can really say about it. And then today something clicked. I thought, what if it's true?
What if out of all the stuff I talk about, what if this one's true?
So what it is, it's called the Bank of Souls. It's also known as, and forgive me if my pronunciation
is wrong, you know how normally I'm really on top of this stuff. But it's the guff. The guff
specifically is the Bank of Souls, but there's a few levels going on here. So what we first have is a
amazingly, mind-bogglingly huge tree that spreads through the universe across dimensions. It's
everywhere. It's nowhere. It doesn't exist. It exists. And on that tree is the fruit of the most
precious resource ever that is and ever will be. And it's a soul. And what happens is when that soul
gets ripe, it falls from the tree. And it falls into the guff, which is a massive treasury of souls.
This exists in what's known as Seventh Heaven, not the television show. That would be even weirder,
but it's not. So in the guff, these souls fall. And when a child is conceived on earth, the angel
Gabriel reaches in, pulls out a soul, and brings it to earth. And the whole time this process is
going on, this life before life, the tree is populated with blue jays that sing songs in joy
of the life that is being created. It's a beautiful image. It's one of those things that I, when we
look at ancient religion, the one thing I tell people, you know, people talk about the creation
story or creation myth, however you want to look at it, the book of Genesis, I always say, how
else, how do you explain evolution to a caveman? How do you explain the creation of a soul to a
caveman? You would say, look at that tree and see how that bears fruit. That is also where we come
from. Yet the tree is, is much more majestic. I do think it's interesting too that the human
imagination is limitless. And whenever we talk about these metaphysical things, they take forms
of objects that we know of, because even though our imagination is limitless, there's restrictions
on it. It's this weird oxymoron. You can have these amazing characters in ancient religions and
mythology, and they're like this creature who, who has existed before the universe was created
has three heads, one of a lion, one of a crab, and one of a seahorse. And you're like, wait, those
things didn't even exist before the universe was created. It's weird. There's this weird combination,
because you can't just say, you know, "Sarabus was this creature that I can't even describe to you."
I have to go, I was a, I was a dog with three heads, you know, call it a day.
"Who's Zeus? Who's this great god?" I don't know, dude. He was a white dude with some lightning bolts.
So it's weird, because these should be creatures that are indescribable. The tree of life should be
something that actually can't be described, but we have to tell another human about it,
so we have to make it a form that we know of. It's interesting to me. The limits of, maybe not
a imagination, but maybe the limits of communication, because we may be able to picture something
completely something that we can never describe. I've always, in one of my stories, I had a color
and it was called amber blue, and it was a cross between blue and gold, and I can picture it,
and I think everyone has their own idea of what amber blue would look like, but to me,
it's like a blue honey, because it's not necessarily gold, it's like a thick yellow,
and when you look at it, you see both the blue and the honey at the exact same time.
One doesn't overpower the other, but when, if I asked someone to draw that for me, and they,
I don't think they would be able to really give me the color that I wanted, the color that I
picture, I'd be like, "No, you need a little more honey." "Wait, no, no, a little less, a little less,
okay, now a little more blue," because the way that I'm communicating it to you, I don't know if it's,
if you can picture it the same way I picture it, but anyways, anyways, I'm getting off topic.
The point is, so I read the story about the guff, the bank of souls where all human souls are kept,
and I thought, you know, that's a pretty story. It's on the conspiracy list, so I'm going to
cover it, but it's really of no consequence, and then today I thought, "Wait a second,
what if it's true? What if it's on that conspiracy list,
because maybe someone wanted people to look into Jewish mythology,
or maybe someone's like, "Hey, I'm going to put this on here," because no one will guess that this
one's true. There's different, and when I say it's true, the key factor to the bank of souls,
the treasury of souls, is that there is a finite amount of souls. There's only so many souls to
go around. Eventually, the tree, like all trees, will stop producing fruit, and when that, all the
souls have fallen, and then Angel Gabriel, each time a child is conceived, is going to keep taking
another one out of there, another one out of there, eventually he's going to be like, "Uh-oh,
I only got maybe a million left," he's pulling them out, "1.2 million people are born in India
every month." That's a side fact that I thought was amazing. I think it's like 5 million people a
month are born worldwide. I'm not trashing on India, I just think the fact that you could have one
country that produces 1.2 million people in a month is amazing. Anyway, so Angel Gabriel's reaching
and he's pulling out these souls, and when it runs out, that's it. Time ends. The Messiah comes back,
the war is on, and then everyone is in their perspective realities for the rest of time.
It's over. Reality, as we know it, is completely wiped off the map. So I mean, obviously to believe
that theory, you have to believe a couple things. You have to believe, one, the human soul exists,
two, that there's a finite factor, and three, that you believe there's some sort of afterlife,
and there's an apocalyptic armageddon thing coming up. But I think it's an interesting conspiracy
theory because there's really only kind of three variations, three kind of thought processes on it.
And there's, I mean, not necessarily three, but three main ones. One, you're an atheist and you
just don't believe that human souls exist, or maybe you're not an atheist, but you just don't
believe human souls exist. That's one form of theory. Two, you have an Eastern form of mind
where souls exist. Everything has a soul, and its souls are constantly being recycled over and over
again, and every so often you'll achieve perfection and you'll be removed from the game board. But
there's, for the, for, you know, argument's sake, it's, it's, there's an infinite amount of souls
because everything's living every single possible life. And the third one, that there is a finite
amount of souls. And the third one is the Western side where each person has one soul, and when you
die, your soul is removed from this reality to never return. That's it. You're done. You're not
coming back. Now, of course, ancient, in ancient Judaism and in ancient Christianity, there are,
there is talk of reincarnation, like the Gnostic, the Gnostics in the, you know, beginning of
Christianity. I'm not for sure how Muslim looks, Islam looks at reincarnation, but so you have
those, those three sets. So if you believe in the third one, if you believe that every person has
one soul, and once you die, it goes to another reality, then the question comes down, do you
believe that there's a fixed amount of souls in the universe or not? And if there's a fixed amount
of souls in the universe, we're on a countdown. If there's an unlimited amount of souls, and it
doesn't matter. Personally, I don't know what I believe as far as how many souls there are.
I think reincarnation would actually be awesome because I like Earth. But if I died and went to
heaven or went to another dimension or ascended, I'd be fine with that too, but I'd much rather
just be like a squirrel for a while, and then like a duck, and then a shark or something like that.
I definitely believe that there's souls, and I definitely believe there's life after death.
If you're an atheist, that's totally fine. I get it. The evidence, for the most part, is on your
side. I'm not knocking that at all. And it's funny, as skeptical as I am about a lot of stuff.
People go, "Dude, I'm surprised you're even remotely religious, let alone believe in souls and
stuff like that. You talk trash about all this other stuff." And I'm like, "Yeah, I'm a skeptic
about a lot of stuff, but I'm not a skeptic about everything." You can, with all of my other beliefs,
if you showed me proof that there were no bigfoot people, big feet, there were no cryptids,
or there were no aliens living underwater, any of my other theories. And you're like, "Nope,
the world is just plain and boring. There's nothing special about it." And you could prove to me 100%
that was true. I'd be like, "Well, I guess that's true." But if you said, "Look, here's some measuring
device showing that nothing happens after you die." You gave me all that information, I would still go,
"I'm going to keep believing that there's something after death." And I'm honest about that. That's
just the way that I look at things. But imagine, back to the guff, I think that's interesting to
think that every time a child conceives, this soul is being taken out and put into this thing.
I'm not saying it is true. It really is just a religious belief, an ancient religious belief.
I'm not saying it is true, but if it is true, that's the ultimate countdown clock.
Because even if you don't believe in some sort of messiah coming back or some sort of armageddon
happening, you just believe that there's a difference, there's a human soul in us. And it's
finite. What happens when it runs out? Does the universe just shut down? Is it almost like you're
putting coins in a game and that's your last man when that last soul is taken out? Interesting.
So that one is on the conspiracy list as well. There's actually a lot of information about it,
because it is something that people have studied in the past. So if you're curious about that,
definitely check it out. I found it fascinating and I always liked that old mythological imagery.
And that idea of that there's something else out there that we're descending from. I just kind
of a beautiful imagery overall. The consequence of it is not so pretty. The fact that everyone just
disappears and dies when this box runs out of stuff. But sometimes we get the good with the bad.
Well, that's going to be tonight's episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I hope you had a great time
listening to it. My chicken just got done cooking, so if you're here at beep, that's what that was.
It wasn't my fire alarm. But it might not have been picked up on this mic.
Email address is deadrabbitradio@gmail.com. Our Twitter account is @jasonocarpenter.
Our Facebook is facebook.com/deadrabbitradio. Make sure to subscribe to our podcast,
review us. Reviews always help. It helps us get noticed. It helps move us up. And if you have
any friends that want to listen to it, have them listen to it too. I'm hoping you're having a great
time. Feedback is always appreciated. Logo art for the website was done by Ash Black and he did an
amazing job with it. We're going to go ahead and end this. It's only like eight o'clock. I don't have
to be the one in the morning editing this. But I did record a little bit longer than I should have
again. But we're going to chop it up and get it out to you. And we'll be back tomorrow for the
ultimate, the ultimate food conspiracy. It took me a week to find the story I will bring to you
tomorrow and I was saving it for the last episode of the week. And it's a weird one. I'll see you
guys tomorrow. Have a great day.