A horrific disaster turns into family fun for everyone, and then we travel back to the
world of folk tales, where we tell the story of a little blind boy and a talking bird.
I hadn't heard of it either.
Well we'll look at both of those today on the episode where I have to have done in 30
minutes, Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
If you listened to yesterday's episode, you know that I'm waiting for a shuttle to take
me to the airport.
The shuttle arrives at 7.30.
It's 6.30 now.
I still gotta put my clothes on, but everything's packed up.
Now when I say I have to have this episode done in a half hour, technically that's correct,
but I don't want you to think it's a rushed episode.
I had all these stories pre-planned out.
It's not like I'm just scrolling through my bookmarks going, "Oh, there's one!
That one looks funny!"
But let's go ahead and get started with the episode.
So you know, it's funny because when you look at the conspiracy iceberg, there's a ton of
stuff on there.
And you see these and you're like, "Oh, wow, that looks interesting.
English travel.
Oh, that looks interesting.
Medieval found footage."
One of them was something called the Legend of Kalos Pit, or Kalos Pit.
This was actually on the conspiracy iceberg.
I was like, "Oh, I'll look that up."
The Treasure of Kalopit is actually what it was called.
I look it up and I immediately regret it spending just five minutes even looking at it because
it is an old folktale about these two dudes in Britain and there's this bog.
And you're like, "Jason, if you didn't want reading it, why are you reading it to us?
Okay, I'll skip to the ending."
Two dudes are in Britain, there's a bog, there's a bunch of water in it and a bunch of gross
stuff.
One day the bog is a little bit lower, so they said, "Hey, let's pull a treasure out of
there."
Okay, I don't know why they thought there's treasure down there.
They stick a hook down there, they reach in, they grab a treasure chest, they pull the hook
up, they pull the treasure chest up, and they get it and they go, "Not even old Nick can
get it from us now."
It sounds like a weird thing to say.
Did they say that all the time?
Like they're at Dairy Queen the Order of Sunday, they had handed it, "Not even old Nick can
get this now."
But anyways, they say that and then the devil comes out of the pit, grabs the box of gold
or whatever is in it, yanks it back down, the little hook thingy, not the hook thingy,
the little, what's that thing called, the little ring on the treasure chest that you
like, you lift it by, handle, I guess was the word I was thinking before.
The handle breaks off and then that handle was used as the knocker on the church door.
The end.
Why is that on the conspiracy iceberg?
That more than anything made me a little like, "Uh, maybe this iceberg's not good.
Maybe this is just a bad thing altogether."
But it's on the iceberg, I wanted to get that out there.
But from finding the Callous Pit, I found a website that was nothing but Folk Stories.
Now I really liked my "Taylee Poe" episode about Folk Stories.
I know I actually said I was going to do this story second, but I've already started doing
it.
And while I was looking for Callous Pit and being disappointed, I found a website of Folk
Stories and some of them are flat out bizarre, which makes sense because they're Folk Stories,
they're passed around, people are making stuff up all the time.
They're kind of trying to teach a lesson more than anything.
But I found this story and I was like, "What the hell is going on in this story?"
I was constantly being shocked by just how ridiculous it could get.
I was just constantly being like, "What is going on in this story?
This is the story."
I had never heard of it before.
I don't think anyone's ever heard of it before, but I could be wrong on that because halfway
through the story, I realized they were in a totally different location than where I thought
they were originally at.
And you'll see what I mean.
This is the story of the blind boy and the loon.
Like a bird loon, not like a lunatic running through the woods capturing children and blinding
them.
There's a blind boy, his sister, and his stepmom.
And they're all living together.
The blind boy is an amazing hunter.
He hunts on sound and smell and possibly taste if the creature is close enough, but he can't
see them.
So he's like the daredevil of hunting.
And his stepmom hated his guts.
Absolutely couldn't stand the kid.
Now I don't know how old any of the people are in this story, but I'm going to assume
I kept picturing the boy and the girl.
Probably late teens, but I could be wrong.
Late teens, the stepmom will say she's 30, she's probably a milf.
She's probably a milf.
Okay, so that's the setup.
So a picture where you think that story took place.
I thought it took place in merry old England.
Or maybe you know like a place with trees and a forest and your hunter.
Even after the whole setup, I get to this sentence.
One day in spring, when food was short and when the ice in the window was melted, a huge
bear smelling meat attacked the ice hut.
What?
If it's going to take place in Eskimo Land or it's going to take place in a place where
people live in ice, tell me that.
In the beginning, say there was a cold wintery day in Eskimo Land.
Like don't start me off picturing a gingerbread house and a bunch of people living in it.
And then all of a sudden I realize their house is melting.
That is a plot point that's going on.
Their ice in the window was melted.
I guess that could be the ice like, well it doesn't matter because they live in an ice
hut.
Anyways, this giant bear shows up, just starts to trash in the place.
And the boy's blind, so actually why didn't he smell the bear coming because he's a super
hunter.
He's beating the house up, the bear's trying to get in the house.
The stepmom gives the boy the bow and says, "Kill the bear, kill it, kill it, it's going
to destroy all of us, it's going to kill us."
He shoots at this so funny, so the blind boy is able to find his target and he shoots the
bear with the arrow.
And the stepmom kills it, kills the bear.
Stepmom says, "You missed!
You missed and you shot our dog.
Leave now.
Get on!
Leave.
That was my favorite dog I liked more than you."
She kicks the blind boy out.
He like, she exiles him, right?
And the blind boy, this is happening later on in the story, the blind boy's thinking,
"Wait a second.
Dogs don't make a huge noise when they fall to the ground."
He's like, "I'm pretty sure I killed that bear.
I'm pretty sure I heard 800 pounds hit the ground, but my stepmom kicked me out of the
house.
She said that I shot the dog instead."
So how big was their dog would be another part of the story I want to know a detail
of.
The little boy's kicked out, right?
He goes to another snow house.
Now they're specifically being called snow houses, so we do know it's somewhere in the
arctic.
And they have dogs down there, I guess, and bears?
Not polar bears?
I don't know.
He goes to another snow house and he's blind.
Remember, this is a key point.
He's blind.
The new house he goes to is abandoned and it's dirty and smelly.
He describes like, "Oh my God, now how smelly, first off, how smelly can ice get?"
Secondly, if you're blind, like blind blind, how do you know something?
How do you know it's dirty?
Like you can have daredevil senses, but I don't think he's like rearranging people's,
like he's straightening people's pictures.
You know, sure, if you trip on a soda can, you're like, "Well, that's weird, I'm in the
middle of a living room, there's soda can here."
But you walk into our house and it's dirty and I will say, if ice doesn't smell, imagine
how smelly something would have to be for you to smell it on the snow.
Anyways, he's in this house, he's like, "This sucks."
I wish I was back home even though my stepmom hated me, I'm pretty sure I did shoot that
bear.
And I miss my sister.
I miss my sister.
Oh, and I guess I should add this too.
She didn't kick him out of the house and he just like walked to this other snow house.
She basically dragged him there and then abandoned him so he couldn't find his way back.
So quite cruel, quite cruel woman, but a milf, actually she could be a, it kylf like an ice
kylf, never mind the stupid.
So he sent it home.
Now back at his house and his old house, his stepmom and his sister were eating a bunch
of bear meat.
And she's like, "Oh, that was a great plan.
Like now I have one less mouth to feed.
We got me and this girl have all this bear meat."
But the sister really misses her brother so she begins sneaking him out, bear meat.
And it's so funny because she, this part of the story, I'm not making this part up, she
brings the shows up at the boys house, the hunters house.
It says, "Hunter boy, blind brother, I have brought you some food.
I know you must be starving.
Here, eat this."
And he eats it and he immediately recognizes the taste of bear meat.
And he's like, "I knew it, that's stupid.
I knew it."
But here's the thing, why didn't the sister just walk in and be like, "Hey, you did shoot
the bear.
Here's some bear meat."
Like why did she leave that detail out?
She knew why he got kicked out.
What if she had to like sit there and like she has a big smirk on her face that he can't
see.
And she's like, "I wonder if he can tell what it is.
I wonder if she'll think we're eating the dog."
Like she should have just said something.
The sister begins bringing him out food.
They probably had sex.
I'm just saying, you know, you're up in the middle of nowhere, it's ice huts, you need
to stay warm.
They probably banged each other.
But anyway, so the sister keeps bringing the brother food and he's still stuck there.
Now why the sister didn't take him back?
You know, the reason why I'm kind of going through this is I should cut to the chaser.
This story has absolutely no moral.
Why someone would tell this legend to their kids?
I mean, take the incest part out that I just made up, but why they would tell it?
I'm going to start cutting to the chase.
He ends up, he's stuck at the house, there's a lake nearby.
He's really depressed and he thinks, "I'm just going to kill myself."
And right when he's thinking about that, a loon, a big old bird jumps out of the water
and goes, "What's wrong with your eyes?"
Straight to the point.
What's wrong with your eyes?
And he's like, "Well, I'm blind."
And the bird's like, "Tell you what."
This is something, maybe the loon is a loon.
It's like, this is something that a serial killer and a cult leader would do.
Bizarre trial.
The loon says, "Tell you what, I can give you your vision back, but you've got to
grab onto me and I'm going to dive as deep as I can into the water and you've got to
hold your breath the whole time."
Can't breathe.
I've got to do it three times too.
It's not just one thing.
So if you haven't died while we're doing this, then you know, I'm going to have a little
blind boy for lunch.
I'm a carnivore bird.
But anyways, he holds on to his neck, they go super deep in the water, come up to the
surface.
A little boy's like, "Oh, I can see light."
And then they go back to the bottom and then come up and the boy's like, "I can see shapes."
And then they go back super, super deep.
The kid's like turning blue.
He's starting to see the light.
He's starting to see the Lord come through the clouds at him.
And he's like, "Oh, that's weird."
He comes back up.
I can see.
He can see everything.
So now he realizes that he's cured.
He goes back to his old house, bow and arrow in hand.
And the first thing he realizes when he walks through the door is how messy that house was.
So apparently, like, I guess one of the moral of the story is clean your house, because
you don't know when blind people will show up, or when blind people will get their vision
back.
Oh, and the loon says, "Don't tell the stepmom you got your vision back."
It'll be super hilarious if you don't tell her you got your vision back.
He shows back up at the house and he's like, "Hey, I found my way back here."
And he looks over at his sister and his sister kind of bites her lip and like, "Mm, yeah,
my brother's back."
So anyways, the stepmom's like, "Good, good, because we need more food.
That dog only fed us for like four months and she's wearing a bear skin, like bear skin
gloves.
There's a bear skin rug on the floor."
She's like, "Oh, those are just dogs.
Those are just big, giant dogs."
Let's go hunt whales.
So they go out to the ocean.
Again, what is going on in the story?
They go to the ocean and there's a giant whale and a little whale swimming by.
And again, he's still pretending he's blind.
So he's like bumping into stuff.
She said, "Shoot that little whale.
I'll help aim your bow.
Shoot the little whale.
We can't shoot the big whale out there."
And then we'll drag it to shore and eat it.
So apparently now these people aren't just Eskimos, but they're Nephilim.
They're basically like 10 feet tall superhuman giants who can drag whales to shore.
The blind boy's still pretending he's blind.
He goes to shoot the little whale.
Her plan to drag it back to shore is she's going to wrap the rope around her waist.
Now you see where this is going.
She wraps the rope around her waist and they're going to shoot the little whale, which still
has to be like four tons.
Shoot the little whale and then she'll brace it and they'll drag it onto shore, which at
that point she'll probably say, "Oh no, our dog was swimming and you shot that instead."
Anyways, pulls back the arrow.
And the loon shows up, grabs the arrow, flies it farther out to sea and puts it on the big
whale and the big whale takes off and drags the stepmom, clawing and screaming into the
water.
She says, "Help me, help me.
You need me.
You're blind.
You can't help yourself.
You need me."
And the blind boy turns to her and goes, "I'm not blind anymore."
Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
She just found a magical way to get his vision back and then he murders somebody.
Then he goes home and bangs his sister.
Now yes, I did add in the incest subplot.
Makes it a little more interesting, but I was just like, "Who is this story intended
for?"
Which made it perfect for me to waste 16 minutes telling you about it.
I love that story though.
I love that story.
They should make a movie based on that.
They could have, let's see, "Who would we cast as the blind boy?"
Never mind.
I've wasted enough time on this story.
But you know what, iceberg conspiracy theory list, this is what you deserve.
Don't put stupid stuff on there like Carlos Pitt because then I have to start reading
about blind boys banging their sisters.
Going from that story of familial, I know I didn't pronounce that right, going from
that story of a loving family, let's take a quick look at Daegu, South Korea.
Daegu, South Korea.
It's a place, obviously.
But more importantly, we're looking at the year 2003.
And even more importantly, we're looking at February 18th.
So Daegu, some of you guys, I'm probably not pronouncing it right.
It basically sounds like I was saying Ragu, but Daegu, if you're just gonna have to go
with me on this, my shuttle shows up very shortly.
I spend way too much time talking about that blind boy, but I gotta take my time with this
because this is an interesting one just from the way that everything played out.
I'm trying not to laugh because I know what's coming.
So Kim Day Han was this dude, he had a stroke, he couldn't work, he was super depressed,
lost his job.
I know it's great, we started this right after the blind boy story.
He's 56 years old and he wants to kill himself.
But there's a problem he also doesn't like being alone.
He doesn't want to die alone.
So technically that's not suicide, that's something else, but he doesn't want to die
alone.
He doesn't go on a shooting spree, I guess he doesn't have any loved ones to kill.
This sounds flippant, I'm sorry, but again I know where this is coming, it's such a
so bizarre out-ins.
But in the beginning he says, "I don't want to die by myself."
Maybe he didn't necessarily want to kill other people, he just didn't want to be alone when
he died.
And again, just jump off a building into a crowd of people, crowd surf from 10 stories
high.
He decides to get two melt cartons, fill them full of flammable liquid, and take a ride
on a subway, the subway in Daegu.
He gets on train 10.79.
And people are sitting on the train, it's early morning so it's mostly full of college
students and young women going to their jobs in the retail district.
And he's sitting there on the train and people are just kind of going about their business,
reading the newspapers.
And someone notices that he pulls out these jugs out of his duffel bag, he sits them down,
and then he starts like trying to find a lighter, and then he gets in and he's trying
to light it.
And at this point people are getting really suspicious, I'm sure they could smell the
chemicals as he got on, but now you see a guy fumbling with a lighter, a fight breaks
out over the lighter.
People are trying to stop him from doing whatever nonsense he's about to do.
One of the cartons of liquid gets kicked and spilled all over the subway car.
He ends up igniting the lighter and he catches on fire.
Kim catches on fire and immediately freaks out, oh my god, oh my god, what's going on?
Oh yeah, I forgot, I was going to try to commit suicide, but this totally hurts.
And he jumps off the train out of the subway car.
And quite a few other people get out of the subway car as well.
But the problem is that you had, it wasn't just one subway car, you had all the cars
connected together as the subway works.
And the insulation that was between the outer metal shell and the inner metal shell, so
you had the outside, then you had some insulation to keep everything warm.
And then on the inside you had the rest of it, and then you had that's where the seats
were and everything.
The fire actually got into the insulation and shot through the train.
So if you weren't in that car, it didn't matter.
All the trains now were burning on the inside of the walls, plastic started to melt and
everything became pitch black smoke.
So people in other cars didn't know what was going on, they may have heard a struggle,
but now their car was on fire in the walls where they couldn't see it and smoke was just
billowing out everywhere.
Within two minutes all six cars on that subway train were on fire.
Either full on, your floor was on fire, or it was on fire in the walls burning all of
that insulation, choking black smoke.
The conductor of 1079 doesn't tell headquarters what's going on.
For whatever reason, he doesn't radio them in and go "oh my god my train's on fire,
a guy just jumped out, he's on fire."
A bunch of people ran out of certain train and now they're smoke everywhere.
Doesn't warn anyone.
Even 1080 is now pulling into the station in the opposite direction.
It stops alongside 1079 so now they're both facing in different directions.
They're both parked next to each other now and the doors open up to let the people out
of 1080 but just smoke is everywhere at this point.
So when their doors open up, 1080, they don't know what's going on.
Black smoke begins filling the subway and they have to close the doors again.
And again, they have no idea that the subway next to them is on fire.
The subway train on next to them is on fire.
The automatic fire detection system in the subway system detects a fire.
And this is such a weird "safety mechanism."
What it does is it shuts down power.
So all the lights go off and the trains are stuck.
The power to the rails is shut off.
The conductor for the train 1080 says "Hey guys, just stay on here.
Stay on the train.
There's a fire next to us but we're safe in here.
Don't worry about it."
Then he calls in radio.
He calls the headquarters.
The 1080 conductor calls in headquarters and says "What am I supposed to do here?
What's going on?
What's going on?"
And they said "We're trying to figure it out.
Just stay there for right now.
Just stay there for right now."
He tells his people "Stay on the train.
There's smoke everywhere.
We're saving our train."
Eventually though, his supervisors say "You know what?
You've got to get out of there.
Get out of the train.
Get everyone out of the train."
He panics and he pulls out the master key of the train, jumps out of his train, but
his master key is what would allow everyone in his train to be able to open their doors.
So now you have two trains that are stuck once completely on fire.
The other one, the people are trapped inside in these subway stations and in most subway
stations at the time.
No fire extinguishers on the trains.
No fire sprinklers in the system.
No emergency lighting.
Pitch black.
Smoke everywhere.
People trapped on trains.
People crawling through over bodies.
Just trying to get away from this fling.
In the end, so many people were badly burned.
They assume 195 people died in this short, brief amount of time.
Burn to death.
So many people were burned so badly, they were like "That might be a person."
The only reason they came up with the number 195, they had to have phone companies go through
and find out who placed phone calls from that subway to loved ones.
That is some dark shit.
They had to go who placed a phone call from this subway.
And they're like "Oh, you know, Sally called, looks like Sally tried calling her mom and
she didn't get through."
And they're like "She must be one of the bodies."
That's how badly you were just charred remains in piles trapped in these cars.
Insane.
Because the guy said it goes without saying that.
The 1080 ended up catching on fire as well because they were so close to each other.
195 people burned.
The only way.
Now Kim survived.
He ended up going to prison.
He got life in prison for multiple murder.
Both train operators actually got sentenced to prison too for four to five years for their
role as a safety thing.
They weren't following procedures, they got a bunch of people killed.
It was more of like negligence type of murder.
It was considered a national tragedy and South Korea looked back at it and said "We think
we were so focused on becoming industrialized very quick.
We cut corners as a nation.
We said "Let's just hurry up and get this stuff done."
We weren't thinking fire extinguishers or power not being...
Let's not shut the electricity off when there's a mass casualty event.
Just try that.
But you're like "Jason, why would you tell that story right before you're about to go
on a plane trip?"
Dude, I got like seven minutes to finish this up, but I don't want to rush this.
Because now this is so bizarre.
That story in and of itself, you're like "Okay, that's a horrible tragedy.
You've covered tragedies and stuff like that before."
It wasn't interactive for good reason.
Now you can go to Daegu, but it is no longer a subway station.
It is a theme park.
It is Daegu Safety Theme Park.
All this stuff is really at this theme park.
There is a replica of a subway car shaped like the one that the people horribly died
in with a twirly slide.
So it's an elevated train.
It's an elevated subway car.
It's sticking outside of the building.
And you can get on it and go "Weeeeeee!"
Go down a slide out of the same style of subway car.
These people horribly died in, calling their loved ones choking on smoke.
You can have the fun way out.
Weeeeeee!
The little twirly slide.
You are shown a video, it's a documentary about the deaths, horrible 195 deaths, created
by a man suffering from crippling depression.
You get to watch a movie about that while you're at the theme park.
And then after watching that movie, you get to go into a replica subway station.
With the real car in the subway station.
So you can go now, you can go underground.
And you can see a car where hundreds of people died and not haunted at all.
There's no horrible ghost residue there.
And while, if you just watch this movie, and then you get to see the car where these people
clawed, tried to claw their way out of the windows while choking smoke when in their lungs
and their feet burned from the hot metal.
No joke.
Then, while you're in the subway, they begin to shut the lights off and pump fake smoke
to let you simulate the tragedy.
So you're in there, you just want to imagine this.
It's the fun safety park, or not fun, it's the Degu Safety Theme Park.
You go there, you're nine, you're probably with your class.
You just watch this horrible video and then you go into the subway station with a replica
car.
The power, the lights start to dim and smoke starts to billow out.
Now the website is there to let you know it is safe smoke, but I'm not worried about
the physical amount of the smoke.
I'm worried about the mental ramifications of watching that video.
I would think ghosts were attacking me.
If I went down there and no one said, "Okay, now we're going to pump smoke through here
and we're going to shut the lights off."
I would assume I was in some sort of hellish universe at this point.
But I was about to get dragged into the eternity of burning to death in a subway car.
And you go, "Okay, so that's the safety theme park, that's all they do."
You go down a slide attached to a subway car and you get to watch this video.
No, there's more because it's safety.
They got to tell you about other problems in South Korea.
You can learn about forest fires, which I know South Korea has forest, that makes sense.
You can also learn how to escape wild pigs.
Apparently, boar attacks are a big issue in South Korea.
And there's an earthquake simulator.
So out of the tragedy of 195 people being burnt so badly that investigators had to listen
to final voicemails of people saying goodbye to their loved ones or begging for their help,
out of that you can now go to a theme park and learn how to escape Pumbaa.
Or is it Timon?
One of them.
Maybe both of them.
Maybe they have maricad attacks over there as well.
But out of all that tragedy, you can now learn what it's like to be in an earthquake.
What I want to learn is how not to die in a subway car.
And they teach you that in the most gruesome way possible by simulating you dying in a subway
car.
You can actually see like phones and pieces of the stuff that's all melted and they're
like, "See, look how bad we were back then as far as our fire suppression technology.
It's much better now.
Oh no, there's smoke billowing through the walls as the power goes out.
That's absolutely terrifying.
Absolutely terrifying.
I can't imagine that stunt being pulled anywhere in America.
I can't imagine them being like, "Hey, remember that cold Columbine thing?
Is there a way we can turn that in with theme park?
Is there a way that we can simulate we have a documentary on Columbine and then while
you're watching it, we simulate gunfire coming from behind you?"
And then as you're running out of the school, simulation will have wild boars attack you
so at the same time you can learn how to avoid wild pig attacks.
I can't imagine this flying anywhere in America.
I can't imagine it, but it would be hilarious if someone tried doing it.
So that is going to be it.
Today's episode, if you can't tell, was a little more...
I guess the subject matter wasn't super late-hearted, but I have to go on this trip.
I wanted to get a couple episodes in the can.
It's possible that there will not be an episode coming out on Thursday and Friday of this
week.
We'll see, because I'm going on the trip and then I'm coming back and all that stuff,
but I wanted to get some episodes in the can for you guys.
You guys have been awesome.
Since I've come back from my break, the download numbers have been astonishing.
You guys really did come back to the show and it looks like you guys brought some friends.
So that's really, really awesome.
I wanted to say that I appreciate all that stuff.
You guys are great.
So I'm going to go finish getting dressed.
I got 29 minutes to do it.
You guys have a great day.
Let me give you my outro.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarvener.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true friend podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great day guys.
Bye.