A man leaving his house one day has a bizarre encounter with a cloud.
And then we take a look at the story of the Gattington Portal, a personal favorite of mine.
Four young college students on their way home from a rodeo tried to take a shortcut.
But instead, the shortcut takes them out of this world today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I'm still dealing with the effects of my rolled ankle.
Woke up today. My toes were numb.
And they were going numb.
I let it go on for a couple hours and I was like, "That's not good."
So I hobbled up to the doctor office.
Got checked out by my doctor. My doctor has those eyes.
She's actually my backup doctor. I have like my main doctor and then there's this backup doctor.
I see her once in a while.
I'm sitting there. My little toes, he's all numb.
And the backup doctor walk. I'm sure she has an official title. Don't remember her name.
But she walks in the office and she has those wolf eyes, like those penetrating blue eyes.
And every time I see her, I'm a little speechless. It's so weird.
She walks in and I feel like a deer that's like walking through the woods.
And she does this all the time. She kind of, she doesn't say anything.
She opens, the door opens up. Backup doctor kind of walks into the room.
She kind of turns around the door and she makes eye contact with me.
And she's completely silent as she's like moving towards me.
And then she sits down and she goes, "Hi, I'm wolf woman, the doctor."
But for those like five seconds where she walks in silently, she makes eye contact with you.
You feel, you, there's just like this primordial fear.
She's a good doctor. I'm not knocking her for her supernatural ability to frighten me.
But anyway, she sat down. She felt that she was like feeling my toes and she checked the pulse
and everything like that. And she's, because I was afraid my toes were going to fall off,
that I had some circulation issue and she's like, "Nah, nah, you're fine."
So there you go. That was a great afternoon.
And she's like, "You can't do anything for it. You just got to heal."
That story had nothing to do with anything we're going to talk about.
Let's go ahead. Oh, and one last thing, one last thing.
Also, we got a new Patreon supporter, Ash Knotts. I know Ash Knotts.
She's a, I guess I would say friend of mine. I've only met her a couple of times, but she's pretty cool.
She's also a director and she also directed me in a short film that should be coming out any day now.
So when that happens, I'll tell you guys about it.
Tell you guys where you can watch it. It'll probably hit the film festival circuit for a while.
And then me and the dude who were in the movie, we already planned this.
I hadn't told Ash and Dan this yet, but we're going to talk about the movie on an episode of
Dead or Abba Radio and one of the special episodes because there was a ghost when we were shooting.
It was either a ghost or a hobo on the set. Maybe both. Maybe a ghost hobo,
but I have a ton of crazy stories from four hours of shooting this short horror film that Ash directed.
And when the movie comes out, we'll do a special. I'll tell you all about the ghost
and how it almost got killed by a spider and almost fell out of a house and all the sorts of stuff.
So, but anyways, so thank you, Ash. Thank you to all the Patreon to have supported the show.
Let's go ahead and get started with the episode now. Let's hop on the Carbentercopter.
It's been a couple of days we haven't used the Carbentercopter. I can't really walk anyways.
Let's hop on the Carbentercopter and I'm going to fly while you work the pedals
because my feet hurt. My one foot hurts, but I'm just like a baby at this point.
I'm like, oh, I can't move my legs. So I'm flying and you're sitting down and you're,
I'm assuming there's pedals on a helicopter. I have no idea. I don't think it's actually
pedal powered. You're like, oh, upper body workout. But anyways, we're flying all the way back
to the year 1975. We are going to Long Island, New York, truly near the city that never sleeps.
And we land. Your arms are all, your arms are all sore and I'm like, carry me out.
Carry me out. So you pick me up and now you're carrying me out of helicopter.
Like Wolverine and Professor X put me down into a hover chair and now we're like, oh,
thanks. We're floating around Long Island. We're specifically going to Oyster Bay.
And on this day, this is a summer day. There's a science teacher, local science teacher named Tom
Deer Cole. I never said that name out loud. Deer Cole. Deer Cole, maybe it doesn't matter.
Sounds like Steve Erkel. Anyways, so Tom's like, oh, he's all goofy, high suspenders. He walks out.
I never didn't even, didn't even think it was anything like that. He walks out of his house,
big glasses. He's like, yeah, I can't wait to get to work. I'm going to blow something up.
He's not a terrorist. He's not a terrorist. He's a science teacher. I should have explained that
before him talking about blowing stuff up through like making potions and stuff, not like rigging
bombs. He's like, oh, I can't wait to kill all my enemies. So he's not a terrorist. He's a science
teacher. He's a high school science teacher. Tom Deer Cole walks out of his house and he's
getting in his car. And it's then when he looks up in the sky and he sees like a little black cloud
floating there. He's like, well, that's weird. According to my calculations, what accent is
that to? That's like hillbilly. He's like, that's weird. According to my calculations, clouds shouldn't
do that. And so the clouds kind of float in there and he notices first off, it's a bright sunny day.
He sees all the clouds in the sky and he sees this one particular black cloud, but it's much lower
than the other clouds in the sky. And then he notices something even more unusual. It's flying
against the wind. He's like, that's bizarre. He's flying against the wind. And then it starts to
lower towards him. Morning. This is the morning. This isn't at a spooky, spooky night. He's not
in a graveyard. He's just walked out of his house and he's watching this black cloud start to lower
itself towards him. And as it's lowering towards him, he notices it stops being like it originally
was like a round globulous shape. So just like this big lumpy cloud. But then it starts to get bigger
and change shape. So it's descending and it's getting closer and it's changing shape. And
eventually he says, he described it as an abstract curved vapor. So it's basically, it almost seems
like it's making some sort of real shape. It's no longer just like a little fluffy cloud with a
carabare on it. It's like this MC Escher designed the cloud and it's still coming towards him.
And then eventually it gets to within spinning distance of him. So it's quite close. And then
he sees, he pulls out his calculator and he's calculating this. He's like, oh, maybe Laura
will love me now that I found this new cloud. I'll name it after her. And he sees the cloud a little
like, he describes it as lips. Like he sees like a little gap appear in the front of the cloud.
And it goes, and he's like, it looked like it sucked in. Like I actually saw a little gap up here.
And then it looked like it had the reflex of sucking something in. He's afraid now because
now it's completely unnatural. First you could be like, well, maybe the wind was pressing against
it and making it small and maybe it was black because it was a tar cloud or whatever. But once
he saw a little mouth appear and go, eh, you know, there's no explaining that. And there's no
explaining what happened next. He's standing on the ground, the clouds in the air. And when I said
spinning distance, I was literal because then it goes, and spits water on Tom slipping in it.
And then it just fades away into nothing. So he's drenched. His car is drenched. And he runs inside
and takes off his wet clothes, puts on some dry clothes, and then puts the wet clothes in a bag,
gets in his car and drives to his high school science lab. And he starts running tests on his
clothes. And he is able to tell the pH level from the liquid on his clothes that it's water.
So it's fit water. I think the first thing, if I was walking down the street and a cloud appeared
and started following me on the street, I'm walking a little bit faster. I can't even walk
right now. I'm using my crutch and hobbling the clouds getting closer. I'm like, oh no, not today,
not today. It's getting closer and closer to me. I'm like, where's my friends who carry me in a
helicopters? And then it starts spitting on me. My first fear would be like, I'm going to melt or
turn into a cloud. Like there's, it spilled some sort of chemical on me that's going to have a
horrible effect. It's not just water, but it was apparently just water. It's considered a cryptid,
and it's known as the sky spitter. And it's the only time it's ever been seen. Or I guess a more
app description is it might be the only time someone's ever survived an encounter with this thing.
No, it's probably the only time it's ever been seen. There's a, I mean, I don't know how it could
kill you unless you were in the Arctic and you're like, I'm all bundled up. Don't have to worry about
anything. And then then clouds start spitting on you and you freeze to death. But I think that
this is one of the stories that either he made it up completely, somebody else made it up,
which having the last name, the oracle, might be a little bit of a clue that it's made up. I never
said that name out loud until I was reading it. Either he made it up, someone else made it up,
or it's true. Those are, with these type of stories, those are really where you're at. And
it's really hard to kind of debunk that. I mean, it defeats all logic that a cloud could spit on
somebody. But I mean, you know, where do things have happened? I think if you believe in stuff like
ghosts and bigfoot and aliens, a cloud, a cloud chasing someone, spitting on him. But it would
be interesting to find out, like, is there a phenomenon that he could have mistaken it for?
That's always, I guess, the fourth thing that the event actually happened, but it didn't,
it wasn't the phenomenon he thought it was. Maybe he doesn't know it, but he's a real-life
Charlie Brown character whenever he gets sad, a little dark cloud appears over his head.
Maybe he's a toon. We don't know these things. All we know is that one day Tom Deerkel walked out
of his house and got spit on by a cloud. I wonder if we ever wash those clothes. I wonder if they're
like sitting behind like a glass frame in his house. Oh, moldy. They're all super moldy. They're
like 30, 40 years. Actually, they're older than me. They'd be 43 years old now, just 43 years old,
a black mold growing on these things. He's like sitting on my lap, grandkids, and I'll tell you
about the time that a cloud spit on me. And they're like, "No, grandpa. No, not again." He's like,
"Smell it. Smell the black mold. Let's go ahead and move on to our next story." He's married to Laura.
We finally got together. Our next story is a personal favorite of mine. It's a story. I think
I heard it on Mysterious Universe a long time ago. I actually really, really like this story.
Let's go ahead and hop back in the carbonar copter and we're flying around. You carry me back in
the carbonar copter. We're looking out for clouds. We have cloud bursting. Actually, no, that makes
more clouds, doesn't it? We're flying around. We're trying to avoid clouds. The little black
clouds are chasing us. We outmaneuver them. We're actually going back in time a little bit further.
We're going back to the year 1972. So, the clouds are shaking their fists at us as we disappear
into the time portal. We'll spit you next time. So, we're back in time now. It's 1972. We're going
to Utah. Welcome to Utah, the big square state. And it's flat. And there's a bunch of Latter-day
Saints there. I actually heard that they're going by the name Mormon now. They're just like, "I give
up." When I was a kid, it was an insult called Mormons Mormons. They went by Latter-day Saints
and nowadays they're just like, "Whatever. That's the term that sticks around." We're flying our
helicopter through Utah. And we are going, "You know what? I'm going to kick back in this one.
I'm going to shrink myself down to a little dude. I'm going to squeeze into the back seat of this car."
What? What am I talking about? Okay. Okay. No.
Okay. I'm going to be just watching this whole thing. I'm going to place you in the driver's seat
of the car. I'm not going to fit in the back seat. No matter how much I shrink, my leg's still going
to hurt. I'm not going on the journey with you on this one. I will, I'll be somewhere. Just
imagine that. I make you get in the car, okay? It's what I'm trying to get at. And you are in
the car with four girls, four young college students. I know some of you, some of you,
your anxiety is already kicking in, being trapped in a car with four people. But see you later.
I wave to you from the side of the road and your car takes off. You're driving. I'll have you drive
down this road. Now the point is, is that this car had four young women in it. And this is where we
start to kind of run into a bit of problems with the story. I'm not going to address them here and
there, but I got to get this one out of the way. Sometimes the four girls are named. Sometimes
they're given fake names and sometimes they're given relationships, like the driver and her sister
and then the sister's friend and then the friend's cousin or something like that. That varies from
account to account. But in this version, we're going to just start it off saying it's four unnamed
girls in the car and you. So you and four unnamed girls, you're like, Hey, what's your name? And
just to look at you, just drive the car. You four girls are driving home from a rodeo.
If you're like, Jason, I hate rodeos and I don't like being crammed in the cars. Sorry,
you're driving home from a rodeo. You and these four girls have just had a great time at the rodeo
coming home. Now you have to get back to college. You guys currently attend Southern Utah University
and the girls have a dorm mistress dorm master, whatever you're called, who is very, very punctual.
If you're not home by 10pm, she locks all the doors. You can't get in or out and she hunts them
one by one with an X, but no, they have to be home by 10pm. Otherwise they'll have to sleep in their
car or maybe it's your place. So you're driving as fast as you can or as slow as you can and you're
driving through the Utah battle lands. I think it's the battle of the whole state of battle land.
It's just one giant hostile desert. It's America's Australia driving through Utah. And as they're
driving by Highway 56, they see a little town of Modena and it's like a tiny, tiny town. It's
like a one stoplight town, at least it was back then. And the girls make an executive decision.
There's no way we're going to get home before 10 unless we take a shortcut. So they remembered,
they heard at least, there's a shortcut if they drive through the Gattington Canyon. Now Gattington
Canyon is part of it is paved, but some of it you're going to have to do a little off, off-road.
And I think they're in like a Chevy Nova or a Chevy Impala or something like that. It's a new
car. It's like 1971, new to them nowadays and piece of junk. But you figure, yes girls, I can get you
home before 10pm. We will take a shortcut through the Gattington Canyon. And so the car goes off
onto like a little side street, start driving into the canyon. And after about a half hour of
driving through this twisting canyon, no moon in the sky, it's completely dark. You see the canyon
walls on both sides of you and you're like, oh, it's kind of spooky. But I'm sure this is a shortcut,
right? But after a while, the paved road, it starts to just turn to nothing, cracked asphalt and then
nothing. And then there's a sheer canyon wall in front of the car. So at this point, the girls
are like, great, we're never going to get home in time. We're going to have to sleep at your house
and you're like, yes, we're flan all along. But in reality, the girls are like, great, we're going
to be stuck when we're not going to be able to get home. We're going to have to sleep in the car.
So you bust the U-turn and you're coming back through the canyon. And as you're driving through
the canyon, that's when you start to notice there's a moon in the sky. And you're like, what?
My high school science teacher, Tom DeErkel told me that moons only appear once a month. Well,
not like that. They don't show up once a month. But if we can't go from one moon to,
we can't go from no moon to one moon in a couple hours. And the girls look at you and they're
like, what are you talking about? You're like, never mind, never mind. And but they also notice
that it is weird there is a full moon when just earlier there was no moon. And when they come out
of the canyon, it's no longer like this desert in front of them. There's wheat fields, beautiful,
beautiful wheat fields shining in the moonlight, I guess being reflected by the moonlight. However
you want to say. And there's a giant ponderosa pine out in the distance. Now they go and you,
because you're in this story, go, let's drive to the tree. Maybe we'll find something over there.
Okay. I mean, these people are driving through canyons trying to find the shortcut. So whatever,
they think they figure nature will lead them home. They drive towards the ponderosa tree. And
it's just a tree. I mean, you can see from the distance, I don't know if they expected it to be
an elevator or like a spaceship, they drive by the tree. And as they're driving by this giant tree,
they see lights down the road. Yes, civilization, let's go there guys. You continue, you just do
what they say and you're driving on the road and you see lights. It looks like a little roadhouse,
looks like a little bar restaurant. So you're like, figure we'll get to bite, eat,
something to drink, talk to these girls for a while, then we'll get back in the car. They're
not getting home by now anyways. But also you're lost. Actually, that's not what they're thinking.
They weren't thinking about eating. Back to their regular story, they're like, where are we?
Where are we? We're surrounded by wheat. They weren't hungry. Sorry, I was imagining my own
self in the story. They go there because they're like, we're lost. We have to find directions.
Let's go there and ask someone for directions. And you're like, and get something to eat. And
you're like, yes, sure, you can get something to eat. Just make it snappy. So apparently Jughead
is also in this car trying to get hamburgers all the time. He did that, right? Or was that wimpy?
Anyway, both of them, Jughead and Wimpy are in the car as well. Driving down the road and you get to
the burger joint and the girl said that they could see this neon sign. They couldn't understand what
it said. It was all just squiggly. And they're like looking out and they're like, oh, it's just,
I don't understand that language. Maybe it's some art deco design. But there's much people kind of
milling about in the parking lot. And there's some bizarre looking cars in the parking lot as well.
Egg shaped vehicles, three wheels. And so one girl leans her head out the car window and she goes
to ask someone, hey, do you guys know where we're at? And I'm like, can I get directions? And you're
like, oh, can I get a number two, please? Diet Coke. But as you're yelling your order out and as
she's asking for directions, the people in the parking lot turn around and the girl starts screaming
right in your ear, screaming at the top of her lungs. And then she just starts screaming, go,
go, go, go, go. And you don't know what it is, but you don't see the people in the parking lot,
like you physically saw them, but you don't see their faces. Just her screaming in your ear. You
hit the gas, car takes off. And as the cars flying on the road, the girl who saw them starts
screaming. And then another girl also looks out the window and sees what's out the window. She
starts screaming as well. So you're driving on the road and you're like, what'd you see? What'd you
see? And they're like, just go, go, go. They're not human. They're not human. And you're like,
gulp. This isn't good. Now that is when you hear. And you look in your rear view window,
and there's four of those egg shaped cars buzzing towards you.
And they're catching up. Now, you saw the cars were weird looking in the parking lot,
but you are 100% for sure. These aren't cars at all. Never seen a vehicle like this before.
Going through the desert road. Eggmobiles right after you. You make an executive decision.
You're like, calm down, hysterical women. Calm down. I'm in charge now.
Bust a U-turn. I don't know. He might have been going the right way in the original story,
but in our version, you have to bust a U-turn because I just imagined it going in the wrong
direction. Now you're racing towards the eggmobiles. Eggmobiles. There's a lot of chasing in this
episode. I didn't plan it this way. Eggmobiles spin out. Now the following you, you made an
executive decision. You want to get back to the canyon because at least you know that area. So
coming after you and you go into the canyon and the eggmobiles are right behind you. Start.
It's like trench around. Eggs are flying at you from the top of the canyon walls. Oh no. No.
They go into the canyon and then they come back out of the canyon and the engine dies. It doesn't
explode, but I don't know how to make the sound effect of an engine just going. So it flies up.
Airbags to play. They didn't have airbags back then. Cars were death traps and three of the tires
are completely shredded. So you just kind of hobble to a hop and I'm standing there with my crutch
going. It took you long enough. And they start hobbling and we all have to hobble because the
car is totally inoperative and it's miles away from Modena. So eventually you have to pick me up.
You and the four girls have to carry me like I'm an Egyptian prince all the way to Modena
where we call law enforcement. At that point officer Vic Lundquist, officer comes out and goes,
"Hmm, that's weird." So your story of this thing that you told me about, I have some questions
about it. Shoot. Not literally. Not literally. Cops, I'll grab it and it's gone. Shoot. Shoot. Ask
your questions. He goes, "Well, it's weird because I only see your car tracks go a short while
from Modena into the desert but then there's no tire tracks after that." And I noticed that
other stuff with tire tracks. And I noticed that one of your hubcaps is missing but no officer here
was ever able to locate your hubcap. Right. And you're like, "Why are you writing down such stupid
details in your police report?" And Vic Lundquist goes, "Well, because people will be asking these
questions whether or not the story is true 30 years from now." And then the camera pans up to
the night sky. There's no moon. Roll credits. That's the story of the Gattington Canyon time portal.
Now, it's one of my favorite stories but let's go ahead and step back for a second. There are some
glaring inconsistencies in that story. Let's tear it apart and then put it back together again.
Because I think there's a reason why this story is popular or it really why it was crafted in first
place. It's possible the story is true but it has some interest and we'll get to that in a second.
It's well but it has some interesting weaknesses to it. One, Vic Lundquist has been retconned
to Victoria Lindquist. So some people have said, "Oh, that was just an error. It was actually a
female police officer who came to the scene." So it was never Vic Lundquist. It was Victoria Lindquist.
And that came about because someone was Google searching to see if there was really a Victor
Lundquist who lived in Utah at that time and apparently there's someone named Victor Lundquist
and Victoria Lindquist both living in the Utah and the area around that time. So that's a weird
retcon. I'm kind of attacking these backwards. Two, every version of the story ends with the police
report saying there's no tire tracks from where the car left highway 65 in the first place.
There was no... Which we can... That one is stupid to begin with because the cars broke down miles away
from Modena in every version of the story. So if a cop came out and was like chewing a piece of
wheat and you're like, "Where'd you get that wheat from?" There's no wheat in Utah and he's like,
seriously an alien. He's like, "Ah." Now a new cop. Cop shows up and he's chewing gum and he's watching
tire tracks and he goes, "That's weird." Tire tracks ended just feet off of the highway and you're like,
"We just walked five miles. You can go out there and see that our car is there." And the cop would
be like, "Oh, that mystery solved." Wind blew the tire tracks away. That's such a stupid part of the
mystery. The hubcap missing. There's a couple other ones that are like tire tracks, like didn't
appear here and they should have been here. But who cares? There went to an alien portal. I don't
expect there to be like good year marks perfectly along the road all the way to the alien portal.
The fact that their car broke down near the canyon should be proof that they left the road. It's such
bizarre detail that comes up in every single story. The moon. There's two versions of the story where
all the details are the same, but in some of them it was a full moon. They went to a world with no moon.
And then in the version I told you, which seems to be the most popular one, there's no moon
and they go to a world with a full moon. Oh, let me tell you about the egg cars as well. A lot of
people. This story, the earliest posting of this story online was 2006 and apparently it happened
in 1972. Now, sometimes again, it could be a hoax. Sometimes it could be written in some obscure UFO
book that was just hanging out at used bookstores for 20, 30 years and someone bought one and read it
and put it online. That's always possible. That's happened a couple times, like Sam the Sanddown clown
was kind of the same thing. That was an old UFO report. So it's not unusual to have stories show
up later, but the earliest version of this story that appeared online was from 2006. That website
is down. So 2007 is the earliest verifiable. You can pull up the website and look at it. And that
was 2007. There is a concept car that has an egg shaped design with three wheels on it. And people
go, whoa, that's the car that the girl saw. That car, that design of that car wasn't released until
2010. So usually when you read articles about the Gattington portal, they always will show this concept
art. But here's the problem with that. They, yes, there is a car on earth that is made to look like
an egg with three wheels, but it's not piloted by aliens in a diner. Like that is just a bizarre
coincidence. It's not showing that they traveled into the future. I don't think unless Utah, if
it took place in the future enough that Utah has wheat and people have turned into monsters,
they're not driving around a car that was designed in 2010. Unless that was like a retro
auto festival where people are like, Hey, let's drive cars from a thousand years ago. If that
much change has happened, why would they be driving cars designed in 2010? So that detail is just a
weird coincidence. Another thing is like, they have so these versions of these stories have so much
dialogue where they're like, Becky said, slam it. So I slammed it. And then she's like, look out,
here comes another one. And then as I turned and I said, Oh, no, here comes another one. The chick
next to me goes, drive, Becky drive. I think they're all in Becky in this version. There's tons
of dialogue in this story, but not a single version says what the people look like. They just say
they're not human. It's like someone wrote a young adult novel and put this all in there.
One of the most interesting details though, is there's no such place officially named the
Gattington Canyon. Now it's one of those stories that like I said, I've enjoyed for a long, long
time, but I never looked into it. And someone else has this website called the debunker files or
something like that. Then that website made some ridiculous arguments against it as well. Like
I was like, that's kind of dumb. But one of the stellar pieces I got from it is there is no place
called the Gattington Canyon in that area because the city of Modena is real. It's a tiny town.
There's two canyon ranges though. There are two canyon ranges. Officially, none of them are named
Gattington Canyon. The reason why, and this is really telling about why I think this story exists,
assuming it's fake, assuming it's fake. The reason why it's known as the Gattington Canyon
portal, the reason why it's referred to as the Gattington Canyon, is Gattington Canyon is a local
name that the Mormons use for that area. The only time you see reference to that is with this story
and the story from the Book of Mormon about a dude named Gattington who led an army of thieves
that were attacking the Nephites, or they were the Nephites. It's this Mormon story. It's this Book
of Mormon story where before Jesus died and came to America, there was a bunch of people like,
"Hey, now here, there were a bunch of people hanging out here." But they weren't the Nephites.
They actually have the Mormon Church actually has an archaeological team dedicated to finding
proof, physical proof of the Book of Mormon in America because they have these giant war machines.
They have these ancient empires. It was a super advanced civilization that waged war across America.
And a lot of times in the Book of Mormon, they ride horses around. There were no horses in America,
so then it turns out they were riding tapers or something, like big old pigs. But anyways,
anyways, I just said an episode on the Book of Giants, so I can't really talk trash about
the Book of Mormon. The only time you hear about Gattington Canyon is in reference to the Book of
Mormon and a group of evil thieves and an army of evil thieves robbing people. And this story.
So I think this is the origin of this story. I think it is a, I think this is where it came from.
I bet dollar to donuts that this is a urban legend. It's a Mormon urban legend, basically. I think
it's probably something that was told in youth groups to scare people because this story has a
moral that is not readily recognizable when you first go through it. The moral is,
do not stay out past curfew. Very, very intro-ed, because when you first hear it,
I didn't pick up on that. When I first heard it, I was like, oh, that's fascinating. You know,
go in another dimension. And then you hear it over and over again. But when I become more,
become more skeptical doing the show, because I just have to read so much of this stuff.
I'm reading it, I'm thinking, there is a moral to the story, like so many stories we cover. Don't
play in the water, so, you know, a dolphin might get you. We'll come up with this legend. Don't
go into the woods, kids, or this guy who makes you walk backwards will get you. Whatever they are.
This particular one is don't stay late anywhere. Get home before curfew is the moral of the story.
Then you would have never been chased by these monsters. And I think one of the reasons why I
think that's clear is that the monster, nobody dies. It's a urban legend you can tell at a youth
group at a lock-in, a bunch of 13-year-old kids, they're not going to have nightmares. People get
away. You don't know what the monsters look like, which in reality, if you knew the dialogue of the
people in the car, and this happened 30 years ago, you would, someone would have said, "Yeah,
they look like they're pig people," or they had giant eyes, or they looked like clouds wearing
clothes. It would have been something with it rather than, "We don't know what they look like."
So I think one of my favorite interdimensional stories involving a bunch of young women getting
sucked into another dimension and having outrun a bunch of aliens, I think also intrigues a bunch
of 13-year-olds in a locked church late at night, because their youth minister goes,
and then the cops couldn't find tire tracks leading off the road, and the kids are like,
"Oh no, I want to go home. I want to go home." I think that's the origin of this story.
But maybe I'm wrong. Maybe my skeptical side is wrong, and I'm tearing apart the truth.
Someone could tell you the truth, and you could be just as skeptical. Find little holes in it.
Make them sweat a bit. Very, very possible. I think the interesting thing about this story, too,
is that you figure it has to happen both ways. If we can slip into their reality, couldn't they
slip into ours? We talk about UFOs being from other dimensions and things like that, and my ghosts
may actually be from other dimensions. We're not actually seeing dead people. But if four girls can
make a wrong turn down the wrong canyon on the wrong night and end up in an alien world, could
they do the same? Have they done the same? We talk about missing people all the time, and most
missing people's stories have a rational explanation. But at a certain point, you have to say, "I can't
explain how this person went missing." They just disappeared. So are there stories of young alien
creatures that look human at first glance? These guys looked like they were human, at least humanoid.
How many times have one of theirs crossed over to our world, turned a corner, appeared in the middle
of a city, surrounded by monsters, not understanding any of the writing on any of the billboards?
And if that's happened, and statistically it would have had to happen, if it can happen one
way it'll happen the other way. Did they get away? Was that young group of aliens from another
dimension driving home from their gloop glorp trying to beat the clock and they got lost in our
world? Would they have simply been chased off by men in Harleys and a guy in a Toyota pickup truck?
Or would they have been cut down, blown up, captured and sent to the US military?
Yeah, probably. And I think that's what would have happened to those young girls as well,
if those egg-shaped vehicles had caught them. The story wouldn't be told in Mormon youth groups.
Their story would only be found in military logs and medical texts in an alien dimension.
DeadRabberRadio.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
Twitter is @deadrabberradio. DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true
crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.