What happens when a heavy metal musician meets Satan?
We take a look at a man who will do whatever it takes to save his fellow Americans.
And then we travel to Japan to take a look at a bizarre story that happened in the 80s.
Two hikers get lost in the mountains.
But three hikers are found today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover.
So we're gonna slide right into this. At second base, we're running dust like flying everywhere.
It's all dirty and stuff. And we're just sliding into...
Our first story is on second base for some bizarre reason. You can't slide into first, right?
I don't know. I don't play sports. First off, I want to give a shout out to our newest Patreon, Petite Bourgeois.
Petite Bourgeois. I believe that's how you pronounce it.
Thank you so much for supporting this show. You are going to be our navigator, our pilot for this episode.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. Just hope to get the word out about the show really really helps out a lot.
I want to take this time to highlight some people who have been doing that. Jim Jam, Flim Flam. Yep.
I saw your comment. I was actually investigating something on that website and I saw that you left that.
I really really appreciated it. It's one in a million that I would stumble across it.
But I wanted to appreciate that. Also, I want to give a heads up to some people who have left reviews recently on the show.
Kate Imkate really really loved your review. G4 75 75 75. Thank you so much.
TESU 8 and H Sucker. Thank you so much for leaving the review. Someone else left a review,
but it was just their name was Gibberish, but the review was very nice. So thank you so much.
That's another way you guys can support the show. Really really appreciate that. But Petite Bourgeois,
let's give you those keys to that carpenter copter. You are going to take us up in the air.
We are flying above everything else. We are flying out to this dude's hospital.
We're just gonna land on this hospital roof. Other medical helicopters are flying around.
They're like clear the airspace get out of her way. We're like, no, we got a story to look at.
Now we're walking through the hospital and we see a dude laying on a bed all.
And we go up to the door. We're wearing like doctor clothes.
They wear normal clothes, but we also now we're wearing lab coats and stuff.
And we're walking around. We got stethoscopes and we're like nurse.
What's wrong with this dude? And the nurse looks at his chart and she's like,
he's he has COVID-19. He's dying. He's actually in really, really bad shape.
So this guy we're looking at his name is Will Carroll.
He's 46 years old. He's a drummer.
For the band Death Angel. It's a thrash metal band.
I guess they were started in the 80s. They're still pretty big in the scene now.
They were just on a tour in Europe. And as they're touring Europe,
like airports are gonna shut down, they're like, come on, Will, hurry up, run, run.
He's like running. He has to do a roll underneath the gate.
They get on their plane. They leave their on tour with two other bands.
But some of the members of the bands got the illness.
Now, Will Carroll was overweight, probably was into the best health to begin with.
It knocks him out. Like literally he goes into a coma.
He's on a respirator. Things are not looking good for Will Carroll.
But after 12 day coma, he wakes up. He wakes up.
And so after he wakes up from his coma, he has this story to tell. He goes, I died.
I died, guys. This is what happened to me. I'm laying in my bed and I'm just like,
and then his soul left his body.
His soul is kind of floating around, floating around a bit and then starts to
get pulled into the earth. So his soul is being dragged down into the earth.
No. And then he meets Satan, who, and first off, the big shocking thing,
he's now he's in hell, right? That's that shocking thing. Number one.
Oh no, hell exists. And I'm in it. So that's surprising thing. Number one,
surprising thing. Number two, Satan is a woman.
So that may not surprise some of you. It would surprise me. It would surprise me.
I would assume Satan was like a dude. I would assume Satan. It's funny.
I wonder, I would assume Satan is a skinny dude.
And I would assume God was an old man, but he's kind of built.
Like he's wearing those robes and stuff like that.
But you imagine he's like, has the body of like Logan. Like he looks old,
but then if God took off his robes, he'd be hella yoked, right?
And then Jesus is probably like a wild, I imagine Jesus is kind of like a Brad Pitt
type of body, Fight Club Brad Pitt, where he's like kind of wiry and stuff like that.
But you know, he could throw down. I'll be honest, I edited out like three minutes of me
and describing Jesus's workout plan. Doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
The point is, is that it's surprising that Satan's a woman. I, it's surprising to me at least.
And then surprising thing number three, Satan punishes Will Carroll by turning him into a
quote, job of the hut like creature. Because he was being punished for his sin of sloth.
Wasn't like 600 pound life overweight, but he was like 350 pound life overweight.
He's a drummer. He just sits there all day long.
I'm sure he had really good upper body strength, but anything below the pecs was just like,
bull. So he turns into Satan, turns him into a job of the hut like creature for copyright reasons.
Satan can't actually turn him into job of the hut because Satan can still get sued.
Turns him into a job of the hut like creature and Will just sat there in this monstrous form
and began puking, just begin puking up volumes and volumes of blood.
Until he died again in hell and then woke up in a hospital bed back on earth.
Now that's awesome. Not awesome that he went to hell and got turned into a monster.
A non-copyrighted monster. It's awesome he survived. He actually celebrated his 47th
birthday on May 13th. And I love this quote. Quote, "I'm still going to listen to Satanic
Metal and I still love decide in bands like that." I'm assuming decide is like a Satanic or like a
dark band. Quote, "I'm still going to listen to Satanic Metal and I still love deciding bands
like that. As far as my personal life and my experiences of what I went through, I don't
I love this quote. I don't think Satan's quite as cool as I used to. So before I'd be sitting
there smoking a doobie with his friends back in the 80s, dude I bet you Satan's a cool dude.
And when we go to hell he'll be like, "Hey man, you guys rock. You guys are way cooler than these
demons that have been here for 10 million years. No, you humans are way cooler here.
Smoke some of the devil's hash." And then get blazed with the dark lord. Instead he went down,
Satan's a woman, turned him into a monster, threw his blood and died in hell. So I love that quote.
I don't think Satan's as cool as I used to. But interesting story, the man survived.
Possible near-death experience, possible just coma-driven nightmare. Either way it's terrifying.
Either way it's terrifying. But luckily he's back alive and Satan's still down there and she's like,
"Drats!" Kind of P.O. to this one got away. I would, I love the idea though that Satan will not
violate copyright. That Satan's eventually when Satan does try to destroy Earth, she's,
because now it's a woman, she's assembling her arming. We're like, "Hey, that kind of looks like,
that guy kind of looks like Darth Vader." She's like, "No, no, no, it's not Darth Vader.
It's a Darth Vader-esque armor." And we're like, "Wait a second. That armor over there kind of looks
like Doom's day from Superman comics." No, no, no, no, no, no, no. That is Day of Doom. That's an
original character. They're all, all of the demons are recolors of existing demons in pop culture.
Satan we know now is unimaginative and is very, very cautious of being sued.
Petite bourgeois. Let's hop into Jason Jalopy. We are leaving behind the hospital.
We're saying goodbye to Will Carroll again. Very, very glad that you made that out alive.
We are headed out to Michigan, Bay City, Michigan to be exact. It's May 17th, 2020.
So this story just took place what, a week ago? Two weeks ago? So we're driving through Bay City,
Michigan, here, our car drives by a house. Inside is a 70-year-old man named Jesse Theodore McFadden.
He is a man with a plan. Step one, steal an attack helicopter, steal an attack helicopter
from the local Coast Guard station. Now I'm going to say this. That's an ambitious step one, right?
Step one isn't, that might be the most ambitious step one I've ever seen. Like, step one isn't
break into the facility. Step one isn't even go on map quests and find out where the facility is.
Step one, take a helicopter, steal a helicopter from a Coast Guard station. I have no idea whether
or not this guy can actually fly, said copter, but he definitely believes he can. I'm sure he played
a lot of Microsoft Flight Simulator in 1998. He's ready to go. Step two, fly. Does the Coast Guard
even have attack helicopters? I mean, I know they have more than, like, whirly birds, but I don't
think they have, like, black hawks. He's going to steal an attack helicopter from a Coast Guard
station. Step two, fly to the local police station, which again, that's awesome, right?
This guy's plan is in results kind of nutty, but right there. He's stealing an attack helicopter,
and then it's not like Layla over two weeks. He's immediately taking off from the Coast Guard
station, flying over to the police station, attacking it with an attack helicopter. And the cops,
that's a scenario where the cops would be completely defenseless. Do you guys remember,
there was two big stories back in the 90s. We had Killdozer in South Park, Colorado, where the guy
had, over the course of months, taken a bulldozer and grafted armor onto it and started driving
through town and knocking houses over. And the cops finally had to, like, run up and, like, shoot
into the armor. Like, the bullets were bouncing off. He had, like, little, like, little eye slits,
and they finally had to take him out like that. And then back in the 90s, too, some dude stole a
tank from a National Guard, National Guard brigade or barracks or whatever. He's driving the tank
through LA, and it was the same thing. Like, he didn't shoot at anyone. He was just like,
crushing cars. All of this footage is available online. I don't know if the Killdozer is, but the
tank definitely was. They had to run up into the tank, open it up, and, like, they were thinking,
"Do we just throw grenades into it?" The guy, a cop finally got on the tank, opened up the top,
and shot into it and killed him. But the police is much armor as they have nowadays.
They don't have an anti-aircraft weaponry. And their helicopters definitely aren't armed. So if
an attack helicopter came flying over a police station, that's not good, right? It's just going
to lay into it. Totally awesome explosions. As long as nobody dies, the explosions are awesome.
Helicopter will then leave behind the burning wreckage of the police department. There'll be
one cop, like, crawling out of the burning wreckage, and he pulls up his radio and he's like...
And then he dies. I couldn't come up with anything cool for him to say. He just dies. So anyways,
the helicopter now flies away from the burning police station. Now it's going to fly to the
local hospital. This is step three. This is really the final step. Helicopter flies to the hospital.
But this time the attacks are precision. You see, one of those missiles is going to go
open the door because the doors have like the little sensor on them.
Flies to the hospital. Flies through the hallway. Passes an eternity ward, stops, looks at the
key little babies. Continues to fly. The hospital crashes right into the power supply.
Of said hospital. Sparks are shooting out and everything. People are running in slow motion
from the sparks. So all the power leaves the hospital. Then helicopter's going to land.
And again, this man is 70 years old. This is a very eventful... This is an eventful,
like, two month long thing for people of good health. This guy's going to do it in the morning.
10 a.m. to be precise. We're going to get to that. His plan is to do all this stuff, hop out of the
helicopter, walk into the hospital. There's going to be, like, because all the power's out now. So
he's just going to be able to go and he's going to be able to open all of the doors and all of the
COVID-19 people who've been locked up. No, I want to see my family. I want to see my families again.
Let me out. I'm still healthy. He's going to go. His plan was... His plan... All of that stuff.
All of that stuff was because he believed that the hospitals were imprisoning people with coronavirus.
He wanted to let them go. He's like, "Run free, my friends! Run free! Return home! Go back to your
job at the retirement center!" And people are like, "Ugh!" And they're coughing through the
streets of Michigan. That was his plan. That was his plan. Now, I don't know if he thought that COVID-19
was a hoax, or if he thought people were, "What? You're sick with an illness and they're keeping
you prisoner for 14 days because you went to the hospital and you want to be treated?
Hogwash!" People are like, "No, no, I really need this. Will Carroll is on a ventilator." And
this guy, Jesse, comes in. He's like, "You're free!" Pulls the ventilator out. And then Will Carroll
is permanently a copyright free monster in hell. He's like, "No." His plan was to "free" all the
people currently being treated for COVID-19. So you're going, "Jason, okay, some crazy old man
made a police. What did he do? Did he post it online? And the cops are involved?" And it was like,
5150? No. No, no. If this was just a manifesto, it'd be funny, right? At 10 a.m. in the morning,
he calls up Jesse McFadden, calls up 911. I don't understand why this was part of his plan.
But he calls up 911 and says, "Step 1." And he tells them what he's about to do. He goes,
"I'm going to go steal a helicopter. I'm going to kill all the cops. I'm going to fly to the
hospital. Missile's going to fly around the hallways. Shuts off the power." I don't know why
he did that, but he definitely put himself on the radar. So you're thinking, "Maybe he just
wanted to commit suicide by cop. Maybe..." No. Let me finish. He then drives to the Coast Guard station
and tries to hack into the control panel. It sounds like a Skrillex song, but it's not.
It's him trying to try multiple keypad codes. And you can imagine the Coast Guard guards standing
there just a couple feet away being like, "Why is this super old man trying to hack our system?
Old man has a skateboard. His hat's on backwards." He's like, "Solve this in a movie.
So, this is a documentary called Hackers. Why isn't this working?" And so then Jesse turns to the
Coast Guard guy who's obviously incredibly puzzled by what he's seeing. And Jesse goes,
"Open the gate." The guard's like, "No, I'm going to open the gate." You just pulled up in your car.
You try to hack your way into our system. I'm not letting you in. And then Jesse goes,
"If you don't let me in, I'm going to ram my car through your gate." And at that point,
the Coast Guard guy must have looked at the car, looked at the gate, and laughed and said,
"Go ahead. This gate is designed to stop Iraqi tanks from coming through. I am sure your Ford
Taurus will knock this down." He does leave though. He ends up leaving the gate. He doesn't decide to
run it down. Cops track him down. Catch him at a gas station. He was inside getting snacks. He was
in the car after trying to steal an attack helicopter. He's like, "Ah, you know what I really want?
I want some Hostess Zingers." So while he's inside getting Hostess Zingers, the cops pull up because
now they know what his car looks like. They'd gotten the 911 call earlier and he had a previous
to rest for fleeing and eluding the police back in 2011. So they knew what he looked like, but now
like they can figure out like what car he was in, what area he was in. He's inside the gas station
buying snacks. There's nothing that makes you hungrier than trying to destroy a police station
and a hospital at the same time. He comes outside the cops, finds a Mossberg shotgun,
which is the coolest of all shotguns, in his car and there's a bit of a scuffle. With a 70-year-old
man again, the cops finally do subdue this ancient mumra-like character and he is fine. Really, his
what he was charged with was possession, felon possession of a firearm. Because you can pull
up to a Coast Guard gate and go, "Let me in!" and you can punch buttons on their control panel.
To be fair, if I did that, I might be facing different charges, but when you're 70 years old,
they're probably like, "Oh, you rascally old coot." But anyway, so that was Jesse McFadden's plan.
He could get 45 days in jail and it might be a life sentence for him. Hopefully not.
Hopefully he ends up doing whatever, actually it's probably longer than 45 days, felon possession
of a firearm. He might get charged with terrorist threats, but so far it's just been the firearm
charges. Hopefully maybe this will be, he'll come out of jail and he'll be like, "Whoa,
those 45 days in jail, it's sure gonna be stopped being an insane old man!" Now I'm gonna go on and
become like, I don't know, just a normal dude who does normal dude stuff and then he'll start
going to Michaels and buying like, batched buckets to resell on eBay or some nonsense like that.
We can, we can, that is lame of a life as that is, that's far better than a man trying to
destroy a, destroy a hospital to release everyone COVID-19. In Petit Boujewal, let's take the
Dead Rabbit-Durgeable. We're gonna take a long slow trip from Michigan to Japan. We are headed out
to take a look at a truly bizarre story. Found a store on Reddit, so I want to give credit to the
person who researched all this stuff, got all these notes together for me. It was a user named
Apis Serena. Apis Serena? I don't know, but thank you so much for doing all the legwork on this.
Petit Boujewal, we're bringing our blimp, we're bringing our Dead Rabbit-Durgeable nice and low.
We're flying over Hokkaido, Japan. It's July 24th, 1989. We're specifically going to a place known as
Asahideki Mountain, July 24th, 1989. So apparently this area is immensely beautiful. It's basically a
collection of biomes on one hiking trail. There's like active volcanoes and there's lush forests,
beautiful hiking, but it's also, the weather can change very quickly. It's easy to get lost. There's
a place where there's two boulders. Well, there's two places with two boulders, right? And if you
turn left at the wrong place, the wrong boulder, you're basically doomed. So there's like landmarks,
but it's not really a landmark. If there's two different landmarks, they look the same. So
you could go up the mountain, find, and I guess there's some like really like steep drop-offs and
everything like that. You can go up the mountain just fine, but if you're coming down and the
weather's a little misty, it's a little foggy, and you see one of the boulders, you may turn left there,
where the real boulder you're supposed to turn at is, you know, farther away and you end up
in a totally different location. So people, they recommend people doing this hike on the buddy system.
It's very, very easy to get lost, which I mean, I guess then just both of you get lost, which is
what happened here. July 24th, 1989, two mountaineers go missing, and the local search and rescue is
like, we got to find these guys, right? That is our job. People are like, no, can we just like
not find people today? They're like, we're searching rescue dude. Like you knew what you signed up for
literally, that's the name of the job. Fine, what? This job sucks. So as everyone gets in their rescue
helicopters, they're flying around, they're looking for these mountaineers. They come over like a flat
area, and they're in the sea, in their helicopter, giant letters. S-O-S. They're letters that mean
things. They're not just C-Q-Y. They see S-O-S. It's 16 feet long and 10 feet wide, this saying here.
Three logs high. I mean, it's massive undertaking to create this, but it allows, because you know,
there's fog and mist, you want to make this sign. Helicopter sees the S-O-S sign and they're like,
okay, this is perfect. So they radio it in, ground crews come, helicopters still looking,
about two to three kilometers, which what, four to five miles from the S-O-S sign, they find the two
hikers. They've been missing for like a couple days. Helicopter lands, ground crew comes, take care of
them, make sure they don't have any injuries, take them home. And they're like, you guys are so lucky,
because we're looking all over the area, we're about to give up. Our captain does really like to
search and rescues. And these captains are on the background, he's like, I hate him. And he's just
shaking his head. But you're lucky that we found that S-O-S sign. And the two Mountaineers looked at
each other and they go, we didn't make an S-O-S sign. What? No, no, that wasn't us. Like, we were lost,
and we're glad that you guys came, don't drop us back off on the mountain. But we never made the S-O-S
sign. So when the search and rescue drops the dudes back off at home, not at their individual homes,
they're like, where do you live? Oh, I live a couple blocks away, helicopters like flying through
the streets. After they drop them off at like a ranger station or whatever, they sit and have a
little meeting and they go, okay, so we all saw the S-O-S sign, right? There wasn't some weird miracle.
We should go back up there, because there might be someone else there. But the thing was this,
if two people didn't make the S-O-S sign, one person definitely didn't make it. And there's also
no one else missing. I mean, it would have been a huge undertaking. These were birch logs. And if
you play Minecraft, just punching a birch tree just to get a one block of it, it takes a while.
So whoever was up there was able to cut down all of these trees, arrange them in the war to S-O-S.
It would have been quite the undertaking for two people. And there's no one else missing.
So who would have made this? But let's just not assume, even though our captain hates his job,
let's not assume that, oh, trees must have just fallen randomly. So they go back up there,
they start doing a ground search around the actual sign that says S-O-S. There's a skeleton.
Just laying there. Now it's so funny whenever I see stuff about people finding skeletons,
not that I'm amused at the fact that people dying to K. But I always imagine it's like
a skeleton from like House on Haunted Hill, where it's like the finger bones,
like the whole skeleton's there, right? Just laying there in the dirt. And I don't think that's
the case. I wonder what the cutoff is for a skeleton. Like if you find the skull, they'll say
they found the skull. If you found the skull and an arm bone, at what point does it become we found
a skeleton? Like does it have to be like 60% of the bone? I don't think the rescue team really
cares about the distinction. They're not like, hmm, we just found three human skulls, but no
skeletons. But I'm wondering if from some sort of, I wonder how they make the designation of
whether or not they report it as a skeleton is found there. Is it like half the body? Is it like
one third of the body? But anyways, that's an equiviling weird comment. They find a skeleton.
He's apparently he was mid xylophone playing with his ribs when they found him. Now that's bizarre,
because they definitely don't have anyone missing at all. No one left the hiking. No
skeletons are like, see you later. I'm gonna go hiking. So now they go, wait a second, we have
someone who's not recently missing, but this is a skeleton. So whoever it was probably died a while
ago, they could tell like some of it had been eaten. Some of the bones had been like, gnawed on by
animals. They find a tape recorder and I can play you some of it for you. I mean, it's in Japanese,
so you won't really know what it is, but I'm gonna play a bit of this audio recording here,
and then I'll tell you what it says.
So what it's saying is, I can't move from a top this cliff. There's different translations of this,
obviously. I've seen a couple different translations, but this is the one we're gonna go with.
I can't move from a top this cliff. SOS, please help. I am near where the helicopter was originally,
and I can't move further due to the bamboo brush being in the way. Please get me out of here.
And eventually a journalist looking into this, the rescue team didn't even find this. They found
a driver's license of a Kinji Aiyawamura, a 22-year-old man. So this is who the authorities now
believe this skeleton belongs to, is Kinji. Kinji went missing July 10th. So the first people they
went missing on July 24th, 1989. Kinji went missing on July 10th, 1984. So he had been missing for five
years, and no one had ever found him. Now there's a lot of really creepy elements to this, which makes
it possibly less of a missing person in the mountain scenario, and something a little darker.
But let's take a look at some of the stuff. The theory is that he recorded his voice on tape,
and was playing it in a loop. The tape itself, he's talking very loudly, and it's actually not
a bad survival technique, because you can only yell so much, right? But if you record yourself
yelling, you can play it over and over again. Hopefully someone hiking by or walking by will
hear you yelling. You could yell all night long. So they think that's what was going on. He's yelling
into the tape, and then playing the tape backwards. And then he's playing the tape loudly.
But let's look at some of these bizarre things going on here. One, I am near where the helicopter
was originally. What helicopter is he referring to? Because obviously not the helicopter from 1989,
right? So a helicopter must have been searching for him back in the day. He had gone missing. It's
not to say that no one ever goes missing on this mountain. People do go missing, and sometimes
you never find them. But he must have seen a helicopter back in 1984. And he was trying to
signal, come back to that area where you saw the helicopter. But look at these questions.
How did nobody see this sign in five years? This giant SOS sign, not a single helicopter
or hiker passed by this area? How long was he lost for? I don't think he was lost for five years. He's
like, "What? My mom said if I get lost, just sit in one location and they'll find me." And then
four and a half years later, he's like, "I better build a sign." But no one saw this sign at all
for that period of time. There's suspicion about his legs being broken, that they found breaks in
the bones of his legs. But the question is, did they get broken before he died? That's kind of
the going theory that his legs were broken before he died, and that's why he was stuck there.
But how do you build a giant SOS sign with two broken legs? Did he break his legs building the
sign? Was he like, "Ah, hope it lasts. Now balance on these logs." Or as he's putting up the last
log, he's like, "Uh-oh, this one's extra slippery. Ah!" Or did they get broken after he died? Was there
a crazy bear who was just like snapping stuff? They spent, back in July 10th, 1984, they spent a
whole week looking for him, and did not see this giant sign. What's weird is this is one of those
stories that I... it feels like there's a paranormal answer for it, but I can't even put it into word,
like alternate reality, because he definitely existed in our reality. But how do you search for
a guy for a week, don't see a giant sign? How is it for five years, the sign is never seen?
Is it possible that he's from our reality? He shifted into reality, where he builds the sign.
And then the him and the whole sign has shifted back into our reality? Years later?
None of it really makes sense. Did he break his legs before, during, or after he made the sign?
Like, it's an area you can get lost in, but it's not, again, a lary you can get lost in for five years.
And you figure if he has the tools to chop down birch trees, and build this sign, but he doesn't
have any tools to catch animals? And if you're saying, "Well, he broke his legs, he can't get out
of the valley, he can't catch the animals," then how did he build the sign? So as weird as the answer
is, is of him going to an alternate reality, when we look for him for a week, we don't find him at
all. But then when he returns to our reality, he could have honestly returned to our reality back in
1989, shortly before the other two hikers went missing.
Maybe, actually, now that I think about it, maybe he didn't build the sign.
Maybe he died, because in the recording, he doesn't mention the sign, right?
Maybe he died, and a ghost built the sign. I don't know, I don't, I don't, that sounds even more far
fetched, bunch of ghosts, like, cutting down trees. It's just the, it's one of those weird,
mysterious stories, and it's super obscure. I hear over and over and over again about the lead mask
case of the two dudes who went up on the hill, and they put on the lead masks, and they took the pill.
They're supposed to wait there for the UFO, and they died. You hear about that case all the time,
and there's probably some weird explanation for that, and there's probably, I always thought it was
a cult thing, I always thought it was some weird cult activity, but that's all well and good.
This story is so obscure, and it doesn't have any reasonable answer at all,
which makes it even more creepy. Because if we can go, oh, he was walking through the woods,
he got lost, he got attacked by a jaguar, that sucks. It's not a good ending to the story.
But when people just disappear, and then reappear, next to giant monuments,
made of wood and desperation, that's chilling. Because while this is a world away on a misty
mountain in the middle of Japan, that doesn't mean it can't happen to anyone of us walking down the
street. People disappear all the time, but when they reappear in bizarre ways, it's even creepier.
Because to me, it means that things can go back and forth. And if a human can disappear into a
bizarre reality, what's to stop something from that bizarre reality? I'm coming here.
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio. DeadRabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it
today. Have a great day.