What would you do if you were attending a group meeting and all of a sudden a new reality emerged?
And then we meet a young man who has a bizarre story to tell from his childhood
Where he saw someone display supernatural powers right in front of him
Is it possible that what this boy witnessed was real or is the answer far more tragic?
And then we meet another young man myself as a little boy
One day I was sneaking around a cemetery and I
met
Jesus today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your Jason Garvin or I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a lot of stuff to cover
So we're gonna get started right away first off. Let's bring in our pilot from yesterday
He didn't get to fly the carpenter copter and I want to make sure everyone flies the carpenter copter one of our Thanksgiving
Livestream supporters give it up once more for an idea guy everyone give a round of applause for an idea guy
You're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you guys can't support the show financially through the patreon or through livestream donations
That's totally fine. Just help spread the word about the show that really really helps out a lot now idea guy
Let's go ahead and start you off in the Jason Jalopy
We're gonna touch you the keys to that bad boy. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command
We're driving all the way out to a
group meeting
Know that's a very general location
There's group meetings going on at all times in all places
But we don't have a lot of details of when and where this story took place
Which are kind of essential for any sort of journalism
We need to know at least that but when we're dealing with the paranormal a lot of people are very shy
And they don't want to have their identity revealed
So we're gonna read this story on this very popular podcast so everyone can hear it
But yeah, I wish I had more details for it, but for right now we're at a group meeting
So we're just sitting there and we're eating chips. It's over eaters anonymous
We're like oops and then the group meeting starts and we're gonna be joined by this young person. Let's call her
Terry it's just a stab in the dark. That's your real name
Terry is sitting there as well and Terry is watching this group meeting going on
They also left out why they're at the group meeting
We don't know it could be something fun like a group meeting for building a quilt for the community
Or it could be something absolutely horrible that we don't want to be photographed as we leave in this meeting
But Terry is sitting at this group meeting and the speaker is standing in the middle of the circle and she's wearing the speakers a woman
She's wearing brown slacks. She's there either. She's like, oh, this isn't one of those weird pervo support groups
Or do I hmm if she has on a leather gear underneath her brown slacks
Terry sitting there Terry sitting there and watching the speaker give this presentation and then
a
Cut in reality appears
Terry says that you could see a
slice a silvery shiny slice
Appear in the space in front of the speaker from her belly button
Curving down over to her hip and then down to her knee. It's this silvery slice in what appears to be
reality
And
Terry's like mesmerized by this and is looking is can't figure out why no one else is saying anything and
she's looking at the slice in reality and
It's bigger now. It's a wider slice and Terry goes the speaker was wearing brown slacks
But when I'm looking through the slice
The speaker was wearing a skirt
With the hound's tooth pattern
That's the whole story
That's a little story, but I find no monsters popped out. She didn't turn into a leather Dom
She ripped off all her clothes. She's whipping everyone. They're like, it's over eaters anonymous quit whipping us. We're not in a crazy sex
I found this post online by a poster known as Alium spaceship
And that's really the end of the story and sometimes a lot of times actually I have to say these are my
Favorite stories not because they're short. I can tell five of them in an episode
It's because usually I read a ton of this stuff and I can usually start to suss out what's real and what's fake
Depending on how dramatic they are. I was reading a story last night
I'll see if I can find it put in the show notes
But this kid was running around the house and like this demon was trying to rape him and he's like come at me
You homo demon. He's like beating it up and stuff like that and demons like all get your butthole next time
And I'm like none of this happened none of this happened
None of this like I know
I've been in the game for 30 years that did not happen and
It's the stories where they just kind of end especially when they're in a
Like usually when people get abducted by aliens stuff can get really wacky
But this kid like was like I think stuff was hitting on the back of the head like all this stuff's
Levitating around and trying to go in his butthole and I was like what if not this is not real
This is obviously a parody or
This guy is thinks he's gonna fool us. Oh, this guy is completely insane
I hope I saved it. I really hope I saved it. I wasn't gonna cover it. I was like, oh, this is nonsense
But so this is how paranormal stuff actually happens for a lot of the people, right?
You're sitting there and you see something weird and you're like, huh?
And then you try to explain it and if you can't explain it
It goes into your unexplained file and your brain and then maybe years later you post about it online searching for an answer
I remember once I was taking a video editing class. This is way back in the day. We're actually using two VCRs
This is back like in the 90s and I got dropped off there by my mom
I wasn't a dolt but my mom dropped me off at this video editing class at at the adult learning center in Rancho Cordova
Or wherever and I saw a man in the distance being beat up by two demons
Not not fans of the San Francisco demons the XFL team
I remember is really late the class was late
It was dark and I see a man in the distance of this dark parking lot and I could see two shadowy figures next to him
Pushing them around and I could see him kind of stumbling
He'd like kind of look like he was gonna lose his his footing and then he'd regain it
But he was definitely struggling against these two large black masses and they had no humanly features
They were just huge and they kept pushing him from side to side and I'm watching this and I go
Oh that guy looks like he's being beat up by shadow. They're not trying to get in his butthole and
Had I then been picked up by my mom or had I then walked because I watched this for a couple minutes
I love this guy get beat up by these demons these shadow in for a while. I'm sitting there
Had I gone in
Early had my mom picked me up or whatever. I wouldn't have waited another minute or two
Until he got close enough to me and I could see he was carrying these two giant vacuum cleaners
Like these industrial vacuum cleaners
He was holding them up and kind of trying to wobble them and sometimes he'd put one down so I would see his weight shifting
That's what it was. All I saw was the giant vacuum bags of big black bags and at the distance in the dark
I it just looked like
Non-descript shapes attacking this guy. I should also note if you haven't already picked up at no point
Did I think about rendering assistance to this man? I'm like dude if you're gonna beat up my demons
You probably probably did something to deserve it
Or not and I'm just lazy so I'm sitting there and I go
Oh, well, I didn't go ask him here
Are you getting beat up by demons cuz it was too vacuum cleaner so but think about it that story could have easily ended up in my
mysterious folder in my brain
Stuff that's happened
So I can see like again. That's a fairly mundane story
It would have been mundane if the demons are actually beating them up and then like a portal hell shows up
He's like you could have saved me. Oh, I'm you from the future. I was like, what was that last part?
Paranormal stories just a lot of times just go and then we don't know what happened
And I enjoy stories like that because they this sounds realistic now
Obviously, she could have been having a nervous breakdown. This could have been we don't know what the group is it could be hallucinators anonymous
But it's just fascinating
We talk all about alternate universes and parallel dimensions and things like that and this would be one of those small
Differences that really don't make at any change in reality or like it's not a groundbreaking change
Whether or not she wears brown pants or the hounds tooth skirt
It's just again a creepy thing and in the middle of the day
You're seeing something that can't be explained and no one else can see it and that really takes us into the next two stories
We're gonna talk about so an idea guy. Let's go ahead and toss you the keys of that carboner copter or leave me behind this group meeting
We are headed all the way out
To a young boys house
I found this story posted on the export the other day and this is kind of the theme
This is what the original poster put up and they were talking about childhood memories. We're gonna take a look at this young man's memory
We're gonna call him
DJ
Now DJ he tells the story. He goes you won't believe what happened to me
I was about nine or ten years old and my parents are out of town for the week
I couldn't watch myself. I was too young so they get my uncle
So to babysit me for a week and he goes do my uncle is super cool. He was a really dope dude to hang out with and
He was six foot eight and
400 pounds
I'm pretty sure his uncle was actually bigfoot and they had some family fun adventure and they like stopped an evil developer from like
Paving over their house to put up a mall or something like that
But actually that probably would have been preferable to what might have happened in this story. So this dude he's six foot eight
He's 400 pounds. He's uncle will call him Uncle Joe and one day DJ sitting there and he's playing video games
And Uncle Joe walks into the living room and he goes hey
Hey, DJ, did you know I can levitate?
And DJ doesn't believe him right? He's still sitting there. He's playing perfect dark or whatever
I don't know when this story takes place either, but he's playing these video games and Uncle Joe goes
I can levitate and he's like trying to convince
DJ that he can levitate finally DJs like okay, whatever you obviously want to show me something. I don't believe it's possible
I'm nine. I'm not an idiot humans can't levitate
But sure whatever and he turns around and he watches uncle Joe stand there all six foot eight of him
Standing there in the room and he starts to strain really hard
Lifts his right foot up off the ground
I'm doing it. I'm doing it DJ DJs like what are you talking about?
I can clearly see you just have lifted one foot up off the ground and Uncle Joe goes no no
Check get down there and check
I'm levitating DJ and
DJ bends over in front of his uncle and he gets down there and he looks and
sure enough
Both his feet are off the ground by a good six inches
He's looking under his feet and he can see his uncle Joe is indeed levitating
He looks up and his uncle is just standing there and
His arms aren't holding on to anything
He was looking to see if maybe he was bracing himself against something
But he looked up and know his uncle is just standing there
Floating
DJ gets down and he's looking at his feet and Uncle Joe was perfectly still it's not like he's wobbling
It's not he's trying to balance. He's perfectly still floating in midair six inches off the ground
Oh
There's a loud thud as the levitation trick whatever it was ends and
Uncle Joe is now back on the ground
Do it again do it again DJ says no no we're done with that
You gotta cut you're not gonna do it again. No. No just that one time levitating
Can you show me how to do it? No
It's over
He never showed DJ how he pulled the trick off
He never did the trick again for DJ and whenever DJ would bring it up
His uncle would just dodge the questions and he goes nowadays it mean my uncle. We still talk
Probably once a year we bring it up. It's like an inside joke. Hey uncle remember when you were levitating
The uncle's eyes are darting from side to side
So here's the thing this is a really interesting story and
The third comment down
I think kind of summed up what my feelings were when I read it and this is gonna get dark real quick
But I'm reading and here's the thing. I am an aficionado of the paranormal
I believe that people do have abilities outside of the norm. I believe they're super rare
But I believe there are people who have abilities that someone consider unnatural
So that is what I have on one hand on the other hand and reading the story and I'm like
and
Maybe like two or three comments down someone said
This sounds like a quote
Obviously impossible false memory to cover up super mega rape
unquote and
I remember when I read that I go
Yeah, that's kind of what I was thinking too. It's super bizarre. Isn't it like
You're the weird one and so is that guy