From the dark watchers of California to the gray man of Scotland
Are their giant shadowy creatures?
That watch are every move and
Then we take a trip to the black bamboo forest of China a
Mountainous region almost constantly
Surrounded by fog what lies beyond the mist nobody knows
because everyone who goes there
Simply disappears today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you're having a great day too just a few quick things that are interesting one
I found a website where they talk about solar plexus clown gliders if you remember I did an episode on them back in
I think it was like episode 65. It was a long time ago
Found a website and I was like oh cool more information. This will be awesome. I went to the website and I'll be in the show notes
I'm the information
I'm listed as one of the known victims of the solar plexus clown glider
It's like no one victim no one victims include Dead Rabbit podcast host Jason Carpenter. I was like what oh, yeah
I mean, I guess that makes sense. I was a victim of it
It was so weird to see my says self in a wiki article and then they included a bit of a transcript of that episode
Very very odd, but it's cool. That's a good way to get the show out there
You know, I was like I'm gonna get a couple listeners from that at least and it's in the preliminary stages right now
but I sent off a video for a
Netflix show called haunted. It's like true stories of ghosts
But I said on my story I sent my shadow people story and in that episode
I think that was episode like 75 or something like that
I said the story about the shadow people invasion and they're like, oh, that story was really scary
Let's see a video of you. So I did I did the video and I was like hey, my name is Jason cook
I'm from Hood River. Here's the story. It's like a quick little three-minute video sent it off to him
I'll keep you guys informed. I put down as my occupation
Podcast host maybe get a couple listeners from that as well. So we'll see we will see I'll keep you guys informed
How the Netflix thing goes that would be cool though, wouldn't it? I
And this is the plan I'm not gonna tell my mom not if I get the show
I'm not gonna tell my mom the next time I see her. I'll just be like, hey, I know you're not really into spooky stuff
But let's watch this show haunted. Let's watch this show on Netflix. I will just turn it on and she'll be like, ah
So anyways, I'll let you guys know how that goes. Let's go and get started with the episode though
First story I want to talk about is something I'd heard about a long time ago really kind of creeped me out
I actually have this old friend named Katie
I haven't talked to her
I think she goes by Catherine now, but I haven't talked to her in a long time, but she told me she goes to her
the creepiest thing is
When people just stand there staring at you. I was like really she goes
Yeah, imagine you're late at night sitting in your house
You look out a window and someone's just staring at you from the field or your front yard or wherever you're at
And I go, yeah, that would be kind of creepy and she's like yeah
Just the idea of them staring at me would be terrifying. I said, yeah, and then they like run to your front door
She's like no no no no no they do something then it's not scary anymore to her if they try to break into the house
Then it all makes sense or if they run away then it makes sense
But just them staring at her was the scary part once they did any other action. It didn't become scary
And I was like that's kind of weird, but it makes sense
That's where we're kind of segueing into this story or the story of the dark watchers
We're going to Santa Lucia mountains which sounds familiar to me. So I think we've been there before
But the Santa Lucia mountains is in California and to get there. We're simply gonna hike
We're actually not gonna use any vehicles this time
We're gonna hike because that's how the people experience these things
But we do have our official dead rabbit walking sticks. So we're gonna use those they're in the shape of a normal stick
But they have a the dead rabbit logo head is on the top
So it's a pretty dope looking Gandalf staff with a ceramic
That's probably not very safe with a steel dead rabbit logo head on top created by ash black now
It makes it really heavy, but we might need them for defensive tools. We're walking through a
Chasm like a valley through the Santa Lucia mountains if you and so this is the way the story goes
If you walk through the area the Valley of the mountains
Either at midnight or at dawn and you look up at the mountains
Look up the dark peaks of the range around you. You will see them
descriptions vary
Sometimes they're seven feet tall
Sometimes they're 15 feet tall damn dude that gives big that makes bigfoot look like a normal person
Makes bigfoot look like a chump
15 feet tall sometimes
Just the shadow of a human
Sometimes they have the shadow. They're still completely engulfed in darkness
But they have a wide brim hat
Sometimes they wear long flowing cloaks now shadow people have been described as wearing the hats and the cloaks before
None of them have gotten to the size of 15 feet. That's it. That's huge
That's like two Jason standing on top of each other
No, that's like two and a half Jason standing on top of each other. It's quite the sight to see and sometimes
They have walking sticks
There were some people have said the navels in the area avoided the area that they saw the dark watchers as well
But there's actually no proof that Native Americans in that area ever recorded any incidents with the dark watchers
Where we really start to see reports of them is when Westerners showed up
So when the Spaniards showed up way way back in time they saw them they called them this is pretty dope name
They called them Los Vigilantes oscarro, which I think means Batman
But I'm not entirely for sure, but they called them Los Vigilantes oscarro and John Steinbeck wrote a
Wrote a collection of short stories and in one of the short stories
He talks about one of the characters seen a dark watcher
Steinbeck's son was obsessed with the dark watchers and ended up writing a book just about the dark watchers
He said I grew up around them
It's not like they were like rock in his crib or nothing like that, but he had seen them all of his childhood
He was really obsessed with what the phenomenon could be and I remember reading about that a long time ago in the
National Directory of Haunted Places. I was like oh that is creepy like the idea of looking up and something's just staring at you is
Very very creepy now sometimes people have reported that the creatures will do nothing
But like so you're staring at the creature and you just see it staring off into the nothingness
Staring off across the mountains staring into the sky other people have seen a move other people have reported
This one guy was saying that he was smoking a cigarette and when he took a puff
He saw the dark watcher do a similar motion
Other people have said they've taken their hats off and they've seen the dark watcher also apparently remove something from their head
Yeah, I think you can see where this is going to this
so phenomenon and there is a
Similar phenomenon in Scotland so there's this mountain in Scotland called the bin Mac Dewey
Or does he and this mountain?
Had it's very high and a lot of people love climbing it and every so often this huge mist rolls in in climbers
You were up there have reported the gray man. What's the gray man?
When you're hiking through the mist in the middle of nowhere
You start to hear footsteps behind you
I think that's enough you get the point and anyways and these people have had an
Overwhelming sense of fear like I've never been afraid of anything as much as I've been afraid of what was behind me
and they turn around and
behind them in the mist
They see a giant again like a 15 foot tall shadow of a person walking behind them
Now sometimes they see it when they're going up the mountain sometimes there's reports of them seeing coming down the mountain
Usually it's coming down the mountain or if it is they're very shortly coming down the mountain because they flee the area
They just see this giant figure chasing them the first reported case of that was in the late
1700s, but it wasn't until the early
1900s where a guy a very famous mountain climber said he was at like this mountain climbing convention and he goes
I gotta tell you guys something one day. I was up on bin Mac
Bin Mac Dewey and this happened and people are like well, that's kind of weird story
He's like yeah, that's why I didn't tell you that he was the one who's saying I was walking down the mountain
Heard something behind me turn around saw this giant gray dude walking behind me
I took off down the mountain but since then other people have reported this phenomenon as well
Always comes with the mist always comes with the mist
so I'm researching these stories and I at first I
Heard about the dart watchers back when I read the book and then I recently discovered the gray man
I was like, oh, this is great story for the podcast
But it's funny because let's go back to that story that happened in the late 1700s the very first sighting of the gray man
There was a sheep herder who was herding the sheep and the mist rolled in
And he's like oh this sucks like it got a hurting sheep is already kind of hard and now I can't see anything
There's all this mist everywhere and he turns and he looks up the mountain
And he sees the gray man first reported sighting of it and he books it out of the mist
He leaves his sheep there. He runs back to his house and he's like, oh my god
There's the scariest thing I've ever seen something was up there. I totally swear, but he's like but I left all my sheep up there
He's not like a mountain climber where he can just run down the mountain and be like I'll go climb another mountain
Like that's his job his sheep are up there
So the next day is like damn it. I have to go back up there
He goes back up there the mist is rolling back in and he sees the gray man now standing a just quite a distance away
But still in front of him and he's looking at it. He's like why is it standing exactly like me?
And he takes his hat off and he sees the shadow take its hat off and he's like, oh, it's just my reflection apparently
This is what these things are and this was kind of a buzzkill
There's a thing called a broken specter
What happens if the Sun hits it at the right angle a shadow is projected onto a cloud
So that's what it is
These people who are up especially been McDewey
Because it only happens when the mist rolls in you're in the mist and the Sun
You're basically projecting your shadow onto a cloud and you see a giant person who's you
Walking after you because you turn around and it's your shadow
You're basically being scared your shadow and they said the thing with the sound like footsteps behind you that can be explained a couple
Different ways it's funny because I've always heard footsteps behind me all the time when I walk
When my feet are hitting gravel it always sounds like there's someone two three feet behind me
And there's nobody there so it could be you're walking down a mountain and every time you take a step little rocks are coming down
So it's making it sound like there's other footprints. These guys are experienced mountain climbers
So they would figure that there's also been things with the moisture in the mist is actually creating that sound as it's making rocks move
Around or something weird like that. So that's what most likely is the gray man of been McDewey
With the dark watchers, I think it's also probably the same thing
I think that they're actually now again because it says that you can see it at twilight or
Dawn I don't know how much Sun is really flying around during twilight because I know that's when the vampires are out
But I think that's the same thing because again
Basically you look up you're wearing you're walking with a walking stick and you look up on a mountain
You see someone else with a walking stick
You're not gonna think oh that must just be my shadow because it's super far away. You don't think shadow works like that, but
That's mostly like that's most likely what the dark watchers are as well is the Brock inspector
And what's funny is I imagine the Native Americans back then would walk through that valley
They'd look up they'd see a dude up there and they'd be like that's just my shadow
I kept on walking and it wasn't until super superstitious people came to America and started walking through that valley
And they looked up and they're like oh ghost like I think the natives are like, yeah, it's probably just my shadow
It's weird. It's kind of actually wait a second
Maybe that doesn't explain the dark watchers because at least the gray man walks with you and makes it look like it's chasing you
But the dark watchers just stand there
And they don't walk with you
Hmm
Maybe the dark watchers are real
Just out of that
Okay, let's go ahead and move on to that. I didn't plan on that little nugget
Let's go ahead and move on to our next topic here
After all blew my own mind
With the dark watchers. It's funny. It's people. I people complain about the show every once in a while
It mostly gets a lot of praise which I appreciate
But one guy's like how come you always like act like you're shocked about this stuff. You've done research on it
I was thinking
Yeah, if you listen to the show, I think you're aware of how much research I do on stuff and two
You'd be surprised how how often when you're looking at your own notes here. I've done that a quite a few times on this show
I'm going through my notes the Ariana Grande episode is the best example of that
Where I had my notes and I had an angle that I was going for with the story and as I started reporting it
I was like I'm way off on this. I think there's something more to it
So that was that I was like, oh the dark watchers are totally just an optical illusion. It's nothing scary, but yeah
They don't that I think I I don't think it they might actually be something interesting
I always like surprising myself, but
done surprising myself
For now, but that'll be in said we are done walking our legs are sore. Oh my calf muscles
I need some bananas. Let's eat some bananas. Let's go get some potassium. Then let's hop in the carpenter copter, baby
It's the only way to fly we are going we are going to hi zoo valley now. We can't really fly over it
Well, we can but we won't see anything
the entire area is
Almost always shrouded in fog, but we're not just going to he's you valley. We're going back in time
We're going back to the year
so in
1949 in China was not the best year if you weren't a communist because that's when the People's Republic of China was taking over and
People who weren't communists were like we got to get out of here
And especially if you were members of the army that was trying to defend the old order
You definitely needed to kick bricks because they're coming after you the previous government
That was there before the People's Republic of China took over was the kumon tang the kumon tang
So 30 soldiers of the previous government were like we got to get out of here grab your guns grab your ammo grab your supplies
We got to leave because these guys are winning the war. We're wearing the wrong uniforms. This is not going to end well for us
Where do you go on a hide?
Person general and the general goes I know a place that we can hide place
They won't look for us and we'll figure it out pack up all their gear they head for he's you valley
They move through the black bamboo forest one of the many notable sites in the area the place is beautiful
It's lush
Mountains valleys waterfalls full of endangered animals endangered plants plants that have died off
everywhere else in China still exist in this valley and it has this constant
rolling fog
The troops get ready
I like okay, let's go. They're not gonna find us in here. They pass through stones gate, which is a natural formation
disappear into the fog
But they weren't alone
Three scouts for the People's Republic of China their military three scouts were following them
They wanted to know where they were going. They're gonna hook up with a larger force
What was going on?
Three scouts go into the fog as well
He's you valley like I said, it's considered China's Bermuda not just because of the mysteries the place holds
But for its beauty it's basically has almost no human interaction. So it's just nature
Unleashed in this area. There's a local tribe of people there that they believe
That beyond stones gate is where their people originated from and now they live farther away from there
But they give tours in the area you can go out to He's you valley walk through the black bamboo forest all that stuff and go through
The tour pretty much everywhere you want the tour guy will lead you but once you get to stone gate they go tours over
We're not going over there. We don't pass stones gate
He go why not and they go well for one. It's a sacred place to our people
It would be sacrilegious for us to do that and two
You're not gonna come back. So tours over
tours over
after those army troops went into the mist and
The scouts followed them a few days later
One of the scouts comes out of the mist
Finds a local village passes out when he starts to when he comes to he said he had a hard time remembering what happened in the
Mist but as he comes to he starts to get his memory back. He said that
They all walked into the mist him and his two scouts were following the 30 troops
They all walked into the mist. He says I started to feel this weird energy surround me
I started to get really dizzy and I looked for my two compatriots. They were gone
All trace of them were gone
No footprints
No broken branches
Nothing, they just disappeared
the 30 soldiers who walked into the valley
Never seen again
ever in
1950 so a year later after that
other people went in for numerous reasons
disappeared
100 people in that year rumor to have disappeared
After that
We jump I think after that people got the got the message people got them out
Don't go over there because it wasn't until 1962 that a geologist team was sent in by the government
To survey the area one guy ends up coming out of the fog and says listen this this is what happened
we walked in as a group into the mist past Stonesgate and
Everyone lost track of everybody else
Nobody knew where other people were at but the thing is the geologist said there was also this weird side effect
He lost a sense of time. He could no longer tell how long he was in the fog for
There was just no way for him to gauge that and then he said he started to hear what he described as frightening sounds and
hid
Until there was a break in the fog and then he ran back out of Stonegate the rest of the geologist team and they don't say how
Many people were there, but I figure maybe three to five
never seen again
1976 three members of a forest prospecting team says, you know what we yeah all those people went missing but we're forest
Prospectors we're gonna go in and find out what these trees are
Never seen again
There's been reports that planes have gone missing over it as well. I haven't really I think that was kind of a retcon
I haven't been able to find anything to support that one of the articles said that planes were missing
If they were that would be too surprising
I don't think they're flying at 30,000 feet
Over the mountains if the planes were flying too low, they're just gonna get caught in the mist and they're gonna crash
But you're definitely not getting rescued if you crash there. No one else is gonna go in so in the place
You can go to the guides won't take you past Stonegate you can walk through yourself
It's not restricted by the government or anything like that, but it's pretty ill advised if you want to go there
So the question is is what is going on at this valley? What is going on here?
Some people say it's very explainable
You just walking through a mountainous region
There's a lot of mist everywhere and you naturally fall off of a mountain or
An animal gets you if you know these creatures are living in the mist all the time they've adapted to it
They know how to work in it. They're hunting you in the mist. They were born by the mist
They were shaped by it. You were merely adopted by it
So you don't have that natural instinct of of mist based combat
Some people think they're sinkholes. There's a bunch of sinkholes in the area and so people walk in and fall in them
Now my pushback to that is I can understand if every show often a hiker went in there and went missing and disappeared
What sinkhole is gonna fit 30 people?
I mean I can understand 30 people those soldiers going in with weapons and maybe a
Big angry panda bear taking out two or three of them doing kung fu on them, but
Come on like I get that you always want to come up with the natural explanations like even high did previous like I get that idea
But at a certain point after you hit a hundred people in a year
I don't think you could be like, I don't know maybe maybe a hundred people are all just falling off the same mountain a
Little ridiculous. So then you kind of do got to look at some of the weird stuff here
Now there are some people who say that there is a mountain in the region
That is shaped as a triangle IE a pyramid and
This valley is on what's called a dead latitude the same latitude as Bermuda triangle and the pyramids of Egypt
Maybe could have something to do with that. It could be some sort of like geological thing
But I think for the most part Bermuda Triangle has been fairly debunked at this point
They think it's just like huge storms that come out of nowhere
They found those hexagonal clouds those huge water spouts and the fact that the Bermuda Triangle is one of the most widely
Used shipping areas and boats and plane ever since GPS
Stuff has come out and satellites and stuff like that stuff doesn't really go missing in the Bermuda Triangle anymore
So that's kind of debunked and it could just be the fog
You're walking through the fog
It's too thick to see
You get lost you get disoriented
You just keep you could turn around you could be walking in circles
You could think you're walking back to Stone's Gate and be walking deeper and deeper and deeper into this force
That would be easy to test
Just tie a string to a tree outside the fog a
Hardy string that can't be crotty chopped by a panda and you walk through the forest and eventually find your way out
But is there something else?
I mean the body count is awfully high
for this area
now again
You maybe since we've had GPS people aren't really disappearing in that area, but I can't really find any
Proof that people are still even going into that area
But what else could lie in that fog?
Could it be the fog itself that isn't just obscuring your vision?
But obscuring your sense of time and space is
It possible when you walk through that fog you're not just entering a valley, but you're entering some sort of
portal
You're going somewhere else, so you would never be found
It's interesting because the locals believe that their race their tribe
Their ethnic group came from that area and
Now you are disappearing in that area
Could there be some sort of opening
Imagine a world on the other side of that portal
beautiful and lush and green and all the beautiful species of plant life and animal life that are endangered here are
Plentiful there a
true Eden in that other world
War those original natives who crossed over into our world and settled here as well
it would be a place of pure beauty and
If you were a lost soldier looking for a place to hide from a brutal regime
You might not have found it in your native land of China
You may have found it in another world
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
Twitter is @jasonOcarpenter. Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)