When a flock of birds drop dead, science thinks they know the answer.
But do they even have a clue? And then we take a look at a bizarre conspiracy involving football.
Is it possible that the entire NFL is based around one goal? Pooping in your food.
And then we finish out the week with a truly terrifying story of a young boy
left at home alone. He thought it was just going to have a nice relaxing day listening to some music.
Instead, his life ends today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys have some awesome
plans for the weekend. Just to heads up some quick housekeeping. I am still looking for people to
submit. We got a lot of submissions already, but if you want to be on an episode of Dead Rabbit Radio,
all I need to do is to have you chant out "Earth First! Earth First! Earth First!" and we're going
to remix... there's a reason for that? If this is your first episode you're like, "What? What am I
listening to?" We're going to remix all of you guys into a classic episode of Dead Rabbit Radio,
"Earth First!" If you want to hear that episode, I'll put it in the show notes. You have until
January 31st. I moved up the date because it's the holidays. You have until January 31st to email me
a recording of you chanting "Earth First!" Email it to DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com and just add
permission that I'm able to use that sound clip. We are going to create this awesome soundscape with
you, the Fluffle, and an episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. So don't forget January 31st is the deadline
for that. Also, take a look at this awesome fan art we have for Fan Art Friday. This is from Nick
Buston. Nick Buston, longtime Patreon supporter, very active on the Patreon Discord and appears,
hangs out with us when we do the live episodes on Sunday morning for the Patreon people. So that
is so awesome. Nick, I really love this. It's the first time we're seeing this version, a 3D version
of the Dead Rabbit Radio logo. Absolutely love it. And we always, always got to give a shout out to
Ash Black, who actually designed that logo. So thank you, Ash Black. But Nick, what a great
rendition of it. Really, really enjoy that. And then let's give a shout out to one of our
Thanksgiving livestream supporters who helps the show so much. Give it up for Cantillians!
Cantillians, also a longtime Patreon supporter. Cantillians, you're going to be our captain,
our pilot this episode. If you guys can't support the show financially, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show really, really helps out a lot. Now, Cantillians, I'm going
to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jet. We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed all the way out to Spain. Now, this might be too fast of a vehicle,
because we're actually going to be talking about birds. I wanted something in the air,
but we have a dirgeable. We have a copter. But I want to get there fast. Let's fly in this fast,
fast jet. We're headed out to Spain. Specifically, we're headed out to Feral Spain. That's where
all the crazy people live. They're all hairy and they run around. Feral Spain. It's November 26,
2021. So, fairly recent story. We're at the Juan Cardona Hospital. We're walking around the outside
of Juan Cardona Hospital. And it's in the middle of the afternoon. It's a beautiful Spain day.
And there's trees near the hospital. And in those trees are birds.
It's starlings, to be exact. I don't know what a starling sounds like. And we're standing there
watching these birds in this tree. And there's a lot of other people milling about now. We're here
because something weird's going to happen. That's why you're listening to this podcast.
The people just going about their day on November 26th. They have no idea what's going on. They have
no idea why all these handsome people are wearing Dead Rabbit Radio Flight suits
standing in the middle of their parking lot. And then all of a sudden, 200 starlings
fly out of these trees. And they're briefly in the air. And then they begin to drop dead.
People watching this said, exactly what I just said. I'll just reiterate it. They go up in the air
and they just seem to fall out of the sky. And no one can understand this. And I'm reading this
article. I was reading this article on Coast to Coast AM's website. And they had these links in it.
And they go, this is also really similar to something that happened in Wales in December 10th
of 2019. So I went back and looked at that article. And that article, this resident, this local to this
area in Wales was driving near the village of Baudedurn. And they see a flock of starlings flying
through the sky. And they're like, Oh, how beautiful is nature? Because they just swarm in these elegant
kind of formations. But on their way back home, there's hundreds of dead birds, starlings, laying
across the street. They call the authorities up. Because here's the question. Whenever you find
these dead birds, you're afraid that it's chemical, that there's something in the air. Now there are
bird die offs like this that are connected to chemicals. But this one in Wales, they did autopsies
on 35 of them, you know, they just take them at random. They said these guys died from blunt force
trauma. So everything's okay. And in that article on the coast to coast AM, it goes, this is also
similar to something happened in Canada back in 2018. So I'm clicking on that one. And that one
is pretty much what we talked about. A guy is walking down the beach and he just to see starlings
falling out of the sky. Now what's interesting is in that case as well, the corner, the bird corner
says they just smashed into the ground. That's how they died. But the question is, why are they
smashing into the ground? And this is something it's so funny. I read this litany of articles this
weekend. And I thought bird, mass bird die offset. So it's talked about in the news all the time. I
would normally not cover it. It's it's unfortunate if you're a bird, but for other people, it's just
kind of inconvenient. So now they're driving home and their car is like, but like, I'm sure the
coyotes love this type of thing. So I never really paid much attention to it. But the fact is that
nobody knows what's causing this. What's interesting is the one in Wales, they go, well, what we think
is because the starlings fly in formation, they usually follow the lead bird. And if you had a
giant predator appear, all the starlings panic, they fly out of the trees, and then they crashed
into the ground because the leader got so scared, he led the entire thing on some sort of kamikaze
mission right into it's not even kamikaze because kamikaze, you killed the predator coming after
you, they just smashed into the ground and died. But remember, that one didn't have a witness.
So you could say yes, or maybe a predator showed up in the Canadian one on the beach, there was a
guy sitting there and he goes, I was sitting there on the beach. And all of a sudden birds just started
falling out of the sky. And the answer for that was, Oh, a predator must have shown up and scared
them into the ground. And he's probably like, I mean, a whale, maybe I didn't see any large
predator. And now we have this one in Spain with multiple witnesses in the middle of the day at a
hospital. And they said they just fell out of the sky. It'll be interesting to see how long they go.
Oh, there must have been a unknown large predator in the area that nobody at the, nobody of the
hospital saw and it didn't get picked up on any security cameras. Just it was that this is really
interesting because I always did also brush this off. But what is killing these birds? Why it's
causing these birds to just fall out of the sky? I know we've had bird dios before and most of the
time it is done without people seeing them, they just wake up to all these birds. So I don't know,
honestly, I'm thinking, I'm thinking they're bumping into some sort of invisible object.
The most likely thing I guess, honestly, to me, the most likely thing is these guys are being
chemically poisoned. And they're dying because they hit the ground, but the poison, I mean, poison
may not kill you, but I wouldn't recommend driving a car while you're on it. If you drank some industrial
paint or got some waste in your lungs, it may not kill you outright, but the car accident,
if you're driving to the hospital because you're sick as a dog or sick as a bird in this case.
So what is killing these birds? Fascinating, fascinating story. And it's one of those ones.
I don't think we'll have any answer for it. I just wanted to kind of highlight it because we have
these mass dioffs as people are looking at them. And science will come up with an answer. The question
is, is it the right one? I mean, anyone can come up with a answer. Cantillians, let's go ahead and
toss you the keys to the dead rabbit robot. We're going to leave behind Spain. We're going to row
all the way back to America. Specifically, we're headed to Santa Monica. I think where this guy's
at. Hoove, ho, splash. Hoove, ho, splash. Row in that boat all the way back to Spain. Cantillians,
the brave captain of this party vessel. The reason why we're headed out to Santa Monica,
because we're about to meet the most lovable, face stealing hobo you could ever hope to meet.
Once again, we're going to look at the life of Max Kramer. Max Kramer, we've done a couple
episodes on already. Homeless man/video game developer/philosopher of our age. Because the
stuff that he comes up with is just, mwah. It's what I like to describe as organized insanity.
It's the ramblings of a madman, but he's able to put it into proper grammar and host it on a website.
Now, this story was brought to me by Oogs. Oogs, thank you so much for the countless hours of Max
Kramer-isms. He's still around. He's still active. Like I said before, I have not even gotten through
all of the stuff he wrote back in the early 2000s. But he is a mind outside of society. Let's go
ahead and take a look at this stuff. Because when you are a man outside of the norm, the first thing
you're going to see is the hidden codes. Because I'm seeing like Pepsi billboards and Coca-Cola
trucks driving by with those massive advertisements. My mouth is salivating as I'm thinking of a
grilled cheese burrito. That's a new thing. That's a new thing that Taco Bell has. It's a
exactly what it sounds like. But I'm a simple man. I'm a man who lives into base desires, right?
I just sit there and I see this food and I want to consume it. I'm the ultimate consumer. What
television show is going to show me an ad next? I can't see the code. So I just eat. I just eat
this fast food, this grease, these oils. I don't understand what I'm putting in my body. But Max
Kramer does. Max Kramer knows what I'm putting in my body. He's probably hiding in my closet and he
takes little notes. The dude is a madman. He wants threatened to wear our skin and attack our children.
So he is nuts. Well, let's take a look. Because he's broke the code here. You've got to be nuts.
You've got to want to steal my skin to realize that Wendy's, you know, that delicious restaurant
called Wendy's with the Frosties. Wendy's actually means when dies. So when you go to a Wendy's,
what you're doing is you're eating humans. You are now officially accountable. If you've ever
eaten a Wendy's in your life, which I just admitted I have, you're eating when dies. This is where they
take people and when they die, they cut them up into square hamburgers. Now, I'm not going to tell you.
I'm not going to tell you what he thinks about Burger King's Whopper because it involves a racial
slur against my Italian brother and sisters. But he thinks that the Whopper is made of you. If
you're Italian without saying the slur, he believes that when you're eating a Whopper from Burger King,
you're actually eating Italian people. So you go like, you know what I'm done being a cannibal?
I'm not going to go to Burger King anymore because I don't like Italian. I'm not going to go to Wendy's
because I don't like eating humans. I'm going to go to McDonald's. Well, be careful what you order
at a McDonald's because did you know that a Big Mac is what you're actually eating? You're actually
eating a Jewish warrior, a Maccabee, a Jewish priestly warrior from the early second century.
So you're wondering why that tasted so, so stale. It's because the meat is from like 168 BC.
So he has this thing. If you haven't noticed the theme yet that fast food restaurants sell human
meat. If you get, but let's say you don't want to go to fast food restaurant. Let's say you just
want to go to your local submarine sandwich shop. Well, hold on. Max Cramer jumps out of the bushes
and goes, what are you thinking? What are you thinking? A submarine sandwich means, the submarine
part means this is meat from people. You like, damn it, Max. Can we just eat something that isn't
human? He's like, no, not if you eat food. If you take, if you capture an enemy submarine,
if you capture an enemy submarine, because there's so many of those floating around nowadays,
you capture an enemy submarine and you turn those people into meat. That's a submarine
sandwich. That's what they mean by they say that you're eating, that would be like a hundred of
these sandwiches produced every year. There's not that many people in submarines, Max. You take these
submarine people and turn them into a submarine sandwich. But what's curious is that sandwich
actually means a witch from the Middle East. So I don't know a lot about the Middle East,
their military capabilities, but I'm pretty sure submarines aren't high on the list. I'm pretty
sure there is not enough submarines owned by Israel, Jordan, Iran, Iraq, any of these countries,
Egypt. They might have some, but I don't think it's enough to provide meat for all of these subway
sandwich shops out there that sell submarine sandwiches. Oh, and by the way, subway, if you
thought about going there, it doesn't mean eat fresh. It actually means they take people who have
died in underground train crashes. And when's the last time you heard about that? He actually,
okay, I'm giving him a little bit of credit because I'm saying underground train crashes as in a
subway. He actually specified the underground railroad. And I'm assuming he does not think that
you're eating Harriet Tubman when you go to subway. I'm thinking he meant underground train
crashes and not meat from the 1800s. Could be wrong. So you want to go to in and out, you're
like, "I just want the segment to end. I don't want to talk about eating people anymore." We're
sitting in an in and out restaurant. They take the meat from prisoners because you get it prisoners,
the revolving door, the school, the prison pipeline. It's not just words. Those are slogans for
in and out burger. Jack in the box, Jack in the coffin, Carl's Jr. I didn't know this. Again,
I'm not a huge scholar on World War II era Europe or the Nazis or anything like that.
So I don't know if this is true. I doubt it. I think this is very, very suspicious.
But Carl's Jr., the restaurant Carl's Jr. means Nazis. So now I love Carl's Jr. So I hope that
doesn't say anything about me, but Carl's Jr. means Nazis. They do have the best barbecue sauce,
not the Nazis. Carl's Jr. The reason why Carl's Jr. means Nazis to Max Kramer is because Jews
in Nazi Germany were called juniors. Now, I don't think that's true. I don't, again, I'm not a huge
scholar on the Holocaust, but I'm pretty sure that is not a fact. I don't think anyone was like,
get the juniors over here. I don't think so. But again, I could be wrong. I could be wrong. He
could actually know more about that than I do. He ends up wrapping up the list by telling us that
Domino's, the last place we could probably eat at this point. Domino's means, well, Dom, again,
I don't know if this is true, but Dom means blood in Hebrew. So when you say I want to eat Domino's
pizza, what you're actually saying, what you're actually telling the universe is you want bloody
nose, you want bloody nose pizza because you're saying blood in nose pizza when you want Domino's
pizza. Now you know all these restaurants. Now you know all of this stuff that you didn't want to
know that there's a guy walking around the streets of America today thinking that when he sees you
walking out of Carl's Junior, you just ate a bunch of Jewish people and he's looking at you
and he's judging you because he thinks you're a cannibal who supports Nazi empires.
Let's see what he has to say about the NFL. Let's see what he has to say about the National
Football League. He starts off kind of strong on this one. He says this, I'll agree with this,
I'll agree with this first part. He says that football is a way to represent war. I don't think
that's a groundbreaking statement that basically we are such a conflict driven species and we have
tribalism and we love to beat other people that we've turned that aggression into sports where I
can go from my town and you can go from your town and we can watch our two combatants fight
against each other. It's modern day gladiatorial combat without people's heads getting rolled off.
Totally agree with him but then he of course takes it to the next level. But the point isn't just
a physical confrontation. This is where Max Kramer takes it. He sees it as a punishment.
So this is what's actually going on when you watch a football game. You're not watching
two armies fight because we did that already. This is two armies trying to throw poop into
each other's food. Here's a quote from him and he's trying to explain a football game
but he also sees it as us trying to poop in the enemy's supply lines. So if you have the
Seattle Seahawks versus the Dallas Cowboys, every time they get down to do the hut hut hike thing,
the quarterback, what he's actually symbolizing is poop. His poop coming out of his butt hole.
You're like Jason of course. I know that you just want to keep talking about poop don't you?
He's pooping into his hands that football is excrement and then his entire team has one goal
to get his poop into the mouths of the enemy. Jason of course watched a lot of football.
I've never seen anyone eat a football. This is how he explains it. If one doesn't have a toilet,
this is actual quote from him. If one doesn't have a toilet, it must squat
down and balance the self with one outstretched hand on the ground to make the ball of feces fall
to the feet. If all the food is not digested, perhaps a quarter comes back to the plate.
Quarterback. That's what that term means. You didn't know what you do now. The food goes down
the line in factories. The touchdown in the end zone represents feces in the mouth and the stomach.
He goes on to say that this does symbolize that no matter what side of the battle you're on,
you've probably eaten feces in urine because people are constantly making touchdowns and what
they're symbolizing is that the Seattle Seahawks went to the Dallas Cowboys Stadium and pooped in
all their food. And then once again one of the most bizarre things about Max Kramer actually
forgot until I was reading this all the way through just now. He goes on to say that he doesn't
think black people are real. It is one of the weirdest quirks that I don't think I've really
dove into it because he just kind of ends conspiracy theories like that. I haven't found
the full one but he believes that black people are actually Asians. Might be specifically Korean but
he believes that black people are actually Asians painted black to turn him gay.
And that even pops up here. When I was reading through this he says that
feces in urine appear to be in most food while people painted black celebrate and act like fools.
But he thinks they're actually Asian men who are trying to seduce him. The dude is nuts. It's
funny because sometimes I feel like I talk about him too much and other times I'm like we have
barely scratched the surface with this guy. I really need to find out why. Can I ever? He's
still alive. I would actually love to talk to the guy. Yeah it's just so bizarre and I just find
it so interesting because I am into hidden symbols and codes. I don't talk about a lot on this show
but I am into hidden symbols and codes and not ARG things but what we see in the world around us
and how it works and how it affects people. I really do think about all that stuff and he takes
that to the nth degree. I've never walked past the McDonald's and thought I wonder how many
Jewish people are being eaten in there. I would assume the answer is always zero so I never need
to think about it but yeah what a different breed. Max Kramer is so bizarre. So so bizarre.
There's no other way to end that segment other than to toss cantilians. The keys of the carbon
helicopter were leaving behind Santa Monica. We're headed all the way out to Poland.
I wanted to give another shout out. I did another podcast recently called The Asylum Case Studies
and it was me and the host Tressa. We watched the The Asylum Movie, three-headed shark attack.
Asylum makes these really goofy. That's being nice. He's really goofy straight to sci-fi channel
movies and I really enjoy Three Headed Shark Attack. That's a lot of fun so if you guys want
some more Dead Rabbit to listen to this weekend I am on Tressa's show The Asylum Case Studies and
if you love bad movies and if you love the culture of bad movies definitely give that a try. It's a
really cool podcast. As we're headed out to Poland we also got to go back in time so cantilians
hit that time travel button and take us back to the month of July 1948. Carbonicopter. It's flying
over the Poland countryside. Specifically we're going to Sosnowyk in Poland. It's a bright summer
afternoon. It's harvest time in the village and everyone's getting their sickles and their little
clamps and stuff like that and they're walking out to where the corn is or the weed or whatever
they're growing in Poland and they leave behind a young boy. Let's call him Timmy. He's a 12 year
old kid and he is left behind in the village to, according to this report, he was left behind to
guard his house which I don't know about. I mean if everyone in the village is leaving he's the
only one here. Who's he guarding it from? I'm almost thinking that this kid they could have been like
oh we don't want him back in the field. All these guys are all caught up when he was just doing that
skythian accident. He was just skythian blindly cutting down that wheat baby. I gotta do it fast.
Other people are like walking around no arms so they leave Timmy at home
and he's sitting there. He's like well if I'm gonna guard the house I'm gonna do the best
Dosh Garn house guarding I can do and he does it for about 10 minutes and he gets super bored
and he goes inside. He goes I'm just gonna go listen to music. Now it's 1948. I actually didn't
know this existed and maybe this is a huge plot hole in this presumably true story but
he goes out to listen to the radio and he had headphones. Did they have headphones in 1948?
And more specifically did they have headphones in 1948 in Poland? I don't know. I don't know.
I probably should check that out. Let me let me check it out real quick. When were headphones
invented?
1910. Okay so they would have had headphones. Okay that makes the story. I was really iffy on the
story honestly. I was gonna tell it anyways but I just want to read it up so it could have happened.
Not that that's the most strange thing. I'm like see you guys later have a good weekend. That's not
the strangest thing of the story. He's sitting there and he puts on the headphones and he turns
on the music and there's no music coming out of the radio. Instead he's hit with a strange unbearable
sound coming out of the radio. He takes off the headphones and he can still hear the noise
and he's looking down at his headphones and he's thinking this must be really loud if without
these headphones on he can still hear it pretty clear and then he realizes it's coming from outside.
He stands up, he walks to the window and he opens it up. Outside what he sees are two
humanoid entities. They both have thin short bodies with large disproportionate heads.
Black piercing eyes too large to be a human. These are what we would describe as gray aliens nowadays
and these two creatures in the middle of the day are standing there in silvery shimmering
skin tight outfits. Now they don't notice him. They don't notice him looking out the window and
seeing these guys. That doesn't matter. It doesn't matter at all. Simply seeing these two inhuman
figures causes him to go into shock and then fall unconscious. Hours pass. Remember everyone else
is out doing the harvest. His parents eventually come home. They're like someone was supposed to
guard her house. What's going on here? Where's the guard? They go in and they find their son
unconscious on the floor and he is revived and the first thing out of his mouth is "I saw the devil
I forgot to add this part. One of them, one of these aliens, which he doesn't identify them
as aliens, aliens aren't really known in 1948 at all especially in rural Poland, but
he's looking at one of these aliens and he had horns on his head. He had double horns on his head.
Now UFOologists today wonder if what he was seeing was a gray alien with a helmet on, a horned helmet
on, or if this alien did have double horns just grow naturally, which would be unusual for gray
aliens. That's something that's not normally associated with them. But it doesn't matter
to this kid whether or not he was wearing a horned helmet or actually had horns. I saw
the devil. For the rest of his life, and he did not have an easy life, he blamed all of his
misfortunes on these devils. He believed that everything that everyone went wrong in his life
could be connected to seeing these two creatures standing outside of his window. Every illness,
every failure, every unhappy moment in his life, it was the curse of the devils that caused it.
No matter what he did, he couldn't overcome that infernal curse.
I got this story from Albert Rosales, Humanoid Report. It's a really, really cool
depository of this information. It'll be in the show notes. They got it directly from a
email. Someone emailed them this story. It was just someone telling the story that had happened
in their village from Poland. So take it with a grain of salt. But I think you can say that about
any paranormal story. You can say that about any story you read on the newspaper nowadays, actually.
Looking at this story, I really find this story curious, and I think it's a good way to end the
week. On Monday's episode, I mentioned that there's a certain powerlessness that comes to
meeting the paranormal. You're interacting with something that is so beyond humanity,
that we can talk about punching gray aliens in the face, or doing extra-sisms, and making
demons run away into the darkness. And those things do happen. But the overriding accounts
of paranormal, a lot of times it's the humans who do the running away, right? We are very powerless
in this paranormal aspect, be it a cryptid chasing us down, or a ghost trying to scare us.
We're always trying to navigate around them. We have to adjust our lives for them. So there is
this powerlessness. And imagine all this kid did. All he did was look out the window, and it drove him
mad. It drove him to the point that whenever something didn't go right in his life, he believed
it was because he looked out a window. The first thing I want to remind everyone who's listening
to this is be careful what you wish for. Because a lot of people, I see this a lot in the paranormal
community, where they go, "I've never seen a ghost. I've never had a paranormal experience,
but I really want to have one." You see that a lot when you're looking in the paranormal community.
They are fans of the subject matter, and they kind of wish that it would happen to them.
Be careful what you wish for. You may get a gray alien showing up and teaching you peace,
love, and kindness. You may get a ghostly visitation from a past loved one telling you everything's
okay. You can also just as easily get a demonically possessed monster rampaging around your house,
or seeing something so incomprehensible. And that's what a gray alien would be.
A lot of times we look at pictures and we look at movies like Paul, and we're seeing these
X-Files versions of them, and that's all makeup and CGI. You, to see something that has not evolved
on the planet Earth, I truly think would break your brain. You can look at the weirdest animal
on Earth and go, but that's still evolved here. It's still part of our DNA. Something that came
from another planet, it would just, and if it's from an interdimensional realm, which gray aliens
very well may be, it's even more mind-boggling. So be careful what you wish for, because you may
see something that drives you insane. Also, the second thing to take away from is, he didn't
wish for this. He didn't wish for this at all. There's no, aliens, gray aliens were not a thing
in 1948 that imagery was not out there in the mass populace. He saw something, he didn't want to
see it. He wasn't reading these sci-fi magazines, he wasn't looking forward to tales from the crypt
being invented, so he could read in the 1960s. He just walked by a window and saw something so
shocking he passed out and then he believes for the rest of his life, everything that went wrong
was because of this visitation. So it's not just about be careful what you wish for, it's about
be careful where you exist. But then there's one other way, there's one other thing that I find
very fascinating about this story, is that we do have to look at the skeptical side of things.
And the most realistic answer is he looked out his window and he saw a trick of the light.
He saw something that was something else. Maybe he fell asleep, maybe he had sleep paralysis,
maybe it was some normal event and it still broke his brain.
He looks out of his window at a particular time and for whatever reason
his mind conjures up, his imagination creates the image of these two short skinny people
with big heads and black eyes wearing skin tight silvery suits.
It's not real, it's not real. Any skeptic in the world and most scientists, most normal people
would say this story isn't real, there are no such thing as great aliens or aliens in general
and they're definitely not hanging out in Poland to be spotted by one person in a village,
they just don't exist. So he didn't see anything. And to me that is even more tragic,
that's even more disturbing because that means that the human mind is so frail
that you can look out your window and there's nothing there. But your mind creates something,
whether it is imagination, whether it is a dream, whether it is a trick of the light,
you're looking at something from a weird angle, it didn't exist, he saw it and it drove him insane
anyways. What's worse, spending the rest of your life blaming every failure
on a bizarre pair of creatures standing outside your house and their energy, their darkness
infused the rest of your life, no matter what you did, you can never succeed in anything.
What is more scary, that or looking out your window at a perfectly normal pastoral setting.
And simply because he's standing at the wrong angle and something catches the light in just
the right way, his mind imagines devils. His own mind drove him insane because of a trick of the
light the rest of his life was miserable. What's worse, being driven mad by a vision of aliens,
or being driven mad by nothing. At least the aliens you figure you would be one of the few
special individuals in human history who has seen alien life. Maybe that's worth going mad for,
maybe it's not really, I want to want to do it, but maybe that's worth spending the rest of your
life wishing what could have been if you hadn't seen that infernal duo. But at least you saw something.
In a skeptics world, in the plausible world, he looked out his window and there was nothing there.
And his life was miserable for nothing. His failures continued to mount and he blamed
nothing. That small patch of land outside of his house contained no alien presence.
But he still felt it. It still scarred him. And to the bitter end, he blamed every bad thing in
his life on something that never existed. I guess the lesson here is, when you hear the bump in the
night, when you hear the rummaging through the closet, when you see something moving in the
distance just by the tree line as you're driving home, simply by looking, simply by turning your
head to see where that sound came from or where that blur moved. You are risking your own psyche.
You are risking your mind. You may see something that absolutely breaks your hold on reality
and will spend the rest of your life cursing the moment you made that decision.
But in this case, we've learned there doesn't have to be anything in the darkness.
There doesn't have to be anything moving through the trees.
Just by thinking there is something out there could be enough to ruin your life.
How do you like that for a Friday episode? You guys have fun. Dead Rapper Radio. Don't look
anywhere though. Get some horse blinders. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email
address. You can also put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
Dead Rapper Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend guys.
Bye.