Can you die from being tickled?
Did they really find a set of mummies in Peru that includes a bird human?
And then we explored the...
Conspiracy? No one has the McFly code. A lot of people say that back to the future predicted the future presidency of Trump
But did it actually predict?
9/11. A lot of people think it did and we'll explore that today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*music*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Parfiner. I'm having a great day
I hope you're having a great day too. I think you can tell from the intro we got a lot to talk about today
So we're gonna jump right into it. Weeeeee
It's just jumping all at the same time and we all say we so the other day
I was kind of just I don't remember how I came across this story actually
I think it was just kind of clicking around on Wikipedia. I was reading about gibbets
I think because I realized that I didn't define them right in the past episode the hand of glory episode
I thought a gibbit was a place like a box you put someone until they died. No, it's actually kind of gross if not
It's a thing that holds your guts together
So after you die they can just post your body up by the like on a sign post and you just like stay there until the birds eat you
And then your bones fall out they they use them for pirates
They posted them out like as the boat would come into Harbor you just see a bunch of corpses hanging in gibbets
Notorious criminals they would want to put in a gibbit so people could see them
Nowadays, you know, they'll well not nowadays but back in like the Western times too
They would display the body but the gibbit was all about just letting the body decay like you didn't get a Christian burial
So it's gonna clean you know how you start falling down the rabbit hole in Wikipedia
I and then you go Jason. Why are you even researching gibbets?
It's stories done, but I was like, I think I got it wrong anyways
So it's kind of jumping around and I clicked on tickle torture now. I hate being tickled
I think most people have a love-hate relationship with being tickled. Yeah, you laugh a little bit
But it's not never really that comfortable. I actually don't like it a lot
But when people like think of tickle torture you think like, you know, someone said on top of you
He he he you're like, no, stop it. Stop it. And that's it, which is not I mean that would be torture to me
But it's it's actually a very effective torture method and it can kill you. It's not completely harmless
So when people start laughing it can indicate many things
Sometimes pleasure sometimes humor, but it can also represent panic and so tickle torture. It's so funny
I just imagine like Elmo like in a dark Guantanamo base cell tickle torture has been used for thousands of years and
It's quite effective
Oddly enough in China during the Han dynasty
They used it when royalty committed a crime because it was
Did suck no one liked it, but it didn't leave any bruises
It didn't leave any mark and I left very little psychological damage
And you're like Jason didn't just just say it could kill you and I was like, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I can kill you but you have to do it long enough in ancient Rome. This sounds quite brutal
It sounds kind of cute at first an ancient Rome
They would take someone who committed a crime and they're like well
It's not crucifixion level crime, but it's not you know, let them go level crime either
It's kind of in between they take their feet and get them wet the criminal not just any random person
it would take a person get their feet wet and then
Rub like dip their feet in salt so now they have salt all over the soles of their feet and then they bring a goat in and
the goat licks the salt off and then
They do it again
They put their feet in salt prop them up goat licks the salt off and very quickly
It became painful because you have the mixture of like the rough goat tongue the salt on the skin and the constant like tickling
And it was not a pleasant experience. It doesn't sound very pleasant
There was a book called the men with the pink triangle a book about the Holocaust during World War two
I guess you guys know when the Holocaust took place and one of the the book was a first-person
Narrative that the guy was saying what he saw over there. He said he saw a guy tickled by SS officers with a feather
Kind of an odd story
There's a lot of bad stuff going on over there. I don't know why they're like, yeah
Let's just see what this guy is gonna do with this feather
But so that's in a book called the men with the pink triangle in ancient Japan. It actually had an official name
Cuz sir, Giri
Zimi which means merciless tickling
Sounds a little menacing and in England when people were trapped in stocks kids would take their shoes off and tickle them
So it has a
It has a long history has a long history of being used, but it still is used today
To extract information
If they're like we don't want to leave any bruises on this guy, but we really want to know what's going on
They can tie down and inmate and tickle them
Yeah, the information they want it's it's weird because you'd think oh, you know
If he had like pliers and they're like threatening to put out their eyeballs and stuff like that like that would be more effective torture
the interesting thing about torture is that
Once the physical pain begins torture actually becomes less effective
Because one of two things are gonna happen one
They're gonna just say whatever that you need to hear to get it to stop or
Once the physical pain kicks in their body can start to kick in and they can either go into shock or
The body goes this isn't as bad as you thought it was going to be threatening someone with a hot poker is
More effective than putting the hot poker on them
Psychologically because as long as your poet like you and I'm gonna put this on you
I'm gonna put this on your hand. I'm gonna put this on your hand
You have the worst case scenario imaginable in your brain
But once it actually touches your hand and it burns and all that horrible pain happens
Your brain then starts to recalibrate itself being like it's not that bad
So the most effective torture is the threat of violence over actual violence and we're talking about torture to extract information and
Probably most likely to extract information from most people of the population
People who are hardened psychologically against torture you may have to go to that level if you're just torturing someone in your plan
I'm killing them in the end. It doesn't really matter either
But for governments, you're just like we're gonna beat you up if you don't tell us that threat is more to an average person that threat
psychologically is worse than
The actual beating
Oddly enough, but yeah, you can die from being tickled and what happens is
You tickle long enough you can start to vomit which you'll choke on your vomit and we're assuming you're restrained
It's not like you're running around the living room and your little sister's chasing you with a feather
You're restrained they can typically use so much you'll vomit and choke on the vomit or
You'll simply laugh so much you can't catch your breath and you die and
They're saying the reason why people that the tickling especially on the soles of the feet are so effective
So because that's where all your nerve endings end
so they're super super sensitive and
It takes a very short amount of time before the tickling actually becomes painful. So that all being said
Like I said, I'm not a fan of tickling myself
But we're gonna segue into a quick dead rabbit recommends here a friend recommended this movie to me
He's like this movie's totally off the wall. I'm not gonna tell you anything about it
You just got to watch it now. I'm gonna tell you my friend a little bit about it to kind of pique your interest this movie
It's a documentary. It's available on Netflix. I believe it's called tickled
it is okay, so what it is is there is a
Young journalist a young gay journalist in New Zealand true completely true story
Who is he does articles like the pot like this podcast does he highlights weird stories from around the world?
He come across this thing called competitive tickling and it's young fit men
Tickling other fit men and there's videos posted online
And it's this competitive tickling league and the gay guys like this this seems kind of gay
It seems funny cheeky, you know these young hot men are tickling each other and trying to win prizes
This would be a good story for me to cover
so he contacts the
Head of the website this woman and he goes hey, I'm so and so I work with this newspaper in New Zealand
We covered the weird in the wacky we would like to do a story on your
competitive tickling teams and
He goes I expected either a yes like that sounds like a great idea or no
We're not interested in being like a wacky news story
Instead he got an email back full of anti-gay slurs and
Talking about how they don't want to be associated with some gay kiwi and he needs to stay in New Zealand blah blah
He's like what the hell like that was not the response
He expected at all he thought that it was kind of gay to begin with he thought there was some sort of gay undertone to this
Because of that one email the New Zealand guy starts to think there's something more to this
Organization very very weird organization. So he starts digging into this and again totally true story
the documentary is
Him and his team traveling to America trying to unravel this mystery and it is a true
mystery conspiracy
story
Young men's lives are ruined. There's blackmail. There's threats of violence
Other men get thirty thousand dollars in a brand new car
They become the part of this web of lies and deceit all
Based on a bunch of tickling videos
this fun website where young men are tickling each other and competing for cash prizes
Uncovers this huge criminal enterprise
Led by one person who will stop at nothing to get their next tickling video. It is
Absolutely bizarre it is absolutely bizarre and it's a true story
You can go and read all the news articles after the fact of what happened
But it was all because of this one young journalist in New Zealand who got that email and thought they're summing up with this
Conspiracies are real
The big mega conspiracies that involve these crazy world connections and stuff like that most likely aren't and the thing is that so many people
Are looking up at those mega Illuminati conspiracies. They don't see the conspiracy happening in Gary, Indiana
It's this it's such a good mystery movie. It's such a great conspiracy movie tickled check it out
Dead rabbit recommends tickled not tickling
But the movie tickled
So our next story actually came as a recommendation from I got an email from a gentleman named Austin s
Austin s. Thank you for this story
very very interesting story
Very very hard to really get some meat out of because most of the meaty stuff is in Spanish
But it's slowly trickling out into the English and it's it's like operation plate where it's kind of like an explosive
UFO alien story
But it's just slowly trickling out into English, which is kind of the bra
That's really where most conspiracy stuff is covered in English and there's a lot of pushback on it
A lot of pushback on it. It's interesting is we're gonna get into what the what the debunkers actually have a problem with so
The Nazca region of Peru Nazca is most famous for the Nazca lines
It's the huge drawings in the sand that when you go up in the air
You see like a bird or a person or a goat or whatever now we covered the Nazca lines long time ago
I'm of the belief the Nazca lines were created by
locals to
Basically, they were signs for the gods to see I don't think there was any aliens doing it if there was aliens making the Nazca lines and
Aliens making the pyramids they kind of shorted Peru on that because you know Egypt got these huge monuments and Nazca
Just got some lines in the dirt
But I think they were made by the locals to celebrate the god and they could figure out how to draw them and they usually come around
The either point near water or are near water can prove that area doesn't have a lot of water
So it kind of lines up to the idea. It's a religious thing, but in 2015 in Peru
Archaeologists we have a lot of archaeologists this week archaeologists. Oh wait. No, no these guys aren't archaeologists actually now
Remember these guys are even funnier. It is a group of treasure hunters
Led by a guy named Mario now. I feel bad for people named. I don't pity people named Mario
But Mario is one of those names that when people hear it they immediately think of
Mario Brothers like all the time so I imagined a treasure hunter and I saw I didn't ever told you this guy story
I have to tell you guys a story real quick
I saw Mario and Luigi in real life once wasn't on drugs wasn't hallucinating. I was driving down the street
I was driving by American River College out in Sacramento and I saw a
short squat
man with a mustache
walking next to a tall taller guy with a mustache and the short guy was wearing a red hat and
The tall guy was wearing a green shirt and the short guy the Mario basically took his hat off and like it was like
Three stooge's sq. He took his hat off and he hit the tall guy on the head and the tall guy rubbed his head like over
Dramatically like it actually hurt just getting there
It was Mario Luigi. It was Mario and Luigi in the real world. I should have joined
I should have walked up to him said can I join you on your quest and they're like, yeah, we're gonna go paint a house weirdo
Treasure hunt. Sorry. I got off of it. It ran there Mario. No. No. No. Yeah treasure hunter named Mario
discovers in the war zone. He's in Nazca. It's year 2015
He finds five mummies
Now he had found mummies in the past and he has some of the stuff he's found in the past
Some people said have been controversial and other people are like, no, it wasn't controversial. It just
He was mistaken. He wasn't trying to pull a fraud. So there's been debate over this gentleman in the past
Anyways, but he discovers these five mummies and he contacts
Gaia.com now Gaia.com is like a alternative
spirituality
Mental consciousness type of website. I looked into him
I was like, I wonder if I can work with them and I was like, no, we're really not on the same wavelength
But because I know they do videos and stuff like that
But so they started investigating it and they went send a journalist out to take a look at these mummies
And I think they had a team with them as well because eventually the mummies do catch the eye of
anthropologists and archaeologists
And they like what is up with these things? Apparently there's five mummies
They've been carbon dated to being 1700 years old back when that area was flourishing and you got these mummies the one that really
Is sparking the imagination. There is a mummy that is about two to three feet tall
And it looks more like a humanoid bird than a human
What's interesting is that that mummy is not talked about in most of the debunking articles
This is really where the schism lies. So
Gaia.com says we found these five mummies. They appear to have metal parts in their body
this one appears to be like a bird baby and
According to x-rays, it looks like it may have eggs in its tummy. The pushback is
Testing was done on one of the mummies one of the weird-looking mummies and it came back a hundred percent human
They never say it was the end the debunking ones. They never say what which one it was
They just say it was a hundred percent human the whole thing's fake. You don't have to worry about it. Mario is a fraud
It's totally fake
They say that the mummies are actually a bunch of other body and a bunch of other mummies
Reassembled to look like weirdo people and then remumified. That's that's their argument
They take these body parts Mario took all these assembled like he just had a bunch of mummy parts laying around in his garage
It's the Sunday afternoon. What else are you gonna do? He made these five mummies and then displayed them
So if that's a weird it's weird that they don't really talk about the the alien-looking one
They talk they go this and really a lot of the there's a lot more debunking on this guy a comms
Really the only one pushing the story again at least in English
Everyone else is like other people involved like guy a comm what if they know those guys are wacky they believe in all this stuff
So most of the debunking is actually attacking the sources rather than the subject
This is the weird part of the story and that was if that wasn't weird
What happened and this is how it came to my attention Austin emailed it to me and he emailed me this four channeling on
November 19th 2018 so just a couple months ago
Gaia TV and a bunch of scientists went to the Peruvian Congress
to present their evidence
Outside of the Congress you had the Peruvian Astrobiology Association
Protesting it wanting to debate and what's weird about that is normally it would be the other side around like normally you would have the
You would have a bunch of scientists people talking about 9/11 to Congress and how it happened and military personnel and outside you would have the
9/11 truthers going no no debate us debate us, but this was the fringe theory
Going to the Peruvian Congress. It's not like a shack. It's not some like weirdo group in there
They're talking to the elected body of Peru
About their findings and outside are the quote-unquote reputable scientists being locked out of that conversation
So here is the oh and to be fair on the people
Disputing and saying that they don't mention the little alien bird, baby
To be fair that information may have come out after those articles were published. I've noticed that a couple times
I've held
Journalists to task. I'm like how come they didn't include this and then I found out that that was revealed much later, but this is what
This description was what was posted on 4chan. It was a translation from
A Spanish description that was being presented to the Peruvian Congress
So we are playing a bit of a game of a telephone. It's going from a presentation in Spanish into English and then post it on 4chan
So lose, you know, you you don't know exactly who's posting this, but
This is what apparently was stated to the Peruvian Congress
about these mummies
No indications of artificial manipulation of the body. It was a biologically functioning entity
They're talking specifically about the bird, baby organs intact humanoid form with reptile characteristics
No hair. No ears. No nose. No nipples reptilian skin hollow bones similar to a bird
two feet tall
Bipedal bipedal, right bipedal with natural wear on the femur junctions that couldn't possibly be reproduced by artificial means
Large head elongated skull retractable neck orbital cavities would have provided the thing with more than 180 degree vision
So on and so forth
Says it has a beak three-fingered claws bird shaped dinosaur feet and that's where they're like no that was the
Mario made that fake looking hand
didn't really have three claws
and they said that
it seemed like it was
unisex where it's basically had two sexual organs and had eggs in its bodies and things like that
So and then when they were talking about the mummies, there was five of them
And they said one is confirmed to have been ritually mutilated
So one had been chopped up or changed one is confirmed at least partially human but has abnormalities
Josephina is the one they named this little bird baby
And then there are two smaller ones that had him tested before the congress controversy
One thing that was interesting and again according to gaia.com and the researchers who presented this information to peru
They said that Josephina shared
Human dna. It was 30 shared with de human dna
And you're thinking well, okay, you know, that's not bad and I was going through the four-champ post and people were saying a banana has
90 percent human dna like pretty much anything on this planet
shares a ton of amount of percentage of dna with humans because we all evolved together
So to find something that is 30 percent human would basically be a complete alien
That shouldn't exist on this planet if a banana has nine, which I thought was so funny
We're basically a banana is 90 percent human actually. No, they say that it's kind of gross
Eat little people. But so again, this just happened in november
This was the first I ever heard of this story even though it really popped off in 2015 a gaia.com for me
Is or is not a reputable site. I know of them. I never really look into their stuff because it's mostly like
Middle-aged mom magic. It's one of those types of sites where they just talk about like self healing and oh and I got nothing
But gaia.com ads on youtube for the past two weeks because I was looking into this story
But it's all stuff like how to make your life better. Which I guess is a good thing
But you know what? I mean it's stuff that
Women are into and to like boost their mental health or something. I don't know why I'm disparaging that but you know what?
I mean, it's opra level metaphysics. I guess is a better way to put it
So it's kind of cool that they're actually pushing this. I think that's an interesting story
And we'll see what comes of this. This is still unraveling. Again, there's a bit of a language barrier
But we'll see I think it's interesting that gaia.com is pushing this
I think it's interesting that they presented this and they were accepted to present it in front of the peruvian congress
And uh, we'll see what comes out from this. We'll see if the debunkers have some better stuff other than just
Look at gaia.com, which I guess is what I just did, but I'm not dismissing it just because
They're putting forth this story. I'm just not a fan of that that type of entertainment to begin with but if they're pushing
Now I sound like a dick, but I think you guys know what I mean, like
I hope that this is true. I hope that gaia.com doesn't make a breakthrough with this
I think this is a really fascinating story and it would add another little twist to the
human story
Now I should say human slash banana story, but so we have run out of time for
The McFly code and I know you guys are disappointed you guys are like you I've listened to 30 minutes of you talking about tickling and baby bird aliens
But I guess we're just going to have to move McFly code back
Oh, we're going to move it back in time slash. Well, no that would be forward in time because it's on the next episode
But close enough think about it now. You're going to think about it for a day
Did back to the future predict 9/11
I'll tell you this man. I will tell you this there is one piece of evidence that is so bizarre
It may it it may it may
May put a little nugget in your brain because I was watching it and I'm like that
is weird
You'll find out tomorrow dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. They'll probably listen to it tomorrow
You're interested in that story. Have a great day guys
[Music]
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]