What would you do if you were having a nice fun time at a summer camp?
making wallets going for hikes enjoying nature and
Then the aliens decided to join you
and
Then what would you do if one night you were kicking back a few Bruce keys down at the local pub and
in walked
Ecryptic today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys are having tons of fun
Doing whatever you're doing. We got a lot of stuff to cover so first off
Let's go ahead and get started walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our newest patreon supporters
Give it up for the lost cumquat again. Woo come on in lost cumquat
How do you pronounce that?
cum cumquat?
Quamquat? The last quamquat people. Jason, I know you have a hard time pronouncing names. This is a fruit
This is a super well-known fruit. Quamquat, right? Quamquat.
The lost Quamquat you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon
I totally understand it just helps for the word about the show that really really really helps out a lot
We got some flyers in the show notes. You can print out and pass around town
We're actually going to do a redesign on the flyers coming up
So if you want if you want those classic Dead Rabbit Radio flyers
Download those images now
Quamquat, I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider
We're gonna jump off the highest point of Dead Rabbit Command and we're gonna glide all the way out to Russia
It's a long it's a long glide. I hope you guys brought some granola bars. I brought mine
And as you're slowly starving by the time we get there you're all emaciated
Luckily we get there eventually it's September 22nd 1980
Specifically we're in the
Sidar region of Russia and it's evening the sun has set the birds are going to bed the owls are waking up getting ready to
do their job being spooky and
In the Sidar region here in Russia. There's a Russian summer camp actually since September these kids
They're a little late you guys need to get back to school. It's fall right?
Sometimes maybe it's a fall camp maybe things are different over in Russia
But anyways, there's this camp and it's mostly these young teenagers most of the campers are like 14 to 15 years old and
You have camp counselors obviously you have adults there watching the whole situation now
I've never been to camp my family was too poor to afford camp and watch a lot of documentaries about camps like me
Balls I watched the meatballs movies the one or the alien showed up. I think that was meatballs for obviously I also watched
salute your shorts
Winning documentary about camp life. I've never been to a summer camp. I've watched camp rock multiple times though
This is what I would think camp would be like right you'd go you'd sing a song you'd kiss a girl
You'd meet an alien and you'd get in a boxing match the alien would levity to you around
Dead rabbit recommends meatballs for whatever meatballs movie that's doing aliens in I don't know how many times I watch that as a kid a lot
But I assume summer camp is like that. Maybe you make a couple wallets. You're like sewing stuff
Maybe maybe a zombie named Jason Voorhees kills you but something like that
Apparently in Russia none of that stuff happens. You don't get to kiss a girl. You don't get to make a wallet
You don't even get killed by Jason Voorhees on this particular day
In Russia, this is what apparently they do in the camp. They were washing their dishes in a ditch
In 1980 I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure Russia had indoor plumbing
They had a ditch they had like this trench dug and these kids are washing their dishes, right?
Grabbing more mud. They're like washy washy washy. They're like, uh, this is why we're still in summer camp in September guys
Learn to wash your dishes, but these kids are washing ditches in a ditch and then all of a sudden
Aliens showed up just like we both for this UFO shows up and it's hovering over the camp area
It's actually a bit farther off
But it's close enough that they can see it. They said it was 50 feet in diameter
It was this massive object and it lands in a nearby field
So the kids start running they're like we can do the dishes later. We've been watching them for hours
They're still money the kids leave the dishes in the ditch and they start running to their cabins
Which specifically in Russia, they're not called camp cabins
They're called barracks. So I don't know what type of camp this was it might have been a prison labor camp
But these kids are running from the ditch
Which would be your natural reaction, right? I think if you saw like a UFO you'd be like, oh dude
Look at that. Look at that unidentified flying object way up in the sky. What is that?
But if you watched it land nearby like I think part of me would want to go check it out
but I'm 14 years old and
So dumb watching watching dishes in a ditch. Obviously not really thinking things through I'm out of there
So these kids are running back to their cabins and they tell the camp counselors and they're like, oh do watch out
Like this big old thing it landed over in that field and camp counselors are smart enough
They go get in the cabins get in the cabins
They're like they're not cabins. They're barracks. They're like these old stone brick buildings. Whatever just get in them
They're all in these cabins that is when all of the cabin windows just kind of just kind of blow open
And they're like the shutters right it wasn't like glass flying everywhere
But like the shutters on the windows just kind of blew open and they were saying that there was no wind the previous to this
There's no wind at all and now this violent force is thrust open the cabin shutters and
You have I think they're all in one barrack at this point. I don't think someone's like, oh, no, this isn't where I sleep
I need to go to my bed. They're like, no Billy. No, he's running over to his own cabin
I think everyone from way this story sold everyone is in one building
And the shutters are thrown open and at this point
Like everyone the camp counselors believe in something weird is going on there in there
The kids are in there and one of the kids will call him Joe
Joe starts walking towards the door
Opens it up and runs outside and he's just running through this now empty camp ground as you have this mysterious force
blowing the shutters open and
One of the camp counselors sees this and she takes off after him and she's running luckily
She's faster than him and she's able to grab him before he's halfway towards
Where they believe this UFO landed
So she grabs this kid and she's dragging him back and while she's dragging him back
He's kicking and screaming. He's saying quote. I want to be with them. I want to be with them
I want to be with them and she's dragging him back
And then he breaks free. Oh, I want to be with them. I want to be with them
Oh, and she's like she gets up and she starts running back after him
Tackles him again is now finally able to drag him all the way
I don't know what the other camp counselors are doing at this point
They're like making bets you're like you think she's strong enough to take that kid down
And so anyways, they bring the kid back once she finally gets close enough to the door and the other counselors are like
Oh, look at here. Let me help you. They had to tie the boy down with bed sheets
Because he wanted to run out to the UFO so badly that a time down and
He was sitting there struggling against the sheets begging pleading to be let go so he could be with them and
Then after a period of time
That didn't sound like you
That didn't sound like it was from another world
It's not like I ran out of breath during the UFO effect after a period of time the UFO begins to leave
*Makes weird noises*
*Bing*
And then the young boy Joe
*Sigh*
Such a pleasurable moan
I don't think it sounded like that my notes actually just said that he stopped he calmed down
It didn't say that he went oh my what it what what an erotic adventure it just said he calmed down
*Laughs*
That weird noise anyways that
Is from I got that from thinkaboutadox.com. They got it from a source called x library
UFO Russia and we've talked so much about Russian UFO encounters
They were covered up for years and years and years
They were never getting out from behind the iron curtain and a lot of these stories weren't even reported because the KGB like you know in America
We had the FBI and the CIA
Looking into all sorts of people saying that they're seeing these UFOs some of them
They knew was test equipment you know stuff we were testing and some of it
They didn't know what it was and then you have the stories of the men in black a
Ultra secret government agency or maybe not even of this world also investigating this stuff
Russia you have the KGB and if you're like hey, I saw something weird in the sky
*Laughs*
Basically got punched in the stomach for a couple days until you
Until you either said you didn't see something in the sky because it was part of their secret
Warfare their weapon testing stuff or they wanted to know if you were a
US spy or you know you were crazy or whatever like people were not people were not openly admitting they saw UFOs
But once the iron curtain fell once the KGB became they just changed the letters in their name. They're still
Anyways, I want to get beat up. Who are they now grew? I think it is GRU
But yeah, they they stopped punching so much. I think nowadays now
I think they only just go with a right hook for a while and then they let you go
But you would now that the iron curtain has fallen the Soviet Union has fallen. We're getting a ton of stories out of the
Russia region, which is cool for us, but let's take a look at this one in particular
When I read this I thought
You we covered a story recently about a guy who went crazy during a UFO encounter and wanted to like join the aliens
I'll try to find that episode in the show notes. It was late last season
I'm trying to remember what what the exact details was but I think it was two friends and one of them wanted to stay and he had
To be like forced or one of them wanted to go with the aliens and he had to be forced to stay
Something like that and then I had this story as well and I thought how stressful must this be?
Like how the situation of already being confronted with something
That yeah, sure
I believe in aliens and I think the recent poll was like 52% of Americans believe that
Extraterrestrials exist, but a big amount of those numbers are sure. Yeah, somewhere in the universe. There's alien life
Like that's a huge chunk of that to actually the people actually believe were regularly being visited by aliens the numbers much smaller
So even if you I you know, I believe in aliens, but if all of a sudden I'm confronted with an alien life form
I would imagine it'd be very very stressful. You notice on a lot of these alien stories
We just covered one yesterday the first the alien say is be calm
Calm down that is almost always the first thing the aliens say even the ones that appear in human form say hey chill
Okay, be cool
Because it would be extremely stressful to meet an alien because all of a sudden you have your whole paradigm shift
Even if you believe in aliens now, it's proof and if you mildly believe in aliens
It's proof of something that you kind of considered and if you don't believe in aliens at all this world shattering
It could destroy your entire way you look at reality
So that's already stressful enough now imagine
Experiencing it with total strangers or people you know kind of well these campers
They forged friendships along the way camp counselors
They might not even like some of these kids. They're just doing the job. It's just kind of a regular assemblage of people and
Then this happens
And you're thrust into this life-changing event that you don't know how it's gonna end
I mean we're reading the story later and it's just something that I'm talking about in a haunted closet
But it's a moment in time. They have no idea how it's going to end
Is this the first wave of an invasion? Is everyone gonna get nuked off the area? Is everyone gonna get abducted?
You don't know so there's that level of stress
You're being confronted with the unknown in front of a bunch of people that you barely know which would make it even worse
And then one of the one of these Nimrods decides to make the situation worse by running towards them
Like there's all just such a level of stress to this story that I find fascinating and that young
Woman running out after him grabbing him and dragging him back. Like I don't know if I would
I mean, I guess it is her job to keep him safe. She's a camp counselor, but
So you have all of that you have all of that stress on there, right?
Someone trying to actually go towards this unknown force and then really the ultimate question is what was prompting him to do that
It could have been two things. It could have been
The idea that the aliens were communicating with him, which again is very common in UFO lore
You have aliens sending telepathic messages and selecting people
A lot of times they say aliens only appear to you if you are chosen. That's why not everyone sees UFOs and then
There's even a time we've covered couple stories like this where the aliens
Choose you and then they run a test on you and say no, you're not going to meet our needs and they leave you
So there does seem to be some sort of selection process was he selected
But then also you got to wonder if his brain just broke
Like if he wasn't selected the aliens were there for some other reason and this kid confronted with something
1980 Russia even in America in the 1980s
Like we were aware of little green men and it was more of a jokey thing with aliens
Like people who believed in aliens when I was a kid were considered cuckoo
cuckoo like total wackadoodle they'd write these books and stuff like that in tinfoil hats
And that and that was in a place where you had freedom of press and people were putting out these books like chariots of the gods
And you were able to watch these shows
Like in search of Leonard Nimoy's
Documentary and all that stuff
Imagine in a repressive government where information is completely controlled and you didn't have that stuff
You probably didn't even have star trek. You were vaguely aware of aliens. Maybe
in 1980s Russia
And you're being confronted with this if we saw a giant
Vehicle descend from the sky at least we can put it into context mean like oh that might be aliens
But if you had no concept of aliens you're 14 15 years old growing up in this area, it would totally break your brain
I think you wouldn't be able to I think I think it would break your brain
Even if you didn't know about aliens if you're a valiant. I've seen a couple episodes of the x-files
Great alien watch your room. You're not gonna be like hey, what's up? How's molder doing?
It's still gonna affect you but imagine if you didn't have any context for it and you saw that happening
So was this kid actually being contacted by the aliens or did was the event so traumatic?
He broke
I think I lean more towards the telepathic thing because when the vehicle left he seemed to return to normal but
My thing is if the aliens we've seen their power level before if they wanted him they would have marched right into that camp and taken him
They would have frozen everyone in the camp the kid would have been gone missing
Right right from the bedsheets. We've seen the power level of these things. So maybe he just went nuts
Which is again a very terrifying answer because how can you really
How do we know how we're really going to react to when we're placed in a situation such a stressful situation like that?
Will we be able to kind of keep our wits about us or will we find ourselves running towards?
the unknown because
At this point everything's unknown everything you ever thought about the world is
wrong
You see this giant ship land and you realize that
everything you've been told that rationally
Happens and rationally exists just doesn't the rules of the universe has changed creepy telepathic communication or did the kid go insane?
We don't know
But an interesting story and i'm glad I could share it with you the last kwam kwat
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys of the carbonic copter. We're leaving behind russia
We are heading all the way out to
a small town
On the edge of the woods
I found this story on the export so as much as I love the export it does have the limitations of
Everyone they're post anonymously
We don't have names. We don't have dates. We don't even have a location for this story, but that's fine
Right, it's still I think a very very interesting tale
But I from what I can put together there's a key detail that makes me think this story takes place somewhere in
Western europe it could be totally wrong about that it doesn't affect the story too much but just
Because kwam kwat's flying the carbonic copter. I think we're going to be somewhere in western europe
Because we're going to be visiting a bar
That is centuries old
In america america is only about 200 and some odd years old
So I don't think it takes place in america. I think it takes place somewhere in britain or france or something like that
So just fly the carbonic copter and we're just going to jump up jump out of the carbonic copter somewhere around this region
And we're going to meet a young man named mark. That's your real name just a guess
but mark
Is at a crossroads in his life when the story takes place. He's 23 years old. He's in between jobs
He doesn't seem like he's had a very pleasant experience
in life
He says that his dad was kind of a jerk
And taught him, you know never back down from a fight never turn your back on someone
Always got them fist raised if someone's challenging you and those while those may be good lessons in context
They can also serve you very very poorly if your boss is like mark where's your reports?
Come on. Don't make me fire you and you're like what'd you say to me?
I'm like there are certain times where you have to be like, uh
But mark does have a caveat to that because again you sometimes do have to back down from fights
One thing he also learned
Because this kid seems like he goes out a lot to a lot of clubs a lot of drinking and he's been in a lot of fights
Mark said one thing that I've learned is I take my social cues
From my friends. So if we go out to a club and some guys talk in trash
And all my friends are like, let's just get out of here. Whatever this club sucks. Anyways, he goes all go with my friends
He goes if we're there and they want to square up and fight i'm down
I'll be the first one to fight but he's not going to put his friends in a situation where
They don't want to be in basically he goes if they're ready to go. He's ready to go if they're ready to fight
He's ready to fight but
If he's not getting those social cues
It's almost like his dad is whispering in his ear. Don't back down
Mark he's in between jobs and in his best friend
He says mark, you know what, you know, you're not doing anything right now
Why don't you come and hang out with my family for a couple weeks? I'm gonna go back visit my family
We live out on the outskirts of the forest
Some sort of fairy tale gingerbread village. We live out in the boonies
But once you come to hang out with us, my family's really cool. They'd love to have you
And so mark and his friend we'll call his friend peter
Mark and peter go out to see peter's family and mark is impressed. His family is super cool
He's exactly kind of what he needed right now. He just kind of didn't need
some chill time
But peter's grandpa while seeming like a cool guy is
quiet
But not quiet in the way that he's shy before he says something you can tell he
Thinks about what he's going to say. He considers
the phrases he uses
Doesn't speak all the time, but when he speaks it means something
And when that first night they're all hanging out grandpa turns to mark and says, you know, you're a city boy
so
Make sure you're in the house
before nightfall
mark thinks this comment's kind of weird, but he understands he is coming from a city and here's this old man
Who's lived his entire life in this region?
mark says, you know
That's nice. That's nice that you're warning me and all but don't worry about me. I'm not just a city boy
I've actually been hunting. I've spent some time in the woods
And the grandpa looked at mark and said
Not these woods
And mark thought this comment was kind of odd
And it made him really curious, right? Here's this old man
Doesn't speak of things lightly. All right. This is just the presence that this grandpa gives and mark asked
What do you mean about that?
And as the grandpa begins to mention
Something about the woods something being in the woods
The rest of peters family kind of cuts off grandpa changes the subject
And the grandpa just drops it
One night all the men in the family go out to this local bar
So you got mark you got peter you got grandpa
And then you have peter's dad and peter's uncle and they're going out to this bar
And they make sure to tell mark thought this was another odd thing as they're going to the bar they kept
Making sure that mark knew how old this bar was. They said the bar we're about to go to is older than your great
great grandpa
This bar is centuries old
Mark's like, yeah, okay, you know, I don't know if like you're warning me the plumbing doesn't work or anything
He goes they really really kept emphasizing how old this bar was
Mark didn't really think anything of it a neat piece of trivia. Sure, but you only got to say it once you don't got to keep
reemphasizing it
Walks into normal bar
Right. I mean it is old
But you know barkeep
patrons tables and most importantly alcohol kind of what you need for a bar
So mark's sitting there with peter's family. They're sitting around drinking
Talking having a good time
And then at one point in the night
Mark is drinking his beer and he looks over at peter and peter
Is nervous
He's giving off this energy right now
That he doesn't want to be here anymore and mark picks up on it right away and he looks and sees what
Peter's looking at and then peter immediately looks down at the table
But mark is now looking across the bar
and what he realizes is
Everyone is gone. The bar is empty now save for this group of men
And a dude sitting by the door
Even the bartender is gone
Mark looks at this figure sitting by the door and he sees kind of a
He looks like a big guy not overly large, but
And before he can really take in any more detail he feels
grandpa's hand dig into
his bicep
Grandpa has mark's arm in a death grip
And he turns and he looks back at grandpa
And grandpa while holding mark's arm squeezing it is staring down at the table
Mark is looking at the table that he's at and everyone is just staring down at the table
No one is moving the room
is tense
And mark thinks maybe this guy's like some super high level criminal in the area right?
He's not familiar with this area. This could be some big drug runner. It could be
No one hit man in the area some sort of organized crime guy, but
This feels different
Sure people may be deferential towards a crime lord and their area are just scared
But something is different here
And he turns to get another look at the man
And grandpa squeezes mark's arm even harder so hard now
It's hurting him
And that is when peter nudges
mark
And hisses don't
look
And right when peter says that
The man at the door gets up out of his chair
And begins walking towards the table
Mark is sitting there and he looks up at this guy
As he's walking towards him and he gets a better look at him. He has
Shockingly red hair
He's young ish. He's a youngish man broad-shouldered
But normal looking
Not covered in these crazy tattoos doesn't look like he's been in a thousand bar fights. Doesn't look like some sort of crazy criminal
Just a normal looking guy
walking towards them
And mark is drunk at this point
And he's looking at the table of his compatriots and he's wondering what do I do?
He's looking for that social cue
Now if everyone at the table said let's get up and leave he would have got up and left with him
And he can tell that there is obviously something going on at this table. They're scared of him
But what do I do?
This guy's walking towards us now
Do I look down at my drink like that doesn't make sense to me? He's walking towards us
Mark is sitting there at the table. He makes direct eye contact with the man
And the man stops in the center of the bar
Mark looks deep into the stranger's eyes and says
What are you looking at?
When he says that
grandpa lets go of mark's arm
And everyone at that table is just pretending that none of this is happening. They're just silently staring
down at the table trying to ignore
Reality
Mark gets up
He's holding his beer in one hand. He walks over to the stranger and says we got a problem
Stranger's just staring at mark
And now for the first time this evening
Mark feels it
He feels like he's
tapped into this energy that everyone else
was feeling
Something is wrong here
Mark is staring at this young man and mark starts to wonder
Is this guy even human?
He's terrified
He's petrified in a way. He's never been scared like this before
But he doesn't know how to back down. He's almost too terrified to even move
So what he does is the same bombastic
Comments that you always make in a club when you're getting ready to fight
It's time for you to leave buddy
Trying to
Bluff his way out of this trying to get the guy to turn around and walk away
But all mark wants to do
is walk away
He feels like he's going to piss his pants right there his pride
And his fear are colliding in this moment
He can't back down
But he just wants to disappear
And when pride and fear collide it makes you make dumb decisions and mark raises his right fist
He's just going to do what he always does. He's going to knock this stranger out
And as he raises his fist to throw a punch
The stranger catches his hand
And immediately mark's skin begins to burn
He said the guy got a hold of his right wrist. He just grabbed it
Mid punch and this guy's grip is holding right onto him and he goes it felt like his skin was acid
I could feel it burning my skin
I didn't know what this dude was. I didn't know I couldn't even comprehend what could actually be happening
Was this guy was this guy like a chemical worker? Was he secreting some sort of caustic fluid?
and almost
The the pain was so intense
My brain was just kind of not working. I'm screaming in pain
And I also remember at this point. I'm holding a beer in my left hand and I smash it against this guy's face
I let out this deep roar and I just lay a left right into this dude's face
And the dude let me go
When that beer smashed into the stranger's face
He released my right wrist
turned
silently walked away
And then he left the bar
But my wrist continued to burn
I'm looking down at my wrist
Trying to figure out how he did that trying to figure out when this pain would go away when the bar keep walks back in from a back room
Pretending like none of this ever happened
Peter's family gets up from the booth
They're immediately asking is everything okay. How's everything going? Are you fine?
And I bluff yeah
Yeah, I'm fine. Just need another drink is all
But I'm terrified
And they know I'm terrified
We go back to Peter's family's house
drinking
playing cards
Just talking
We stay up
until the sun rises even grandpa
stayed up
till the morning
Which is good because I didn't want to go to sleep
And we drank and we played cards and we talked
But we never talked
about what happened in that bar
Life goes on, you know, I was just visiting for a couple weeks
I go back to the city
Start looking for work just continue my life
but
To this day
Mark's wrist
Is numb
He says right where that guy touched me. I have no feeling in that part of my wrist. It's completely numb
He said I went to the doctor get a check down and he had this little pin
And he kept poking it. He says he poked it 10 times. I can't feel anything and the doctor goes
Based on your symptoms. I think you had a mild stroke
But you definitely have no feeling you definitely cannot feel anything in your wrist
And he's told this story. He was talking about one of his girlfriends. He said that she was just a weirdo
When she would bite it she would bite his wrist as hard as she could
He wouldn't feel it
And he told her about what happened at the bar, but she just said I think the doctor is right
I think he just had a mild stroke. I don't believe anyone could be carrying acid on their skin or whatever
Maybe another bite on your wrist will persuade me
And he says
When I look back on that situation, I think that I came out of it on sheer luck
This thing could have taken me apart
But I escaped
Just out of
luck
He didn't overwhelm it with physical force. He didn't scare it away
The thing
Decided not to kill him. It wasn't because of anything
That mark did his life was literally in this stranger's hands
And he says he's asked his friend because obviously his friend was familiar with this person
Right friend was nervous the second he realized this guy was in the bar. He asked his friend
He's asked him a couple times. Hey, what was that?
You know now that he's safely at home and life has returned normal
What was up with that guy at the bar and his friend?
Responds when he asked this question his friend responds quote
It doesn't matter now
And it's better you don't know
Unquote
It's fascinating story obviously the idea of cryptids being in the woods being on the outskirts that is as old as humanity the werewolf in between towns
But when you it would make sense that you would have some of these beings interacting with us in our
infrastructure in our big cities would be perfect for cryptids to hunt
sewage sewage systems
Obviously subways things like that
But bars as well
Right and you think this was a some sort of cryptid that came out of the woods something old and ancient that the people in this area knew of
And they knew to avoid
And I keep using the word cryptid but I actually have another theory for what this could be
Recently, I think it was a week or two ago. I did an episode the missing 411
multidimensional man-bear demons versus the us army and in that one we were talking about the nephilim
We were talking about giants living up at where was it mount sin helens mount shasta one of the two
giant
red-headed
nephilim
right
And the idea of the red hair being connected to the nephilim is very very common in
Modern nephilim lore. I don't think it's actually in the bible where it's specified. They have red hair
But on a lot of modern accounts that are connected to giants or to the nephilim the nephilim are when an angel and a human woman have a child
It's
known as the nephilim red hair is very commonly connected to we did an episode about
Do the nephilim look like clowns? Is that why people find clowns so terrifying because they have pale skin and red hair?
And i'm wondering if that's what this could have been as well
Now nephilim they're usually these giant eight foot tall people
But again, that's kind of a misnomer in the bible. It says the nephilim these men were giants heroes of renown
um, and it may be not necessarily a giant physical stature
But a giant reputation a character like hercules for example
Was not physically eight nine feet tall, but he was giant in the sense that
Everyone knew who he was. He was a hero
So is that what he faced down?
This man this human looking person with red hair, but the heart
of a corrupted angel
A creature something not of this world or of heaven or of hell, but something else
All of them and nothing at the same time
That operates in this area
And the people in town know well enough that when he walks into this bar or when he walks anywhere in town
That part of town shuts down and you just pretend that he's not there
But he is
A terrifying story because it could have gone either way whether this guy was ecripted
Whether this guy was a nephilim or just some lunatic drug lord who happened to shoot acid out of his hands
Uh mark could have easily just disappeared right and the fact that this town was so terrified to even acknowledge the sky's existence
Had this guy ripped mark apart in front of all these witnesses and then left the bar
Mark would have just disappeared
They would have cleaned up the area and they would have kept a code of silence like they already keep a code of silence
This is a town of secrets
And whoever this individual was
His identity was known to the people in the town or at least his reputation was
They knew this guy was not
from around here
And they kept this secret
They hoped when they took mark out to the bar that they would never even meet this guy, right?
But he did show up and an outsider had an encounter with him
He didn't know the rules. He didn't know how you're supposed to deal with the stranger, but
To everyone else in town. This wasn't a stranger. It was
A phenomenon they knew
to avoid
One of the things that I think's easy to forget about stories like this is they are told by survivors
And there are countless stories where people go missing or people die
And we are left wondering what happened
And we never know
We don't know if it was a natural death or a natural disappearance falling down a crevasse or something like that
Because the only time we know that it's paranormal when someone survives it and says man, you won't believe what happened
I was out at a russian summer camp and the ufo showed up
Or I went to a bar and I ran into someone who wasn't quite human because this town was so good at keeping secrets was so good at following
the rules
To avoid these things that had mark lost this fight had this creature completely
decimated mark
They would have just cleaned up the mess
and gone on with their lives
peter would have a horrible secret
He invited his best friend to hang out with him
And he got his best friend killed
But the world would never know this story
It would just be one more secret
In a town full of secrets
But we know about this story because mark survived
The world of the paranormal is only known
Because of people who make it back alive
So think about that
Before you hope to someday see proof
That aliens or ghosts or cryptids exist
Because you may find proof but
You may not be lucky enough to live to tell the tale
DeadRabberRadio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also do this up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio
TikTok is @deadrabberradio
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great day guys
[Music]