Did a glitch in the Matrix change the course of the Civil War?
Is a man stalking the streets of New York City, making women poop?
Then we take a look at an interesting case of when life after death and UFOs collide today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. So almost time for the weekend
and I hope you guys have some awesome plans and if not, if you're just chilling at home, that's cool too.
I want to give a shout out to our latest Patreon supporter, Platinum Piss. Platinum Piss?
I mean it's an upgrade from a golden shower. It's Platinum Piss. Thank you so much for
supporting the show. That really, really helps out a lot. If you can't support the Patreon,
that's fine too. Just help get the word out about the show. That helps a lot as well.
I totally understand some people just can't do the Patreon thing. Just help people about the show.
Helps it grow. We also have a merch store if you want to look into that. And if you are a Patreon
supporter, I'm still sending out the stickers. So give me your address. We're going to get you
one of these cool stickers. I'm getting emails from people who've received these stickers. I'll
reveal the design eventually, but I want to get out a lot of these stickers. So thank you so much
for your support. Platinum, we're going to start off in, let's take the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're going up nice and slow. And then we're back in time. We're floating over Maryland. Now it's
old timey cannonballs and muskets. Civil war time. Balls flying everywhere. Deadly balls. And we're
just like bouncy balls. Not a balloon party. The North and the South have collided in the field
of battle. It's brother versus brother. Dad versus son. Everyone's getting shot and stuff.
And like cannonballs. Now we're way up in the Dead Rabbit Durgible. We don't have to worry about
none of this stuff, but we're flying over the battlefield. We do kind of have to worry about
it because the fate of the nation is decided on this thing. Are we going to be a nation of Freeman
or a nation of slavery? It's all going to be decided now. It's fall of 1862 and Confederate
General Robert E. Lee has had several decisive victories. We're flying the Durgible up when
we see General Lee being like, "Ha ha ha. I've had several decisive victories, but I'm ready to take
DC itself. I have a plan. We're going to get out of the South because it's kind of muggy down here.
It's super hot. It's big old mosquitoes. We're going to move into the North. We're going to take
DC. Now he has 50,000 troops. He has to fight through an army of 85,000 Union troops only to
face another 72,000 men protecting DC. But Lee thinks he can do it. He has a plan. He's going to hit
Harper's Ferry. He's going to take that first. 12,000 troops versus their 50,000. No sweat. He sends
out orders. Special Order 191. He decides to split up his forces. So he sends all these messages out
to all of his other field commanders. They didn't have Wi-Fi back then. You had to give a note to
someone and they ride on their horse and they go to this other dude and they hand him the note. That's
how it was done. September 9th, 1862. Corporal Barton Mitchell is with the 27th Indiana Regiment.
He's about to change the course of American history. He's walking through a field
and he sees a note wrapped around three cigars. He's like, "What? This is kind of weird. He's
smoking the cigars. Oh yeah. Nothing like these Virginia Slims, but I'm from the North. So
nothing like these good New York Slims. He's smoking these things." Now, he's scanning over the letter.
He's using this as an ashtray and he sees at the bottom it says, "By command of General Robert E. Lee
and it's signed R.H. Chilton, Assistant Adjunct General." So he's like, "I don't know who this
Chilton dude is, but I know who General Lee is. He's had several decisive victories. He takes it to
his commanding officer. It goes up through the Union chain of command and the dude who gets it
is Colonel Samuel Pittman." And he's looking at it. He knew Chilton before the war. He knew his
handwriting and he's looking at it. He goes, "This is official. This actually came from Chilton himself."
It detailed where they were going to attack, locations, numbers. It was basically, it was the
battle plan Robert E. Lee sent out to say, "This is what we're going to do to take the war to the
north." The Union finds this. Now the north, instead of just sitting there, having to have a defensive
posture in this upcoming battle, can make a move. It results in the battle of Antium. It's the bloodiest
day on the war and it halts Lee's march on Washington. People predict if Lee had been able to take
Washington D.C. would that have been a major political blow? Would it have been a morale
blow? Would it have been a strategic victory? There's a lot of people who go that losing
this Special Order 191 to the north was a pivotal moment. Some people go, "Eh, he may not have been
able to do that stuff anyways," but this allowed the north to preempt that type of attack. It
definitely would have bolstered morale in the south. This stopped General Lee from taking Washington
D.C. So they still have the copy of this letter. And what's interesting was this letter was written
to General A.P. Hill, because there's multiple of these orders now of Special Order 191. They're
sent out to all these other field commanders. One of them, this one was specifically addressed to
General A.P. Hill. It was written by Chilton by command of General Robert E. Lee. This is all,
we still have this note, because it's an important piece of American history, but A.P. Hill actually
got his letter. He still has it, and we still have the one wrapped in cigars. Both are authentic.
What? Each general only had one letter assigned to them. And again, this wasn't like someone ran
to Kinkos and made a copy of it. These are all handwritten. And A.P. Hill got his Special Order,
looked at it, goes, "That's a pretty good plan," puts it in his jacket. Why was Hill sent two
letters? Everyone else only got one. And the one that Hill got said by command of General Robert E.
Lee, and it was signed Stonewall Jackson. R.H. Chilton, after the war, was asked about this.
Because again, this wasn't just some, this changed the war. A lot of people do believe this changed
the war. They asked Chilton about it after the war, and he goes, "Oh, no, no, no, I wrote that.
Stonewall Jackson didn't write that letter. I wrote that letter, and I sent it out, and it
must have not got to him. But I don't remember who I gave it to." Because they asked, "Why was it in
the middle of the field?" He's like, "I don't know, bro. I did my part. I wrote the letter and gave it
out, and then it just kind of disappeared into the ether." So it's interesting to think that the
letter, there shouldn't have been two copies of this letter. First off, and I should have said
this earlier, I got most of this information from a very well-written Reddit post by SlutforBacon
on the Unresolved Mysteries subreddit. So I wanted to give SlutforBacon a shout out. But I really,
really appreciate it. And I did some additional research, but I got a lot of it. I had never
heard of this until I had read that Reddit post, so thank you for that. Obviously, because of the
scope of the show, and I think what we're interested in, the first thing that I thought of was, like,
time travel. Right? That somebody interfered with time to drop the... Think about, "Dude, fields are
no one to be big and like, full of nothing." The fact that this guy was walking by, the time
traveler was like, "You know, I should bribe this guy with a couple cigarettes." Actually, maybe he
put the note, and the dude walked by it, and the time traveler was like, "Ding it." He puts a cigar in
the note, and the guy walks by it, and the time traveler was like, "Ding it!" Finally, he, going back
and forth in time, buying more cigars. He finally adds the three. That's a magical number for the
guy to notice it picks it up and stops the South marching into the North. It's very, very interesting.
Harry Turtledove, he writes books about alternative history. This was a plot point in one of his books.
"Was Special Order 191 a glitch in the Matrix? Was it the result of time travelers setting time right?
So the United States would remain a union instead of a Confederacy of States,
freeing the slaves and creating a path towards a better future? Was it a simple issue of two
people writing letters and not being aware of anything that's going on? Bad management."
Maybe that's actually the most likely scenario, but it's also fascinating to think that a simple,
even on that level, a simple mistake could change the course of a war. But time travel,
glitch in the Matrix, the Chilton, right it and then hand it to someone who just kind of faded
faded away. What if the person who was carrying it was abducted by aliens and then Chilton got his
mind wiped? I can say ridiculous things all day long, but the really important story is that due
to a small issue, literally the size of a piece of paper, the union prevented military
catastrophe. So glitch in the Matrix, alien abduction, time travel, or just poorly managed
military forces. I like the time traveler thing because I just like the idea of a time traveler
coming from the year 3000 being like, "Dude, if I have to buy this guy one more cigar, I'm done.
I don't care who wins the war now." But eventually three cigars was enough to get that envelope
noticed. But platinum, let's hop back in that Dead Rabbit Durgible, we're actually going,
we're leaving behind old, timey America, we're coming to modern day New York City, the glitz,
the glamour, the muggings, the stabbings, everything you love about New York. If you love those last
two, you love the purge. But we're not going to purge New York. That's four years from now.
We're going to modern day New York, modern day being 2018. On July 31st, 2018, we're going to hit
the clubs, dude. I'm liking good. You're looking good too, dude. You lost weight. Good job. We're
sitting there unless you want to put on weight and then, did you put on weight? Are you more muscular?
Good job. Insert compliment here. And we're walking around, we're dressed in the nines.
We're going to the hottest nightclub in town. We're dancing and stuff like that.
We're hanging out, dancing, grooving. And we see this girl walking. We see, it's a club. There's
a ton of women. But anyways, we have to focus in on this one particular girl. And we see her on
her phone. She's like, swiping left. Which one's the bad one? I think swiping left means they don't
like to do it on Tinder. And then they see, ooh, I match him and they do a swipe to the right. And
then, and then she meets with his dude, right? So he comes into the bar and we see them dancing
together and stuff like that. And romance is kind of cute. And then he's like this charming and
successful. He's this good looking guy. He's no dead rabbit radio host. But you know, he's all
right. He's all right. They go out on a date. They have a great time. They go out on another date.
They have another great time. They go on a third date. And you know, or this is going,
I can't remember the last time I waited three dates. But anyways, I guess chivalry is not dead.
This gentleman waits for three dates. He invites her back to his place. So they go back to his
place. The dancing's over. It's time for a little bit of love. Oh, my stomach, she says. Oh, what?
Oh my, oh, can you give me a second? Oh, you're like, are you really going to make noises for
the next five minutes? Next seven minutes, maybe. She starts pooping, right? She starts pooping. Now
she's in the toilet. She's pooping everywhere. And the guy doesn't seem to really care. He's just
like, okay, honey, whenever you're done. And she's like, oh my God, I don't think I've ever, I think,
I think the eye of Cthulhu has opened up inside of me. I think this is my fate for eternity.
It's okay. Just keep going. Let it come out. She eventually, there's a break. It's like the eye of
the storm, right? You know, when you're that sick to your stomach, there's a short period of time
where you're able to at least get up off the toilet and maybe like get some water,
maybe some crackers before you have to go back in there. Grab your phone. Sometimes grab your
tablet so you can really watch a show in there. Before she got into the bathroom, she pooped
a little bit in her underwear, right? So what happened was she's like, oh, you know, I pooped.
I pooped a lot. She's like three. That's how she describes it. My tummy made me poop poop.
She realizes after, she realizes in that short eye of the storm period that she actually pooped
her underwear. Like she wasn't able to get in the bathroom soon enough. She's like, oh, great. I'm
going to smell like poop the rest of the night. So, I mean, she has better things to worry about,
i.e. the storm is moving on. It's going to get bad again. The eyes almost over. But she does hop
out of the bathroom for a bit, get some water. And when she comes back in her date, her Tinder date,
the charming successful man, is sniffing her underwear, smelling her poop. And she runs out
in horror. You can keep the underwear. I don't know how far she got before she had to knock on a
neighbor's door and be like, I really, really have to go. But anyway, she runs out. Now, she tells
a friend of hers, I had the worst date last night. Trust me when I say that, you're not going to be
able to talk to me. I had the worst day last night at horrible diarrhea and the dude was smelling my
dirty underwear. That in and of itself is just would be a weird new story, right? Just a weird
new story. But apparently, this is happening all over New York City. Glasgow, Glasgow Leeds,
District of Columbia. Maybe it was Robert E. Lee. Maybe it was Robert E. Lee's great descendant.
He goes, if I can't take DC, I'll make him poop. I'll make all those northerners poop their pants.
This guy is in all these major cities. And the story goes around and people are like, hey, listen,
my sister's cousin's best friend was on Tinder. And she went on a date and her stomach started
to hurt and she had to poop really bad. And then the dude was smelling her poop. And people start
sharing this story all over. And it's weird because nobody has firsthand accounts of this. It's always
my sister's cousin, this girl that my friend went to school with. No one will admit, which to be
fair, no one's going to be like, excuse me, I was the one who pooped their pants. Please. It's always
this back around stuff. What's interesting though is that it sounds like an urban legend. It sounds
like a game of telephone. No one can ever point out. But people have said when you look at those
cities, New York City, Glasgow Leeds in DC, they've actually thought he may have gone to school in
Europe and then moved to the United States. He was working in finance or something like that.
Maybe Harry Potter. Maybe he's like, I'm done at Hogwarts. Time to go make some people poop.
But I can't you just use a magical spell. He's like, oh, I'd much rather use that.
That was the thing. So using that joke as a segue, this newspaper called The Tab in the UK
did an investigation on this. It was Annie Lord. She actually, because this conspiracy theory,
this whatever you want to call it, has been going around basically the internet. It's basically,
it sounds like a game of telephone. The story had been going around. So this journalist, Annie Lord,
looks into it. She calls the police. The police are like, she actually calls the police in Leeds,
is where the story first popped up. And they go, we haven't heard any cases of this.
She did. The journalist also called up a sex therapist. Sex therapist goes, you know what,
it actually does fit the profile of a type of guy like this. I've heard this before. One,
scat fetishes are more common than you would think. It's more common than you would think.
Pooping, making people poop and eating poop. Sorry. Sorry, you're eating your Jello pudding.
You're like, what's this episode about? I hope it's not about poop. Jason never does poop episodes.
This week, he's getting a big scoop of it. Anyways, he just melted chocolate barg
with the peanuts in it. Anyways, it's very common. I've heard that before too. It's probably one of
the most secretive common fetishes. You know, like people have a foot fetish. People have a hair fetish.
But poop is like one of the big ones too. But people don't talk about it for a good reason. It's
super disgusting, right? But anyways, so she said that's actually paid. That actually sounds like
someone who has that fetish because it's not just about eating poop. It's about degrading the other
person. Either you're getting pooped or sorry. Platinum piss is like, listen, I know my name
kind of goes with the theme, but I didn't sign up for this. I didn't sign up for this. Sorry,
Platinum. But people like to get pooped on. Not me. Don't do this to me. I don't want this to happen.
Some people like to get pooped on or poop on other people. And making people poop is part of the
fetish because it degrades them. So the sex therapist goes, that actually makes sense. Like,
of course, there's no proof this guy actually exists. But it's interesting that it does seem to be in
those four cities. And they said, like, if you had a job in finance, that might make sense.
Twitter would be the perfect way because you could fake everything. You could delete accounts,
things like that. And you get to take the super hot chick back to your apartment. And then she's
like, oh, her stomach's super hurting. And that is part of the fetish is making her embarrassed,
making her feel pain, and then eventually making her poop everywhere. It could just be an internet
rumor going around too. But it does seem to go into, it does seem to be a little bit realistic. So
if you live in one of those four cities, and you are a young woman looking for love,
always make sure to swipe left if that guy bears a striking resemblance to Robert E. Lee,
because it might be his descendant. Or, you know, just don't use Tinder. That's,
I don't get it. I don't get it. I wouldn't hang out with people. I mean, obviously,
I hang out with strangers. That's how you get to know people. But like going on a phone and like
looking at people or going on the internet and looking, I've had blind dates before. I've had,
actually, let me phrase it, I've had one blind date before. I think I told you that story. I tried
to convince her I was like, this date sucks, but I was too nice to end it. So I told her I was a
vampire. And she wouldn't leave. I told her that I could feel the organs shifting in my body.
She wouldn't leave, dude. I was too nice. And then I told her that I had a cookie
in the shape of an alien in my fridge that I was like four years old. And I talked to it.
The funny part was that part of the story was true. I actually did have an alien cookie I bought
us at Starbucks. It was so, so awesome. I refused to eat it. I named him Grigo, and he hung out in
my fridge. And I also had a jug of milk that I bought the day I moved into that apartment.
And then five years later, the jug of milk was still in there and his name was Melky.
I swear Melky was sentient at some point. Probably wasn't sentient the whole five years,
but at some point when that cream, oh dude, it was so gross. Did I have to say that? Do I have to
have that part? You're like, no, what? I didn't think it was gross until you said that part. I
thought five year old milk was totally normal as you're talking trash about someone making people
poop. Actually, you know what? I will talk trash because I didn't make people drink that milk.
Nobody drank that milk, right? I didn't make you drink that milk. I might introduce you when
you came over. I'd show you Grigo and Melky, but you know what's funny? I got evicted from that
apartment and I never threw out the milk. So when they came in, they probably like these people were
like, oh dude, he got evicted. He's bum. And they opened up my fridge and they're like, oh,
it's such a long day at work. I'm not going to check the expiration date on this milk. Glug, glug.
He basically went from milk to butter to some unknown element. I'm sure some scientists in
Livermore laboratories would have loved to see what was in that milk. It was his own pocket universe.
So let's wave goodbye to all the lovely ladies of New York, Glasgow, DC and Leeds. We hope you never
meet the man on the poop patrol. We are headed out to Russia. So platinum, let's take up this
carbonic hop to reflux out to Russia. So earlier in this week, we did a story about a man who was
kidnapped by aliens to work on a berry farm. He's like, I'm out of here. The only berry farm I work
on is knots. And I'm not working on this one. What are you talking about? You're from Russia. You
don't even know what knots berry farm is. He's like, you're right. I don't. It was just a reference. I
like Snoopy. So knots berry farm. Man, that was like the second cousin of theme parks. Right? You
had like Disneyland, which was like the dope one, right? That was like your cool uncle. And then you
had six flags. I don't even think they're still around. That was your uncle who went to prison.
And the knots berry farm was your cousin who never really made it. It's like they tried really hard.
They tried really, really hard. And you saw like kind of struggle through high school and college.
You're just like, oh man, I know if Barry could get his act together, he'd be really cool. But
knots berry. It's knots berry farm still around. Anyways, platinum. Let's go out. We're going to
Ufa Russia. It's nighttime. And there's a woman and her brother walking at night. We'll call her
Mary. It's a good name, right? Mary and Joseph. That's a bad combination. Mary and her brother
Hank. There's typical Russian names. Mary and Hank are walking through Ufa Russia. They're
enjoying the countryside and it's a peaceful night sky. No clouds. Just a bevy of stars in front of
them. And they see a pink star and a blue star. And they start to kind of float around and interact
with each other. Now, Mary and Hank are looking at each other and they're like, that's kind of weird.
Stars don't normally do that, right? But they don't really have time to process it because the stars
begin to dance amongst each other. And then a sphere appears out of the pink star and it's coming.
That vast distance in space doesn't matter. The white light coming from that pink star is getting
closer and closer. It's a sphere coming down to earth. It flies down. Now it's hovering,
not too far in front of them. It's hovering off the ground. And Mary, here's a voice. A voice she
hasn't heard in three years. It's the voice of her son who's passed away. Mom, watch. Nothing will happen.
Mary looks at this hovering light. She says, son, how did you know I was going to be here?
You like this theater of the mind? Son, how did you know I was going to be here?
And her son tells her, I knew you and uncle would be here. I just knew it.
The sphere is so bright. It's like daytime in this glen. It's super bright. They can see
everything. There's a butterfly hanging out. A bunch of crickets are waking up. It's daytime.
And then her son is standing there holding flowers. Now I'm realizing this now.
It doesn't say how old her son is. When I first read this, I imagined him, he was like 10 years old,
right? I thought, that's weird. Not that a 10 year old is coming down from spaceship,
but what I'm about to explain to you. So reading it now, I'm thinking, oh, he's an adult son.
Like even when I said his voice, he's like, mama, mama, watch. Nothing will happen. I was reading
it like a little boy. I'm thinking about it now more clearly. I think he's an adult son. Because
when I think of sons, I think of like little kids, right? So you can choose to imagine the rest of
the story as a 10 year old boy, which is how I thought of it. And I was like, what? This is weird.
Or you can imagine it as what it probably was. So this woman, her son is standing there and please
wear an Oshkosh be gosh. She's like, Stuart, get away. Anyway, started to ruin the emotional impact
of the story. Her dead son is now standing in front of her and he's holding a bouquet of flowers.
The mom is super touched. And then a woman steps out of the sphere holding a little baby,
little baby. And the son goes, this is our child emotions to the little baby,
the little daughter that the woman's holding again. I thought he was 10. I was like, that's
I honestly thought that I was like, why? And I was thinking, is it like time travel?
Like I know I've totally ruined the emotion of this story. I was thinking, why is a 10 year old
have a little baby? Why is he married to this adult woman? And I remember thinking, well, you know,
because he's a space. Space. It's like time travel. For whatever reason, I didn't comprehend an adult
son dying three years ago. For some reason, I thought I was a kid. Makes far more sense if he's in his
20s, right? And he's 10 year old, if a dead 10 year old showed up in front of his mom and goes,
this is my adult wife and this is our baby. The mom's going to be like, you have some spleying to
do. So I think what's an adult son? Anyways, man, I totally plan this to be super emotional.
Anyways, forget I said any of this. There's an adult son. He goes, mom, nothing will happen. And
then she's like, what? And then he hops out. We replay the events and he's standing there,
strapping young lad. And he goes, this is our child points to the little girl. And then the woman
and the child disappear and then three dudes walk out of the light too. And they're all wearing
these sparkly clothes. And the son goes, and these are my friends. These are my age appropriate
friends. These are the old men that I'm hanging out with. I am an adult man as well. I just died
a couple of years ago. And the mom's like super happy. And then the woman and the child reappear
and now they're both dressed in super blue sparkly clothes. And the son goes, goodbye, mother. Goodbye,
uncle. I love you guys. You guys like totally rock. And then a cold wind snaps through the area.
The sphere disappears. And then they look up and they see the blue and the pink star
dance a little bit longer and then they fade from view. Despite the fact, despite the fact,
I botched that because I thought it was a 10 year old boy. I do think that's a really
interesting story. One, I mean, talk about the peace that mother must have felt. One, knowing that
knowing that her son was not 10. That'd be the first thing, right? She's like, that's weird. He
died in his 20s. Why did he appear as a 10 year old wearing suspenders and not should be gosh.
That'd be her first sign. Secondly, that even though her son died, which must be the most tragic
thing, that scares me the most about having kids. One, there are a lot of money to the take a ton
of your time. And three, I can't. Oh my God, I don't have a kid and it paralyzes me with fear,
the idea of losing a kid. And I don't have one. That'd be like me going, I hope I never lose
my switch. I don't own a switch. I care less. But like, I can't imagine holding something.
Like if I lost it, for whatever reason, this podcast disappeared tomorrow, I'd be like, well,
it was a fun ride. You know, I can't do it no more, but it was awfully fun. It was cool thing
about some cool people. I'd move on with my life. I can't imagine holding a child.
And then like losing it someday. Oh my God, I can't imagine that.
And so the piece that this mother must have felt to see her son again in the flesh.
It's an interesting story. I think that there is a big crossover between a lot of people have the
theory that you know, like the aliens are actually demons and stuff like that. And I don't know if
I've done an episode on that. I've mentioned it before. I think it's pretty common conspiracy
theory. I don't think that's why I've done an episode on it specifically. I've talked about it
before, but I think there probably is just like we're seeing through the course of the show,
there's a big connection between Bigfoot and aliens. We've done a lot of episodes on that.
I think there might be a connection between aliens and spirituality in general. I think the world
of paranormal, we try to divide it up with ghost hunters and UFO hunters and Bigfoot hunters and
stuff like that. Demonologists. But it's possible that they're just far more connected than we could
ever really know. And whether or not this was a visitation of angels that took the form of
extraterrestrial visitors, whether or not this was a simply ghostly activity that took the form
of UFO visitors. We have to say it's possible that it was demons trying to fool the family and
taking the form of her. I don't believe that's the case, but you know, there would be people who would
have that scenario as well. But I think it's a very, again, despite the fact that I got the ages
wrong in my head, I think it's a very touching story. And even if the child was, even if the child
was, the way I was reading it was that her son died when he was younger, and this was her showing
that even in the afterlife, life continues. He was able, even though he, this is how I imagined it,
even though he had died when he was younger, he'd still been able to fulfill his life,
getting married, having children himself and stuff like that. She was seeing him as a younger being,
but he had matured in the afterlife. That's how I read it. But again, now saying it out loud,
I think he was an adult when he died. It was just this weird thing. But again, when I think,
I don't even like thinking about children passing away, but for whatever reason, I couldn't imagine
like an adult passing away, a son passing away. When I hear that term, I always think of children
and it just rips my heart out. I can't imagine. I hate, that's one of the, actually one of the
things I hate about doing this podcast is the amount of stuff I read. I just read sometimes
some horrible articles, just stuff that, real sad stuff. I try to avoid it at this point in my life.
When I was younger, you know, you'd be like, oh, let's watch this crazy Syrian war footage and stuff
like that. And you get to a point where you're just like, it's just, just reading headlines sometimes.
You just, I can't imagine having to go through that. So the idea that a mother could find peace,
that her mother could see that her son died, but the life didn't end. He got married and had a kid
and the afterlife he's making friends. He's still able to visit her, not only visit her, but he knows
where she's at. Even if she never saw him again after that, just the idea of having proof that
not only is there an afterlife, but you continue to grow and live and be happy in this afterlife is
incredibly peaceful. Incredibly peaceful moment. So I wanted to share that story with you. I want,
I honestly believe that in death, there is a continuation of life. And the passing of us from
being alive to being dead is similar to us being born. When we're in the womb, the only
universe we know is the womb. It's all we know. We may hear sounds and feelings and hear voices.
Music we can't really describe as we're in the womb. We don't know what's going on. All we know
is the womb. And then we come out and everything's colorful and loud and bright. We have these new
sensations. We have taste. We have touch, sight and sound. I think that's what it's like when you die.
Like you can't, we're in the womb. This is simply another womb. We can't comprehend what it's like
outside the womb that we're in. And it may be scary. It's very scary, I think, to think this is all
there is, but just like a child in a womb thinks this is all there is. This is my whole reality.
And those nine months or its entire existence, it can't comprehend anything outside the womb.
We're basically just infants. And when we pass from this life to the next,
we're reborn into a reality we couldn't even comprehend. I truly believe that. I truly believe
that. So I hope that gives, it gives me peace. I hope it gives you guys peace as well to know that
death is not the ending. It's just the beginning of another adventure. We're being born into a new
reality. Maybe it's as simple as being reincarnated back onto this earth as a new consciousness.
Or maybe it's something we couldn't even begin to comprehend. But either way, I believe life continues.
[Music]
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
Twitter is @deadrabberradio. DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true
crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]