What would you do if someone presented you with a book that if you read it would tell
you exactly the way you die?
And then we travel to British Columbia to meet a young homeless man wandering the streets
of a city looking for a computer so he can email his mom.
Instead he finds himself on a collision course with a witch, a zombie, and a voice in his
head screaming "Kill, Kill, Kill" today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garbender, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a great
day too, I hope you guys are having tons of fun out in the world doing all the stuff that
you're doing.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, everyone give a round of applause for our newest Patreon supporter, writing himself
into Dead Rabbit Command.
Give it up for Horseboyo.
Woohoo!
Yeah, get on boy jump on his back riding around like a horse.
Like his name says.
Horseboyo, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode if you guys can't support
the Patreon I totally understand.
Just helps read the word about the show that really, really, really helps out a lot.
It really does, it helps the show grow.
Now Horseboyo, get that bit out of your mouth, he's like not a real horse, it's just a nickname.
Get that bit out of your mouth but I'm staying on the saddle.
I'm gonna toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible, we're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit
Command, fly us all the way out to a library.
We're walking around this library, it's like any library you've seen before, any city library
that you can walk around, there's books and nerds and then it's surprisingly hot librarians
nowadays, have you guys noticed that?
I don't know what it is, nowadays librarians, they're just hot, they don't even have to
let their hair down or take their glasses off, it's not like 'cause she's all that,
are they nerdy or hot type of thing, they're just hot, have you guys noticed that?
I don't know, maybe it's just me.
But you're like okay, you pervert, I'm not allowed in the libraries anymore.
I'm outside on this segment 'cause I'm in a restraining order.
However, you guys get to walk around the library and you're looking for a book.
Now we don't know the name of the book, we don't know what part of the Dewey Decimal
system it would be and probably dark magic occult knowledge, I don't think there's a
Dewey Decimal number for that.
We're looking for a book that may or may not exist, in fact, as far as we know, there's
only three people who know of this book.
So with teeters on the edge of an urban legend, a fictional tale, right, this could be completely
made up, or something that's real that was never catalogued because in a sense you wouldn't
want this book around.
There is a guy online, he goes by the name Few Conflict 4038, he told this story, we're
gonna call him Joey for short, but Joey, he normally posts online about like car transams
and stuff like that, like hey is this muffler look cool, I don't know, I'm not a car guy,
I have no opinion on that, he talks about music and stuff like that, he talks about
relatively normal stuff and that's kind of what I like when I see stuff this bizarre
online.
I've said this before, if someone's always talking about once in a lifetime paranormal
events, it makes it seem less true, right, but if someone is just talking about ordinary
stuff all the time and then one day posts something like this, just out of the blue,
I'm not saying 100% that I know this is factual because I don't, but it does add a lot of
weight to this story, and let's take a look at this.
What Joey says is, he went online and he goes, I'm looking for a book and I want to know
if anybody knows about this book, I know about it because my mother used to tell me about
this book and she knows about it because her father owned it.
And Joey comes from a Hispanic family as well, so Hispanic family, we're about two
generations back, Joey's grandfather owned a book and this book, if you read it, would
tell you exactly how you were going to die.
Joey says that he's looking for this book and not necessarily like he needs possession
of it, Joey's going online and he's like, has anyone heard about this?
Does anyone know anything about this?
He posted about it in the Urban Legends subreddit and he's like, I haven't been able to find
anything online about it.
Was this something that my grandpa told my mom to scare her to kind of keep her mind
there, it's like you better go to bed honey or I'm going to make you read that book, you're
going to find out you die, you die in your sleep when you're nine.
Did he use it to scare the mom into doing things?
Was this something that actually existed?
Because Joey's never seen the book.
So that's kind of what prompted this and he wasn't able to find anything online, he doesn't
have a ton of information to go off of.
But he did add this and this really I think is the thrust of the story when he was talking
a little bit more about the book.
His mom had told him that people who read the book went insane because they became so paranoid
trying to stop the way that they would die.
In first glance, if someone came to you with a book and they said if you read this book
and it's funny, it's not like an envelope, it's not like a page in the book, I imagine
you're like, okay, come on, all this Jacob stuff is super boring.
When does Edward come back into the story and then tell me how I'll die?
I don't know how thick the book is.
I don't know if there's a plot, you're like, you're too bored, you're like, I don't want
to read tonight, but you're going to find out how you die.
Yeah, I'll read more tomorrow.
I'm too busy watching Cobra Kai.
Like, was it a real page turner or was it just like you opened it up and it said you
will die?
You'll see this is the thing like imagine, I imagine you open the book up and it says
you'll die in your sleep.
It doesn't specify, at least according to Joey's description, when you'll die, just how you
will die.
If I read that, I thought, okay, I'm going to live to be, you know, 80, 90 and I'll die
in my sleep.
It's pretty good.
What if it said you will be buried alive?
Like, at that point, you know you're being murdered.
You know you're the victim of some brutal crime.
You open the book up and it says you will bleed out in an abandoned basement.
Like, it would depend, right?
If it was a good death, you'll die in a hospital surrounded by your loved ones.
It's like you're on an adventure and it's on the end and you're like, oh, there's a
little drawing of you laying in a bed.
Like that would be fine.
Like see, that's the gamble, right?
If I told you, listen, you could open this book up and it'll tell you exactly how you
die.
First off, would you do it?
Would you read that book?
And it's funny because the way Joey, and this is a very, very short post, the way Joey
has presented it is we don't know, it doesn't sound like the mother ever looked at the book
and we don't know if the grandpa is even still alive.
But would you look at that book?
Would you open that book up?
If somebody said this book will tell you exactly how you are going to die, would you do it?
And I think it would drive you insane because if it told you in a year, if it told you the
timeline, I think it would be less traumatic, right?
You're like, oh, buried alive.
I'm not buried alive, but it's 25 years from now.
Time to party it up.
Like you know what, if it's farther off in the future, no matter how horrific it is,
you're like falling a wheat thresher, what, I don't even hang out at farms.
But you know, it's not going to happen until I'm 82, so maybe it's some soil in green situation.
I'm feeding somebody.
So whatever.
But if it just said you will fall in a wheat thresher, you would drive you nuts.
And if you knew it was no matter what you did in life, you were going to die by falling
in a wheat thresher, you first thing you would do is you'd move to a big city, right?
You'd be as far away from farms as possible.
And then you would not want to live, I'm assuming by like any roads, right?
In case like a wheat thresher was driving through the Macy's parade in New York, you're
out there with your balloons, you're like, yay, and then you fall in the wheat thresher
float.
But no matter what you did, something would make you die in a wheat thresher.
You would end up becoming a punk rock band called the Wheat Thresher.
You're like at the concert and you're dancing like, oh, who's this band opening up for slip
knot?
And they're like, it's Wheat Thresher.
You're like, what?
Get in here and move from the music.
And they're like, it's Wheat Thresher.
And you're like, no.
And then the band stomps you to death.
That's their signature move.
They stomp a single person to death each show.
Yeah, like it would drive you insane if it was something.
Again, if it was you dying bed, you dying a hospital, you dying your sleep, you'd be
like, OK, even if that happened tomorrow, you'd be like, oh, OK, it doesn't give me the exact
date.
But I don't think you would never sleep again.
You would assume that'd be a peaceful death.
But if it was like killed in a mass shooting, stabbed in the brain, you could stop naming
the worst possible things you can think of.
That would make you more paranoid.
That would make you 100 times.
You wouldn't be able to enjoy life, right?
You would constantly be worried about someone stabbing you in the brain during a mass shooting,
oddly enough.
Yeah, so does this book exist?
That's the first question.
And it would be terrifying if it did.
I'm a fan and a believer of items like this.
Like, if this story turns out to be totally fake and some sort of ARG, I apologize for
wasting your time.
But I do believe items like this can exist.
Most objects are one of those things that I do personally believe in.
From haunted dolls to things like this.
Ancient texts.
Not so ancient.
I mean, I'm sure somewhere in some used bookstore, somewhere in the world right now, there's
a copy of a paperback Dime Store romance novel published in 1987.
That is cursed.
It has some sort of dark energy attached to it.
I believe in that stuff.
I've come across that stuff personally.
Did I ever tell you, I told you the guys, the story about the doll we found in the backyard
that hypnotized me and Jackie.
I told you guys that story, right?
Put in the comments or email me if I never told you that story.
Like, no Jason, you clearly didn't tell me that time where you were hypnotized by a doll.
I'm pretty sure I told that story.
But anyways, if I didn't, I'll tell it in a future episode.
I believe in those things because I've come across those things.
This story fits with things.
I've never come across a book that would tell me if I was dead, but that's why I'm so fascinated
by this, even though there's not a lot of information to go off of.
And two, if it did exist, would you read it?
That'd be the big question because it's a gamble.
If it was a piece of...and again, not knowing the date.
If it just said the way you died, that's the big difference.
If it said I was going to die violently at the age of 92, I'd be fine with that.
Because I know I could...I know that I could be as violent as I wanted to other people.
People are beating me up and I'm like, "Haha, nothing will stop me till I'm 92."
And they throw me in prison.
And I'm like, "Oh, I probably shouldn't have been violent towards all those random people.
Now I'm going to be in prison until I'm 92."
If it told you the date, that'd be one thing, no matter how brutal it was, you could at
least not be paranoid until that last year of your life.
But if it was just like, you are going to be crushed by a wall and you knew it was going
to work because it happened with everyone else who read that book.
They ended up dying the way that the book told them to.
You would become super paranoid because you don't know if it happens while you're reading
the book.
It happens a hundred years from now.
So would you read that book knowing that it could either give you peace of mind, that
it'll be a very peaceful death, and there's nothing you can do to change that peaceful
death.
You could go skydiving, you could do all these crazy sports and stunts.
I'm the next evil, kind of evil.
It doesn't say anything about me.
I'm sure you might be able to break all the bones in your body and still be alive.
The book's not that specific, but you would have a freedom knowing that you were going
to die in your sleep.
You're like, "Well, I know I'm not going to die following an airplane.
I've always wanted to go skydiving."
You know what I mean?
It's super interesting, but if you open that book and it was a bad ending, it was a choose-your-an-adventure
that you can't turn to page one and start over, would you open it?
Forbidden knowledge.
Like at what point do you access it?
In my 20s, I probably would have read the book.
But it's funny because at 45, it turned 46 in about two weeks.
I'm much closer to dying than I was when I was 20.
Well, it doesn't seem like that.
I was a knucklehead in my 20s, but I don't think I would read it now.
I think it probably would drive me insane.
But what would you do?
Very, very interesting.
Sorry, right?
Very interesting dilemma.
Would you read the book or not?
Does it exist?
Who knows.
It might be sitting in someone's library somewhere.
Waiting to be read.
Waiting to be innocently picked up by somebody, not knowing what it is.
They read it and they wouldn't believe it.
They wouldn't know the lineage of it.
They'd be like, "What?
It says that I'm going to die.
It says I'm going to die by dismissing a book, throwing it over my shoulder and knocking
over a huge thing of molten steel."
He's reading it in his molten steel factory.
It's not going to make sense.
So who knows?
Horseboy, oh, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Carbentercopter where we are
leaving behind this molten steel factory as a tidal wave is chasing us.
Sorry, we can't save everyone.
We have room, but we don't have time to pick you up.
Horseboy, oh, take us out of here.
We are headed all the way out to British Columbia.
[imitates horse noises]
Specifically, we're headed to Abbotsford in British Columbia.
It's November 1st, 2016.
And before we get started, I want to give a shout out to the person who recommended this
story to me, Brew.
Brew emailed me this story quite a long time ago.
Quite a long time ago, I got his email and I don't know why I waited so long to tell
this one.
This is a really cool story.
On November 1st, 2016, in the town of Abbotsford, there's a young man walking down the street.
His name is Gabriel Brandon Kline.
On this particular morning, Gabriel's walking around town and people can tell something's
wrong with him.
Even though on video camera, video surveillance footage that we have, he looks like he's smiling,
he looks normal, right?
He looks like anyone else walking into the store.
He wasn't being video-taped.
A lot of witnesses said, "Yeah, we noticed this guy walking down the street.
He was screaming at the top of his lungs.
He was shouting at people randomly."
Oddly enough, when he walks into a liquor store, he has a big smile on his face.
He's not screaming.
He's not drawing any attention to himself, which is probably smart on his behalf because
he's actually going into shoplift.
And we see on video him shoplifting two bottles of alcohol and throwing them in his backpack
and then just walking out of the store.
Now like I said, this wasn't the town he grew up in.
He actually was originally in Alberta, Canada.
But early in his childhood, early in his childhood, he knew there was something wrong with him.
He was having these delusions.
He was believing things that weren't real and he was hearing voices and he said he had
two voices in his head.
A good voice and an evil voice.
The evil voice he named Lucy and she would tell him to think awful thoughts, to do awful
things.
And as his delusions grew, he ended up fleeing Alberta because he believed he was being chased
by three different organizations, white supremacists, the Hell's Angels and the Mounties, the Royal
Canadian Mounted Police.
Which if I was being pursued by white supremacists and the Hell's Angels, I would hope the Mounties
were chasing me.
I'd be like, yeah guys, I'm glad you're here.
I'm currently being pursued by a bunch of white supremacists and Hell's Angels.
Can you help me out?
But his delusions weren't making sense, right?
What were these groups doing running together?
So he ran.
He left Alberta and he was homeless, just walking around.
He finds himself in Abbotsford in November of 2016.
He's stealing that liquor.
Now he did take a couple shots, a couple shots of alcohol and he continues walking down the
street screaming at the top of his lungs.
And yet people just passed by him.
There's no report that I could find of anyone calling the police and saying, hey, there's
this lunatic walking down the street screaming at the top of his lungs.
Everyone just kind of minded their own business.
A few hours after going into the liquor store, we have him on video going into a Cabela's,
which is an outdoor sporting hunting type store, if you're not familiar with him.
And we have him.
We see him on video walking into the Cabela's and he goes straight to the hunting knives
section.
This pretty dope store that you have an whole area just for hunting knives, but he's walking
around, he's looking in the hunting knife section and he sees one that he likes and
he just walks out with it.
Just walks right out of the store holding the knife.
Didn't even put it in his backpack.
Walks out holding this knife.
As he's walking down the street screaming, shouting, drawing all this attention to himself
and yet no one is paying any real attention to him, he begins to see things following him.
The shadows are back.
He catches out of the corner of his eye dark figures slowly stalking him.
And the voices in his head are only getting louder.
The alcohol didn't help, which it rarely does, right?
You can self-medicate to a certain point, but when you're in this level of a mental crisis,
a couple shots at Jack really aren't going to do, they're not going to do Jack at that
point, right?
And he, this isn't the first time he felt this way, but on November 1st he is completely
suicidal.
And he's alone.
He's walking through the street.
And he decides, you know what, all I want to do is talk to my mom.
All I want to do is talk to my mom, and it might be the last time I ever talked to my
mom, right?
I want to let her know the despair I'm feeling.
I want to let my mom know that I'm at my lowest point.
I feel like killing myself.
So he walks to Abbotsford Secondary School, which is a high school in Abbotsford.
And the reason why he went there is because he wanted to use a computer to email his mother.
There is no other way that he could think of to really get to a computer, so he figures
they're in the high school.
He walks into the high school completely uncontested.
No one even thinks anything about this adult, this 21-year-old man walking into this high
school.
You could say, "Well, Jason, you know, he had a backpack on, so maybe he looks like
a student."
I should also add he's barefoot, right?
Not a lot of students are walking around barefoot, not a lot of students are 21-years-old.
Not a lot of students are screaming to the top of their lungs.
He's like, "Go team!"
It was weird because he would only scream out loud when he wasn't trying to be stealthy.
And so you have to start to wonder, like, was he insane?
That's a question that'll pop up as this story progresses.
He walks into the high school not acting like a lunatic.
He walks in a library and there's no seats available at any of the computers.
So even in the darkest moment, he still can't reach out to the one person he knows who will
always have his back, his mother.
So he walks out and there's this rotunda in the school and he kind of sits down there.
What do I do now?
Right?
Wait for a computer?
Do I just continue walking?
What's next?
Right?
I just want to talk to my mom.
And at that point, he sees pure evil in front of him.
In this school, he sees a witch, an evil practitioner of the dark arts.
Possibly the cause of all of his hallucinations, the voices in his head, the shadows that stalk
him.
The supernatural warlord is walking right in front of him and standing next to her
a zombie.
The decayed remains of a human somehow walking upright, maggots crawling out of its skin,
monsters through and through.
He may have questioned what he was seeing.
He may have thought, well this doesn't make any sense.
If he did have that thought, if he did think, wait a second Gabriel, don't overreact.
It's the day after Halloween.
There's no way that could actually be a real witch and a real zombie in this school.
He may have had those thoughts, but when these two creatures walk past him, Lucy, the evil
voice in his head, begins to scream at him.
Gabriel pulls the hunting knife out of his backpack and attacks the demons in front of
him.
We have video footage of this as well.
As far as I didn't look super hard for it, I saw one screenshot, I don't like watching
video of people being brutally assaulted.
I saw a screenshot and then YouTube had taken down the video.
There was a lot of articles from the local authorities saying please do not share this
video with people.
This is very upsetting and it's upsetting to the people involved in it and just upsetting
to watch.
There's a six second video going around and you see Gabriel standing over a teenage girl
swinging his knife at her.
She's trying to crawl away and he's continuing to attack her.
You hear a piercing scream over all the other noise, over all the other chaos.
Still the rotunda that they're all standing in.
And then a man approaches Gabriel.
Gabriel immediately drops the knife back away.
Once he dropped the knife, Gabriel said he looked down.
There was no witch.
There was no zombie.
It was simply two teenage girls.
So we have this situation where now he's looking down, he sees that there are two young girls
in front of him and once he drops a knife he says a voice in his head, assuming the good
voice said you're going to hell now.
And while we don't know what his eternal punishment will be, we do know what happened
instantly after he dropped the knife.
The school principal tackled him and the staff restrained him while other members of the staff
tried to perform first aid on these young girls.
One was 13 years old and one was 14 years old.
It stabbed multiple times in a very, very short period of time.
Both girls had to be airlifted out and fortunately the 13-year-old girl, she died.
She died of this attack.
The 14-year-old girl did not die but she was stabbed multiple times as well.
Eventually his trial was held and it just really came to a close in 2021.
He was sentenced to life in prison, eligible for parole in 16 years and he was giving
seven years of credit because he was in jail for so long.
So technically he could be out for parole in 2030.
What is that?
Eight years from now he could be out.
It's super weird.
The crime took place in 2016.
He was sentenced in 2021.
So I'm bad at math but that's only five years between 2016 and 2021, right?
How did he get seven years' credit if only five years had passed?
I don't know.
Canada has a really weird justice system.
Britain has probably the worst that I've ever seen.
They let lunatics go all the time.
They do.
I'm not saying America's justice system is anything that I know about.
But Americans' justice system tends to over prosecute and other countries tend to under
prosecute or under sentence.
America tends to over sentence.
Anyways, this guy murdered one girl, injured another one, and it's possible he'll be out
of jail in 2030.
But this story, I wanted to talk about this story for a couple different reasons.
I want, I just find it fascinating, we talk about mental illness a lot on this show, right?
What it must be like to be in the mind of a maniac.
Secondly, you have to wonder about those voices, right?
Like, whenever we encounter stuff like this, there's two different ways to look at it.
As it being straight up mental illness, this guy has a chemical imbalance in his brain,
or he had so many bad experiences in his life, it just warped his worldview.
And that's definitely possible.
I think there's always a conjunction of two things, right?
I think that's the majority of people who quote unquote go crazy.
It's a chemical imbalance in the brain, bad upbringing, maybe both of those smashed together,
horrible life experiences, all that stuff, right?
We've seen people get head injuries and become completely different and completely violent
people.
They're totally normal up until then.
But then you also look at the demonic influences, right?
Which I think is a minority of mental health cases, but I do think that there are people
who are plagued by that.
And then you wonder what the Venn diagram is between someone who's in a mental health
crisis and being preyed on by forces of the supernatural.
And you'll never know, right?
You'll never know.
We covered that one story, the one episode on this podcast that gave me nightmares.
I think the guy was named Michael Taylor.
He was a brutal, brutal killer who was infested with all of these demons.
I'll put that episode in the show notes like that.
Was to me the scariest episode of this entire podcast.
Really of all my research of paranormal stuff in general, the story of Michael Taylor.
These two voices, were they part of his imagination?
Were they part of his illness?
Were they an external force putting pressure on him?
Like a demonic force instructing him to kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
It's a sad story too, you know?
I mean, like, definitely he was at his lowest point possible.
Like he was getting ready to kill himself.
And what's interesting is the psychiatrist, when he first got arrested and he was being
interviewed by psychiatrists, they thought he was faking.
They actually didn't believe his delusions.
And I thought he was making it up.
Which is always a theory.
And this is so interesting too, because recently I did a net like real recently.
It was in the past week or two.
I don't remember what the episode was, but I was talking about someone snapping and going
crazy and how scary that is.
And a long time listener of the show, a long time supporter of the show, Fabio Nurbon, commented
on my YouTube channel.
I never thought about this before.
This is so fascinating.
He said this right when I was prepping this story.
He goes, "I don't fully buy the snapping phenomenon.
How come that the one who snaps only seems to target weaker opponents?"
Wow.
I didn't think about that.
And here we have this.
He snapped and he saw these monsters and he attacked him with a knife.
And the second that a man showed up, an adult man showed up, like walked onto camera.
Once Gabriel sees a man show up, he dropped a knife and the delusions went away.
Like as I was prepping this story, Fabio left that comment and I go, "That is so fascinating.
He's right.
You're right, Fabio."
Generally speaking, these people snap and they don't snap and start punching Marines.
They don't snap and start walking.
They're like, "That's it.
I'm done."
And they walk into a mixed martial arts gym and start fighting people, right?
Teenage girls.
Fascinating.
So you do have to wonder in these certain circumstances, how is it mental illness?
Was it a lifetime of mental illness that was causing these problems?
Was it actually a demonic influence?
Piggybacking on the mental illness or a demonic influence of 100%?
Did he make it up?
Did he make it all up?
Or is it that Venn diagram where a little bit of it's exaggerated, a little bit of it is
authentic mental illness and maybe even a little smidgen of it is something darker?
Who knows?
The only person who really knows the answer to that story is sitting in prison.
The only person who knows what's actually going on in his head, because the delusions
are gone now.
He says he's been on the right medication and everything like that.
He's better now.
So the only person who truly knows the whole story is sitting in prison and it's possible
he'll be walking the streets again in the year 2030.
If it was mental illness and he's better, the delusions are gone.
I still don't think he should get paroled in eight years, but if he does and he's better
and the mental illness is treated, then do we have anything to worry about?
If it was these demonic forces that were kind of piggybacking on the mental illness, now
he's served his purpose.
He's killed people.
He's sent fear throughout the community.
He's shattered families.
Maybe the demonic influence is gone.
But if he's making it up, if the mental illness was all in act and he really just wanted to
kill some young girls, everything else was faked.
There's a chance he will be walking the streets again in just eight years.
A man who fooled the justice system.
A man who convinced the court that he had no control over his actions.
When really, he was the only one in control.
When he grabbed the knife, when he headed to the school, when he stood in court and convinced
a judge to give him possible parole in 16 years, Gabriel was the one in control.
Not the voices, not the demons, not the illness, but a master manipulator who's already murdered
once and may soon be walking the streets once more.
[Music]
(upbeat music)