Previously on Dead Rabbit Radio.
*Growl*
*Shrrrrr*
Knocking stuff over!
This is a Dead Rabbit show!
Whatever it's called, Dead Rabbit Radio is the actual name,
but this show is revealing the secret truths we have.
Every episode he does is true!
But some of his episodes contradict the other episodes that he does.
It doesn't matter!
Those episodes are actually even more true!
We have to stop him.
We have to stop him before he exposes all of our evil plans!
*Pfft*
Oh man, so fun playing Apex Legends while my break's going on,
but it's time to shut it off!
And now I'm going to sit back, relax, and assume nothing bad is going to happen!
*Pfft*
Oh, what was that?
Game's off!
*Pfft*
I ran outside!
Open my squeaky door!
Oh my god.
Bodies.
Everywhere.
The destruction, if you could only see it, is...
It's shocking.
But I don't know any of them, so...
That's cool.
But...
Oh my god.
My...
My hanger.
And my garage that's attached to my hanger.
*Pfft*
No, I wasn't clapping.
I was running into the hanger.
Oh my god, no.
Carpenter copter.
It's on fire.
Oh my god, and it's destroyed.
It's completely destroyed.
*Pfft*
The Jason Jalopy.
Oh no.
Oh no, the Jason Jalopy burned to a crisp.
*Pfft*
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Oh my god.
The Dead Rapid Durageable is still here, and it's in one piece.
No!
There's only one thing I can do now.
I have to assemble a team.
*Pfft*
After I finish playing some more Apex Legends, but now I will assemble my team.
So, I heard you're the man to come to...
If I need some muscle.
Mmmmm.
Mungo has lots of muscle.
Given to me by god, and supplements.
Thank you, Mungo, will you be on my team?
*Mungo grunts*
As long as we can push nerds.
Hey, do that anyways.
Come on, Mungo.
Hey.
*Mungo grunts*
A bunch of pictures being taken.
*Pfft*
I don't know how to make that sound.
I don't have phones.
Either using phones.
There's no noises.
All these photos are being taken.
Hey, hey.
*Gasp*
Jason, my best friend ever.
Yes, yes, Miley Cyrus.
It is I, your best friend.
I'm putting together a team.
Say no more.
Now, we just have one more person to put on our team.
*Mungo grunts*
Hello?
Is anyone here?
Here?
*Mungo grunts*
Mungo no like this house.
Looks like Gollum's house from nerd novel.
Yeah, what we're about to face is far worse than Gollum.
*Mungo grunts*
Did you know?
Okay, Franz, Franz, dude, quit creeping us out with your-
How are your arms that long?
Why do you come here?
Franz, listen, dude, what, truce, I need your help to fight the bad guys who blow up all
my stuff.
Hmm, you need my help.
As I sound very Gollum-like?
Yes, Franz, we need your help.
I'm declaring a truce.
Hmm, did not know about the truce.
What do you have to offer me?
How about a 12 pack of diet cranberry spray?
Maybe, listen, Franz, you don't have anything better going on.
You're scurrying around your dark apartment.
Just come with us.
Okay.
And now, season five of Dead Rabbit Radio.
Pshh, pshh, pshh.
Meow.
That's a preview when we go to the jungle and we get attacked by a giant cat and I throw
Franz in front of it.
[Music]