A horrific murder has people asking, not me, I don't agree with this, but does have people
asking, is it okay to murder some children?
Again, I'm saying the answer is no.
Fascinating article, we'll take a look at it.
And then we end the week by taking a look at the story of a young boy who begins to see
the future in his dreams.
When the real world begins to perfectly match his dreams, can he fight the future?
Can he prevent his own death?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a great
day too.
We have some awesome plans for the weekend.
We got a ton of stuff to cover, so walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one
of our Thanksgiving livestream contributors.
Everyone get on your feet and give it up for Corbin's Channel.
Woohoo, yeah, come on in Corbin's Channel, walk all the way in, VHF, UHF, we don't know
what channel you are, but you are welcome at Dead Rabbit Command.
Long time supporter of the show, Corbin's Channel.
We're going to be our captain or pilot this episode, if you guys can't support the show
financially, I totally understand that I really really really do.
Just help spread the word about the show, that helps out so much, that's another way
you can help the show grow.
Corbin's, let's go ahead and tassue the hair hang glider, we're going to jump off the highest
point at Dead Rabbit Command.
Glide us all the way out to Illinois.
Specifically, we're headed to River Grove, Illinois.
It's June 2013.
And in River Grove there's an apartment complex, and how this apartment complex lives the Sportalacus
family.
The Sportalacus family, as it's probably correctly pronounced, the Sportalacus family, is currently
undergoing some life stressors, to put it mildly.
Dorothy, the mother, is trying to take care of her 14 year old son, Alex.
But Alex has been diagnosed with severe autism.
He requires around the clock care.
And things have gotten so bad, that the police have been called to the residence several
times.
He's combative, plus he's a 14 year old boy, he's physically strong.
And sometimes they just can't handle him.
Even though you have Dorothy living there, you have his godmother, who also helps take
care of him, Agatha.
And then the father and Alex's brother all live there as well.
Alex requires around the clock care, and the family's just having a hard time dealing
with him.
They love him, but they're at their breaking point.
Now like I said several times, the police have been called out.
Alex has been hospitalized, there's photographs of this.
When he's hospitalized, he's taken down and he's strapped to the bed.
He's restrained to the bed, and of course that's making him panic even more.
No one would want to be restrained.
You lose all sense of control, because you literally have no control, you're tied down.
And his mother's watching her son in agony.
He's being treated like he's a wild beast by this uncaring medical center.
Well that's how she sees it.
That's not my personal opinion.
That's how she sees it.
And she's starting to see a future with no hope.
Not just no hope for her, not just that she's going to have to spend the rest of her life
taking care of her 14 year old son.
No hope for Alex either.
What chance does he have at being happy, having a long fulfilling life that any parent would
wish for their children?
This having a hard time with Alex.
The mother is distraught.
Now the Chicago Department of Children and Family Services have reached out to the Sportalockeys
family.
You know they've offered their services, there are things we can do to help.
This isn't, you're not alone.
You're not alone.
There are a lot of children like this across the state.
There are a lot of children like this across the planet.
So we will help you.
What do you need?
We'll see what we can get you.
Well in June 2013, Dorothy decided enough was enough.
And that doesn't mean that she picked up the phone and called the Department of Children
and Family Services and said, "Okay let's have this meeting.
Let's do this."
It doesn't mean that she called the police and says, "I need my son to be hospitalized
for however long."
I'm not able to take care of him anymore.
We're not able to take care of him anymore.
He can't take care of himself.
This is just too much.
She doesn't do that.
Dorothy and Agatha poison Alex.
They give him a massive dose of sleeping pills.
But it doesn't work.
It actually very rarely works.
We see that in movies.
It's really hard to poison somebody.
Unless it's a fast acting drug like penicillin.
Unless it's a fast acting drug like cyanide or VX nerve agent like we covered on a previous
episode.
They rubbed VX nerve agent all over this dude's face.
You try to overdose on a lot of things.
You will vomit them up before they can kill you.
Not everything though.
Don't put that to a test.
Use police outside.
Oh, it's the Christmas parade.
They do this in town.
You hear that?
Okay, it's going to be a couple of minutes.
So I'm going to have to take a break here.
I'll come back.
Okay, I'm back.
What was just the second to you was a day for me.
I ended up going to bed.
So sorry if the sound changes a little bit.
We were talking about this horrific crime and I'm like, "Oh, I'm going to go to sleep."
I guess we haven't gotten to the crime part yet.
Oh, yeah, we did.
They poisoned this poor kid with sleeping pills and that didn't work.
Alex survived that.
So what happened next?
It's so horrible.
This is such a horrible thing.
Not a time to take a nap.
What happens is later, Alex's father and Alex's uncle come home and they find Dorothy and
Agatha under the influence of sleeping pills.
They've actually tried overdosing on sleeping pills themselves.
Even though it didn't kill Alex, that's the way they chose to go out.
Father and the uncle come home to two barely aware adults and Alex has been stabbed to
death.
He was stabbed multiple times in the chest and then his wrists were slid.
He was murdered by his mother and his godmother, the people who needed to protect him.
And this is where we get to this...
I mean, it's a tragic true crime story.
Undeniably tragic true crime story.
The way I found out about this though, so fascinating, I was reading an article in Forbes
written by Emily Willingham.
She wrote this piece for Forbes and what she says is there are people out there, numerous
people out there, who believe that when a parent or a guardian murders an autistic child,
it's okay.
Now, they're not rooting for it.
They're not necessarily advocating it, but when it does happen, there are groups out
there that give these parents a pass.
Now, Emily's not one of them.
Emily's article is against this.
She highlights the case of Alex and she goes, "There are groups out there that say the
system is so cumbersome, the medical establishment and law enforcement, they're just this mind
less bureaucracy and sometimes parents cannot deal with it."
And so they kill their children.
They kill their autistic children and there are groups that are like the poor mother who
have been put in that situation in the first place.
That's the tragedy.
It's fascinating.
I never thought about this before.
And again, that's why it's important to know that there were social services trying to
reach out to this family.
And yet this was still the path that they took.
This is a super interesting quote in this article here.
I want to read this section of Emily's article because basically what she's saying is, "You
do have these support groups that when an autistic child is murdered, they side with
the parents."
They side with the parents in these cases.
And she says, "No other condition draws this kind of judgment or leads people to blame
the condition, the murdered, and everyone except the murderer for killing her own child."
If Alex had had Down syndrome, cancer, schizophrenia, ADHD, or a traumatic brain injury, no one would
be giving his mother a pity pass for having brutally taken his life overwhelmed by his
needs.
Now, see, I thought nobody did this.
I thought there was no condition where if you murdered your kid, you got a quote unquote
pity pass.
But Emily does a pretty good job laying out the argument that there are people who go,
"Well, you know, the mother, she tried her best and when the best wasn't good enough,
what else could she do but murder her child?"
Apparently, part of this, not everyone who agrees with it's okay.
And again, it's not that it's okay to murder an autistic child in their view, but when
it does happen, they go, "Well, she was just so put upon this poor mother.
What else could she do?
She tried everything."
Part of the people who argue that are the people who believe that vaccines cause autism.
Not all of them, but some of them.
So they blame that.
See, they have that viewpoint.
This child would have been perfectly fine had he not gotten vaccinated.
Interesting, right?
We're rolling back into that.
We're rolling back into that conspiracy theory.
And those people are like, "Well, what do you expect when you have this profit driven
medical industry, this soulless corporate run healthcare?"
They vaccinated him in the first place.
He got autism and then the mother couldn't deal with him and the mother killed him.
It's not her fault.
It's fascinating.
I actually thought there would be no cases where anyone would argue on behalf of the
murderer.
I mean, there are times, like you read the article about the elderly couple where the
woman has cancer and the husband kills her and then kills himself.
I mean, again, I'm not advocating that.
We see those as tragic.
It's always tragic.
There is a CBS News report that called Dorothy a "desperate mother."
So again, it's kind of reframing that.
It's framing that passage.
Now, Emily does say, "Listen, because I think some readers reached out to her and she said,
'You do also see this for parents of children with advanced cerebral palsy, but would they
get the pity pass?
Would they get the desperate mother coinage by the CBS News?'"
Now I read Emily's article, I found it super fascinating.
Then I went back because this story is a couple of years old.
I go, "Well, let's see.
Let's see what the penalty was for Dorothy and Agatha."
Remember, this is premeditated all the way.
They tried to poison them with sleeping pills.
When that didn't work, they stabbed them four times in the chest and then slit his wrists.
Premeditated murder was dropped down to involuntary manslaughter.
Both these adults got time served.
That was it.
Three years, they were in jail during the court process.
They got involuntary manslaughter time served, both set free.
It's a tragic story.
It's a horrifying story.
Do I think these two people are going to go out and murder again?
No.
Do I think they're a danger to the community?
Well, maybe that's the second part.
Who knows?
The concern is that people see this now as an out.
People who see this case may think, "Well, I can do that."
And it goes from being a story of Dorothy and Agatha to a Casey Anphony type person who
has a child who's mildly autistic and she has other reasons for wanting to get rid of
her kid.
I don't know.
I mean, you can slippery slope anything.
It's a tragic story and it's so interesting to find there are support groups out there.
Again, it's not like there's not a support group is kill your kid incorporated, but when
this happens, they back the parents and it's more about the condition and the murder victim
and their behavior than the murderer and their behavior.
It's absolutely fascinating.
It's subculture within a subculture.
And who knows where this will end?
Who knows how far this will spread out?
I remember there was that case.
There was that famous true crime case.
I'll put it in the show notes of a guy who killed his wife sleepwalking and he had been
having trouble sleepwalking his entire life and he was acting out in his dreams.
He accidentally killed his wife.
He was sleepwalking.
And there is the theory that you started after that became a known event, you started having
more people claiming to kill people in their sleep.
I mean, it's not a super common defense, but since then there have been other people who've
been like, oh, I didn't mean to kill my wife.
I was simply sleepwalking because you can look at that now and you just want to get rid
of your wife.
You might have a mild sleep disorder, but you just want to get rid of your wife.
And what's interesting is that it worked the first time because there was like years of
documented treatment, but the subsequent ones, it didn't.
They were found guilty for murder.
The one guy murdered his wife in his sleep and then washed his hands.
And they got, I think he got rid of his bloody clothing.
The cops were like, okay, you might have murdered your wife in your sleep.
That's tragic.
But the hiding the evidence part, you're probably awake for that.
Corbin's channel, Corbin's channel, I have to be on that episode.
That was super depressing.
Corbin's channel, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carpenter copter we are
leaving behind Illinois.
Fly us all the way out to a middle school.
We're going to this middle school.
We don't have an exact location.
The story was posted online by someone who goes by the name Lazar Yeat Mehta.
We're going to go ahead and call him Jim.
Jimmy's in the seventh grade.
He just transferred schools and things are not going well at all.
Yo, Jimmy, that's a lame name.
What?
Oh man, I tried.
That's the principle.
That's what the principle yelled at him when he was starting his first day of school.
Jimmy sucks.
Jimmy is walking around the school and he is instantly targeted as this is the guy to
bully.
I'm going to beat you up.
I hope school never ends and the teacher is like extra school because that's what Jimmy
wants.
Now we're going to beat him up twice after school.
The bullying had become not physical just yet but people were threatening to beat him
up and he's like, I don't want to go to school anymore.
Man, this totally sucks.
I transferred schools and it's like a war zone.
I have no idea where he went.
I don't know if he went to the school from dangerous mines or the substitute or something
like that.
Well, one night Jimmy is deep asleep and he has a dream that he's in school.
He's like, oh man, I cannot have been in the unicorn glen again.
He has a dream that he's in school and he's sitting in his math class and he has a substitute
for math and he's kind of sitting there.
This sucks.
This is the worst dream he has dream homework now.
He's like, oh man.
Then he goes to PE and when he's in the PE class, the other students are cussing at him.
Things are really getting out of hand and then eventually a student throws a punch because
he's never been physically hit at this new school.
In the dream he gets punched and then pummeled.
Jimmy in the middle of PE gets beat up.
So he's a little apprehensive about going to school the next day and he has to, right?
That's part of life.
You got to go to school.
He goes to school and just get, he's happy that he just gets threatened.
He doesn't get beat up.
But then he goes to bed that night.
He has a dream.
He's at school.
He's sitting in his math class and there's a substitute.
Then he goes to PE.
The other students are cussing him out and then whap.
He gets punched and then beat up.
He has this dream in total four times in a row.
Four nights in a row he has this dream and on the fifth day he goes to school, walks
into his math class and there's a substitute teacher there.
Now he doesn't specifically say it's the exact same person he saw in his dream, but it was
a substitute.
His regular math teacher wasn't there.
He goes into the math class.
There's a substitute there.
Next he goes to PE.
People start cussing at him.
He's like, "Uh oh, I know where this is going to go."
Bap!
He gets punched.
Then he gets beat up.
The first punch in a way he knew was coming, right?
He'd been through this four times before.
He gets punched.
He begins to get beat up and at that point he realizes, like you could chalk it up to
maybe just a coincidence that you had a substitute in math class.
Him getting cussed to PE was nothing new, but now that he's getting beat up he's laying
on the ground in the fetal position.
He's going, "Hmm, this is quite familiar.
Maybe I saw the future in my dreams."
They're like, "Quit pontificating."
They're punching him even harder.
He's like, "Ah!"
He said this happened in total during his time at middle school six or seven times.
Not six or seven more dreams.
Six or seven more times did he have the same dream over and over and over again.
And then he would eventually go to school and the day at school would perfectly mimic
his dream.
He knew exactly what was coming and each time it was him getting beat up.
The dream ended with him getting beat up and that day where he goes to school and every
detail is exactly the same, he gets beat up and he says, "Here's the thing.
I tried my best.
I know that I had a clear idea that I was, for whatever reason."
He says, "I don't know how this happened.
I was able to predict the future.
I was able to have a dream and then the day would start off.
I'd have this dream multiple times in a row.
And then the day would come that when I got to school, I knew this was the real life version
of the dream."
And so he'd get beat up and then some time would pass and then he would have a dream
where he'd get beat up at school and then he'd have the dream the next night and he's
like, "Oh no, this is going to happen again."
And so he started to try to change events because he saw the future so clearly, he goes,
"I don't want to get beat up.
So how do I prevent that?
Now I remember in the dream this happened, this happened, this happened.
I will do something different."
And no matter what he changed, he would still be forced into the position where he would
get beat up.
There was no way out.
So he might be able to change key details.
Let's say that he was having the dream, he didn't use this example, but let's say he's
having the dream and in the dream he gets up to use the bathroom in the middle of social
studies.
And then he comes back to class and when he walks right through the door, the bully who's
going to beat him up later starts yelling at him and that's what sparks everything.
So after school as he's getting his backpack, the bully beats him up.
Jimmy would go, "Well, I just won't go to the bathroom.
I will sit in my social studies class.
I'm going to hold it in.
So I will prevent me from coming in through the door so the bully won't yell at me at
the first place.
I will be sitting here in the classroom."
Now again, he doesn't give that specific example, but that's kind of what he's saying, but this
is what would happen.
He would be sitting in the classroom.
He would say, "I'm not going to go to the bathroom."
He's like, "I probably shouldn't have been in that Taco Bell before school."
That's complicated, this whole thing.
"I'm not going to go to the bathroom.
I'm going to hold it in as much as I can."
But for whatever reason, even if he didn't come in the door and draw the bully's attention
to him and start yelling at him, he'd be sitting there in the classroom.
He would try to have changed the events and the bully would find something else to yell
at him about.
Hey, who's pooping over there?
Who's pooping?
Who's pooping in that seat?
It was me.
He couldn't change the events.
Of course, he kept pleading, "I don't want to go to school today.
I don't want to go to school today because this is the day I'm probably going to get
beat up.
I've had this show you multiple times in a row."
But that's not going to work either, right?
Unless your parents are firm believer in the paranormal and/or you've helped them win several
lottery drawings, go to school, Jimmy.
Go to school.
Oh, you and your fear of getting beaten up at school.
You got to go there.
I have one of the lottery money we can pay for your medical bills.
Go to school.
And he said this happened overall six to seven times throughout his middle school life and
could never change it.
He could never change it.
He'd go to school to get beat up.
The idea of premonition in dreams is a fascinating one.
A lot of people make those connections.
And if that was the end of the story, it's still a fascinating look at the idea of are
our dreams more than just neurons firing and us making sense of the images.
But in high school, Jimmy had a different dream, a more alarming dream.
You get beat up at school.
Listen, I got beat up and I beat people up.
That's just the way of the world.
That's just the way the school system works.
America at least, during the 80s it did.
I don't know about nowadays, but it was whatever.
You come home with a black eye, your parents get mad, call the other parent, and that was
it.
No big deal.
But this next dream is a bit of a big deal.
Next year I mean definitely it's a little more than just wearing sunglasses the next
day of school.
Jimmy, who has had multiple dreams that have foretold the future now, he's in high school.
He has this dream that he's in his favorite teacher's class.
He's sitting there, everything's totally normal.
Until a man wearing a ski mask walks into the class, pulls out a gun, and points it at
the teacher.
Jesse jumps up, and this is his favorite teacher, right?
Had this been the witch-hop teacher he probably would have been a little slower, but this
was his favorite teacher.
Jimmy jumps up and knocks the gun out of the dude's hand.
But this guy in the ski mask has a backup plan, like most maniacs do.
He pulls out a knife and begins stabbing Jimmy to death.
And as Jimmy gets stabbed multiple times and he falls to the ground and starts bleeding
out as his vision becomes blurry, as his life is leading his body, he sees the man on the
ski mask pick the gun back up and shoot the teacher multiple times.
If I had that dream that would upset me.
I think if most people had that dream it would be really upsetting.
But our dreams don't normally tell the future.
So to Jimmy that really set off alarm bells, he had the dream again and he smuggled a knife
onto campus that day.
Like he was preparing for it because of his past experiences with his dreams telling the
future.
He brought a knife to school, which is in most if not all school districts instant expulsion.
He brought a knife to school.
He was afraid that the dream was going to become real.
Can you imagine going to school that day?
I mean it was bad enough for him to go to school and get beat up, but to think that he may be
murdered by some stranger.
And then his favorite teacher gunned down.
He brought a knife to school.
And what's interesting is he said that it wasn't the last time he had the dream.
He brought the knife to school the second time he had the dream.
But he said in total he had the dream four times, which kind of fits the pattern.
He had the dream four times.
The fourth time he had that dream he said he was there in class.
See I don't think the dream version knows about the, I don't think the, you know what
I mean?
Like I don't think when he's sitting there in the dream goes, oh this is just a dream.
And I've had this dream a couple of times before.
I know what's coming.
Like each time dream Jimmy has the dream it's new to that Jimmy.
But the white awake Jimmy who's sweating profusely when he wakes up, he realizes he's
had this dream multiple times and he knows what that means.
But anyways in this last dream, the fourth time he had this dream, he's in the classroom.
The man in the ski mask bursts through the door, points the gun at his teacher.
Jimmy jumps up, knocks the gun out of his hand and the man then pulls out a knife and stabs
Jimmy.
Plunges the knife right into his chest.
The man then picks up the gun, points it at the teacher and shoots her.
But this time Jimmy is somehow able to get to his feet, pull the knife out of his own
chest and slit the man's throat.
That dream never became a reality.
And he never had a dream of the future after that.
What a fascinating story.
I found this online, of course it could totally be fake.
It could have been a made up account.
It didn't seem like it to me.
Like I said, a lot of times I go through these people's past posting history to see if they
are constantly talking about one of a kind paranormal events and that's like, "Oh, on
Tuesday, then this happened."
Obviously I've been fooled.
We've talked about that on the podcast before.
I've been fooled by stuff.
But to me it's always interesting when they post something like this on a paranormal board
and then everything else they're just talking about like video games or memes and things
like that.
And I think that's why they always add some sort of legitimacy to it.
And I'm wondering, I mean there's so many ways we can look at this.
I think kind of my takeaway from the whole thing is that this dream was going to happen.
The teacher and him were going to get killed in real life.
And I think it's interesting that the man was wearing a ski mask because it renders
the viewer of the future more powerless.
Like obviously if he had a dream and he saw a guy walk in and he could totally recognize
his face and this was his favorite teacher, maybe he could trust the teacher and say,
"Hey, do you know anybody who has like a black buzz cut and like a cartoonishly large mustache?"
She goes, "Oh yeah, my ex.
I used to date this guy.
He's a total lunatic."
"How'd you know what my ex looked like?"
"Have you been stalking my Facebook, Jimmy?"
If he could tell what the person looked like, it would be easier to at least kind of prepare
for in the sense that if it was Ronald Schwarzenegger coming through, you're like, "Oh no, he's
going to go commando style.
He's going to bring in a bunch of machine guns."
I think that if he could describe the person, it would be much more, you could convince
people because then people go, "Yeah, we had an ex employee.
He looked like that.
Yeah, that was my ex-husband."
So on and so forth.
You could also figure that the man in the ski mask wasn't necessarily a person but an idea.
In the sense that it wasn't that an idea was going to come in and shoot her.
It was just going to be some sort of random act of violence.
The person may have actually come in wearing a ski mask and it could have just been a maniac.
It could have been nothing metaphorical about it.
It could have just been a lunatic and a ski mask.
And I'm wondering if the reason why the future was different, they were able to change it
because the first time they could get everything down to the exact detail, they would remember
standing in line to go into school and they knew who was going to be in line before them
and after them.
They had already seen it four or five times in a row at night and then when they're standing
in line to go into class, they're like, "Great, I know how this is going to end because I
know exactly how this line is made up."
When you get it down to the exact detail, the dreams are that vivid and then this dream
somehow they're able to change the ending in the dream.
And that might have been the issue that Jimmy was having all along.
He was constantly trying to change the reality to be different than the dream.
The key was to change the dream to change reality.
And you could look at it as him predicting the future.
You could also look at it as him manifesting the reality where he is bullied and beat up.
A big part of manifestation, a big part of law of attraction is the subconscious, is
the moments before we fall asleep and the dreaming itself.
If you want to look at it, you can't say there's really any proof for the law of attraction,
but I always think it's so fascinating when you hear about Marshall Mathers sitting in
his trailer and he has covers of the source magazine all around his walls and his ceilings
and every night before he went to bed, young Marshall Mathers would sit there and think
about hip-hop stardom.
A while back I got in touch with this true crime podcaster who hit the big time.
He's making a lot of money in the true crime field and I asked him.
I practiced the law of attraction myself and one of the things about the law of attraction
is to not dwell on dark things.
That's a big part of it.
And I go, "But yet I'm a true crime podcaster myself and I talk about paranormal ghosts
and everything like that."
I go, "How do you balance the two?"
First off, I go, "Do you believe in law of attraction?"
He was super interesting when he said, he goes, "I do believe in the law of attraction."
He goes, "What I would do honestly is I would lay in bed and every night before I go to
sleep all I would think about."
And he goes, "I was living in a basement.
I was living in a basement.
I was sitting on the ground basically in a gunny sack.
He's far worse off than I am and I'm not that bad off.
I have a great place."
But he goes, "You know, I would lay there on the hard ground and as the cockroaches
scrambled all over me."
He goes, "I would sit and imagine what life would be like if I was a professional podcaster.
First thing I would buy would be a bed."
So that time is super important.
That time before sleep leads into what we dream of.
You may not think so, but your subconscious is constantly firing off in the background.
Even though your dream may be about you swimming in a can of spaghetti-os with Christina Ricci,
your subconscious is constantly-
What do you mean?
Maybe that is your subconscious.
Maybe you're like, "How did he know my fetish?"
No!
Your subconscious is constantly going in the background and I'm wondering if that he may
have been manifesting the bullying.
And he may have been very close to manifesting his own murder and the murder of his favorite
teacher.
But he was able to stop that at the last minute, right?
The dreams normally went.
For a couple of days, this was on the fourth night he was able to stop it.
It's a fascinating story and it asks a lot more questions than it answers.
What are dreams?
Can they tell the future?
Like that's a whole paranormal belief in and of itself.
Are dreams symbolic or do they mean more than that?
Is there actually a structure behind the dreams?
Are there warnings?
Can you use dreams to achieve your dreams in the real world?
And if that's true, can nightmares also become reality?
It's all fascinating questions, but to Jimmy, it's a little more than just a theory.
He knows for a fact that sometimes dreams do come true.
He was so certain of that fact that when he began dreaming of his own murder, he knew
he had to change the future or he wouldn't have one.
It's almost like all of those beatings paid off.
Had he not had any dreams that told the future before, would he have paid attention to this
one?
All of those nightmares that turned his days into dread actually ended up saving Jimmy's
life.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]