A mother's death may provide a clue of an upcoming AI revolution.
And then we traveled to Italy to meet a farmer driving through town on his motorcycle.
It was just another quiet evening until he saw the glass cage sitting in the town square.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carvin, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have a ton of fun doing whatever cool stuff you guys are doing.
We got a ton of stuff to cover, so we're going to get started right away.
First off, coming in right now is one of our Thanksgiving livestream supporters that we
had recently.
It's a Dead Rabbit command.
Everyone give it up for Joaquin Stick.
They're the name matches what he's doing.
He's Joaquin, and he's Joaquin.
Joaquin, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the show financially.
I totally understand, and it's fine.
It honestly is.
Just help spread the word about the show really, really, really helps out a lot.
You can also go to our merch store and do all sorts of fun stuff there.
You can click on things and buy them.
Wee!
Joaquin, I'm going to go ahead and start off by giving you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
After leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command, we are driving all the way out to Hollywood,
California.
And as we're driving down there, I want to do an update for a story that I had done
not too long ago.
I actually got some new information.
Episode 777.
It was castaways from beyond the stars.
It's a really cool story about a UFO that crashed on an island.
We don't have any more information about that, but on that same episode, I covered the story
about an anime convention, and it was called Anime Friends Brazil.
And apparently, there is an urban legend that a guy was so into cosplaying as this Naruto
character who was a puppet ninja that he took a real corpse from his medical school
and stuffed it into his costume.
This doesn't make sense.
Right now, you're trying to picture this guy walking around with his rotting corpse.
Look it, we're wearing the same shirt as arms are falling off.
No, it was like he had this casket or this urn strapped to his back, which is from the
show.
And it's supposed to be like this puppet drops out, and apparently this puppet was a homeless
man's body that the guy who was dressing up as a Naruto, Naruto character, I'm totally
butchering if people even listen to that episode.
They're like, "What?
I totally have lost you."
The point is that there's an urban legend that a guy snuck a human corpse into an anime
convention.
And this one might be real, we actually have a screenshot of this magazine and I famously
said, I've had, I have no joke, I have had people stop me walking down the street because
a lot of people here in town know that this podcast, they listen to the podcast, they
go, "Jason, you said recently, right when they start, I know exactly where they're going
with this."
In that episode, I said, "I don't speak Spanish, but I know a little bit of Latin, so when
I'm reading this article about this Brazilian rumor, it does look like it mentions a little
bit about a decaying body."
And I got stopped multiple times and they said, "You know they don't speak Spanish in
Brazil, right bro?
Is that like a bit where you do it a bit?"
And I was like, "Eyes are going side to side."
"Yeah, it's pretty funny, huh?"
So they don't speak Spanish in Brazil, they speak Portuguese, right?
And the magazine was not in Spanish, but this was interesting.
I was able to make out a couple of the words after getting, after getting publicly flogged
for making that mistake, on YouTube, Hayan Cangiri on YouTube said, who does speak Portuguese
and they're Brazilian, and they were able to translate the article.
They said, "Listen, it was a weird angle from the photograph and it was blurry, but
from what, this is cool, because this gives us more information.
What the article actually says, what they can read at least, is that there was a rumor
about an anime friend's convention where a guy was carrying a cadaver.
In the article though, it says it was a small animal, likely a howler monkey, and then the
convention organizers denied the rumors."
Pretty much the summary that Hayan Cangiri gave.
So that was awesome.
Thank you so much for that.
I wanted to give you guys feedback, wanted to give them that shout out.
Bear, very interesting.
So yeah, it does sound, I was thinking it was weird.
Getting around 180 pounds of dead weight, whether or not you put it in a box, that's
going to be an ordeal.
That's a long day at the con.
A little howler monkey, but that makes a little more sense.
But I wanted to update that story and probably something to it, probably something stinky
in there, but not a human corpse.
So thank you, and that is a really cool update.
I really like that story, because conventions are already really smelly places.
So if you can smell something over the normal smell of the unwashed nerds, then you know
that it's bad.
Then you know that it's bad.
I spent many, many an hour at Magic the Gathering at, not at cons, but I'd go to a lot of comic
book shops, play Magic the Gathering and G-Hod and all this stuff, these old card games,
and yeah, the smell is quite unbearable.
But we are done with that story, Joaquin.
Let's go ahead and keep driving that Jason Jalopy down here to Hollywood.
And we get out.
We're walking around.
We're not looking for Steven Spielberg's house.
That is not what this episode's about.
It's not a callback to yesterday's horrifying episode.
We're walking around Los Angeles and we come outside a studio and it's like, has all the
big posters of all the television shows that are going on.
We're like, "Hey, look it.
It's Will and Grace."
We check our watches.
We're like, "What?
Is it 2012?
Why is that still out there?"
We're seeing all these television shows.
Like this is where they filmed the set.
We're standing outside and we're looking at this Will and Grace sign.
We're like, "Oh, that's kind of weird."
That's still up.
That's kind of weird that anyone watches the show in the first place.
And we see kind of this hustle and bustle going into the studio.
And going into the studio is the staff, the staff of this whole show.
One of the people who's working on this show back when it was actually in production was
a woman named Karen Ray Schick.
She's an assistant director.
She's had a very, very long career in Hollywood.
The very first show that Karen worked on is one of my favorite shows growing up.
I don't know how well it holds up, but I remember just being thoroughly entertained by this show.
So hats off to you, Karen.
That's not a joke.
"Get a Life," starring Chris Elliott.
You guys remember that show, "Get a Life?"
Fox was always trying to do really weird entertainment.
They still do with stuff like, "It's Always Sunny."
But "Get a Life" was unlike any sitcom.
It really spoke to my kids in the hall, comedy sensibilities.
I loved "Get a Life."
And that was her first show as well.
And she worked consistently.
I mean, it almost looked like she was doing multiple television shows a season.
And this goes on and on and on.
And she's doing some really, really big shows as well.
Long career, long career in Hollywood.
But she's passed away recently.
She's passed away.
And that's where this story starts.
Because Karen Ray's child one day wanted to kind of Google her and kind of see, you know,
just going through this user's post, they go by the name Spooks and Giggles.
We're going to call them, we're going to call her Stella.
I don't know her exact name.
So Stella decides to Google her mom one night and is a fairly small internet presence.
It does have a very active IMDb page.
But as they're googling this information, they get directed to a website called Celebrity
Deaths.
You know what?
That's weird.
Like, I mean, I guess she was a celebrity.
I mean, she was an assistant director in all these hit shows.
But like, I wouldn't really classify her as a celebrity.
It's odd.
And this sets off a whole chain of events.
Because when you click on these articles, what you are seeing is a bot written article
that's scouring social media posts.
There's a website that all it does is look for celebrities dying or any sort of true
crime murder news.
And it scrapes the information off of Facebook or Instagram, wherever it's getting it, probably
everywhere.
And then this AI, this bot, is compiling these articles.
Now we've seen stuff like that before.
We've actually talked about stuff like that before.
Episode 773.
I talked about the Miami Herald bot.
They're now using a bot to write real estate ads.
But this has become far more sinister than just that.
It'd be one thing if they were just scouring the web and putting this stuff up.
And on these websites, it does make a note.
It says this is not an obituary.
They were just pulling information from tribute sites and social media posts and things like
that.
When we go to these sites, Stella was saying, kept saying, because they started posting all
over Reddit about this.
And I honestly thought it was an ARG.
I almost ignored this story when I first saw it.
Because I was seeing this in Mysteries of the World.
I was seeing this in Reddit Bureau of Information or Investigation.
Seeing this in all those places.
There was no engagement.
No one was playing around with it.
I was like, God, this is probably just an ARG.
But for whatever reason, I went back to look at it.
And they said, listen, I'm finding all these sites that are mentioning my mom's name.
It looks like a bunch of them are from India.
I don't know what any of this stuff means.
They're getting really mad.
They're posting-- because there's a Reddit account called Jocko that it posts, I don't
know, 15 times an hour boosting these articles.
Like it's pumping these articles out quicker than you could write-- OK, maybe not quicker
than you could write them, but incredibly fast.
So if you go to the subreddits for Jocko, the subreddit called Celebrity Death.
That's what it's called in the subreddit, Celebrity Death Subreddit.
It's just link after link after link after link after link of all these articles.
This computer is just pumping these things out.
I'm sorry, the subreddit's called Death Obituaries.
Death Obituaries is the name of that subreddit.
Dozens of posts an hour.
And that's weird, right?
The fact what would be the point of scouring this stuff to get this information?
People-- what's some engagement on Reddit?
They go, it's clicks, right?
They have you click on this, and then they get a couple of pennies.
And if you do this enough times, then the pennies add up.
The question is, why are they trumping up Karen as a celebrity?
Because I guess she worked in the television business, and she did a lot of good work,
but just an interesting thing.
But that's not even the weird part of the story.
While I'm investigating this, I'm scrolling through the Jocko account on Reddit, and I'm
looking at all the other articles, and I'm just kind of scrolling through them, looking
at all these other articles they've posted.
I come across one, and this is the headline, and this is pretty typical for how these bot-written
headlines are read.
Quote, "James Crumbly Death.
Dead.
Obituary news.
The second Blahino profile pic is of a Spanish soccer player who passed away.
James Crumbly was a kid soccer coach.
Click link to read full story."
And you click on it, obviously I'm like, "Click the link, gotta know more."
And the reason why, I mean, the guy post 50, or the bot post all these articles, the reason
why that stuck out to me is I know that name, James Crumbly.
That's the father of that kid who just shot up that school, Ethan Crumbly.
Ethan Crumbly, I do have to say this, he looks like the flu.
Have you guys seen a picture of this new school shooter?
He looks like the Musa Nex guy.
He looks gross.
I don't know, I don't know why this is all the sudden become a Paris Hilton podcast,
but he looks like a human disease.
It's really weird.
Like you can see the goo coming out of him.
Either that, or I need to go talk to my doctor and start taking some anti-halosanogenic medicine.
'Cause he's gross looking, he looks like Grimace Wormtongue on a bad day.
Anyways, James Crumbly was his dad.
And James Crumbly's like, "Oh, you're super gross, you're super disgusting, don't hug me."
James Crumbly, and I recognize the name and I go, "Wait a second, maybe there's two James
Crumblies walking around, I'm sure."
So I clicked on that.
And it was an article, it was just gibberish, talking about James Crumbly, talking about
Blahino, and I go, "Who the hell's Blahino?
I don't know, this guy is..."
Blahino is a weightlifter who's so notorious, apparently he has his own Wikipedia, not his
own Wikipedia page, he has the Blahpedia, where people post stuff about all this cringe
things he's done.
Apparently he's a weightlifter who was also a CIA assassin, believes the Illuminati is
fake and not only is the Illuminati fake, which I, that's a fair assessment, he believes
the Illuminati is fake and it was invented by Muslims on the internet.
And I go, "Ooh, I gotta check this guy out.
I mean, I've spent five minutes looking at his page.
This is fascinating, so we're probably gonna do a future Blahino theme segment."
But so he has nothing to do with soccer, I tried finding, is there another guy who plays
soccer who does Blahino?
Nothing to do with James Crumbly, so what it looks...
Oh, and it says in the article, "James Crumbly was a kid's soccer coach," so I go, "Is that
true?
I don't know."
So I looked it up in James Crumbly.
The only connection I could find between...
This is all tragic, the only connection I could find between soccer and Ethan Crumbly
and James, the dad, is that one of the victims, a young woman who was injured, played soccer.
So that pops up in these search fields, these bots are just constructing these articles.
So it's not just they're doing the celebrity deaths, it's not just they're taking people
who actually passed away, it seems like they're trying to find things that get hits out there
and trying to consolidate them, but that's not even the weirdest part of his story.
So I'm going to all these websites and if you type in Karen Ray Schick, even though she
had this long career, she didn't have a huge internet presence, you will see page after
page of these bot articles.
That's the number one hit for her now is all of these bot articles.
And you're clicking on them and you're looking at them and stuff like that, and it's just
all this AI generated stuff.
Like I said, it's even weirder than that because one of the art, this is the article that caught
my eye.
This is the article that when Stella was putting out there, caught my eye.
Is this is the headline?
Is the assistant director dead or alive?
Karen Ray Schick, Deaf News, Hokes Rumors, Details.
Now this article was just published on December 3rd.
I don't know when Karen Ray Schick passed away.
This article was just published on December 3rd.
And it tells the story about Karen Ray was a worldwide famous assistant director.
I don't think any assistant director is well-famous, but anyways, it goes on.
You're an assistant director.
You're like, "Aw, sorry, you're famous."
But everyone else, I don't know.
And it kind of goes on through her career.
And it says in 1989, she started as a production manager.
So I mean, we just have these weird generated sentences.
Now it could be, as I was saying this, I was saying it could be a translation error, but
I don't think so because even with the translation errors, the output is just so much.
I do think it's AI pushing this stuff out, but just weirdly worded sentences.
And then it goes, "Does the first initial question arise," this is a quote, "Does the
first initial question arise about her after the current situation that is she dead or
alive?"
Even the official sources of news have not confirmed the death.
So there is a lack of confirmation.
And that's why absolutely she is alive and doing good in work.
We will also get more amazing work from the personality in the upcoming days.
Then it lists some random show she worked on.
And Estelle has written this article and it's infuriating.
It's very hurtful.
This is a mother who has passed away and now there's a death hoax surrounding Karen Ray
Schick.
Now, obviously I'm going to go on the record.
I don't believe in this hoax.
I'm not trying to prop up this hoax in any way, shape, or form.
Why is this doing that?
The site made up a death hoax.
All it knew about her was that she recently passed away, she worked in Hollywood and it
generated an article that would get people to click on it.
Maybe 10 people and then the article would just be forgotten in a source but that would
be 10 cents or maybe you get a dime each time.
I don't know how it's working.
Clicking on the ads.
But hoaxes and death hoaxes and celebrities faking their deaths, that all is part of pretty
common conspiracy 101 lore, right?
Tupac, Elvis, Miley Cyrus, all these people who have faked their own deaths or been killed
and replaced by clones, stuff like that.
So we are at a point that I predicted this what a couple weeks ago I did an episode called
Should We Melt the Conspiracy Theory Iceberg?
It was episode 704, so it was actually a couple months ago.
But the point is that we were coming across conspiracy theory icebergs that were generated
by AIs.
And I said eventually we're going to get to a point where you're going to have conspiracy
articles written by AIs.
And here we are now, it's happening now.
This is a conspiracy article.
It's not true, it's not true, and it's written in a mysterious way that maybe they are alive.
And then it says no, no, they are alive.
All that information was fake.
It made up a conspiracy theory.
Now 99.999% and this is not to diminish her work, but 99.999% of humanity will never
Google or look up the name Karen Reschick.
They just won't.
So I don't understand why this is doing that.
I guess that if you do it enough and you get enough clicks, they're getting what they
want, but this is such a niche article.
Neach whatever.
The point is it's such a small audience for the article.
It's an assistant director who recently passed away and then people who are also into death
oaks.
And it's almost there.
The machine is almost ready to go because here's the thing, you keep perfecting that.
And they see which articles get the hits and which ones don't.
That James Crumbly article with Bohino probably got a lot more hits.
There's a lot of times it's just a local crime thing.
Guys got shot at ATM and no one's really going to click on that.
I mean, maybe the guy's family is sad, but they'll just go to the legitimate news, but
like the James Crumbly, Bohino thing, that probably gets more clicks.
This AI is going to keep fine tuning itself.
It's that whole idea.
You build a machine that makes nothing but paper clips and eventually it turns the entire
universe into paper clips because it has one sole purpose to make paper clips.
They're creating AIs that have a purpose to create clickable articles and it will learn
what articles are the most clickable, whether or not they're true or not, is irrelevant.
Whether or not the planet Saturn wants to be turned into paper clips is irrelevant.
And the AI will get good enough and it knows what we want and it will make conspiracy theories
up.
And the worst part is, is people will believe them.
Not a lot of people read articles nowadays.
A lot of people just read the headlines, but as this AI, I'm not saying it's going to happen
tomorrow.
I didn't think this is going to happen as quickly as it did, but I think that's what
we're going to see.
We're going to start seeing these AI generated conspiracy theories getting out there.
And most of them are going to be like this, just a blink.
It really, really irritates the people that is close to you and no one else is aware of
it.
But then we're going to get the big ones, some big ones like I don't know flat earth level,
but orange is evil monkeys don't exist level, which does have a cult following.
And the AI will learn and learn how to make better conspiracy theories and people will
start to believe them utter nonsense.
They will believe utter nonsense because the computer told them to.
This is a very, very dark path we're going down.
And that's not even the weirdest part.
Because as I was researching this story, I got hacked.
My P cloud account, which I never really have anything in suffered multiple brute force
attacks.
And so I took the IP and I put it in.
I'm my IP locator.
They came from India.
And I put those links in the show notes.
You can actually see the IP and where it was at.
As I was researching this, just because I was clicking on these links, my Google accounts
started flipping out.
I got multiple emails going.
There's an attempt that someone's trying to log into your account.
Someone's trying to log into your account.
So ended there doing it for multiple locations because I was clicking on these articles.
Now I'm a seasoned computer guy.
I know my way around computers.
I work with other people's computers.
I do not get viruses easily.
This was just from pulling up the website.
This was from me not clicking on anything.
Not watching it.
Not seeing a sexy, ebony video game ad.
Just from pulling up the website and going there and looking at it.
My P cloud account had several brute force attempts.
And I thought, you have that two factor authorization set up and all that stuff.
So that's the future.
That is the future of, I think, conspiracy theory content.
We're going to have to fight against this.
Because it's going to be really cool and it's going to be super sexy.
And the stories the AI will put out will speak to us on a certain level and will make us
go, whoa, this is coming from some enlightened person.
They'll get better at the text generation.
They'll get better at the sentence structure.
And those headlines to get people to click on it in the first place, they'll be indistinguishable
from what a normal lunatic would write.
And it'd actually be better because it'd be fine tuned for what type of things people
are into.
Could you imagine an AI getting a hold of a pizza gate level, creating a pizza gate
level conspiracy?
That's what I'm worried about.
So yeah, fascinating story.
Sorry for your passing, Karen.
And sorry for the pain that it's giving to your child.
That's awful.
Because they're like, I don't want this.
So but it is a harbinger, I believe, of future bad.
Joaquin, let's go ahead and leave behind this story.
I'm going to touch the keys of the carbon recovery.
Leave behind Los Angeles, California.
If we are headed all the way out to Avonio, Italy.
It's spring 1980.
And there's like bumblebees flying.
They're like sitting on flowers and there's like the sun is going goodbye.
And he's just like, I just looked down at my notes and it takes place at night.
The sun sets and then it's like an evening.
It's a cool, crisp spring evening in Italy.
There's a local farmer riding his motorcycle through town.
Let's call him Terry.
So Terry.
I was going to see how long I could do that.
I was going to see if I could do for the rest of the episode.
I just like making motorcycle noises.
He's driving through town on his motorcycle and he sees something in the town square.
A giant glass cage.
It stops his motorcycle.
Pulls his key out.
I should just stop doing this podcast and just do an episode.
Nothing but motorcycle noises.
That one was pretty good.
And he gets off of his motorcycle and he starts walking over and he's looking at this glass
cage in town square.
Now it doesn't say exactly what time of night this was.
It doesn't say how alone he was.
But I'm imagining there weren't a lot of people around because he's the only one at
this point who notices this giant glass cage.
And maybe it's in our project.
Maybe.
But if you let me finish, if you didn't interrupt me, I could tell you what was going on here.
So walking towards this glass cage and he sees inside of it is something.
Something sitting down.
And as he's getting closer to this glass cage he looks and he notices there's someone
inside of it.
Or something.
This figure was very tall.
Even sitting down.
Terry could tell how tall this thing was.
It was sitting straight up with its hands on its knees.
Perfectly poised.
But that would just be Abraham Lincoln getting ready for his photograph to be taken.
He's just a tall guy.
But this thing, that's why it's a thing, its entire body is covered in long green filaments.
Each inch of its skin seems to be a little green.
A little furry.
This thing also had long hair.
But for whatever reason.
I don't know, fashionable, interdimensional physics.
Its hair was standing straight up in the air.
He continues walking towards, I would have left a while ago, right?
I would have been making motorcycle noises back at home.
He continues walking towards this giant green monster.
And that's when all of a sudden he's hit with a powerful odor.
It is so strong it actually begins to disorient him.
He can't get any closer.
This thing smells so strong.
Not bad.
They don't specify that it was a bad smell.
It's just such an overpowering smell.
He couldn't get any closer.
It begins to back off.
And he turns and he starts walking to his motorcycle.
He's like, "If it wasn't our project, if it was the most smelly our project ever, I
don't know what could it have been.
It was a giant guy in a glass tube.
I could have just been, sculpture something like that."
And then all of a sudden he hears the sound of glass breaking.
He turns back and he sees two blonde women standing in the town square screaming at the
top of their lungs.
According to the report, it just says he walked back to his motorcycle and then heard a sound
similar to glass breaking.
As he looked back, he saw two blonde girls screaming.
No other information is how this report ends.
That was reported by Maurizio Virga.
He actually is a really big UFO writer in Italy.
He wrote the very first, at least what he claims, the very first book of UFO sightings
in Italy in English.
It was the very first time that those sightings had been translated to English.
There's so much stuff you could talk about with this story as short as it is.
There are so many places you can go with it.
We don't have a ton of information.
I tried looking for the book that this specifically came from.
I couldn't find it, but he is still putting stuff out.
I'll tell you this right now.
If you want to go to the website of this man, Maurizio Virga, you will see the website of
an Italian UFO researcher.
If you picture an Italian UFO researcher, it's him.
It's the hunkiest researcher you've ever seen.
The photo is like welcome.
Here are the books I have to sell about ET and the website is bordered in photos of him
with his shirt off.
He was just standing there against a rail with the Atlantic Ocean on his back.
It's like, "Is this a dating profile?
Are you trying to find aliens, bro?"
Because you found both.
So you have this hunky UFO researcher on the scene.
But let's break this down by element, because there's really a lot of interesting stuff
to talk about.
One, the glass box appearing in the town square.
Just that alone makes me think of some sort of interdimensional event.
It is just there.
It's something that is out of place of the environment.
So right there, that's just a creepy image.
The giant creature in the box.
We don't get it.
I mean, a humanoid, I'm assuming.
The filament thing, was it an artificial filament or was it, I keep saying hairy just because
I couldn't think of another word, but was it like more of a mechanical or a biomechanical
feel?
Was it more like tubing?
How thick were they?
I think that's really fascinating.
The creature with its hair standing up.
To be honest, I don't like that detail.
That detail is super lame to me.
I make some sound like a giant troll doll, but I'm a reporter.
I got to include it.
But yeah, again, like how is that the physics plane?
And then I find it so much so he's a...
And I joke about wanting to leave, but I would also probably get pretty close to this thing.
He gets close to it.
He's hit with the overpowering smell.
It's very, very common in paranormal lore, whether it's sulfur, whether it's, well, it's
usually sulfur, but these smells that are associated with Bigfoot sightings.
Well, Bigfoot sightings not necessarily sulfur, but it's just a horrible smell that we have
associated with Bigfoot.
So that's interesting.
It ties into the lore.
Let's go back and look at this final ending here, this final event, because there's two
ways to read it.
The first way I read it, and the second way I read it, there's probably more than just
the two ways that I read it.
I'm not God of the universe, but anyways, so the first time I read it, I pictured it
like this.
He sees the giant green guy.
He smells it.
He's running around a leaf.
He hears the glass break and he turns back and he sees the two blonde women screaming.
And the, to me, the implication is that they, the creatures after them, that they got too
close to it and the creature broke out of the glass cage and was coming after them.
That was my initial read on that.
No other information is how that ends.
What a great cliffing.
You're like, did this thing come out and, you know, eat them?
Did it brutally maul them?
They could throw armor on each babe and be like, where's the nearest club, women?
I'm from Orion's Nebula and I'm ready to party.
Like we don't know.
We don't know.
But there's another way to read it too, just using the exact same text.
And this is, when I was reading it later, this is like, well, maybe this is what happened.
He then heard a sound similar to glass breaking.
As he looked back, he saw two blonde girls screaming.
No other information.
He hears the shattering of the glass.
There's a big giant green monster in the glass cage.
He's not looking at it.
He turns back and now, in place of the glass cage, he sees two blonde women screaming.
Because that's what it sounds like when you read it like that.
He doesn't say that he saw the monster at all.
He doesn't say that he saw the glass cage in rubble.
He turned back and he saw, in its place, two blonde women screaming.
Which to me is infinitely more bizarre and a little terrifying.
Because that goes back into that whole reality shifting alternate.
I can't even really wrap my head around that.
If I saw a glass box and monster breaks out of a glass box and attacks a bunch of random
people, not me, I'm fine with that.
I can wrap my head around that because that's what animals do.
That's what humans do, right?
You break out and you fight.
You start being a people near you.
Never play couch cushion for it with me because I'll push out of them and start being you
up.
But I'm thinking about this now.
What if that box shattered and two blonde women who had been abducted by aliens or
something like that appeared?
This was some sort of dimensional placeholder.
The beast was no threat.
The beast was just some sort of image that was conjured up.
And when the glass thing disappeared, the women were returned.
Or...
The glass box explodes.
I'm making this way weirder than...
He turns back.
He sees two blonde women screaming.
Are the two blonde women real?
Are they also an image?
Like where did they come from?
You know what I'm saying?
Like what if this green monster man shows up in a glass box and he's sitting there and
he's like, "I've journeyed long from Orion's Nebula.
I wanted a party, but first I have a mission to complete."
And then he breaks out of the glass cage and becomes two hot blonde chicks.
And they're screaming because the mission is a success.
Because you can't tell the difference.
When a woman's screaming, you can't tell if someone just chopped off her right foot or
she saw her best friend she hasn't seen in three years.
And so Terry turns around and he's like, "Ah, and now there was these two hot blondes walking
around Italy, but it was really one giant green alien guy split between them."
And they're like going to the clubs and they're like dancing with each other, all sexy against
each other.
But for him, that would just be him like playing with his own, like tweaking with his own nipples.
Little nipple clamps.
But to everyone else, looks like these two hot blondes are like rubbing up on each other.
And then he goes, "Okay, I got that out of my system.
I really wanted to..."
It's like, "Next up, the shower."
But anyway, so after about two or three weeks of him just exploring himself or herself's,
now that he's two blonde women, then they go get a job at like, I don't know, a nuclear
power plant?
Do they have those in Italy?
They go to France.
And if he has used these blonde women's bodies to infiltrate our planet, because I'm going
to tell you this right now, that is the perfect disguise because just people will let you
go anywhere.
Like if you're walking into a nuclear facility, they'd be like, "Jason, they didn't even
recognize me."
They're like, "Not again.
No, you cannot have any plutonium."
And if you did, it would not turn you into a superhero.
You have to leave.
You have to imagine like a super hot blonde, like walking by.
She's like, "Oh no, I need to go in there."
It's like an open reactor.
They're like, "Sure, go ahead."
And if there's two hot blondes, I'm glad, does it even say in the notes that they're
hot?
It just says they're two blonde girls.
But you know, if two hot blondes showed up at the White House, they're like, "We want
to see the president."
The Secret Service is going to be like, "That's cool."
And just like, "Let him in."
My point is, I don't know what this ending is.
Not this ending I'm recording right now, but this ending of the story.
I think there's the way to read it, and I think the classical way to read it is, the
monster broke out and went after the girls.
And maybe we have lost time.
Terry doesn't really remember what happened.
Because that is very common in UFO lore that something crazy happens and then the memory
just stops.
Totally possible.
And it would also be a hundred times more puzzling if he turns around, the green monster
is gone, the two blonde women are there screaming, and then they just walk away.
That would also just be the end of the story.
And you would have a harder time wrapping your head around that.
Monsters attacking people, that's what monsters do.
Monsters turning into people, or monsters ceasing to exist, and then two people just
standing there.
That's way weirder, and it's infinitely more scary.
Because then I have to wonder, who's to say, like when I'm walking down the street, that
the people around me aren't trying to green monsters full in half?
They probably aren't, right?
If that's your unique paranoia, I'm not saying, I'm not trying to worry you.
But it would be the perfect way to infiltrate.
Coming down and turning into beautiful women, and you would be marrying super powerful people.
You'd be marrying UFO researchers, hunky UFO researchers.
That would be, yeah, I wonder, actually, now that I say that.
That would be really good, and aliens come down and then they start banging UFO researchers,
because you know we're like the top of the genetic breed.
But then they could change our research.
So yeah, I don't know.
I think, there's like, Jason, the story was actually really creepy.
The idea that there's a monster appears in the middle of town and starts chasing women,
that was creepy.
I don't know.
I don't know what you're going on about all this women can go anywhere you even at when
you're saying that a beautiful woman can walk into a nuclear power plant.
I'm not saying, okay, maybe not the White House, but I think it's easier for them to
get access.
I'm talking like top models, right?
If you're super hot, you'd have an easier time getting into a restricted area.
And where do aliens want to go?
Restricted areas.
They're constantly flying their UFOs over nuclear power plants, and maybe they go, now
let's go see what's inside.
So they tried being like a little gray alien and they got dissected.
And then they just tried looking like a normal nerd who works in a nuclear power plant and
they're like, can we see your ID?
And then they showed up as like Jessica Rabbit.
And then the general's like, boy, his eyes are like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
They're like, oh, we need to keep him away from that plutonium.
And they started to melt his face.
He's all, aw.
And so that's what I'm talking about.
Aliens should become beautiful women and infiltrate these high level places.
I just realized, I think I've described like five CineMax soft core porn's in the past
10 minutes.
But yeah, I think that would be a good plan.
So, so was this really a spooky monster that broke out of a glass cage that I ruined a
story?
That I ruined a really cool story about a monster that broke out of a glass cage and attacked
two women.
And then Terry just had no recollection because his memory was wiped.
It's possible.
It's very scary.
It's very scary that I discover a conspiracy that aliens is very, very specific conspiracy
theory.
No AI can come up with this, that aliens are coming down and turning themselves into two
hot blondes.
Because if you think that we can fight off an alien invasion, you're probably right.
But what if the aliens were super bangable?
Would you be willing to pick up a pulse rifle and shoot Pamela Anderson like an army of them
coming at you in the Baywatch outfit?
They're not dressed in like some dummy alien outfit.
They're dressed up in the red outfit and like Britney Spears is like on this commander ship
and she's like sending a bunch of Taylor Swift out.
Those are like the ground forces, the foot soldiers.
They're like, oh, you can wipe those off the map.
They're coming across the field, but no one take out the Britney Spears.
We wouldn't be able to do that.
We would just battle down to our beautiful alien overlords.
And I've realized that now that I've spoken that into the universe, on the Omnicron Nebula,
they are already in their ships right now, headed out to Earth.
It'll be the sexiest invasion of all time.
[Music]