Today we visit Romania to check out a mysterious mountain range and the unexplained mysteries underneath
and then we will summon, not literally because I'm not gonna do it, but
and then we will summon the Ouija Demon known as Zozo.
Is it real?
We'll find out today.
If I was a demon, I think I'd pick a better name, but we'll talk about Zozo today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
*Demons playing*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too.
If I was a demon name, yeah, I don't think I would pick the name Zozo.
That just reminds me too much of Bozo.
It's a very, like, I assume that demons are kinda like bikers.
Like, I'm sure the angels got assigned to their names and God's like, "You're Michael, you're..."
"What's in that?" "Gabriel, you're..." "Ausereel, whatever."
But I'm assuming the demons, they probably had angel names and God's like, "Your name is Christopher."
And then when they go to hell, they're like, "Man, no way, dude. I'm Agamemnon."
Or that's actually a real guy.
"I'm Azeroth or I'm a badden or I'm something like dope and this poor demon got stuck with Zozo."
But I'm getting a little ahead of myself.
So let's go ahead and get started because I am already getting ahead of myself.
You're gonna have to wait for more Zozo commentary till the end.
Let's talk about, now, okay, if you've listened to the show long enough,
when you heard me say we go to Romania, I'm sure a lot of you were reaching for the skip button
because you know I can't pronounce stuff.
And when a story takes place in any country other than America, I can't pronounce most of it.
And to be fair, there's a lot of stuff I can't pronounce in America either.
But yes, we're going to Romania.
So we're going to Romania.
We are going to take the carpenter copter over there.
It's quite a long journey, but it's a very comfortable helicopter.
It's quite roomy.
It's like a Chinook. It's like big.
So anyways, the carpenter copter...
[mimics carpenters]
...goes all the way over to Romania.
And we're going to the... Here we go, guys.
[laughs]
Here we go with the pronunciations.
We're going to the Busegi Mountains.
So the Busegi Mountains is a mountain range.
It's actually... Well, it's part of the bigger mountain range throughout Europe.
But the Busegi Mountains are in Romania.
And there's a few reasons.
People have always thought there was something off about these mountains.
Some people thought it was often a good way.
Some people thought it was often a bad way.
So there's two monuments on the mountains.
One is the Sphinx.
I got that pronunciation, right?
Sphinx.
And the other one is the Babel.
So the Babel means old woman in Romanian, supposedly.
But it's just two big old mushrooms.
Two big old rocks that look like mushrooms.
The Sphinx is part of the mountainside that does, admittedly, look like the Sphinx from Egypt.
But more weathered.
So you can kind of see the outline of a chin.
You can kind of see the outline of a nose and so on and so forth.
Obviously, though, when you look at it, you go, "Yeah, I guess it can kind of look like a Sphinx."
But the idea was, the rumor going around was that there really was a Sphinx there,
and it just got weathered so much.
And so aliens made it.
And scientists go, "No, that's not true."
What happened was it was a normal mountain that just got weathered down
and just happens to kind of look like a face.
But locals were like, "There's something mystical about these mountains."
Now, in...
Oh, and I do want to say this.
There's not a lot of information, or I should say there's not a lot of well-written information on this mountain range,
but it is supposed to be a big deal.
That is an interesting story nonetheless.
So in 2003, the rumor goes, in 2003, the Pentagon was flying a spy satellite looking for geological deposits.
It had like this ground penetrating beam that let it see what was under the earth.
I don't know if those actually exist, but it wouldn't make sense,
and you'd want to know what resources were in certain areas to deny enemy access to those areas.
But anyway, so the ground penetrating satellite was shooting beams into the mountain range,
and it discovered a massive underground chamber inside the mountain.
Then what happened was, I'm going to read this quote from this book.
There's a book called Transylvania Sunrise, which is a bomb name.
It's a great name, and it really goes into the story of the Bussegee Mountains.
This is a quote from it.
Okay, so it says in 2003, the Pentagon discovered, the story I just told you,
then it goes on to say, "Through the highest levels of Freemasonry,
the Pentagon was able to secure an alliance with the most secret department of the Romanian intelligence service,
which is known as Department Zero."
So, and first off, the Pentagon wouldn't need the Freemasons to put them in touch with the Romanian government.
It took place in 2003, they could pick up a phone or just fly over there.
But anyway, so apparently they had to use their Freemason contacts to get a hold of the people in Romania
to say, "Hey, we want to look and see what's in that mountain."
And the rumor goes that that's the reason why Romania was allowed to join NATO.
Not because it is a kind of a choke point against Russia,
but it's because they have something in their mountain range.
We had the Vatican and the Freemasons and the Pentagon all going to Romania,
and what they supposedly found was huge underground caverns with huge chairs and huge tables made of stone.
So it made it look like a race of giants lived under the mountains before.
These tunnels apparently crisscross around the world.
So these tunnels, you can go into the tunnel in Romania.
So you can hop in like a little mine cart and go from Romania underneath the Busegi mountains to underneath the Sphinx in Egypt.
Okay, so then you catch a little mine cart, it takes two of us.
So it's one of those ones where you're like one person's pump in each side and moves down the rail.
It's going to take us for like eight years to do this journey.
We can go to Egypt. We can go to Baghdad. The tunnels also go to Baghdad.
They also go to Mount Kaleesh or Kaliash in Tibet.
And they all kind of meet in one or two places underneath the Gobi Plateau in Mongolia.
It's this massive opening where it's like everyone's just kind of hanging out.
And it also, you can take it all the way to Antarctica.
So I just to be clear here, the stories is that you can take a tunnel from Egypt to Antarctica.
I don't care how big you are. That is a long walk.
So unless these giants had some sort of technology, that's, you'd still be like, dude, I'm not going to Antarctica.
Like I don't care what's down there. I'm hanging out underneath the Sphinx. I'm good.
So the story goes is that that's where the government wanted it because they realized there is this huge underground civilization.
They're gone now. There was no reports at least that I saw.
I haven't read Transylvanian sunrise.
But again, from what I read, there weren't like fighting giants down there.
Anything is just all kind of empty rooms.
So I read all that stuff and I was like, you know, I guess it's possible that there's tunnels crisscrossing.
Oh, actually, there are tunnels crisscrossing the planet.
But and I, you know, there's been theories about giants in the past and things like that.
But I read the, and that was it. I was like, I hope this is kind of a dead end.
And I was like, oh, they found this tunnel that I've never heard of no other conspiracy sites to ever really talk about this mountain range.
So I was like, but then I found something interesting.
When I say found something interesting, I simply continued to read the article I was previously reading.
But at this point, I was getting kind of bored. I was like, oh, yeah, tunnels, stone, big tables, no bodies there, no technologies.
Just even if I accept the story of it as being true, it's just much empty tunnels that go everywhere.
Then I read something interesting as they scroll down another three inches.
So from the year 82 BC to 106 AD, in that area, there was the kingdom of Dachia, kingdom of Dachia.
And the people there were known as Dachians. They were also known as Thracians.
So, but anyways, they lived in this area until the Romans eventually conquered them in 106 AD.
Now, there is a Greek historian named Herodotus.
Herodotus. Now, I have to say, imagine you're born and your parents holding you a little baby boy and it's Greek times,
and they look at you and they go, your name will be Herodotus.
And you're like, yes. And then they go, Dotus.
You'd be like, come on, man, why couldn't you just stop that Herodotus?
But anyways, this guy's name is Herodotus. I could be pronouncing it wrong.
I'm most certainly pronouncing it wrong. But anyways, Herodotus was a Greek historian.
And he wrote about the Thracians. They had a story.
They worshiped this god named Zalmoxis.
Zalmoxis was their deity that watched over him.
And Zalmoxis lived in the mountains.
And I have this. This is actually from Herodotus' histories of the area.
He just thought this was crazy. So this is referring to the Thracians.
They believe they are immortal forever living in the following sense.
They think they do not die and that the one who dies joins Zalmoxis, a divine being.
Some call this same divine being, Gebollecius.
Every four years, they send a messenger to Zalmoxis who is chosen by chance.
They ask him to tell Zalmoxis what they want on that occasion.
So he says, "Hey, we're going to pick you and we're going to tell you the message we want delivered to Zalmoxis."
And you're like, "Oh, okay, I'll go do that. Let me continue with Herodotus' story."
The mission is performed in the following way.
Men standing there for that purpose hold three spears.
Other people take the one who was sent to Zalmoxis by his hands and feet and fling him in the air on the spears.
If he dies pierced, they think that the divinity is going to help them.
If he does not die, it is he who is accused and they declare that he is a bad person.
And after he has been charged, they send another one.
So basically, you get pulled out of the crowd.
You're like, "All right, I'm going to go meet Zalmoxis."
And you're kind of suspicious because you realize you've never seen anyone come back from this ritual.
And you get there and you see dudes holding spears and other guys grab your hands and feet and they start going one, two.
And then you realize that's why no one ever comes back.
So if you get stabbed, if you die from being landing on the spears, that means it's a good omen.
If you don't die, if you just get horribly mangled, then you are a bad person and not a good offering to Zalmoxis.
Little ritual bizarre thing to this God, but here's the weird thing.
Zalmoxis, according to Herodotus, who did the history of this area, Zalmoxis actually existed.
He was a freed slave of Pythagoras, the math guy.
And so he learned all about math and Pythagorium theorems and a bunch of smart Greek stuff.
And he went to Romania and used his knowledge to make himself incredibly rich and powerful
because he was smarter than everybody.
And then one day he said, "You know what? I need a break.
I'm gonna go dig a tunnel in the Buseki Mountains."
And he did.
He just went in and created this home and people thought he had died.
Three or four years had passed.
And then he showed back up and was like, "Yeah, no, I'm fine. I was just building a massive tunnel system under those mountains.
What do you guys want?"
People would get his advice and then after a while he'd be like, "Yeah, I'm gonna go back."
Weird.
That was a weird connection because now it's definitely possible that the guy who wrote Transylvania, Sunrise,
knew of the legend of Zalmoxis and said, "Oh, tunnels underneath the mountains.
I'm gonna weave that into my story."
But I mean, that's the most likely scenario, but it is still weird that they had this god that they sacrificed people to
and they were able to track it back to a living person who was like, and he did take that time period
where he was gone for a couple years, he was gone for four years, and then he comes back out
and that's why they had that thing where every four years they'd have to sacrifice someone to this guy under the mountain.
Really, he was probably just a pile of bones they were sacrificing this guy to.
But it's still weird to... How often can we track a deity back to a real person, but I just realized that's Jesus.
And Muhammad. Yeah.
Okay, so maybe it's not so... I still think it's an interesting story.
So let's go ahead and move on because I still think it was interesting.
Let's go ahead and move on to the next story.
So the next story is actually a request from a YouTube user under the name Jackie.
Jackie hit me up and said, "Hey, why don't you do something on Zozo?"
Now, I was slightly familiar with the name.
I actually thought Zozo was more of like a Charlie Charlie type of thing.
I didn't really put much credence into it.
I knew of Pazuzu, which is supposedly like this ancient Babylonian Assyrian demon.
And I think it was the demon in the Exorcist. I've never seen the Exorcist.
At a certain point, the movies become so parodied that I don't think I would enjoy it.
I don't think it'd be scary to me.
But anyways, so Zozo.
So the story behind Zozo is this.
It is a demon that primarily uses the Ouija board as its conduit into our reality.
A lot of times it will... When you're trying to talk to it, you can dress it directly,
but the planchette will be moving to the Z's a lot.
It will be doing crisscrosses, so it hits like Z-E-O, Z-E-O, Z-E-O, Z-O.
Sometimes people say it spells out the name Zaza, which technically isn't its name.
And then other people have a more sinister story.
They're saying that Zozo is being contacted during a lot of Ouija experiences,
just using different names, because Zozo is basically like a Ouija board demon.
So Zozo, the story of Zozo really started in 2009.
Now people, and that should give you spoiler alert, but people say that there's records going farther back.
But in 2009, a man posted on the internet on a website that has the reputable name "True Ghost Tales".
But anyways, he posts on that and he tells a story about his encounter with Zozo.
He said that it's... He was talking to it and it was being sinister.
He kept going back to the Ouija board, like over the matter of days or weeks or months or something like that.
He wanted to possess his girlfriend, he wanted to possess women, take them into paradise.
And when the guy who wrote this post, Darren Wayne Evans, asked where's paradise it spelled out, hell.
He also claims that the demon tried to drown his daughter somehow.
And then he claims that he asked the Ouija board, "What should I name my band?"
Now, again, I don't know the exact sequence of events, but I think after...
First off, if I'm ever using Ouija board, and I never have, they don't really interest me,
but if I was ever going to use the Ouija board and it started telling me it was going to possess my girlfriend and take her to hell,
I'm done with the Ouija board.
If my daughter gets drowned, I'm done with the Ouija board.
I'm assuming that he asked what he should name his band before all of this.
But anyways, he goes, "What should I name my band?"
And the board spelled out "Iron Tongue" and he's like, "Oh yeah, that'd be a dope name!"
And then his daughter's tongue swelled up.
Whatever the sequence of events, if you ask for your band's name, and the band's name was "Iron Tongue"
and your daughter's tongue swelled up, put away the Ouija board.
But then he continued to mess around with it and he said that he went to different states,
totally different locations, got different Ouija boards, Zozo still showed up.
Again, dude, if this happens once, why are you still playing with Ouija boards?
His daughter ends up getting an infection that almost killed her because he's blaming it on Zozo.
So there's three things that are possible here.
One, the story is creepypasta, it's 100% fake.
And the evidence to that is that there's really not...
There's... people say there are earlier mentions of Zozo, but I couldn't find any.
Now, people say there are cave paintings of Slenderman, people can say all sorts of things,
but it doesn't actually mean that they exist.
So there is the demon Pazuzu, which people have said, "Oh, maybe Zozo is just a bastardization of the name Pazuzu possible."
So the possibility is that he just made the story up.
Second possibility is it actually happened.
It's totally real.
Actually, I guess those are the only two options.
I don't know why I had a third option in mind, but anyway, so he either made it up, or it's real.
Or actually, no, here's a third option.
It's real, but it was coincidences.
And he was able to compress them all into one thing, so it may have said your band's name is Iron Tongue,
and then four weeks later, his daughter got stung by a bee on the tongue or something like that.
Like, you could have a string of coincidences.
But the Zozo story really took off.
There is a movie about Zozo.
There's tons of sites on how to, like, deal with Zozo if he shows up, how to know that you're talking to Zozo.
One of them is... it spells out the name Zozo.
That's a pretty good sign that you're talking to Zozo.
But it really caught fire.
I think there's an intrinsic creepiness to playing with the Ouija board.
It's like half board game with your friends, half communicating with the dead.
It has a very, very low skill entry.
It's not like, "Oh, we have to lay out these eight candles and smudge the room and draw this pentagram and salt."
It's just a piece of wood and a little plant shed, this little moving thing.
One thing, again, talking to the dead doesn't really interest me.
Ouija boards don't really interest me. I think it's a parlor trick for the most part.
But I don't actually buy the scientific excuse for Ouija boards.
What they say is... because, of course, they've done tests on this.
They say that you put your fingers down on the plant shed.
It's called the ideometer effect.
And it's... your body is subconsciously or unconsciously kind of moving constantly.
And when you're putting your fingers on the plant shed, it's moving to letters that you want the answer to.
So, you know, here's a quote here.
It says, "The unconscious muscle movements responsible for Ouija board phenomenon seen at seances are an example of a class of phenomenon due to what psychologists call a disassociative state."
Basically, like, I'm putting my fingers on the plant shed and I'm like, "What do I want for dinner?"
And it's like, "E...G...G...S."
And I'm like, "Oh my God, how did it know that I was hungry for eggs?"
But I don't understand how the ideometer or the idiometer effect takes place when most Ouija sessions have multiple people.
So everyone's going to have their own unconscious thing.
I guess maybe one person pushes it more than the other.
But to me, Ouija boards, it's... I'm in this weird gray area because I don't believe they work personally.
But I don't believe the scientific explanation for why they don't work.
Like, I think if they did work, every general would be like, "General Washington, will we win this battle?"
Every politician would be consulting the debt.
Like, if we knew that they worked, they wouldn't be toys.
They would be... You would have to go to, like, a lab to check one out or something like that.
I mean, okay, maybe you could buy one over the counter, but it would be this thing that everyone did because everyone would want advice from people in the afterlife.
There's no proof that we can talk to the debt at all.
If I'm proven otherwise, fine.
I don't think they work, but I don't buy that explanation.
It almost feels like scientists said, "You know what? We don't think these work, and we're just going to come up with an explanation why, and we're just going to stop halfway through."
Because it doesn't account for all these other things.
All these other things going on.
So I'm in this weird area where I'm a skeptic towards them.
I don't think they work because if they did work, everyone would use them.
And they used to be super popular.
They actually started... This is kind of sad.
They boomed in popularity in America after the Civil War because everyone wanted to talk to their dead relatives.
So many people lost so many loved ones that they started manufacturing these spirit boards.
And that's just a sad thing.
That's why they boomed because of the loss of so many American lives, men and women and young kids and all that stuff.
People turned to the spiritualism.
If they actually worked, I think people would still use them on a greater scale than they do.
But I don't believe that the scientists are really being...
I don't think the scientists are really making their case for why they don't work.
So I'm just in this weird area with them.
I don't know.
And as far as the existence of Zozo goes, that's another thing.
Like, it's possible?
It's possible.
And if they're... Okay, let's assume for a second that Ouija boards do work.
And they contact the dead and they can contact demons and stuff like that.
We buy into all the stories that Ouija boards can do.
Yes, then absolutely there can be a demon named Zozo.
His actual name may not have been Zozo.
It could have been Pazuzu or something else.
And he shortened it so he could do that swirling motion.
Or maybe because the name sounds a little funny, a little creepy.
It's like a playful, jester type demon.
If you accept that Ouija boards work, then yeah, Zozo could definitely be true.
Again, I'm skeptical on Ouija boards, but I still think that there would be demons out there
who would follow you from state to state.
Like, if it really knew that it could have had a gateway into your life,
it would follow you from state to state.
But I do have to say, guys, despite all the warnings and the signs
and everything about that on what to do if Zozo shows up at your Ouija session,
if he does and makes your daughter's tongue swell up, gives her an affection, tries to drown her,
stop playing with Ouija boards.
Like, the guy almost, the author almost seems like he had an addiction to him.
I don't know, man, hey, maybe that was part of the Zozo's curse.
Maybe he couldn't control himself.
Maybe Zozo was making him, in a way, communicate more.
Or maybe it was all just really entertaining creepypasta
that ended up spawning an entire internet myth.
I guess we won't know unless we break out the Ouija board.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[Music]