When a young boy is told not to play in his parents closet, he's gonna do it
anyways. But what's waiting in that closet may have him questioning, what is reality?
And then we meet a young couple starting off life together. While they currently
live in a small town home, they've always been on the search for their dream
house. Little do they know that their dream house is also searching for them.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm here with
Stays and Carvener. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day
too. I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing. We got a
lot of stuff to cover sure we're gonna get started right away. First off, walking
into Dead Rabbit Command right here is one of our legacy Patreons. Long time
supporter of the show. Give it up for... I can't pronounce your name bro. You're gonna have to forgive me.
Rolf! Woohoo! Yeah, Rolf! Come on, everyone's like, is he calling my name? I don't know. No one's walking in yet.
Rolf. R-O-L-F. Rolf. You're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode. If you
guys can't support the Patreon, if you guys don't want to hear me totally butchering your name,
that's fine too. Just help spread the word about the show. That really, really
helps out a lot. Rolf, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit
Durgible. We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're gonna start our
journey off by flying all the way out to a little house in suburban America.
[Durgible sound]
Also, while we're taking the journey out there, I want to tell you guys that this
week drops a new episode of the Asylum Case Studies. It is a podcast hosted by
my friend Tressa, where she invites people on to watch Really Bad or sometime I like.
I don't know why she keeps having me back on. I was like, oh, that was a good show.
That's a good one. She invites people on to watch Asylum Movies. Those are those
sci-fi channel mockbusters like Transmorphers or Android Cop and things
like that. We recently did Mega Piranha. Piranha is so big they eat a
battleship. It's hilarious and grueling. It was one of the worst movies that I've
watched. Definitely one of the worst movies I've watched on the Asylum Case
Studies. So check out that episode. I'll have it in the show notes. The Asylum Case
Studies. It is a great podcast. Rolf is flying us on out to this house. Now we
don't have a lot of details. This story was posted anonymously recently on the
export. Someone was asking for weird creature stories. He had some good ones.
He had stuff about like reptilians or seeing like weird things in the forest
and stuff like that. There's some good stuff. But again, the question always is,
is it dead rabbit radio interesting? And as I'm scrolling through this thread, there's a
lot of good stuff. But this was the one that I was like, wow, this is a crazy
story. Crazy if true. Obviously whenever we come across stuff anywhere online,
written in a book or a magazine, World of the Paranormal, a lot of people lie, make
stuff up. But let's take a look at this story. Now we don't have this person's
name, no date, anything like that. But I'm gonna call this guy Gary. We're gonna say
that he lives somewhere in suburban America. Gary tells this story. He says,
listen, when I was around five or six years old, this happened to me. I was a
young little guy. His dad goes, hey, Gary, listen, don't ever go in my closet.
Don't ever go in my closet. I don't know if he said it that ominously. I don't
think if he hopped out every so often, like the little boys getting out of the
shower, dad jumps out, don't go in the closet. Mow in the lawn, dad pops out of
the weeds, don't go in the closet, he almost get ran over with lawnmower. I don't know if
it was a constant refrain, but the dad was very clear, do not go into my closet,
Gary. I'm assuming Gary was a little whippersnapper, a little Dennis the
Menace-esque character constantly getting the escapades. He did almost run over his
dad with a lawnmower that one day, but Gary goes, listen, my dad told me not to
play in the closet and I knew why because he had a gun in the closet, but he
told him not to go in the closet. So of course Gary's going to go in the closet.
That's what kids do. And Gary said, sure enough, one day I was at home and I went
into the closet. I went into my parents' closet and he goes, when I'm in the
closet, I find this small, plain cardboard box. He's looking at this box and he said
there were holes on the side where you could pick the box up. And he picked it
up and it was empty. The box was completely empty. He said, okay. And then he flipped
the box over to use as a table. So I don't know if he brought, I don't know if he
brought in a spread of meat and cheeses and he's like, oh, this is the only place
I can relax. The parents' closet. I got my little snack ready to go. My PSP. I'm just
gonna sit here and play some video games and eat these snacks. I don't know why.
I mean, I can understand one thing wanting to go into a closet if your parents say
don't go in the closet, but I don't know why once he was in there he decided to
turn it into a little living space. Brings in a beanbag chair. He flips the box
over and he says I'm gonna use it as a table and he said, what happened was
after flipping it over and setting it down on the ground hundreds of bugs
began to crawl out of the holes on the side of the box. Now he shirks back in
fear, but it's that type of paralysis fear. He can't do anything. He can't even
scream as he sees an untold amount of beetles and cockroaches and ants and
cinnapedes spill out of this box and he goes those cinnapedes were impossibly
large. Like they were just the grossest biggest cinnapedes I'd ever seen in my
life and he goes I'm just watching this ocean of insect life pour out of this
empty box. He didn't pick it up and go huh this seems like it's holding an
infinite number of bugs. He was empty, but when he flipped it over all of these
bugs are pouring out of the box and he was freaking out and he's so scared he
can't even scream. He goes I didn't move. I didn't say a word. I just sat there and
stared at all of these bugs pouring out of the side of this box and then he goes
I don't remember what happened next. He goes I was staring at this gross
monstrosity. I was staring at all these disgusting bugs crawl out of this box
and the next thing I know I'm not in the closet anymore. Like I just I don't
really remember anything. I think I might have passed out. I don't know. I'm just a
little tipped Gary. It's probably not good to pass out when there's a bunch of
bugs around because they're gonna climb inside you right. They're gonna climb in
your mouth and your nose and all that stuff. But assuming an insect, assuming a
human controlled by insects didn't type out this post. He goes I don't even
remember the end of the story. He goes here's the thing it could have been a
dream. It could have been a dream because it just doesn't make sense and I don't
remember it ever ending. He goes I could have hallucinated it but I never had a
hallucination before or since. Nothing like that. I'd never seen anything
like that before. He goes I don't know. I'm pretty sure that was a memory though.
Like I remember it. And that was an interesting story. There right there is
interesting story where he picks the box up and flips it over and a previously
empty box. Again if he had picked it up and it was heavy, bunch of bucks poured
out of it. That's just him releasing his dad's private insect collection. But the
fact that the box was empty when he picked it up and when he set it down
they crawled out. Interesting. Now assuming the story's not a hallucination or not a
dream, there's an interesting spin on this. Another person posting on the
X-board gave this theory. And to be fair even they said it's just a theory. This is
just a theory but we talk about this a lot on the show. He said I think that when
you went in that closet there was the box you found was the box with the gun. And
you accidentally killed yourself. And as he was sitting there looking at all the
bugs coming out he was watching the decay of his old body. Like the bugs and
the centipedes and the cockroaches were all these things that were crawling
around this dead boy's skin inside this coffin. It was a representation of that
but he shifted into a universe where he was still alive. He still has the memory
of the decay. He still has the memory of these horrible life forms crawling all
over him. And the only way his mind can process a memory that happened after he
died was in this sort of theatrical manner. But basically you accidentally
killed yourself when you went to the closet. Your parents told you not to go
in the closet. You accidentally shot yourself. You died. And then you have
brief memories of being dead. And then you got slotted into a universe where
you're still alive. Quantum immortality. We've talked a lot about it on this show.
And I think I'll put a couple episodes in the show notes that talk about that. I
think it's very fascinating. It's a theory I'm not 100% on. I don't I have
some serious questions about that which I've talked about in past episodes so
I'm not gonna reiterate it here. But this story also reminded me of the story
it was about the wheel. This guy got in a horrible car accident and then a giant
city-sized wheel like a water wheel showed up and scooped him up and we're
trying to throw him into a random universe. What a fascinating story that was
and that this is right like this is possible. It's possible the author
totally made it up but it's also possible that it was a dream or
hallucination but it could be again the fact of someone dying in one universe
and shifting over to another one. And it kind of matches some of those details.
Really really creepy story nonetheless though. Rolf let's go ahead and toss you
the keys. I'm gonna put the keys for the carbonar copter in a box full of maggots.
Rolf go ahead and reach your hand into this box of maggots and I don't know
why I tormented my Beijing border so much. I'm so grateful for your assistance.
I will reach in and grab it. That's the type of gentleman I am. I will squeeze the
maggots for you. Rolf here's the keys to the carbonar copter. We're leaving
behind this young boy's house. We're headed all the way out to another house.
This is a lot of houses. This is a house themed episode.
Before we move on I want to do real quick Dead Rabbit Recommends. It's called the
Movie House. The Movie House. That was a creepy movie. I actually don't know if I'd
say Dead Rabbit Recommends that but it was about like if I remember correctly
John Goodman and Bill Maher they were fighting Vietnam veterans who were
hunting a house or something like that. Maybe that movie was a dream actually
and now that I think about it. Rolf fly this carbonar copter over to this town
home. Now again this is a story. This wasn't posted on the export but it was
posted anonymously and the person who posted. I had this story sitting in my
file for a while. This was one of those stories where I wasn't for sure I was
going to do it. Not because it's not cool but we'll get to that in a second and
then in the meantime I found the story. I was prepping the story and the person
deleted their account and deleted this post. Everything's disappeared but
luckily I was able to find... I mean literally like as I was working on it
this week I went to go double check something. They just canceled everything
out. Luckily I was able to find it in the web archive so there is a way for you to
read this story as well. But long time listeners of the show know that I'm not
a huge fan of dreams. Not that I don't want you to have your own hopes and
aspirations. Not that I don't enjoy my own sleepy time dreams. Dreams are so
weird already. Sometimes there's a lot of symbolism. Sometimes it's just neurons
firing that. I've never been a huge fan of telling people's dreams or
interpreting dreams and things like that. However this story hits a certain bar
because this story does something quite odd. So that's why I was kind of teetering
like "Dude is this Dead Rabbit Radio interesting?" and I decided to go with it
and let's go ahead and get this story started. This user they deleted their
account but we're gonna go ahead and call her Monica. So Monica currently is
engaged to a young man we'll call him Brad and Monica and Brad are living in
the small town home along with Brad's son. And she said you know this was a nice
house but we were always looking for our forever home. We were looking for our
dream house and we would often go through Zillow which is a real estate
website looking at different houses and they'd watch all that HD TV do the home
or blow the home and where you can either figure out if you want to live in it or
set it on fire with a blow torch or the two brothers knock out your window in
the show where they just walk around and kick windows out of random houses you
know all those HD TV shows. Garden it or gallow it where you have 24 hours to
make the perfect garden or you get hung all that stuff and they're looking
through Zillow and they're constantly looking for their dream home. Now on
this particular day apparently this is fairly recent she said the night before
we had a big family dinner. So they're retired right they're all got the big
bellies full of turkey and they had to prepare everything for all these people
coming over and they probably stayed up too late and they're watching HD TV they're
like oh no I hope that guy doesn't get home today I really like the way he
planted those petunias. The next day they're still beat and they said how old
are these people? Are these people like 65? What are you talking about? Anyways they
don't they get tired if they stay up too late or something like that. So they take
a nap in the middle of the day they take a nap they go you know what there sure
was a lot of work last night let's both take a nap so Monica and Brad catch a
couple snoozies. Monica is now walking through this big house and she's
admiring it like it's large and it's old and it's everything her and Brad ever
wanted in a home. She's looking around and she's like oh look at all these open
windows look at how the sunlight comes into this room and I'll go in this room
oh it's so beautiful they have like four walls and a ceiling and then look at
look at stairs I can go down a floor and she's walking around this house they
just purchased their dream home and as she's walking through this house she
starts to realize that this house is not just big it's huge. She's checking out
all the rooms and she's walking on the hallways which seem to be more like
corridors that go on forever. The house seems infinitely large. Her and Brad meet
again this house they're sending smoke signals to each other they're like I'm
down here here they meet back up this is their new home they bought it they go to
bed and Monica wakes up and something is not right. She goes this is a dream this
is a dream I live in a town home like this is just a dream this house isn't
real and Brad is like no honey this house is real trust me trust me when we get
the first mortgage payment you realize how real it is and she's like no no no
something's off like this isn't real I'm just dreaming. Monica would spend the day
walking through the house looking at everything wow I can't believe we just
bought this house so beautiful and then she'd wake up in the bed in the house
this old house she'd wake up in a bed in this house and go this isn't real this
is just a dream and her fiance would say honey no this is real trust me once you
get the first mortgage payment you'll realize how real this no no no this
isn't real something's wrong she'd be walking through the house during the
day and she started having this thought in the back of her head this isn't real
I'm gonna wake up tonight and I'm gonna know that this is a dream but right now
this feels real this is real is it and then she would wake up at night I knew
I knew something's wrong I'm I can't get out of this dream like I've spent a
couple days here and this is all a dream this is all one dream this isn't my real
house and Brad is like no no this is a real house once you get the mortgage
payment she's like shut up this is a this is a dream during the day she'd be
walking around with Brad and she heard a voice off somewhere in the house can't
make out what they're saying or who they are but someone's in this house with
them and she tells Brad do you hear that and Brad's like what and how what are you
talking about I don't hear anything Monica goes you don't hear that that's
clearly people talking Brad's like no I don't know what you're talking about I
know you keep trying to say that everything's a dream that this is a
dream yeah it's a dream house that's why we bought it but this is reality and
Monica is trying to ignore Brad because she's starting to recognize the voices
in the distance she's hearing herself and Brad have a conversation somewhere in
this house she wakes up in the middle of the night and she's sitting in this house
and she goes what is going on I know this is a dream and I can't get out of it I
know this is a dream it has to be a dream but Brad always reminds her it's not a
dream then Monica begins to get a sensation a feeling a way out Monica
starts to get this obsession with finding the mirror she doesn't know why
it's a mirror she doesn't know where this mirror may be and if I'm mispronouncing
that you know that's that thing that shows your reflection a mirror she begins
to obsess somewhere in this house is a mirror and if I find the mirror and I
look in the mirror I can escape from this dream now again the whole time her
fiance is going what dream what are you talking about this is real and she
spends her days looking in all the little rooms in this house trying to find
the mirror she wakes up in the middle of the night this is a dream how can how am
I waking up in a dream the bedroom door opens up and her fiance son walks into
the room she can't see him really clearly in the dark but she recognizes his
voice and this little boy crawls into bed with them crawls underneath the
sheets and crawls into the bed with Brad and Monica and as he is moving his way
up underneath the sheets in between the both of them she realizes this isn't his
son she's looking at this form of moving under the sheets and she goes it's
sounded like him but I knew it wasn't him the figure under the sheets was too
long too big to be the boy
Monica wakes up in the middle of the night she needs to get out of the dream
striving her insane finally on one of these daily journeys when she's going
room to room to room to room to room she finally finds the mirror and she turns
and she looks into it and she sees herself as an old decrepit woman she
wakes up she's in the bed in the town home laying next to Brad and she goes
listen I had a really really hard time believing that this was this was real
like when I woke up in the bed I went to sleep in just a couple hours ago I had
been trapped in this unreal world that seemed so real for so long that when I
woke up in the town home I couldn't believe that it was real I immediately
woke up Brad I was like oh my god oh my god is this real is any of this stuff
really what are you talking about it's gonna sound crazy but I can't figure out
if this is real or not and Brad goes yeah I don't I mean he's just kind of
flustered by this whole thing right like how do you respond when someone's
yeah they wake you up they wake you up from a deep sleep and they're like am I
real am I real Brad's like listen listen listen I mean like you just woke me up
to have a really bad nightmare just let me catch my bearings before we have
whatever conversation you want to have she goes you had a nightmare I had a
nightmare was awful and Brad's like yeah dude I had like one of the worst dreams I
was I dreamt we were in this giant house it's huge house and possibly large house
and it was I don't I don't even know how to explain it the dream kept looping like
I kept like doing stuff during the day and then I would fall asleep at night and
the I mean that's what normal that's normally how the life works but what
happens I started to realize that this was fake like this dream house was not
real but you didn't believe me you kept saying no no Brad it's real it's real and
then I started looking for a mirror it's just weird and you kept trying to
convince me that I was way older than I actually am but you kept saying I was like
in my 50s and I was like no I'm not like I'm in my 30s and I could play a young
20 it was super weird you were constantly trying to convince me I was older and
then I was running around the house and I knew that I needed to find a mirror I
was looking all over for this mirror and then I would wake up in bed and the whole
loop would start over again and then I'm looking for the mirror and then the next
thing I know you're shaking me and you woke me up now what's interesting is she
wrote this post like the same day it happened she was posting this on the
high strangeness subreddit which is a great subreddit they have a lot of really
cool stuff high strangeness is a term a catch-all term for just the world of
her normal really really good subreddit she posted this on the high strangeness
subreddit and she posted it that day and she goes I don't know what to think she
goes I believe that I'm back in the real world and I do believe it was a weird
dream but how could my fiance have had the same dream like how does this work and
she goes he went back to sleep and she hasn't been able to fall asleep she
hasn't been able to fall asleep like which would make sense because he didn't
see the mirror right his dream didn't come to an end he didn't see the mirror
she saw the conclusion of it as this old decrepit person in his dream she was
just trying to convince him that he was old which 50 is not that old but when
you're in your 30s it might seem old so that could be why he that's could be why
he went back to sleep because he wasn't confronted with that horror of his own
mortality it's interesting she does say she goes listen I'll be honest like
in the past I've had issues with dreams that I kind of have a loop where I fall
asleep and wake up she goes that has happened to me in the past she goes I
used to have severe insomnia so I'd have things like sleep paralysis I would
have lucid dreaming but she goes even with those experiences one it's never
been like this before she goes even when I was suffering through severe insomnia
I've never had a dream quite like this ever never felt the same it didn't play
out the same and she goes how is it that he had the same dream like the exact
same dream and that's really why I wanted to cover it because that goes
against everything we know about dreams when I have a dream that's super creepy
like I famously I've told this dream a couple times on the show it's really
only two or three sentences I don't remember what the dream was about but
at the ending it had something to do with Jesus and the devil and all this
stuff because at the ending there was a knock on the door of my door and I
opened it and standing outside my door were these two big bodyguards and then
there was Satan standing there they're all wearing like little business suits
Satan and he had cut off Jesus's face he like tore the skin from Jesus's face
and was wearing it it was like stapled to his face and the devil did this little
dance like this little like da da da da da da want want type of dance and I
screamed so loud in the dream I woke up I was screaming in real life like it was
such a shocking image to see Jesus his face ripped off and stapled to the
devil's face and he was doing this little jig the jig isn't what scared me
the dances I'm scared I remember I screamed so loud I woke up that's a
weird dream right do I think it symbolized anything not necessarily
it's weird it's not paranormal it's just a dream but when you have two people
sharing the dream that is paranormal that's not possible in what we know
about dreams and that's what she's saying in the high strangeness subreddit she
ends it like that is there a term for this like the dream sharing has anyone
else experienced this before why were we in the same house in both of our dreams
why were we both looking for a mirror why did we both age in our dreams all
really good questions and you could do dream analysis on some of them the
aging the mirrors I'm sure there's reasoning behind that but again that's
just dreams how are they both in the same house how are they both even having
the same dream those are the important ones I think you can analyze dreams all
you want but how are they in the same house how do they share a dream and
that really led me to this and this is how I want to wrap it up we all know
that when we're sleeping we're at our most vulnerable that's why animals in
general don't sleep out in the open right but that's we're talking about
physically physically vulnerable when we talk about a subconscious right you're
incredibly vulnerable when you're sleeping because you unless you're a very
experienced lucid dreamer you just kind of go where your subconscious takes you
and we talk about being in haunted houses or we talk about having experiences
with ghosts but remember they're in our world there they have to follow certain
rules that we have I mean of course they can float through walls they can be
invisible and all this stuff but you very very rarely there's only a few
counts of ghosts flying we've covered stories of like there was a three-story
building the third story was haunted when they knocked down the third story they
put up a new building you can still hear the haunting like 20 feet above the
roof there are examples like that for the most part ghosts walk on boats they can
actually stand on the deck of a boat if you're in a two-story apartment in your
apartment's haunted the ghosts isn't constantly floating floating through
your floor hunting the downstairs neighbor like ghosts do have to walk on
floors does that make sense like ghosts have a set of physics that they follow
but in the dream world there there is zero physics the only reason why people
walk on the ground in your dreams is because people walk on the ground in
real life there is no fit there's no actual gravity in a dream digital clocks
and digital devices do not work in dreams this is something they've studied
if you have an analog clock that goes tick tick tick tick tick and if you look
at that clock in a dream and it says 302 and then you look away and then you
turn back and look at that clock again it'll say 302 and 33 seconds if there
is a digital clock there that says 302 and you look away in the dream and you
look back it'll say 2704 it's a weird quirk of dreaming digital devices do not
work in dreams why because they don't have to there's no physics see a clock
that has actual mechanisms in it we understand how a clock works and it's
little gears going click click click click you actually walk watching it
click a digital device does not have those things it's just the display of
something that it knows the time that we don't have any access to you take a
bit apart but it's weird quirk it's a that's one of the tricks people who are
interlucid dreaming use to tell whether or not they're dreaming because dreams are
so realistic a lot of times they're indistinguishable so there are no rules
in dreams so imagine not being in a haunted house imagine being trapped in a
haunted dream like if something wanted to get you that really would be the best
place to haunt you that's terrifying I mean we did an episode of you know
Freddy Krueger was based on a true story I know that sounds like the dumbest
thing I've ever said on this show I will put it in the show notes Nightmare in Elm
Street is in fact based on a series of articles written in the LA Times kids
were really dying kids were really dying because of this phenomenon so it's a
real phenomenon but two people having the same dream of being trapped in this
it really seems like this is a serious issue but what's causing it where is it
coming from and more importantly how do you stop it do you find a dream priest
like if you're in the dream itself and you think you're being haunted would you
then go to a church in the dream to have the demon be exercised or have the
ghosts be banished in the dream like all bets are off this is so fascinating to
me how do you stop it do you wake up and consult a religious leader do you try to
handle it in the dream I don't know like my advice to this person I don't really
have answers to any of their questions which makes it even more terrifying
because you have to sleep you have to sleep but if when you fall asleep you
live three years four years five years however long you're trapped in this loop
and the whole time there's something in that dream with you eating your fear
devouring your loose your emotional energy that powers it I mean you could
produce more psychic agony in a single night of a ever looping nightmare then
you couldn't an entire life because you can fit 15 20 an infinite a number of
lifetimes into a dream and they could become more terrifying than anything you
could possibly imagine because it doesn't have to follow any sort of
consistent guidelines it doesn't have to follow any rules it's just the sub
conscious making it up as it goes along a terrifying story a terrifying
phenomenon if this is true what are these people in for this is a new story
this popped up maybe like two or three months ago and now we'll never know the
ending to it right anyone can pop up and say oh I was that person I posted that
but we'll never know was this a continuous haunting was this something
they were able to get rid of or no it's a terrifying story and it used what they
wanted to invite them in during the day during reality they would watch shows
about new homes and designing new homes and decorating new homes and they would
go on Zillow and look for listings of new homes this is what this couple wanted
they wanted their forever home and that's exactly what the darkness gave
them a home they would be trapped in forever
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address you can also
hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Tiktok is at DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you
don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to it today have a great day guys
[Music]