A bizarre alien sighting in the middle of nowhere forces us to ask the question, "Wouldn't
it suck to be stuck on planet Earth?"
And then finally we travel to Brazil to take a look at a terrifying story of a family that's
under assault from a violent poltergeist.
What does this evil spirit want with the family?
It turns out the answer to that question is more horrifying than you could ever imagine.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenterder.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world doing all your stuff.
Everyone who I know always has fun, more fun than anyone else.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our long time Patreon supporters.
Everyone give it up for Garrett Rice.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Come on into Dead Rabbit Command.
He's walking on in.
You can already tell this is the funnest dude ever.
Garrett, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode?
You guys can't support the Patreon.
That's fine too.
It really is.
I don't just say that.
Just helps read the word about the show.
That is another way you can really help the show grow.
Garrett, let's go ahead and toss you a little engineers outfit, a little wooden whistle.
Hop on board the Carboner Caboose.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Chug, chug, chug us all the way out to Brazil.
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug,
going down the mighty railway.
You all know the one railway that leads from the Pacific Northwest straight to Brazil.
We're actually doing a Brazil Toof-er.
Two different stories in Brazil.
Let's start off in the country of Brazil.
Specifically, we're headed to Boa Vista do Tupam in Brazil.
So what this story is, is one night, August 16th, the night of August 16th in Boa Vista
do Tupam, a group of people saw a short man standing there, just kind of standing in a
field, right?
He's three feet tall, wearing a tight fitting grain cover all.
He's just standing out in the field with his arms raised up to the sky.
He's staring off into space, his arms held up high.
He was also wearing a transparent helmet, and he had this circle on the chest of his
coveralls that was glowing.
So there's this little three-foot guy just standing there, and his arms are outstretched
to the heavens.
He's looking up into the night sky, and his arms are just reaching out, a wide embrace,
staring into the darkness of the universe.
Now that's the whole story.
That's the whole...
He doesn't do anything.
He's not chasing around tentacles.
He doesn't put someone in a wheelbarrow and push them down a hill.
He's just standing there, staring off into the universe.
He's like, "Jason, it's going to clearly just be a tiny three-foot guy."
Maybe, but most three-feet people don't have a little glowing chest on them.
Don't have a little glowing disc.
Now one or two of them might, but if they did, would they be staring into space?
Huh?
You skeptic?
That's the whole story.
Yeah, he doesn't have tentacles.
He doesn't have laser beam or anything like that.
But I do find this story...
Intra...
I love the visual of it.
Like when I first read this story, I found it on ThinkAbout@Ducks.com, one of my favorite
websites.
And they got it from a group called GEPUC Brazil, which is a UFO investigation group.
The imagery struck me, right, of this little guy standing out there just reaching out into
the vastness of space.
And I thought...
That dude's boned.
I thought that little guy got left behind.
And he's looking out and he's like, "Oh, he's like, "Come back!
Come back!"
He knows there's no way they can see him, right?
Despite their advanced technology.
He's...
They're gone.
He's not walking on a UFO.
He's not surrounded by a bunch of other three-foot tall people with lit up chests.
They're gone.
Now, what's possible, I guess you could...
I guess this is an optimist story, right?
This is just pessimist.
You could think, "Well, maybe he knows that his space brothers are coming down."
And he's like, "Here I am, people.
Here I am."
And he has his arms reached out in a sense of joy.
But you could also be like, his arms are reached out and he's like, "Aw, man!"
Because he's now been left behind on planet Earth.
I'm like, you can decide.
I'm generally an optimist, but when I read this, I go, "He is just like...
defeated in a sense."
And we've talked about this on past episodes.
I'll see if I can find those episodes for the show notes.
We haven't talked about it a lot, but I imagine for being an alien, getting stuck on Earth
would be a punishment.
If it was accidental, it would be a sucky punishment, but I could see them honestly
doing this on purpose.
To people they just don't like.
Other aliens, other members of their crew they don't like.
Because Earth...
Listen, man, I'm Earth-first all the way, baby.
I love the planet Earth.
But on a galactic scale, we're totally backwater.
And we hate...
We hate other humans who are slightly different than ourselves.
So imagine if you were an alien stuck on this planet.
You know the best case scenario is you're in hiding for the rest of your life and you
can totally stay out of everyone's view.
Like you're eating chickens, stealing them out of farms, maybe fashioning some sort of
shelter super far away from civilization.
The next best scenario is you get spotted a couple of times and people think you're
encrypted, but for the most part people don't think you exist so they're not actively looking
for you.
Every other scenario is literally the worst case scenario.
People know that you're real and they're trying to hunt you and kill you.
They're trying to take you to some sort of government laboratory where they can interrogate
and then kill you.
They're trying to do autopsies on you and then keep you as long as they can.
What is it?
Vivisection when they're still alive, right?
Do a vivisection and then kill you.
Like it would be a bad place to be caught.
So your best case scenario is you're just living on the land from 7 billion people, right?
It would be horrific because there is no scenario where you make it more than a couple months.
If you don't completely stay out of the cities, if you're on some government's radar or even
some ranchers' radar, you're boned.
You're going to get a shotgun to the face at best.
At that point your best case scenario is you're still in someone's chicken and they blast
you with a shotgun and then photos of you end up on the Daily Star and people go fake.
That's totally fake.
Worst case scenario is you get captured by the government and they do the vivisection,
right?
They're keeping you alive as long as they can and torturing you and stuff like that.
It'd be horrific.
It'd be an absolutely horrific thing.
So imagine what must be going through this dude's head, right?
Like he's standing out there and he realizes he is...
Because you...
How...
I mean, unless he has some sort of communication device or something like that, he may not even
be able to rendezvous with his people.
They might have left him there on purpose.
They might have done this on purpose.
It wouldn't be the equivalent of being like, let's say you were a Spaniard, right?
You were in the age of exploration and you got lost somewhere in South America.
Just yourself.
A conquistador in South America.
That would be preferable to this dude.
Because at the end of the day, sure, you may take a couple arrows to the chest and die.
But there was a chance, though, that you could find a tribe that was starting to ally themselves
with the Spanish Empire against another larger tribe.
Tribe's not the right word if we're talking about the Aztecs or something like that.
You could possibly meet a hot girl.
Have a couple babies.
Hang out, be the chieftain's right-hand man.
You have all of this technology and stuff like that.
You could probably make a bit of a life for yourself.
And you would always...
Even if you were left behind by your squadron of conquistadors moving through, there's always
a chance you could...
It'd be slight, right?
You'd have to know where the next galleon was coming with all of these troops and stuff.
There's a bigger chance of you just staying along the coast always trying to look for
the giant ships.
This guy's stuck on Earth.
There's no...
There's beautiful women on Earth, right?
But he's not being a non-formal.
He's a laylian, dude.
All of his experiments have been taking women aboard ships and like injecting them with all
sort of baby-making DNA fluids.
I don't know if his equipment even works, right?
He can't go to the nightclub and be like, "Picking up chicks."
These three-feet tall wearing a green cover all with a little luminous chest.
I don't think it would work.
Like, you...
They would...
The bouncer wouldn't even let you in.
You're obviously an alien.
You're obviously a little alien, bro.
You got on this big old space helmet and I'm sure maybe he could go get a tux and then
just look like a normal, like, short man.
But it wouldn't work.
He would be coming into disadvantage, again, unless he had a space laser, and then the...
The second he pulled that out on the bouncer, the government's coming in, it would be terrible.
It wouldn't be the equivalent of being a explorer left behind in South America or you're leading
an expedition through the North Pole and you get lost.
Well, you're just dead then.
I mean, you can only eat so much penguin before the polar bears get you, but what a horrible
tragedy.
And I would assume because we can parallel what we've gone through to what alien life...
There's so many parallels, right?
We question what are...
What is the alien experience?
Is it interdimensional?
Is it extraterrestrial, i.e., coming from other planets?
There's so many parallels, though, between what we do and what they do that there's...
You can draw some conclusions, right?
And one of them would be, we've had expeditions on Earth go south.
Not literally not trying to find a way around the South America, but they've gone poorly.
So you can imagine, even with the most advanced technology, and this is a big part of UFOlogy,
there's crash, people get caught, people get left behind aliens set up bases here and then
they just get wiped out by humans, things like that.
So you would have those parallels and you would have those people who are left behind
on these intergalactic expeditions.
And it's not like, well, I'll see what I can do.
I'll try to make a good life here.
No, it's like I have to spend every waking moment staying away from people.
Otherwise, I'm going to end up dissected.
I'm going to have... I went from being in this suit, because even like the Spanish Empire,
right, they just like had armor.
They had armor and horses.
That was like their high technology.
You could went from armor and having a horse to your bonus South America.
It's still a pretty chill life down there, right?
You got tons of food, you got tons of water, you got this hot chieftain daughter that you're
kicking it with.
This alien guy went from a world of like hyperdimensional travel, holodex, laser beams that could disintegrate
your enemy and now he's fashioning a spear in the darkness as he hears people rummaging
through the woods looking for him.
Like you would go to instant, like it would be the worst.
It would be the worst downgrade in technology.
Aspanyard and South America, they're like, "Ah, you know, things are just a bit different
here."
It wouldn't have been that big of a drop.
You're talking about a race that has secured all diseases.
So now this little dude is getting bit by mosquitoes.
He's like, "What's a mosquito?"
I didn't even know these things existed.
It would be awful.
It would be awful to be left behind.
So I don't know what this guy's plans were.
He could have been here.
He could have been part of a scouting party to take over the planet.
We shouldn't feel sorry for him.
Maybe he was awaiting his space brother's return, right?
Maybe he was happy to see them coming back and it was just like a short away mission.
Or this little dude back in 1995 got left behind and he was holding his hands up in despair.
Knowing he would never again grace the night sky at the helm of a starship.
Instead, he would spend the rest of his life smashing two coconuts together, hoping to
get a single drink of milk.
And then he gets devoured by a wolf.
A unfitting end for any traveler, human or alien.
Garrett, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carpenter copter.
We're leaving one part of Brazil.
We're still going to be in Brazil this episode.
We're leaving behind this field in Brazil.
We're waving goodbye to that guy.
We're leaving behind this part of Brazil.
Take us all the way out to Jabbo Tocabal, Brazil.
The year is 1965 and we're in the town of Jabbo Tocabal, Brazil.
Jabbo Tocabal, probably closer.
I know the guy there's accurate but close enough.
1965, Jabbo Tocabal, Brazil.
We're at the Ferraria home.
The Ferraria family.
Now, we don't have a real idea of how this family was, you know, before these events.
It could have been a real peaceful family.
They could have been sitting around the dinner table, eating soup and eat cornbread and stuff
like that, talking about their days.
It could have been a chaotic family.
We don't know.
But however their life was before these events, a venture cut.
One day, things got out of hand.
A rock materializes out of nowhere and lands right on the floor of the house.
They're like, "What?
Where'd that come from?"
Everyone's kind of looking around.
That's weird.
That's a once in a lifetime event though, right?
A rock materializing out of nothing and hitting the ground.
Happens to every family, at least once.
What happens though is that this isn't a once in a lifetime event.
It almost becomes a once in an hour event.
These stones begin to materialize out of nowhere and begin flying around the house.
Smashing into walls, destroying property pictures and vases.
They have these rocks flying around.
Bricks as well.
You'd see a solid brick just up here out of nowhere fly across the living room and knock
over a lamp.
And this goes on for a couple days before finally they're like, "Okay, the novelty is totally
worn off."
It's completely destroying our lives and our property.
So the Ferrari family contacts a priest.
He comes out.
He comes out and full body armor.
He's all dodging rocks.
And he goes, "Tell you what, I'm going to perform an exorcism on the house.
I believe an evil spirit is taken over the home."
And he performs an exorcism and then he's like, "I'm out.
I'm out before I know whether or not this worked."
And it didn't work.
In fact, it made the phenomenon worse.
So now you had more rocks flying around, bigger rocks flying around.
One of them was over eight pounds.
Listen, if I came home one day and pebbles were flying around my house, that'd be pretty
cool, right?
Dirt, right?
My apartment's so dirty.
Anyways, it's so dirty.
Just like literal dirt.
Like all the clothes are picked up.
There's no food stuff laying around, but there's like dirt in my apartment somehow.
Anyways, there's a little dust devil floating around in my house.
I would just like close my eyes and be fine with it.
Boulders, eight pound rocks flying through my house.
Uh-uh, you can't do that.
And some of the...
So I read a couple articles on this and some of them specified that some of the rocks were
magnetic.
And I thought, "Okay, that doesn't make it any worse or better."
I mean, it's kind of a cool novelty, right?
ICP's like, "Oh, we don't believe this part.
These rocks, some of them are magnetic.
What does that have to do with anything they're appearing out of nowhere?
That's the bizarre part."
Not like they're like, "Did you know that this rock is Ignatius?"
I'm like, "It's going out of nowhere.
I don't care where it came from on the planet.
Some of these rocks are magnetic.
They're flying around the house."
I guess it would be funny though if you were carrying your car keys or like, "Time to go
to work."
And then a magnetic rock flew by and your keys stuck to them.
And then it dematerializes.
You're like, "Ah, my car keys!"
Okay, so I understand why they listed magnetic rocks.
But anyways, then almost as soon as it started, the phenomenon stops.
The rocks stop materializing and pelting the family and all of their property.
There is a brief moment of peace, right?
They think it's all over.
These rocks aren't flying around anymore.
Whatever is causing this then begins to pick up pieces of their furniture, whole couches,
and chairs and flinging them against the wall.
So now all of the stuff that survived the initial barrage of these rocks, they now are being
lifted up.
You're like sitting on the couch.
It's all flying around.
You're like, "Woohoo!"
You're like riding like a rodeo bull.
Now this goes on for a long time.
The entire phenomenon from the very first rock materializing to when it ends, we're talking
about five years.
This was going on.
What a chaotic place to live in.
Again, if they are already a chaotic family, it's just adding to it.
If they are like a peaceful family, like the Leave It To Beaver people, you can't even try
to have a normal household when all this stuff is going on.
This whole story takes place in the span of five years.
Here's one of the things though, but here's really the main thing.
What the family realized that most of this activity centered on their daughter, an 11-year-old
girl known as Maria Jose Ferreria.
This is super common in poltergeist lore.
Most of the time when we look at poltergeist activity, it is tied to a preteen to teenage
girl.
There is the theory that all of the emotional turmoil they're going through, all of their
hormones and everything like that, for whatever reason, this is something that parapsychology
has been trying to figure out for decades, a hundred years at this point.
Why is it that young girls?
Why is it that poltergeist activity centers around them?
They've never been in, a lot of times they do say it's like somehow their emotional
seesaw that they're constantly on and all of these hormones and stuff, but obviously
there's billions of teenage girls out there and they're not exhibiting this, so what else
could be the key?
What's the other factor?
Well, this story kind of answers that question and the answer is not a good one.
Maria has this poltergeist activity kind of centering around her.
She is being personally tormented by this force.
So the rocks are flying around and everybody, it's knocking over everyone's personal stuff,
the furniture doesn't matter who's sitting on it, it's going to go flying around the
room, but with Maria this invisible force would slap her right across the face.
She would also complain of being bitten and you would actually see bites and bruises on
her body.
She also was complaining that she could feel needles underneath her skin.
In fact, at one point, one incident, because you're thinking, "Oh, whatever, do one needle
in my skin, I can do that, I would go to school, I'd go to school all day long."
Big wussy.
Not only did she have these needles appearing in her skin, at one point, one incident, she
had 55 needles that had to be removed, 55 needles all in one ankle.
That sounds like self-harm, right?
When I was reading this, I go, "Nowadays, if you just took that stuff, there are people
who put needles in their skin."
There's that story of that one woman who kept, I know people are going to throw up when I
talk about this, I'll find it for the show in a second, but the woman who kept picking
at her scab on her leg or she had self-harm issues and she was picking at her leg and
she eventually pulled out an entire nerve ending and then they had to amputate her leg.
That's real.
I read it online, I didn't do that much digging on it, but I guess there's photos, I didn't
look at the photos, I can imagine and I'm about to eat spaghetti for dinners, I don't
want to imagine it too closely, but you can self-harm to the point that you lose body parts.
You think, "Well, maybe she's just outside of the rock."
Even that, a lot of poltergeist activities, the stories end when a certain person's removed
from the house and a parapsychologist goes, "Oh, that's because they were the center of
the poltergeist activity, they were the center of the turmoil," or they were the cause of
it, right?
Not in a paranormal thing, but they were throwing rocks around the house, they were flipping
over furniture and stuff like that.
That's a lot of times the case when we catch people doing voices, like hearing voices in
the wall and it turns out the girls that people were on the other side of the wall making
the noises on purpose to fool paranormal investigators.
We do have stories in like this, but remember this story's going over the course of five
years, this is going over the course of five years, so it'd be a long time to keep up a
fraud like that.
Plus, it doesn't seem like it's a particularly famous story, I found about it in a List Verse
article written by Alan Boyle.
List Verse is really good because they always got a gumma with ten stories and there's always
at least one I've never heard of and I've never heard of this one and List Verse is
really good about citing their sources too, so I can just click on a link and read the
book that they got it out of.
Look at news articles they cited.
Anyways, nowadays you would think self harm.
Maybe, right?
But there was also the time where she woke up with a cup over her mouth and she felt like
something was trying to smother her in her sleep, trying to stop her from breathing.
Fine, you can fake that too.
Well, one day she was at school and her clothes started to smolder like her clothing was catching
on fire.
I mean, you could fake that too or really cause it yourself, right?
If she's committing self harm, she could be causing that herself, but the more witnesses
you have, the harder it is to pull off these type of stunts and the fact that they're not
all centered in the house where she could be constantly fooling people.
Maybe she's putting the needles in her own foot but considering for the past couple months
rocks have been flying around the house, I think we can safely link it to that.
So this has been going on at this point when her clothes starting to burn at the school.
I'm sure she was excused from school that day.
They're like, "Oh, you can just go home.
We'll send your homework home with a friend."
This goes on for a year.
At this point we're one year into the phenomenon and Maria goes to see a medium.
She's like, "Listen, the exorcism didn't work.
Things are getting personally bad from me.
I'm almost caught on fire.
I got needles under my skin.
Something's trying to suffocate me in my sleeve.
I'm ready to look for an answer anywhere."
So she goes to a medium and this is terrifying, culmination of the story.
She goes to the medium.
She says I'm being plagued by all of this stuff.
Spirits attacking the house, throwing these rocks around.
This has been going on for a year, but I've personally been singled out.
I'm getting attacked.
"Something's trying to kill me.
It doesn't matter where I am.
It doesn't matter what time of day.
Something's trying to kill me."
And this medium says she knows why Maria is suffering so much.
There is a dark spirit after her.
After her specifically.
The family's getting tormented just out of spite, right?
The family is not the target for the spirit.
What happens to be in the way?
This spirit is specifically gunning to torture Maria.
And this spirit is going to torture you for the rest of your life.
Move away.
Start your own family.
Get a good job.
Doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter what choices you make in life.
This spirit will personally be following you and it is going to continue to physically,
emotionally, and spiritually cause you pain.
Maria is like, "Why?
What did I do, right?
I'm an 11 year old girl.
I'm living at home.
What could I have possibly have done to piss a spirit off this much?
To piss off anybody this much.
Living or dead.
What could I have done in my life?
What could I have done to deserve this?"
And the medium says, "You're right.
You didn't do anything to deserve it in this life.
But in a past life you were a witch and you killed a man.
You took a man's life and he became a vengeful spirit.
Now why he waited until you were reincarnated into the body of this young girl?
Who knows.
But he waited.
Through all that time he waited until you were reincarnated and then he made his move.
Now it's possible that the witch could have easily banished this vengeful spirit, right?
A young girl who has no knowledge of the dark arts, what's she going to do?
This spirit that's so filled with hatred and revenge is after you because in a past life
you killed him.
And there is no way to get him to stop.
He will not stop.
He will keep coming after you.
You obviously see the level of power that he's at right now.
That is what hate has given him.
That is what some sort of dark allegiance has empowered him with.
He will not rest.
Now like I said that happened a year in.
Like I said this story goes on for five years.
And the torment never ceases.
This spirit is constantly harassing Maria.
And to a lesser extent her family.
I mean throwing polders around is pretty harsh.
Flipping over furniture but remember most of this is targeting Maria until at the age
of sixteen Maria can't take it anymore.
Maria has been told for the rest of her life that this spirit will torment her.
So at age sixteen she poisoned herself.
After she died all the poltergeist activity completely stopped.
It's a fascinating story because it touches on so many things that we love about the paranormal.
And first off obviously a skeptical to go well yeah she was causing all the stuff and
she was committing the self harm herself.
So it would make sense that when she died it stopped.
That would be the skeptical answer.
But from a paranormal point of view we have a poltergeist right which is a it's a specific
type of ghost or ghostly or paranormal activity.
However you want to put it it's quite rare.
Most ghosts are just a sighting or even just a scent or the feeling of a presence.
That's the majority of ghost sightings.
Poltergeists are so rare they actually have their own category and most of the time they
are connected to a young woman.
Sometimes a young man but usually a young woman.
That's where objects are flying around the air.
Think about the amount of energy it would take to do that right.
It would be in anomaly even in the world of paranormal.
So we have a poltergeist then we have witchcraft we have magic being brought into the story
as well.
And then the idea of reincarnation.
So you have all of this interesting stuff kind of laid out in the story.
What I find fascinating and ultimately tragic and this is the way we're going to wrap this
story up is who's to say that her committing suicide stopped the activity.
I mean sure this is specifically what the story said.
But if this dark force could wait for her in between incarnations it would have stopped
this time.
But when this young girl when Maria is reincarnated once again will the force come back after
her?
I wouldn't make an effort to say I'm going to get her the very next time she incarnates.
I don't believe people reincarnate instantly.
That's my theory.
I'm still kind of iffy on reincarnation all over.
I do like the theory but I think it's not like you die at 10, 17 p.m. and the very next
baby born that's you.
I do believe that if reincarnation is real there would be time periods in between.
Do I have any proof of that?
I don't have any proof of that but if he could wait in between times let's say there's a
60 and it probably varies between person.
I believe that's where you would have an idea of penance or a purgatory.
You don't reincarnate right away.
There would be a time period where your soul is in some sort of purgatory or some sort
of learning state or trying to grow.
Whatever.
I don't know.
If it could wait between the witch and Maria who's to say that when Maria is reincarnated
at some point that the spirit's just not going to start the activity up again?
It is interesting that it waited until she was 11.
What is the symbolism of that?
Did it need her hormonal energy to feed off of?
Do the poltergeist needs it?
And really and that goes to the question we don't know why poltergeist tend to fixate
on that particular age group but maybe it does have something to do with who they were
in past lives.
Because we don't see the majority of young girls when they go through puberty rocks are
flying around the house.
If they did then they would just be a natural part of the world.
It's rare.
It's exceedingly rare.
But does it have something to do with the energy that they're emitting and this spirit
just waiting and waiting and waiting and waiting and once she is giving off this psychic energy
that it can feed off of that's when it attacks and if it attacked her back in Brazil who's
to say when she gets reincarnated in the middle of China as some farmer's daughter that it's
just not going to start it up again?
Where she's reincarnated as a baby in the Pacific Northwest?
Who's to say it's not going to start up then?
And this girl forever for all of eternity or at least as long as the spirit can retain
some sort of energy.
We do believe that spirits bound to earth start to lose energy at a certain point.
But again that's standard ghost lore.
It's a theory.
We don't even know if that's true.
That doesn't calculate poltergeist activity.
She may spend not just this lifetime of Maria these five years under this torment.
This may be something that just continues to happen to her until the heat death of the
universe or something like that.
She may after millions of reincarnations end up the daughter of a captain aboard the Starship
Frisco floating out somewhere near the Pleiades star system.
Little baby born in deep space and there's just some poltergeist floating around on a
battleship.
Floating around on this giant high tech vehicle.
Just waiting for this little girl to turn 11 and then he can start throwing hurling
boulders around this spaceship.
Like will she ever be free of the curse?
Is the question.
And really based on just this short story.
No.
I would say no.
It's tragic that she killed herself and I can understand her being so hopeless and this
is never going to end.
And what's interesting too is it could have been a standard poltergeist and the medium
was a fraud.
Mediums are a lot of times they just make stuff up and the poltergeist activity may have
been petered out as she moved past Peeferty which is how poltergeist activity normally
works.
Right.
So then you have that tragic ending as well.
The medium may have just been trying to earn a quick buck and made the story up and that
the girl is like 16 and she's like what's the point of going on this is going to happen
the rest of my life and she kills herself.
Or the medium could have been right.
And it was going to keep going on as long as she was alive and when she reincarnates
it's going to happen again.
And again next life and again the next life.
Terrifying story.
How much hate you would have to have in your heart to hunt someone down through multiple
lifetimes.
Right.
This witch did something so now you're tormenting, you're trying to suffocate an 11 year old
girl while she's sleeping.
You're shoving metal pins, metal needles into her skin.
Think about the hate you would have to have in your heart.
And if you can't imagine that level of hate and that level of absolute revenge, absolute
hatred.
Right.
It's just a level beyond what I think most people could even understand.
That's the difference between you dying and your soul either going to the afterlife or
you dying and becoming a ghost.
That's what would happen to most people.
But to become a poltergeist, to become a spirit of vengeance requires a level of pure insane
hatred that most humans will never understand.
But when this witch killed this man, he felt that level of just raw uncontrollable hate.
He despises her so much he will use all of that hatred, all of that loathing to power
himself, lifetime after lifetime after lifetime to torture her physically, mentally, spiritually.
Until the end of time.
A young girl paying the price for a crime she doesn't even remember committing.
But her victim does.
And he will never forget.
And he will never ever forgive.