Is the magical staff of Moses still out there somewhere?
And then we take a look at the bizarre conspiracy known as "Don't Get On The Ships"
Is simply having an EBT card or shopping at Walmart
Opening you up for alien abduction today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*Message from the video*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day
I hope you're having a great day too
The snow has brought the war to me
Yesterday another snowstorm hit Hood River
It actually killed the power, shut the power off
I prefer the term "killed the power"
That's what snow does, it kills things
So that sucked, I had no heater
I had to go to work and when I came home the electricity was back on
But the hot water is not, and I have to take a shower
So we'll figure that out, we'll figure that out
But that's my problem, not yours
But I appreciate your sympathy
We're gonna go ahead and move on to our first story though
Now our first story, quite a few episodes back
I don't remember exactly which one
I was talking about the staff of Moses
And I go "I wonder what ever happened to that thing?"
And YouTube user AlexF reached out to me and says
"Oh, it's actually kinda well known where it's at"
Let's take a quick look here
Now what the staff of Moses is, I had to do a bunch of research on this
It may actually be two staffs
It's kinda weird, not even rabbinical scholars can really agree on this
Cause I guess there were two staffs
I always thought it was Moses who threw his staff down and it turned into a snake
It was actually his brother Aaron who threw his staff down
So for those of you who aren't familiar with it
There's a story in the book of Exodus where the pharaoh is like
"Hey, your god sucks, I'm the king of magic
I got all these magicians over here, they have all sorts of powers"
And he commanded his magicians to sorcerers
To throw their staffs down and they turned into snakes
And then Aaron goes "Pfft, whatever dude"
Throws his staff down, turns into a larger snake, eats the other snakes
Turns back into a staff
And I was like "What?"
So magic is real
Magic actually exists and people are like "No, no, no, no, no, no"
Only that part was magic, everything else is not magic
So I was like "What?"
Like obviously those guys' staffs turned to snakes
So they knew magic of some sort
Anyways, so that was Aaron's rod now
Of course scholars think that it was just one staff that the brothers were passing back and forth
But this was the same, and we'll accept that for an answer
That there was one staff that for some reason he loans to his brother every once in a while to turn into a snake
And he's like "Hey Aaron, you got my staff and Aaron's like "Uh"
And there's like a giant snake slither around the house
He's like "Yeah, yeah, give me five minutes, I'll get it ready for you"
This is the same staff that Moses hit a rock with and a bunch of water shot out of it when the Israelites were thirsty
They were in the middle of nowhere, it's not like they were just simply parched
There was like a Gatorade stand, 200 yards down the road, but they're like "Nah, I'm thirsty now"
Like they were in the middle of the desert
And it was the same staff he hit the ground with and parted the Red Sea
One of the weird things was that once the staff blossomed almonds
That's pretty mild compared to bringing about the plagues of Egypt and turning into a snake
And it's interesting because then there's like this retcon to it
None of this stuff is in the Bible, but there's been this retcon to it that the staff was actually created on the sixth day of creation
It wasn't mentioned, but God created this staff when he was creating the world, that's how powerful it is
He went out of his way to form this staff and at one point the staff was stuck into the ground
And only someone worthy to lead the Israelites would be able to remove the staff from the ground
I.e. the sword and the stone
So it's interesting how all these legends just continue to spread
I'm sure at some point in world history something was stuck somewhere
And they go "Ah, whoever strong enough to do that can lead"
And there is a very common corollary to that
If you can open a tight jar in a house, you are officially the man of the house, even if you're a woman
If you're strong enough to open a jar of pickles and nobody else can, that puts you in charge
It is your everyday sword and the stone
Now of course some people say that the staff was just a normal staff
And other people say that the staff itself was magical
The people who say it was normal said it's just a normal staff, God gave it power
And other people say no, the staff itself has some sort of mystical quality to it
But what's interesting is we don't really know what happened to the staff after that
There's one of the, one of the, basically the story ends where when the first temple is destroyed in Israel
The staff was lost under the rubble of the temple
So we're, we're, that's way, way back in time
Other people say that it was locked in the Ark of the Covenant
And the Ark of the Covenant is another holy relic from the Bible
It's actually like a super weapon
You open it up and all your bad guys die, kind of like Raiders of the Lost Ark
Apparently that is rumored to be in Ethiopia right now
It got smuggled out of Israel all the way to Ethiopia where it's at
St. Mary of Zion Cathedral, off in this little island
But other people say, and this is kind of where it's registered at
Is there is a museum, and this is what Alex F. said
There's a museum in Turkey called Topokapi Palace
And they say that they have the staff of Moses
They say, you can visit, you can go look at it, they don't let you handle it
Because they're afraid it's going to slither away, but they do, you can look at the staff
Supposed to staff of Moses
They also have the sword of King David, that'd be pretty dope
I'd, I'd, I'd wield that, I'd be chasing security guards around with that
They have the Pot of Abraham, which I'm assuming is a metal pot and not some dank weed
And then they have a footprint of Muhammad and his tooth
That he lost in a battle, all at Topokapi Palace
Now here's the thing, the tooth and the footprint and the pot and the sword
Are probably there
But stuff like the Ark of the Covenant and the staff of Moses
If these things have any power whatsoever, because also the staff of Moses
I forgot to mention earlier, there was this massive battle going on
If Moses was holding the staff high, the Israelites would win the battle
And he says, oh, my arm's kind of cramping up and he'd start to lower it
The tides would turn, they'd start losing the battle
So eventually a bunch of his homies had to like help hold his arm up
The whole battle, so the Israelites would win
So it's had some combat power, combat based modifiers as well
If these artifacts are still around, they're not in Turkey or Ethiopia
I could almost guarantee that, there may be copies of them in those places
But any government worth their salt, if these things actually had any sort of power whatsoever
Even if it was just symbolic power, any government worth their salt would have those in their possession
And especially something that was created on the sixth day of creation
That can do everything from blossom almonds to turn the tide of battle
That's in a US warehouse somewhere
Wouldn't that be interesting if it turned out, here's my conspiracy theory that I just made up
Every US general in World War II carried a little sliver of the staff in his pocket
He put a splinter in his finger and they're like, okay, General MacArthur
Once you go do this military battle, just hold your hand up
Everyone will think you're just waving at the troops, but you're holding up a splinter of the staff of Moses in your finger
And then they'll die of snake, internal snake bites, they're like, oh, I should have thought about that other part of the story
If these objects are real, I think the US government has them locked away somewhere
And there's facsimiles in these other locations
And if they are super weapons, as has been purported, we definitely have them
And they're probably not locked away somewhere, they've probably been used
There's a little conspiracy theory for you, that would be interesting to find battles that morack
I've always thought, like, there's always these weird coincidences when you read about old-timey battles
And you're like, hmm, if it hadn't been for this factor or because it was raining that day or something like that
The US won that battle, maybe they're using some divine super weapon or some divine tool
Who knows, or maybe it's just fate and luck and good strategic planning
So thanks, Alex, for reaching out and letting me know where that artifact supposedly is
But I doubt it's there
Okay, so let's go ahead and move on to our next story
Now our next story is a fascinating look at a website that gives us a very clear command
A very, very clear command
Do not get on the ships
Now, this website is written by a couple, this man and this woman
And they talk about, they've been researching this for years and years and years and years
So I want you to imagine two people in a cluttered apartment, not far from mine, but minus cluttered with happy things
Like movies and clothes and toys that I've got collected over the years, not like a big toy collector
But you know, just like little Nicknack, I think I have a Ninja Turtle from each line, just one
You know, it's a happy clutter
This is a coming, this website's coming from a clutter of cigarette butts
And discarded mountain dew cans everywhere, detritus surrounding the place
When you come to visit these people's houses, this is actually probably bordering on slanders
So I'll stop talking about how trashy their apartment is
But madness, an apartment surrounded in madness
Do not get on the UFOs
All of their information comes from three different sources
One, something they call a biofeedback machine or biofeedback meter
I'm assuming it's something that tests the electromagnetic, electromagneticity or whatever
Some made up thing in the human body, probably close to an oddity machine that the Scientologists use
So they get it from that, they do these readings on people and they're like, "Oh, that's interesting
Your pulse is in Morse code for do not get on the ships"
So they use the biofeedback meter, they use people's dreams, the number one authority of all things true in the world
What people dream, that's a huge source of information for them
But both of those, the made up technology and the sparks in our brain while we're unconscious
Are far more credible than the other source of information they use
They constantly refer to the movie, Jupiter Ascending
The movie that nobody saw but them, I'm sure half the ticket sales for that movie came from these people watching them over and over again
They're still petitioning for the director's cut of Jupiter Ascending
Jupiter's ascending, I didn't see it, Star Channing Tatum and Mila Kunis
It turns out that Earth is a factory farm and aliens have created factory farms all over the galaxy
And once the population is ripe, they come there and they throw everyone in a meat grinder and eat them or drink them
Or they live longer because they're drinking our juices or something
Here's the little thing, this is the thing, I get it, science fiction is a view into our future or the horrible implications of technology on mad or both
But these people could have easily walked into Transformers 5 and created a conspiracy theory that yes, Merlin did discover Transformers on Earth
Because that's really how ridiculous this is and they use the argument of predictive programming
So there's this stupid rule out there, stupid thing that somebody came up with that before evil people can do something, they have to tell us they're going to do it
But anyways, they say Jupiter Ascending is part of that, now I will give the Illuminati credit
If you're going to hide messages for what is in store for the future, you should put it in a movie you know no one's going to watch, i.e. Jupiter Ascending
You should put it in Jupiter Ascending, you should have put it in Han Solo, you put a lot of predictive programming in that because nobody saw that movie either
So anyways, they went to see this movie, Jupiter Ascending, they finally crawled out of the garbage of their apartment
They swam through it, all the credible newspapers, they swam through all that, get out to the movie theater and watch Jupiter Ascending and they're like "Oh my God, this is what is going to happen to us"
Those are the three sources, they also use V, the television show V which I absolutely love, but they use that as well, but most of the stuff they keep referring back to, they're like just like in Jupiter Ascending
This part of our story is just like the movie Jupiter Ascending, and again, if they said the future is going to be a bunch of racetracks, i.e. speed racer, people would know that they are just full of nonsense
But nobody saw Jupiter Ascending so they can't really debate whether or not these guys are accurate
So this is their idea, there are good aliens and there are bad aliens, that's pretty normal in UFO lore
The bad aliens are going to show up in their spaceships and they're going to say "Do you want to come on our ship?"
And if you say yes, they eat you
The good aliens will not ask you, and this is what they say the difference is
The evil aliens, part of their law, part of their rules, again they have rules for some reason, they have to ask you, they have to trick you into coming onto their ship
And then at that time, you're basically filled with fear, you finally see the horrible things that are going to happen to you
The torture, they let you know they're going to eat you, they're going to eat you slowly
That makes you produce this chemical called Adrenochrome in your blood, which apparently makes your blood not only incredibly tasty
But also helps the aliens live longer, they got that from Jupiter Ascending, the live longer part, they stay young longer
The good aliens won't do that, they won't ask you, they won't trick you, they'll simply take you
This is a quote they keep using, yes there are good extraterrestrials out there, but if they decide to rescue you
They do not need your permission to do so, which on earth we call kidnapping, but good extraterrestrials will transport you aboard as quickly as a ship's crew would rescue a drowning man
What's bizarre is that last sentence about the drowning man, they use over and over and over and over in this article, it's kind of weird
It's almost like some sort of, to me I was like this article sounds like a conspiracy, that sounds like a trigger word
Because they kept using that same phrase over and over again, they will rescue you like a ship will rescue a drowning man
In the sense that if you're drowning, a ship doesn't come up alongside you and go "Do you want help? Do you want us to help you?"
They just rescue you, they throw you out a life preserver, they throw you out a life saver, climb on it
They don't ask and get your permission, they just help you
So that's how they differentiate the two, the evil aliens will show up and say "Would you like to come on our ship?"
And you're like "Yeah, I've always wanted to meet an alien"
You get on the little walkway, door shuts behind you, it's darker than you thought it would be
The lights are dim, you start to see aliens crawl out of the corner
Oh no!
So that's how they differentiate the two, interesting, interesting idea
They tell you that if aliens show up, the best place to be is your house
You should have four weeks of food, which isn't a bad idea anyways, but you should have four weeks of food, four weeks of water
Which would be very heavy, but that's their idea
And the reason why, the reason why you should stay in your house when the aliens show up is very very simple
Don't know why I didn't think of this during a zombie invasion or anything, the aliens show up
A man's home is his castle, bam, that's all you need to know
Trump's all technology, Trump's transported technology, laser beams, conventional firearms
A man's home is his castle, that's a universal law
They can't get you in your house, apparently
They also recommend you to put signs up on your front lawn that say "Do not get on the ships"
To help spread the message for other people to not get on the ships
Now those signs will probably not be really popular in a navy town
But, I don't think it'd be popular in any town, and if you have a homeowners association, you're gonna be in a lot of trouble
Because if you were walking by a house in your neighborhood, and you saw a sign that said "Do not get on the ships"
You're gonna think the people who live there are crazy
And as you, every time you pass their house, you hear Jupiter ascending playing at top volume
Now again, the people who believe in this stuff don't really care if people think they're crazy, it's part and parcel of their belief
They think that being thought of being crazy is persecution
So they're totally fine with it
But again, I don't recommend that, I guess I should have said this in the beginning, but again, it probably don't have to say it
Don't do any of this
Don't put a sign out on your front lawn saying "Do not get on the ships"
They also recommend, and they took a while for them to clarify this
Early on in the article, they said "Wrap your cell phone in metal"
And I'm thinking, who wrote this, Superman?
Like who has the ability to wrap metal?
Tin? Maybe, with pliers?
But am I supposed to use iron? Am I supposed to use steel?
About, I don't know, 20 minutes reading in the article, they specify aluminum foil
Which I guess is a metal
But you might want to have said that earlier before people went out to Home Depot and got a giant metal crunching machine
To wrap their cell phone in, it would actually be easier than wrapping your cell phone in metal to just throw your cell phone away
But they say wrap your cell phone in aluminum foil and then about, I don't know, 5-10 minutes after reading that, they started calling it metal again
So guys, come on, you gotta be specific, our lives are at stake
They say that, this was probably my favorite part, this was a revelation to me
I don't know if you knew this, but this was a heading, this was like a specific part of their article
And trust me dude, it took me like an hour to read this whole thing, it's massive, but
This was a specific part of their article
Headlined, aliens use carpet and wooden desks just like judges do
So forget all the idea of the stainless steel spaceship
Forget the idea of hover chairs or giant vials of water that they float around in
Nope, they use carpet and wooden desks just like you can go and buy at any retail store, they use them
This comes from a whistleblower named Bill Shonoblin
Comes from this guy, credible name
In the 1970s, he was all of this at the same time
They were very specific, Bill was all of these things at the same time
He was a high ranking freemason, okay
A witch, a satanic priest, that's kind of doubling up, that's like when you split your classes on D&D and you want to go as like a rogue and a bard
You're never great at any one of them, but you're kind of good at both of them
I don't know why he would be both a satanic priest and a witch, you gotta specify your class if you really want to rank up in your levels and get to the good stuff
High ranking freemason, a witch, a satanic priest, and a Catholic priest all at the same time
I have three jobs and do the podcast and I'm busy and I don't deal with aliens or witchcraft, so I can't imagine how busy this guy was
But all at the same time he was all four of those
And so Bill ends up getting abducted by four aliens
Four aliens
He's abducted by a gra-- this was in the 1970s, by the way
So he was abducted and when he goes to their spaceship, he sees four aliens in a carpeted room behind a desk
Now, I'm gonna assume that he was quote unquote "abducted" on Halloween and he was just taken to the freemason lodge
But apparently he was abducted into a spaceship that has carpeting, I'm assuming shag, it was the 70s, and a wooden desk
And here who was sitting behind the desk, a gray alien
A Nordic, which are the tall, blonde hair, blue-eyed, white aliens, which these guys say are evil
Generally they're considered good aliens that fight the grays, but in this world they're evil
A gray, a Nordic, a thing with a squid face, which is the first thing I thought of was Plocoon from Attack of the Clones
The Jedi with the squid face, or you could really say any species of-- not the Mon Calamari, who were the other ones
They were actually squid-faced ones, but anyway, so he's saying, "This guy might be George Lucas," but--
And we're definitely gonna get to that, 'cause he sees a gray, a Nordic, a squid face thing
And then, this--here's a quote, "One of the aliens in the center was all in black, tall and masked
He looked vaguely like Darth Vader, oddly enough." Not really, exactly. This happened before Star Wars came out
So, either Darth Vader is a real alien--according to this, that there is a real alien out there who looks like Darth Vader
And we're supposed to wrap our cell phones in metal because of this, because of this guy's testimony
But anyway, so these alien--Darth Vader, Plocoon, a gray and a Nordic abduct him
He's like, "Oh, you got a nice carpeting," and they're like, "Silence!"
This is the reason why they abducted him, he's not a good enough mason. They said, "You need to go down and be a better mason."
They put him back on Earth. That was the end of that story. It had nothing to do with getting abducted on ships
It had nothing to do with the cell phones being wrapped in metal, nothing. They just threw that in there
I don't--and I guess they threw it in there as proof? That's--that's--come on, that's ridiculous
Carpet and desks and Darth Vader all telling someone to be a better mason and then dropping them off, that's ridiculous
That is a total waste of technology. If their bosses ever found out they used that beam-up technology for something that stupid
I guarantee they're getting fired. Then they have the heading, "Yeah, but you didn't know this."
We also find out that aliens act like lawyers, not robots. They don't act like they're aliens. They don't act like Darth Vader
So apparently at Roswell--I love this quote. Before they tell this story, this is the quote the website says
"The other story is harder to verify, but we find no reason to not believe it."
At Roswell, when the ship crashed--okay--there's some aliens who showed up to be like, "Hey man, sorry, our ship crashed, but we need our stuff back."
One of the aliens who walked in, Gray Alien, had a suitcase handcuffed to his wrist. A briefcase. A briefcase that a normal human would carry around
Now you know how thin a Gray's wrist are? It would have to be baby handcuffs. It would have to be tiny little baby handcuffs
It would be the size of a bagelbite handcuff. After that nugget that the alien walks in with a briefcase handcuffed to his wrist
Quote, "That is, he was acting as a regular lawyer. When is the last--when's the first time you've seen a lawyer with a briefcase handcuffed to him?"
Outside of Jupiter ascending, outside of a movie where a guy's carrying around nuclear codes, I've never seen a lawyer, even in television, having a briefcase handcuffed to him
But apparently that's how regular lawyers work in this world. Did you know, did you know, that you are being programmed to trust aliens?
Here's some examples of friendly aliens on television. Tell me which ones don't belong here. Teletubbies? No explanation given. There's just a picture of teletubbies. That's it.
My little ponies, we do have explanations for the next two. My little ponies. Did you know they're aliens? Quote, "These almond-shaped creatures do not look anything like ponies, but they make some very colorful aliens."
I think they left a key word out there. Now I'm not sitting here, I just don't want to crap all over these guys because they can't copy edit their manifesto that's supposedly supposed to save your life and your soul from eternal torment, but
These almond-eyed shaped creatures, they don't look anything like almonds. They don't look--they look more like ponies than they look like almonds, but anyways, they're aliens. They're getting people to believe in aliens.
Dora the Explorer is an alien. Did you know that? Dora. Little Dora. Because her giant eyes and almost non-existent nose and, quote, "a monkey friend who was about the right size for a grey alien."
Great aliens are like three or four feet tall. Dora is three or four feet tall. I don't get--we're bordering on Han's territory because they're just looking at pictures of stuff. And what's weird is they then choose--this is the last example of aliens that are friendly to us--Barnie the Reptilian.
No, there's just a picture of them and it says "Barnie the Reptilian." No, telling me why--and no one watches that show anymore either. It's so funny, nobody watches that show. But let's get into the real stuff.
Now they believe that simply by ha--so the aliens have to ask you to board on their ship. You have all this predictive programming on. Jupiter-Seni was the number one film, 12 months in a row, everyone in America, everyone in the world saw it at least five times.
Everyone watches My Little Pony's Friendship is Magic. Everyone's a huge Dora the Explorer fan. We can't get away. We love this stuff so much. All of our lawyers have handcuffs attached to their briefcases. It is a truly wonderful world that the alien overlords have created for us.
So they do have to ask for our permission to come on the ship. Now, they do. There's a caveat to that. If you have an EBT card, which is a food card, which is basically food stamps in America. If you have an EBT card, you've actually signed away your rights to say "No, I don't want to get on the ship."
If you have an EBT card, it's too late. You get food stamps from the government, actually in the fine print, you are now selling your soul to the aliens. Maybe. Because even these guys say, "We don't know if that's true." Like, it might be true. Then why are you even saying it?
Why are you even throwing it out there saying, "Ah, it might be in the fine print." I don't know. A lot of stuff might be in a lot of fine print.
I may go to get my car serviced at Jiffy Lube and I don't look at the little alien claws at the bottom saying, "By authorizing us to do these repairs, you will get on the ship." So I'm like, "What's this about?" And they're like, "Ah, just sign it." "You have EBT?" "Yeah, well, you already signed it. It's fine."
I mean, like, you should know. This is life or death, guys. You should know whether or not me having food stamps will make me get abducted by aliens.
But now we get into the dreams. And this is an interesting place to end this at, because I gotta humdinger for you. If you guys are just like, "Hey, he's reading off a crazy website. This is kind of wacky."
This story gets weird in the end. It's really weird.
There's dreams of people going to Wal- A lot of dreams about Walmart, Audelina. Dreams about people going to Walmart and not coming out.
These are dreams that people have submitted to them. Dreams of people going into Walmart and never coming out. Long lines outside of Walmart. There's troops surrounding it.
You're in, like, a huge queue. Not like the letter "Q" but a line. And you go in to get your rations for the day and you don't come out.
Another person had a dream that people would go into Walmart. This guy was dreaming. He was standing outside of Walmart.
And every time someone went into Walmart, two guys as big as sumo wrestlers grabbed him and carried him away. I think this is just your average day at Walmart, honestly.
But apparently that means something. But they have a lot of dreams about military control of these places. Of these Walmarts. They're big stations, basically.
Dreams of a fake rapture, which is the Christian theory that before the end times comes, the believers, the followers of Christ, are going to be raptured. They're going to be lifted up into the sky and escape all the hell that's going to happen to everybody else.
So there's been a lot of dreams of these ailing ships coming down and saying, "We are here on behalf of God. We're going to take you off of the planet before the Tribulation.
And you'll be safe and people getting on the ships and then being eaten." That's been a dream that's been shared with these people.
So what have we learned? Don't watch Jupiter sending because it's going to drive you insane or just waste two hours of your life.
Wrap your cell phone in metal, preferably steel or iron, but if you can't get that aluminum foil works as well.
Put a sign out on your front yard saying, "Do not get on the ships." Most importantly, do not get on the ships at all. Don't take a tour of them. Don't be tricked into them.
Don't follow apples like you're really hungry one day and you see a bunch of apples leading out your front door all the way into a waiting UFO. Don't do that either.
Do not get on the ships and after a while the ships will leave because again they have to trick you and then you'll be left on a planet that has all the idiots. They're all gone because they got fooled by the ships.
So Jason, you found a crazy website. A lot of craziness in the world and you found one. So why did you profile this one other than you just wanted to take the piss out of these guys and talk about how dirty their apartment was?
Probably about five years ago now. I remember one day I was in Hood River. My mom came up to live with me for a while and I was sitting in the living room and my mom comes out of her bedroom and she goes,
"I had the weirdest, creepiest dream last night." So I'm gonna preface this by saying my mom doesn't believe in any conspiracy stuff. She doesn't believe in any paranormal stuff. No aliens, no Bigfoot, nothing. She's super, super skeptical.
But she's a devout Christian and not like a Bible thumping Christian. She understands you gotta question things and stuff like that. She's a devout Christian. She's constantly reading books. She listens to Christian radio and stuff like that and Christian speakers and stuff like that.
But she doesn't believe in anything paranormal, conspiracy, none of that stuff. She doesn't even do true crime. She doesn't listen to podcasts at all.
She comes down the stairs. I'm sitting in the living room and she goes, "I had the scariest, creepiest dream last night." It was super weird. And I go, "What was it about?" And she goes, "I wake up one morning and the moon has a symbol on it."
Like you could see the symbol carved into the moon. And I go, "Do you remember what it looked like?" She goes, "I do." She goes, "I don't think I could draw it." But it was just an odd symbol on the moon.
And then these alien ships approached Earth and the aliens were very friendly. Very friendly aliens. And they told us that the rapture was coming and that they were here to save us before the tribulation started.
So we packed up all of our things. We got on the ship. She goes, "I remember when we walked onto the ship, around the ship, like it was a traditional UFO, so it was a circle.
And inside the ship were all of these steel beds placed against the wall, so they were upright. So you would lean back against them and they would strap you down for the flight."
They didn't have seats. They just had these metal slabs all along. And she goes, "I started to get nervous, but the aliens were... And they were typical gray aliens."
She described it as that. I don't think she knew the term gray aliens, but I think she was talking about the aliens from the X-Files. She's like, "They were from the X-Files type aliens."
She goes, "They were very polite and were getting on the ship, and I remember getting on the ship and getting really nervous, and everyone else was super happy to be there."
And she goes, "I saw a couple of the metal slabs that people were leaning against and getting strapped onto for the flight. Some of them were covered in plastic, like kind of covered in like a dark, thick plastic so you couldn't see what was under them."
And she goes, "And I noticed one or two of them had some blood on them. And I started to get really nervous and I wanted to get off the ship."
And the aliens were like, "No, no, no, everything's fine. Just go ahead and stand against this wall. You'll be totally fine. Don't worry about it."
And they strapped her in. And she goes, "Then I knew that this wasn't the Rapture. Then I knew that I was tricked to get on this ship."
Don't get on the ships.
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio at gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter.
DeadRabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend, guys.
[Music]