Are children really the future of mankind or telepathic freaks ready to expose our secrets?
And then we attend a real-life exorcism to take a look at a story of a Monsignor
who had been expelling demons left and right a professional exorcist who's traveled around the world
But his biggest challenge ever
Sending a human soul back to hell that soul
Belong to Judas today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day - we got a ton of stuff to cover
So we're gonna get started right away sliding into Dead Rabbit Command on a ocean of milk
It's totally flooding. I hope you're not lactose intolerant. You may die this episode
It's milk umochi. Milk umochi. I'm doing I'm hoping that's how you pronounce your name. You are sentient milk
Thank you so much for supporting the show
Milky moochie says we'll give you robot hands or something so you can pilot a vehicle milk
Umochi you're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon or you're not liquid based lifeform
That's fine, too. Just help spread the word about the show really really helps out a lot milk umochi
We're gonna give you some gloves and some boots
Now you're just a silly puddle of milk with there's boots and gloves there and we're gonna shovel you in
We're gonna put you in buckets and just put the bucket in the Dead Rabbit Robo
Everyone grab an ore we're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We are headed out - I didn't think this one out
There's no water where we're going to we circle around America and we end up in a small town in suburban America
We're gonna crash this party with so over like who wants free milk look at mochi's like no no don't drink me don't drink
Who wants free milk?
There's this dude named Mike. It's his birthday party and he's sitting there and he's an adult
He's like in his 20s and he's like has a little birthday
Still likes birthday hats and he has the pinata and balloons and everything he's sitting there and his five-year-old niece
Natalie walks up and goes hi uncle Mike. I love you so much. I drew a picture of you
And he's like the cheapskate. That's the only gift you can get come on
I know you get allowance good she shows him the picture and the pictures in the show notes
But I'll describe it to you because some of you are driving you guys are trying to look it up
Cars are sliding everywhere. You hit a giant puddle of milk. It's a picture of a birthday cake. It's all poorly drawn
I think he's five she's five so don't expect to see some Thomas can Kate stuff
It's a birthday cake and then there's a man. These are all stick figures. There's a stick figure sitting in a chair
There's another stick figure on what appears to be their knees in
front of the man in the chair and
Then there's a third stick figure who is identified as a woman has a long hair like how a little girl would draw a woman
Stick figure and she has her hands to her face
She's sad Mike's looking at this picture and he's like what one one tarnation is this I love you uncle Mike
You save that forever
She goes back
Who's the drink more milk? So why are we talking about this this child's drawing?
There was a post online recently where it was like misunderstood children's drawings like isn't it so funny?
It's supposed to be this thing, but it's really this other thing. You had all these responses. Oh that one's fake
That one's real da da da da da da da da, but in the middle of all that stuff is a deleted post. It's actually been removed from the internet
Now I have also posted his post on I put it in the show notes, but I removed his name
I actually took a screenshot of it. I was so interested by the story when I saw it
I took a screenshot
But I posted so you could actually see what he wrote I removed any identifying information from the post itself because obviously he doesn't
Want this part to remain out there connected to him, but he says I got this picture from my five-year-old niece
The weirdest thing is and again this was all about like children's drawings like funny children's runs that could be misinterpreted
He goes I asked her what's going on in this picture and she goes
I don't know she goes that's you in the chair
But I don't know who that person is by you and he points to the woman who's walking away goes
Who's that and she goes that's your girlfriend?
She's sad
And he said he goes what is really terrifying?
Was at the time not all this birthday party was going on
But he goes in this period of time. I was cheating on my girlfriend
when my girlfriend left he goes I had more than one woman swing by my place and
Give me a blowjob. We weren't sleeping together
Eaton's not cheating. This was his motto. He goes. There's no way she would have known that
There's no way at all. She would have known that
But here is a drawing of what was going on now
According to this this is gone now. We have the screenshot, but there's no follow-up to this that I could find
So it's not like his girlfriend caught him
But one of the things I've never cheated on anyone in a relationship
But one of the things about when you do cheat on someone in the relationship, they know
They know so his girlfriend probably was sad because she knew something was off and she couldn't figure it out. I find that super
Fascinating and so funny. I saw that it was so fascinating to me. I took a screen. I read
nonsense all the time and I saw that and it stuck with me and I read that during the vacation I
Took a screenshot, which I'm glad I did. I you know stuff gets deleted all the time
And it's a one-off creepy story, right? This guy is engaging in a horrible act
He's cheating on his significant other and this child somehow knows what's going on
She she says I don't know what the person's doing down between like the little girl wasn't drawing a sex act
But she was somehow seeing this she didn't know what it was though and
What's so funny about this is I have a similar story that I have had in my maybe folder for over a year
I researched this 400 episodes ago, and I thought it was too creepy
Even for a radio. I thought it was too weird and too disturbing even for dead rabbit radio, but it is so related to this
Milk-o-mucci get behind the wheel of that Jason Jalopy. We're driving a couple houses down
It's the same neighborhood is a really weird neighborhood or once again in a suburban neighborhood in America
I presume it could be in the Balkan states where I know but we're walking into this house. It's really nice
Really nice house. There's a little party going on people drink and wine watching the big game
And as you kind of move through the house you start to see like the crowd gets a little younger
So now it's like teenagers and stuff like that. Hey walla you want to go play ping-pong?
Where's the beaver at apparently this house is in the 1950s this story actually takes place in the early 2000s
But you know how parties kind of break out you have the adults hang out the little kids are normally hanging out with the adults
Then you have the middle kids are kind of making their own group and then the teenager
It's a pretty big party and in this crowd of people
There's a young man named
What I'm gonna make up a name if this is his actual name if you're listening to this and this happened to you and your name
Having to be Jones. I apologize, but we're gonna meet this young man named Jones
And before this party even starts I have to go back in time a little bit before this party even starts
Jones is sitting at home alone. It's early 2000s. He's just hanging out listening to some 41 and he comes up with an idea
It's like some 41
Will make me think of this next thing some 41 makes him think hmm. I wonder what it would be like to
Taste my own ejaculate
He used those words I don't think he was dr. Rangstein, but he thinks I wonder what happened if I tasted this stuff
Wonder what happens. He's not gonna turn into a month. He's not gonna turn into Frankenstein
It's not that he was just wondering he was curious about tasting it
But he's this guy is Jones
Thing Jones is a go-getter Jones does he's not just gonna like put it in a cup
like some lame-o Jones actually comes up with the idea to
Somehow do this apparently apparently he belongs to Cirque du Soleil
He's going to not only taste his own ejaculate. He's going to ejaculate into his own mouth
So he's gonna like
He gets a hot wheels track and makes a loop-de-loop or something like that
I assume he's standing on his arms standing on his hands at this point
Anyways, he comes up with this idea to ejaculate in his own mouth and he does and then he instantly regrets it
Right. He which which is the post-coital regret
He's like that was
One I didn't turn into the wolf man to my arms are super uncomfortable three
This this is grow this is just gross in my mouth the next day
So that all happened the day before the party next day. It's the party. Hey now you're an all-star
He's so glad some 41 is not playing on the radio. He could never listen to that band again
So I can on the parties doing finger guns to people. Oh, Joan. You're such a crack up
Do you ever call someone he's like a cut up oh that guy's such a load
That's mid from now on when someone's really funny be like dude. You're such a load
So that joke makes sense. Anyways, he's walking around he goes and he's on the trampoline in the backyard
There's this big trampoline in the backyard everyone's bouncing up and down on it and
There's all these kids all these young people teenagers everything are jumping on this giant trampoline
one of the people on the trampoline is this boy named opi and
He was mute. He was deaf and he was mentally challenged, but that's okay. It's a trampoline, right?
You don't need any of that stuff to enjoy bouncing up and bouncing up and down and almost breaking your limbs every three seconds
So Jones is bouncing on the trampoline opi's bouncing on the trampoline a bunch of people are bouncing on the trampoline
But over time
Families are like Betty time to go home. Oh, oh your dad's such a load. Oh those jokes. He was telling
Time over time
People are leaving the party till eventually only Jones and opi are bouncing up and down
On this trampoline the sun barely peeking over the mountain range a crow a crow is sitting watching the two young men
still on the trampoline
Jones Jones is not aware of the sinister events him and opi are bouncing on trampoline by themselves and then opi
Kind of like does a little belly flop just are doing tricks
Super showing off he kind of jumps down and then he's sitting there and opi stares at Jones and starts
laughing
But opi's laughing and Jones is kind of still bouncing on the trampoline being like why is he why is he laughing?
opi's like younger than him opi's younger teenager and
Jones is still bouncing up and down on the trampoline and opi is kind of rocking back and forth laughing and
Is pointing at Jones laughing and Jones kind of starts bouncing slower and slower and goes. Why are you laughing at me?
He said that opi pointed at his crotch and started pretending to masturbate and then pointing out his mouth
While the whole time with his other hand pointing at me and he's laughing
Jones has lost all interest in the trampoline at this point no bouncing allowed. He's just staring at opi
And he thought there was no way
There is no way this kid
Could have known what I did
Was just yesterday. I totally regret doing I instantly regretted doing it and here it is just me and opi on this trampoline and he
knows my shame
Jones just kind of shook his head, but he knew that the kid was right
Jones
Takes one final jump off the trampoline and heads back inside the house
It's creepy. It's so funny because I didn't tell that story one because I don't want to embarrass the guy even though he posted it online
I assumed at some point he would erase it. It has been erased
-
It's more sexually suggestive than a lot of stuff I cover on the show three. It's downright disturbing
I find this really fascinating and find the story really fascinating
Because what you have is two children spread across these stories take place across different decades and they're able to not only see
Something they shouldn't have information about but they're actually able to see a secret the narrators are trying to hide
It's not like they're thinking. Oh, you had grapes today, right? Did you have grape jelly all over your shirt?
They're actually seeing something that you would remain that you wished would remain hidden
It's like they're tapped into some sort of guilt matrix
Very odd detail could be completely made up could be a one-off thing
I thought it was weird that I've come across at least two cases of this and you wonder if it happens more often
That more I'm not saying all children, but there could be a lot of children out there who are able to
tap into other people's sins
They can't make sense of them because these sins are so adult
The emotions are so adult the actions are so adult and the children can't really understand
What they're seeing or sensing
So they have to use childlike terms to describe it
But here's the thing we all know we all know children are creepy by default
So if even a few of them have this power
No more no more babies. No more babies can be born now the next time babies are like walking by I'm like move along
Nothing to see here. No mental stuff to see here. They see me eat a bunch of grapes drinking my patreon supporters milk you mochi
Let's go ahead and call in that carbonicop to relieve me behind the suburban neighborhood. We are headed out to
the Vatican City
This is a really cool story that was sent to me by AZ
Really really appreciate this one. It's funny when he sent it over to me
I kind of thought it was a joke not that he was playing a joke on me his live or fools
It's that it sounded funny when I first heard of it and then I looked into it and it's quite terrifying
It was a nice little twist. I was like I liked being surprised on the story. So thank you, AZ
We're in Vatican City and we are here just in time. We're attending a
Exorcism
seminar
You're like dude, this is so awesome. We sold that movie. I brought my own holy water. No, we're it's a stuffy
It's a stuffy seminar. There's a slide projector
Super boring, but we're sitting there and Monsignor Steven Rosetti is he's doing the slideshow
He's doing this presentation about exorcisms
and
He's talking about this case he had a
There was an exorcism that took two
Years to complete. That's one thing a lot of people get confused about exorcisms
They think it's like the movie you just show up do a couple rituals
Maybe it takes like a day or two throw some holy water say the right words demon spins around jumps out finds the nearest trampoline
Wee wee there's a little kid sitting on it. He was like, oh, this is not gonna end well for me
I got a lot of secrets
Exorcisms can take a long period of time which is an interesting tidbit, which is an interesting exorcism tidbit
It's not generally a one night thing
So they'll often take breaks they'll often we covered a story about that a long time ago
It's actually the one episode of the show that gave me nightmares. I'll put it in the show notes
Where the exorcists took a break and they shouldn't have and really bad things happen
I actually had nightmares after recording that episode, but
You have this Monsignor they're doing this exorcism for two years they get a couple demons out
The guy's doing okay demons show back up continue the exorcisms or he just they had some just holding on that whole time
But two years into this they're doing this
Exorcism and one of the things is you want to know the demons name you want to know who you're dealing with so a lot of times
You'll compel them to tell you their name
so the Monsignor is demanding to know this demons name and
It gives a name that the Monsignor didn't expect you do because you heard the intro to this episode, but he didn't expect it
This demon really this spirit says I am Judas is
cariat
This person's eyes go from side to side. I don't know if I pronounced that right, but I am Judas
I'm the dude who sold Jesus out to the Romans for 30 pieces of silver
If you haven't attended if you've never attended Bible school
He was one of the disciples who's the traitor he betrayed Jesus and said he's over there and the Romans grabbed Jesus
held the quote-unquote trial crucified him Jesus comes back to life
There
School now you got it. You got the whole story Judas is obviously obviously. He's a
Pivotal evil figure evil human figure in biblical tradition. He is the one who turned in Jesus Christ
So Monsignor Steven Rosetti is looking at this dude and he's like
On the bed and he's talking and saying I'm Judas and now
Steven Rosetti says listen, I have been doing exorcisms for a long time and I've never encountered
Someone possessed by a ghost
He says that after this exorcism and I'll get into how they get rid of Judas in a second
But after the exorcism he talks to other exorcists and he goes hey guys you won't believe what happened
They're like Judas. He's like, what do you know?
apparently Judas had been popping up in
Possessions it's not super common
But he does there's actually a exorcism case that lasted from
1975 to 1978 it was a woman in Switzerland
There's actually a transcript of that
Exorcism it'll be in the show notes originally I was going to do like a dramatic reading of it
I decided not to
Decided not to be in the haunted closet playing the role of an actual evil spirit repeating the words
So you can do that you can do that at home, but basically I'll sum it up for you
It's the priest compelling him to leave and Judas mean like now I like it here boss
There's a lot of stretching actually that's a little more dramatic than actually is but he's telling him a leave and Judas is like
No, no, and then Judas is like you don't understand like the priest. I I'm a little so I'm a little sauce
Authentic it is but Judas is basically like you the priest today suck because they don't teach the way that Jesus wanted them
The guy's like writing it down. He's like I hope the Pope gets this
This is my complaint letter to him basically Judas is complaining that
Satan not even complaining. He's saying that Satan's winning and here's all the ways to defeat Satan
But I'm kind of poking you I'm kind of poking you and saying you'll never defeat me because you guys aren't teaching the eight
Cataclysms you're only teaching the six so it's a little suspect on that, but anyways, it wasn't interesting reading
I'm just gonna read the words of a departed spirit in my haunted closet, and it was super long
He's talking to these other exorcists, and they say oh no, we've encountered Judas as well
And one thing he found in common with all these other exorcists and his experience as well
Nearly impossible to remove
nearly impossible to
Exercise out of the human body the Monsignor says that he has gone toe to toe with some high ranking demons
There's a method to this an exorcism at its core is basically
Scientific for lack of a better term you had like science you want to add baking soda and vinegar
You make you make the volcano that's how volcanoes are born
You know it's gonna do it the exact same time you get the measurements right same thing with exorcisms
You say the right words you command the right things use the right items like holy water holy relics the demon will leave the body
The none of this is working on Judas holy water. He's taking a bath. He's like more more. I'm so filthy from being possessed
The rights weren't working on the exorcism rights were working and the Monsignors thinking about this again
This isn't a one-day thing that they're dealing with Judas. He's thinking about it. He goes Jesus in the Bible
Jesus gives his disciples the ability to
Command demons out of bodies. That's one of the powers that Jesus passes on to his followers
But it's fallen angels is specifically what they have the power to get rid of not fallen humans
Jesus like I'll teach you guys that tomorrow. He's flying up to heaven. No, no, I think we're gonna need that
He's like bye. See you when I come back
so they don't know that skill and he goes we tried everything to exercise this man of
Judas he wouldn't leave
Apparently what happened is the end the Virgin Mary showed up. I don't know
Here's the thing here's the thing I believe in demons and I believe in exorcisms and stuff like that
I don't know how this happened. I don't know if she came like in the vision
I don't know she walks through the door and they're like whoa, and it's like you and Judas Judas actually nothing about Jews
Judas would know her
Judas probably in real life outside of outside of the exorcism Judas would have met Jesus his mom
You have the disciples over for dinner. Mary's like making a bunch of like food make much of lasagna. They're like, whoa
This is magical. This doesn't exist back now and she's like, I know it's gonna be super delicious someday
He would have known her but anyways the Virgin Mary shows up. I don't know if it was a vision
I don't know if she physically showed up
If she physically if she physically showed up, I think he would have gone with that
I don't think he would have told this whole story about Judas first. He would show up the Vatican be like guys
I know we're having an exorcism seminar, but you won't believe what just happened the Virgin Mary just showed up
She's walked into a room and they're like why'd she walk in the room? He's like, okay
Now let me tell you the Judas story because you don't bury the lead on the Blessed Virgin Mary just walking into a room
Being like hey guys, what's up got any lasagna? How's my lasagna recipe doing?
Mary comes down and she compels Judas to leave this young man's body and that's when Judas is like I'm out and
He floats away the spirit floats away. It's an interesting story again
There's a lot of ifs if you're skeptic
It's just kind of a fun story if you believe in demons and things like that. It's actually incredibly chilling
Because the one thing you want to hope for is if you do get possessed by a demon, which is one thing you don't want
There's a lot of things you don't want you want to get attacked by someone possessed by demon either
But you want to at least believe that someone could rescue you someone could pull your consciousness out of that demonic control
And we have all these safety mechanisms and all of these prayers and rituals that can help
Reverse the demonic possession, but now they're running into something that is immune to all of that
And it's a fellow human not just a human, but one of the most reviled humans in
Biblical tradition
Possessing people
The idea of whether or not a human can possess somebody is
Theologically divisive
Some say they shouldn't be able to do that. That's the province of demons. That's something that demons have the ability to do
They can corrupt you they can make promises to you. They can trick you
But the idea of someone being possessed by a ghost is
It's not unheard of
But it's so rare
The only other instance I could really think of we covered it back on episode
367 the patriarch there was an allegation. It was never proven
There's an allegation that the father of the family was possessed by the grandfather of the family and he murdered everyone or convinced them to kill themselves
I think
But being possessed being possessed by demons is synonymous. That's really what possession is demonic possessions being possessed by an earth human is quite rare and
There's the and we don't even know if that was the case in the patriarch episode
The question is is could it happen at all? Like it would basically be like you have a house and then it's possessed by another house
It would be like two houses mixed together, but you know what I mean like a human soul and
A human soul not in a body. How do those interact? It's the same thing
The demon would latch on to some sort of parasite. It's almost designed for demonic possession
It's almost designed to take control of you now a demon can pretend to be a human
Right a demon could pretend to be a human and you think you're possessed by a human
But the same exorcism rights would work against that thing because they're not actually a human
This thing claiming to be Judas apparently was Judas none of the proper rights of exorcism would work on this dude
And I actually think being possessed by a ghost might be scarier
Because you imagine that demons live in this world
They're looking at the game board the idea of the demonic war between heaven and hell is they have an endgame
They go we know eventually Jesus is going to come back
We're gonna have this huge battle and Armageddon
We're quote-unquote prophesies to lose but we think we can actually win we think we can do this
So let's summon our troops. We see people are starting to live really good lives
We see someone who's gonna end up inspiring millions. Let's go to them. Let's ruin their lives
We see this person out here. They're making a difference in their community. Let's go to them
Let's get them addicted to drugs like we are looking at this game board
And if we can keep upsetting the pieces if we keep attaching ourselves to these people
Who are trying to better themselves try to better the world?
We can maybe
Pull out a W in the end
The demons are looking at this huge battle plan
There's seven billion and counting moving pieces and
The demons may be looking at these things where we're gonna put our forces here. We're gonna deal with this
We're gonna do this you just moving through the masses of humanity may go unknown
May be totally unseen
You're not a pivotal player in this war between heaven and hell just like me just a dude living life
Trying to make the best of it, but since the ghost has no plan
It's just energy. It's angry energy. It's mad that it didn't get what it wanted on earth
Everyone's a target
Not just the youth ministers not just the drug counselors not just the politicians
Every single person can fall victim to a possessed human
Doesn't matter who you are. It doesn't matter what you plan on doing. It doesn't matter what you've done in the past
Everyone is a target
That is terrifying
When you go into politics, you know people are gonna write you nasty letters
You know people may try to assassinate you you know that there will be spiritual forces trying to go to you one way or the other
You don't expect that when you're the garbage man
You don't expect that when you're a video game tester
You don't expect that when you're just a student
But there you are
Looking at your reflection in the mirror one day
You get a flash of something else
behind your own eyes
You never played a Ouija board you never went to have your tarot cards read you never engaged in anything that could open yourself up to
demonic forces
But sometimes when you're sitting at home eating dinner
Your right hand shakes a bit
When it reaches for that knife
You never wanted to change the world you never wanted to do anything more than have fun
But now you find yourself somehow
Standing outside a stranger's home in the middle of a rainstorm
You don't get to live your life now
It lives your life
It drives you it commands you it makes you do horrible things and you can just watch it
from behind your own eyes
And after you have annihilated families after you have led police on a multi-state
Hunt it is not until you are tried
convicted in sentence to death
That the spirit of this vicious bloodthirsty human
Leaves your body leaves you to sit in the cell leaves you to contemplate
Leaves you the memories of the crimes it committed
And when the appeals have run out
When you yourself are being laid down on that metal bed a
Needle inserted into your arm that will slowly inject medication that will stop your heart
You pray for mercy, but none comes
Dead rapper radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also do stuff at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio twitter is at the rapper radio
Dead rapper radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)