Today all those recent egg jokes will make sense as I cover an excellent conspiracy theory.
And then we take a look at the newest conspiracy theory going around.
Did Sean P. Diddy Combs write a book? That's not the conspiracy, although that's bizarre enough.
Did Sean P. Diddy Combs, famous East Coast rapper/producer,
did he recently write a book called The Adreno Chrome Witch that finally exposed the secrets
of the dark ones today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. I'm gonna have a really great day
if I can get all these episodes recorded in time to go on vacation. You guys won't even notice
I'm gone. We'll have one week of repeats. But in the real world, I will be sipping my ties
on a couch in California watching every sci-fi channel movie ever. A couple of Polina brothers
throwing in there. It's gonna be great. Now as the marathon begins and I try to get these
episodes recorded, not rushing them, they're quality episodes, I want to give a shout out to our newest
Patreon supporter, David Laz. David, thank you so much for supporting the show. We're all saluting,
you thank you. That means a lot. Since you've supported the show, today you're going to be our
captain, our pilot, our escort through these crazy stories. If you can't support the Patreon,
that's fine too. Just help get the word out about the show. That will really, really help out a lot.
David, let's hop in the Jason Jalopy. We're going for a ride. We're headed down to San Francisco.
We're in San Francisco and we're gonna meet a guy named Josh Tetrick. And we walk into his lab.
We're like, "Hey, what's up?" "Shh. I'm working on something." He says as he adjusts his nerd
glasses over his face. "Hmm. What are you working on, Josh? I just told you to shhh."
Puts his finger to our lips. All of our lips, everyone who's listening right now has a finger
on our lips. And he's steady in this empty jar of mayonnaise and he goes, "There is a way. I had a
dream. An angel came to me in a vision last night. Did you know that eggs are a required ingredient
in mayonnaise? You have to have at least one egg in it. And 65% of it has to be vegetable oil."
And then as disgusting as it is, that's 100% true for the FDA to declare it as mayonnaise.
Basically, it's just a jar of vegetable oil and one egg cracked in it. But he's like,
"But for the vegetarian market, I must find a better way. I must find a better one."
I'm glad he sounds like the Riddler trying to figure out a plan to be Batman. I must find a
better way to get this available for kids. It's not fair that vegans don't get to eat this disgusting
food, right? It's just not fair. So he makes his own mayonnaise using like chickpeas and a bunch of
other like vegetarian stuff. Carrots, whatever. Puts it in there. He comes out with this product.
The product in Zygostria Different Names. I think it was originally called like Beyond Mayo.
Now it's called Just Mayo. And he's like, "Ta-da!" And he's like holding his suspenders.
He got during the montage of him developing it. Now he's holding his suspenders. He's a little
entrepreneur. He goes, "Now I have Just Mayo." And it starts flying off the shelves. Vegans,
vegetarians, people who have no taste buds. Everyone are running to the store to buy Just Mayo.
But according to the FDA, like I said, it has to have an egg in it. And you can mess with classics,
but sometimes the classics have allies. The lightning storm. There's a huge building
somewhere in America. It's in a swamp. It's in the shape of a giant egg. It's basically the
Legion of Dooms headquarters, but an egg. And inside this headquarters, there's an 18-person body
called the American Egg Board. And at the head of it is Joanne Ivy. She's the chief executive.
And she's standing there. She has like this long purple cape on. She has these little
henchmen running around her. She turns around. She's like, "Drats! Just Mayo is biting into our
profits because we get a percentage for every egg shipped, but there's less eggs being shipped.
If you do the math, we're getting less money. If eggs aren't being used in Mayo, and people are
buying this Just Mayo, then we're losing money. So we got to do something about that.
Now while they're trying to figure out what their battle plan is to take down Just Mayo,
Helmins actually sues Just Mayo. They say it's false advertising. You have to have an egg in it.
That's not an egg. And I mean, it's so ridiculous. Basically, you actually had a trial. Like you had
like juries get selected for this. You had a judge. Had to look through this on its dock. And
he's like, "Ugh, wish I had another one of those triple homicides, but black Mayo. I hope they
don't make us taste it. I hope they don't do a taste test during the trial. It's all going on
because you can't call it Mayo because it's not real Mayo." And he's saying it's Just Mayo. It's
not even close to Mayo. Eventually though, the company, Just Mayo says, "Okay, fine. We're going
to stop declaring our Mayo." This is so weird. I'm surprised that this worked. Basically,
we're going to stop calling it Just Mayo. And Helmins is like, "Okay, that works."
They change the name to Just Mayo as in justice. As in bringing about justice to the world. So it's
no longer Just Mayo. It's Just Mayo. I'm going to start a cereal called Cheerios. I'm going to
start marketing my own cereal called Cheerios. People go, "You can't do that." I'm like, "No, no,
no. I'm saying cheer Eos." As in I'm trying to bring cheer to the world. And lawyers are like,
"Well, there is a precedent for that. You can sell Cheerios." No, no, no. Cheer Eos, Mr. Carpenter.
Thank you. Thank you very much. So you think the story's over, right? Everything kind of got resolved.
Just Mayo is still sitting on store shelves. You think the story's over, right? They quote,
unquote, changed their name. The lawsuit was finished. They no longer claim to actually be
main names. And that would be the end of the story if it wasn't for an expose on the American
Egg Board. The reason why I've been making those American Egg Council jokes, which was a name
change to avoid getting sued, because you can't actually say you're sponsored by somebody, even
joke you can, but you better have a good lawyer. Mine was the American Egg Council. The American
Egg Board, it turns out, took the threat of just Mayo incredibly seriously. Incredibly seriously.
And eventually some emails came out where two executives, to be fair, they were joking. Everyone
said these guys are just joking. But jokingly, they said, "Hey, maybe we can get all our money
together and hire Hitman to kill Josh Tetrick." So that's pretty bad, right? But that's not
where it ended there. And they were just joking. Everyone, all sides agree they were just joking.
But the American Egg Board, they ended up getting really worse off than just foods,
because they started a whisper campaign. They began putting out feelers. First off,
they were buying Google ad results. So if you looked at stuff like Beyond Foods,
which was the original name of the company, if you googled that in, stuff about the American
Egg Board would pop up. They were buying Google keywords. So if you were looking for just Mayo,
or if you're looking for Beyond Foods, they might have even done it for his name. Stuff would come
up about American Egg Board. You're like, "Well, that's no big deal. Like, you type it in, you're
trying to find Josh Tetrick, and then you see an ad for eggs." It wasn't just them. They began
trying to get people to talk more about eggs. That's what they're supposed to do. Hold on,
hold on, hold on. This is why I was making those egg jokes, okay? Because I want a big,
fat paycheck from the American Egg Council/Bord. Because listen to this, listen to this, because
they were so scared of Josh Tetrick and his just the Mayo, they were paying food bloggers
to talk about how awesome eggs were and how yummy eggs were. $2,500 a post. I'd do that, dude. I might
do not talk about eggs ever. But if they were paying me $2,500, I would do nothing but talk about eggs.
Okay, maybe not that. I would find a way to ruin the middle of a true crime story. I'm like,
and then the family was horribly butchered. But before that, they sat down to a delicious
plate of eggs. When the autopsy was done and they looked at the contents of their stomach,
they found purebred American eggs, the best eggs on the planet. They started this whisper
campaign and they were trying to recruit high level celebrities and just normal food bloggers.
And they were paying them to talk about how great American eggs are. Now, that's against the law.
There's not like some big brother out there. You're in shopping. You're like, "Oh, I heard
this brand of eggs is good." And you get grabbed by the Gestapo. You can talk about eggs all you
want. You can't because the American Egg Board, it's so weird. It's a quasi-private organization.
It's the American, a bunch of egg growers decided to get together and said, "We want to market eggs
back in the 1970s." But the government has to appoint the 18 people in the council. It's really
weird. So they have a limitation. It's not a government organization, but they're involved in it.
You can't do that. Like, you can market your own product, but you can't talk trash about other
people's products. Eventually, Joanne Ivy, the chief executive, she took an early retirement
because of this scandal. And then everyone else was required to do, quote, "Additional training"
to learn. Uh-uh, don't do that. That's that story. That's that story that I built up for two episodes
with my stupid egg ads. I want my money, dude. I want my money. I want $5,000. Think about it.
I would have earned $5,000 for those bogus ads had this podcast been around in 2011, dude. I
would have gotten paid. And the reason why I wanted to cover this story, because I think it's
hilarious, also I have to add this because it's written in my notes. In 2012, the American Egg
Board had a contest. This is just dragging this segment on too long. But I love this fact.
The American Egg Board had a contest. You would record yourself singing the song "The Incredible
Edible Egg." And if you did, these are the prizes you could win. You could win an iPhone 5,
that's the top of the line, guys. Oh, if that's not enough, that's that cutting-edge technology
isn't enough. An Xbox 360. And, I mean, I get it. At the time, those were probably good prizes,
right? At the time, that might have been the most pr- best prizes. But you win an iPhone,
an Xbox 360, and 12-month supply of eggs. Where are you going to- where are you going to put
12 months worth of eggs? Do I get a- can I sell my Xbox and get a new fridge for that?
Anyways, that probably can't edit it out this segment's going on too long. I wanted to cover
that story, one, because I want my $5,000. And two, I always hammer this point home. We always
talk about these conspiracy theories. These are the ones that affect real people. The government
was basically the quote-unquote, like, this private organization was kind of chasing this
guy around. It's so funny, because every- the stories that I don't ever worry about, like,
the next story coming up, I'm not worried about covering, it's the stories that involve private
entities that I'm always like, "Ugh." I'm always like- like the eBay stalking story, that one was
a good one, these guys- these are the ones that I'm more worried about coming after me than,
you know, Hillary Clinton breaking into my house with a baby under each arm. That's actually a
perfect segue to our next story. "David, let's hatch a plan and blow this joint." I can't think
of any egg-based puns other than that, and that one is barely an egg-based pun. David's shaking his
head. "You know what we're going to do right now? Call in that carpenter copter. We are flying out to
New York City." Me and David, we got on glasses, we're wearing all-white suits, we're doing
dances to a zoom lens. If you're under the age of 30, you did not get that joke, it's possible no
one got that joke. We're in a Puff Daddy video, remember? Remember back in 2000 when music was,
like, happy and fun? Remember 2000 when you actually had, like, music videos and TRL and stuff like
that? I can't stop- now, uh, 'cause I'm too cool. I never listened to East Coast rap.
I was West Coast, dude. 100%. I despised East Coast rap. And I did not make an exception for
Wu Tang either. Don't get me wrong. I understand why people like Wu Tang Clan, but even now,
I've never listened to 36 Chambers. I've never listened to- I've listened to maybe two or three
RZA songs. Like, the only time I ever came across anything from Wu Tang Clan is if it was on the
radio or they were guest rapping on a rap- a West Coast Rappers album, which didn't happen a lot.
I've never heard Ready to Die. Never- I've heard only radio songs. I've never listened to Ill Mottic.
I've never listened to a single Naws album. But I'd hear him when he's rapping with DMX
on Grand Finale. So I was not into East Coast rap. It just wasn't my style. So- but- so full
disclaimer here. We're going to visit- the reason why I said all that stuff- DMX like,
"What are you taking off his white suit? What are you talking about? Why are you talking about
rap all of a sudden?" Because sir, we are going to visit Puff Daddy, aka P-Ditty, aka Diddy, Sean
Combs, head of bad boy entertainment. Helicopters flying in between the buildings of New York.
We see this sterling high rise in the sky and it's all like flashing. We ain't go nowhere.
We can't be stopped now. Cause we're bad boys for life. Helicopter's flying around.
And this is P. Diddy's building. We're gonna fly. We fly next to the building. Put on autopilot.
We jump into the building. Quite dramatic entrance, right? We're from the West Coast though. So you
know, we- we don't take the stairs, man. We're from the West Coast. We're walking around P. Diddy's
building. We're brushing glass off of our clothes. The reason why we're here is recently
Mr. Combs has written a book. Written a book called The Adrenal Chrome Witch. Now obviously when I saw
this pop up I go, "Oh that's fake, right? Like that was my first instinct. But I gotta check it out.
I gotta see what's going on with Puff. It's not just that Puff Daddy wrote. I'm like, "Puff Daddy wrote
a book. Puff Daddy, before you- I'm not saying Puff Daddy's stupid. And I- I always call him Puff Daddy
just cause I'm older. So I'll try to correct that. P. Diddy is not- I'm not saying P. Diddy's stupid.
He famously said in- in Bad Boys for Life, that song, "Don't worry if I write rhymes, I write checks."
Which is a great line. And he's basically saying, "I'm not a lyricist. I pay people to write my songs
because I make that much money." And I remember- I remember where I was. I'm such a huge rap fan.
I remember where I was when I heard that line. I was sitting at Josh Moore Meyer's house and that
video came up and he dropped that line and I went, "Ohhhh!" Like straight up out of a movie. Because that
was a killer line and I think everyone knew it was true. So when I'm laughing about P. Diddy
writing a book, I imagine that him just not writing rhymes but writing checks would extend to his
literary career as well. He's obviously a very savvy businessman, despite the fact that I have
a West Coast/East Coast rivalry. But recently he wrote a book. He wrote- I just always get stumbled
when I say that. Sean Diddy Combs wrote a book called The Adrenal Chrome Witch. Or did he?
Now this book appeared on BarnesandNoble.com and it popped up and it made a massive splash. Like
right away people were really delving into this mystery. Let's look at some of the key details
here. The cover of the book. Just a picture of P. Diddy. Right? That's all- that's all you need to
buy, right? Especially if the book's called The Adrenal Chrome Witch. Just a picture of P. Diddy.
It is seven pages long. Whoa dude, must have a- it must be either free or the best book ever,
because it only needs seven pages. How long's the Declaration of Independence? It's not a 300-
it's not a Harry Potter novel. Just have a couple- I don't know how long- Declaration of Independence
is technically one page. I think it's like King George is reading and he's like, "I'm too busy to
turn the page. Give him what they want." Pretty sure it's just like a scroll, right? Weren't they
still using scrolls back then? Anyways, he writes a seven page book. Sean P. Diddy Combs
writes a seven page book called The Adrenal Chrome Witch. It's either amazing, everything's
compacted into seven pages, or it's free. It's not free. It's $100. It's a $100 seven page book
written by Sean P. Diddy Combs. The cover again is just P. Diddy holding his chin, looking suave.
Here is the description of the book. In case you just thought maybe Adrenal Chrome is- I guess for
you guys who, like, this is your first episode, you're not making a conspiracy theory world,
I should tell you. Adrenal Chrome- and we'll get a little more into it, but just so this makes
sense, Adrenal Chrome is this chemical that supposedly, Satan worshipers and the Illuminati and
the elite and reptilians and stuff, drink. It comes out of the human adrenal gland. They drink it,
and it either gives them eternal life, gets them high, they get addicted and they need it to have
eternal life, all three. It really depends on the mythology you're following, but that's what
Adrenal Chrome is. We'll get a little more into that. So Sean P. Diddy Combs writes a book called
The Adrenal Chrome Witch. Here's the description. Seven pages, 100 bucks, here's the description.
Quote, "The Adrenal Chrome Witch is a true story about the elite secret society
and their bizarre eternal youth rituals, not for the faint of heart." This book is no longer on
BarnesandNoble.com, so that should give you an idea of what happened here. I'm looking at this,
read the description, I'm looking at a photo of P. Diddy, and I'm like this, obviously this is fake.
Now you can set up a book, let's say you're going to BarnesandNoble.com, you can put up an e-book
and put written by George Washington, and it's called The Story of How I Oh Jason Carpenter 20
bucks. And then I'm basically like, "Hey, I'm like going to his relatives. I'm like, you know, with
interest, that's like $15 million. Look at this book. You can put whatever off their name you want.
It can be up there as long as it doesn't get noticed." That's what happened here,
because the book got taken down and actually all the author stuff got taken down, and we actually
found out, I don't know if this is the real name of the author, but this is another name the author
goes by, Candy Michelle Johnson. Because there's a bunch of other books, because you were new,
and you click on the Sean P. Diddy Combs, it took you to like an author page, and you start seeing
some P. Diddy books, some by this Candy Johnson character, and other books were written, The
Illuminati was a book, The Illuminati Foundation, separate book, don't get them confused, two
completely different plots, and then Daddy Warbucks' house, and that had a picture of
P. Diddy with his daughters, weird, and then some book called French Kisses. That did not have a
picture of P. Diddy and his daughters, thankfully. So it seemed to just be this collection of all
those other books, and there was a few other ones, but all of them have been taken down now.
What happened was Barnes & Noble obviously got alerted to this, he probably got tons of emails
about it, "What, tell me, have P. Diddy's email me the secrets personally?" Whatever, they took it down,
and that just fueled the fire of the conspiracy. What's gone on with this is completely insane.
Within a day or two, we went from the world where P. Diddy did not write a book called The Adrenal
Chrome Witch, to now this being, because there's screenshots going around, now this being a real
part of the overall mythos involving Adrenal Chrome, involving the elite, I have found full
Twitter threads where people are like, "Thank God, someone finally took a step towards revealing
the Adrenal Chrome." And then other people go, "No, no, no, he knows that Q's about to shut him
down, so he's trying to get ahead of it." No, no, no, he's trying to expose it, and all this
argument over a screenshot of a book that no one read, because it was $100. Now there is the look
inside function of the book, so you can read three pages, you can read half of it, right?
Seven pages, you can read half of it, and it starts off, it's basically just like stuff you know,
if you're a lunatic, like if you follow this stuff like we do, not saying we're all lunatics, but
if you believe in the stuff, the adren-- and we're gonna, I don't want to just gloss over the Adrenal
Chrome, because we're gonna end with that, but it's stuff like, you know, the elites take this
Adrenal Chrome, and they get it out of the Adrenal Glance, and da-da-da-da, all this stuff. And then
one page is lyrics to a song I didn't recognize, and then the other page quoted the song "Hotel
California," which is the most boomer conspiracy theory that I've come across. It's been around
since I was a kid, "Hotel California," that song by the Eagles. "Hotel California" is about telling
your soul to Satan for fame. I don't know, I don't particularly-- it might be, but I don't-- if it
is, I don't think it's a hidden message. I don't think they're like, you know what, no one will
ever discover this. They're writing this, "You can check in, but you can't check out." It could
have been-- it could have referred to drug addiction, it could refer to just life in general misery.
We've heard a lot of different things, but anyway, that's been going-- I mean, my stepdad was talking
about "Hotel California" being a song about selling your soul to the devil in like 1998. That's not
a new revelation, so P.D.A. you only got seven pages to tell this story, dude. Super boomer, but
that's that book. Now, what's funny is we have this thing going on, and again, the idea is this
whole idea about Adrenal-- so, he-- no, he did not write that book. You'll see-- I think you'll see
this go on for a while. I think you'll see this part of the conspiracy theory go on for a while,
but here's what-- here-- this is what's really interesting about this. On the Twitter thread,
someone goes, "Pfft, you know," and they were saying it unironically. They actually thought
they had exposed something, but really what they exposed was a massive flaw in the Adrenal
Chrome argument. They're like, "Yeah, those sickos, those perverts, you know you can buy Adrenal Chrome
right from China." Okay, I've heard that myth before. I heard that the coronavirus was actually a bad
batch of Adrenal Chrome, and that's why celebrities got it, or that's why Tom Hanks got it or something
like that. He's like, "Mmm, mm, mm, sweet human, human adrenaline, ah!" And that-- first it was that
they spiked it on purpose. Someone had spiked the supply on purpose and gave everyone coronavirus,
or it was an accident, whatever. So I had heard that conspiracy theory before, but I hadn't seen a
screenshot. I had not seen a screenshot from the online marketplace Alibaba of Adrenal Chrome.
And again, I go, "That's fake, but I better check it out." Dude, you can buy so much Adrenal Chrome
from Alibaba. Actual Adrenal Chrome. Because Adrenal Chrome is real. This episode might go a
little long. This is-- I find this very fascinating, though. The chemical Adrenal Chrome is real. The
question is, does it do what the mythology says it does? Can it give you eternal life? Spoiler
alert. Well, actually, that-- I can't give a spoiler alert on that, because that's an
interesting question. You can buy Adrenal Chrome straight from Alibaba. They will ship it to your
house. I'm tempted to buy it with a caveat. You cannot-- you cannot use this stuff. They take
Adrenal Chrome and they slightly alter the chemical compound to make a derivative of it.
Adrenal Chrome, with the chemical that you can buy, is used as a blood clotting agent. So it's
medical grade stuff. You can buy it. You can 100% buy it. I did not see any restrictions.
It is legal. It comes in the form of a powder, and it is cheap. And that's the thing. When
Adrenal Chrome thing is like, "Oh, out of one human body--" I was watching this YouTube video on it.
On one human body, you can get 10 cc's of Adrenal Chrome. Adrenal-- I know this is kind of rambly,
but Adrenal Chrome, what it really is, outside of the derivative that you can buy on Alibaba,
when the human has an Adrenaline response, it floods the body with Adrenaline. As that Adrenaline
decays, it becomes Adrenal Chrome and then it eventually just disappears. It dissipates.
Adrenal Chrome is a real chemical. It is created by the human body. The conspiracy theory is that
you can pull it out of the base of the neck, or you can pull it straight out of the adrenal glands,
which-- neither of those are true. It's flooding your body. Adrenal Chrome is basically flooding
your body. It's Adrenaline. It's not pure Adrenaline. It's Adrenaline that's starting to decay.
And you can get 10-- according to this YouTube video, you can get 10 cc's out of a single human
body. So what they do is the elite, they kidnap people and they scare them and they torture them
and they make them all super panicky, and then their blood is super sweet, and then that's when
they take it out. It doesn't make sense. You have to wait till the Adrenaline starts to decay.
So you'd have to be like torture them and then you're like, "No, no, no, here's like a stuffed
animal. Let's watch some Charles in charge." And they're like, "Oh, this isn't so bad."
"Oh, my spine!" Like, you have to wait until it starts to decay. So that's what Adrenal Chrome is
in our body. The Adrenal Chrome you can buy through China is that compound fixed a bit and it acts as
a blood clotting agent. So definitely don't be like, "Oh, I'm gonna be like the elites. I'm gonna
eject. I'm gonna eject this into my arm." Or snored it or whatever. You can buy though from Alibaba.
You remember, 10 cc's that have a human body. It takes 10 cc's to get this out. But somehow China
is able to sell you 10 metric tons for about 400 bucks. You can buy, like for 200 bucks, you can buy
like 10 kilograms of it, which is still quite heavy, but I would love to just have it as a
conversation piece in my house. Invite people over. "Hey, yeah, here's my Bigfoot painting.
Here's this awesome rabbit cup from Lana. Look at this. Oh, yeah, no, no, no, don't touch that.
That's 25 kilograms of Adrenal Chrome straight from Alibaba. You can buy it. A conversation piece
to say the least. But somehow they're able to take this 10 cc's and turn it into 10 metric tons
and then sell it to you for $450. So what that did was that post made me go, "Well, yeah, it is
Adrenal Chrome. Adrenal Chrome is real." And I honestly think I've said in past episodes,
I didn't even think the chemical was real. I would have misstated that. I don't think the
effects that were being told of it is real. Because really, when you look at people saying
about Adrenal Chrome, first off, the story was Adrenal Chrome gets you higher than you've ever
been before. And all of that stuff comes from fear and loathing in Las Vegas. And Hunter S. Thompson
said, "Totally made it up. Totally made it up. That drug that Johnny Depp wore in the movie, but
the drug that I did in the book, I made it up. I made it up. He told the director, Terry Galium,
I just made it up. There is no drug." And in the movie they go, "You take it straight from the
adrenal gland of a living human." And that started this myth that Adrenal Chrome was a real drug.
In the first episode of a British television show called "Louis," which was a spinoff of
Inspector Morrell, the first episode aired in 2008, that they were trying to break up a
drug ring that was draining adrenal fluid from humans. So it's an old story. It was from way back
when fear and loathing in Las Vegas, the book was written. This is how the mythology grows.
You have someone make adult, Adolphus Huxley, was the first person to talk about it. And he goes,
"There's this thing called Adrenal Chrome." In the mainstream, there's a thing called Adrenal Chrome.
And it's from the oxidization of adrenaline in the body. Huxley wasn't claiming that it did
anything supernatural. And then Hunter S. Thompson talks about it in his book, and talks about it
being this amazing high. But he's like, "I never did it. Like, there's no such thing as that."
But you see how that myth evolved. And nowadays we have people putting up fake books solely in the
good name of Peeditty. We have people releasing YouTube videos and all this stuff claiming that
if you ever see a rich person with a black eye, it's because that's the Adrenal Chrome thing.
They're either going through an Adrenal Chrome withdrawal, or they get it injected into their
eye. And if it goes wrong, gives them a black eye. You'll see these photo montages of all these.
Over the course of 50 years, photos of rich people with black eyes. They're not Iron Man.
People get black eyes. But anyways, you can pick out these photos of Bill Clinton in 1992
and Kevin Specy tomorrow with a black eye. I gave that one to him, by the way. But you have this
montage, right? And so you'll always see that connection. And so the mythology has evolved.
What's dangerous about this? What's dangerous about this? First off, I would hate to see someone.
A lot of people, it's so weird. A lot of people who investigate conspiracy theories
would love to join the Illuminati. That's a trend I've seen over the years.
Like, they hate them and they're always talking about it. But if it comes down to it, a lot of
them will want to join. So I'm afraid that someone's actually going to buy some Adrenal
Chrome from Alibaba and go, "Well, you know if it's good enough for Katy Perry and snored it,
or inject it and just instantly die, because it will clot their blood."
My concern is this. There was this documentary I watched a couple years ago. I don't remember
the name of it. But it was about how the movie Godfather, and gangster movies in general,
shaped gangster culture. Because before you would just be an Irish gangster,
you'd be an Italian gangster and you'd be like, "Yeah, give me your-" And you could even go back
further than the Godfather. But you'd be an Italian gangster and you'd be like, "Hey,
you know if you should give me some money because I protect the neighborhood
and your shop's in my neighborhood, it would be horrible if it wasn't protected." And the shop
owner's like, "Yeah, I kind of get what's going on." Irish gangster would be like, "Hey, you,
give me all your money." And as movies started to really hit the culture, and you started to have
these gangster movies, specifically movies like Godfather, it'd be like, in real life,
gangsters were emulating the gangster movies. The gangster movies were based on like broad
stereotypes. This documentary, and they were interviewing real gangsters. They were interviewing
these old Italian gangsters and they were like, "Back before Godfather, we acted differently."
Because they're older now. They're like, "We were just a bunch of dumb kids and then all of a sudden
we were walking around in our suits and we were doing all this stuff and we were trying to be like
the gangsters we saw on the movies." The whole pirate accent "errr" comes from one movie. One movie.
I think it was Treasure Island. I don't remember off the top of my head, but it was one movie.
Before that, if you look at old pirate movies, nothing. They weren't like, "Errr, say all the seven
seas, matey." It was one actor. That was an acting choice he made. An entire subculture was based
around that one movie. So you can have these mo- you can have, obviously there were pirates
before that movie came out. And then you have a movie come out and then everyone goes, "Errr, matey,
I got a patch and a peg leg and a parrot." It's all from that movie. Not saying that pirates didn't
have those things, but it would be super rare if they did. This is my worry. This is my worry.
You have a dolphin, you have Huxley talk about it in his book. You have Thompson talk about it in his
book. Then you have this whole theory going around that it'll make you immortal and stuff like that.
People who would have never thought about doing this before now will. You never ever thought,
"I wonder what it's like to inject another human's adrenaline into my body." Maybe, maybe, maybe if
you're sick of it, that thought crosses your mind. But now imagine you are super wealthy and you're
bored. You have no morals and you're bored and you're reading this stuff online all the time.
"Oh yeah, you know the elites do it. That's why Hillary Clinton looks like she's 27."
Because she injects adrenochrome into her skin all the time. That's why the elites have all this
power and so on and so forth. It's the best high ever and you have to do it all the time. And you
have people who are researching this, who are stumbling across this information. It's totally
fictional. It doesn't happen. But people with the means and the lack of morals are looking this and
they go, "I wonder if this is true?" And the next time that they have the opportunity, they're gonna
try it. Just to find out. That's out of the means of you and me and 99% of the normal human population
who would never do that. If you have enough money, if you have the means and you have the lack of
morals, and the opportunity presents itself to you and you never thought about it before, but you'd
been reading online all of this stuff. Mark Marin. He's not doing this. Mark Marin, he's the guy who
does WTF podcast. When his career was in the dumps, I remember listening to an episode a long time
ago, when his career, he was a stand-up comedian, tried to get in on SNL stuff, wasn't working out
for him. He was talking about an episode, he goes, "When I was, when my career had stalled and I was
just sitting there, he goes, 'I was doing research on the Illuminati and I was thinking, 'I wonder if
this stuff is real.'" Because his career, he was, he felt like he was an outsider, he felt like he
was working as hard as he could. He wasn't going anywhere. He's thinking, "I wonder if the Illuminati
is real. I wonder if that's why I'm not successful, because I'm not in the in-crowd and things like
that." So, and now he is super successful. It's not because he joined the Illuminati, but you have
powerful people who look into this stuff as well. Maybe they weren't powerful when they were looking
in the way, but you'll have people like these subjects. People like reading about this stuff.
My fear is that somebody's reading this stuff now, they're buying into the hype,
they believe P. Diddy's trying to expose the truth, and they have the ability
to find a human victim. The story, I believe, is fake today. But stories like this don't stay fake
for long. Eventually, we will come across the serial killer. We will come across somebody who
is taking the adrenaline out of a human body and injecting it into their own veins. We can make
the myths real, and that's the scariest truth of all.
[Music]
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabberradio. Twitter is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]