America is a nation in decline.
And if you disagree with that, then please tell me how in a free country a man could
be minding his own business sweeping up his kitchen at 1.30 in the morning when the lovable
sitcom character Alf kicks down his door and shoves a hose in his throat.
You got an answer for that?
America's burning people.
And then we travel to Australia, the alphalist country as it's known, to join a young school
teacher on a walk.
She's just enjoying nature, feeling the warm sunshine on her skin, birds chirping in the
trees.
But everything changes when she found a statue missing an arm.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing out in the world of
being you unless you're a shapeshifter.
And I hope you're having fun being someone else.
But someone who I know only shapeshifts twice a year walking into Dead Rabbit Command right
now.
Everyone give it up for one of our Thanksgiving live stream contributors.
And Idea Guy.
Woohoo!
Yeah, walk on in, walk on into Dead Rabbit Command.
Long time supporter of the show.
And Idea Guy, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
You guys know what I'm going to say.
You can't support the Patreon if you can't support the show financially.
That is okay.
You're not a freeloader.
There's a lot of other podcasters called people who don't give them money.
It's ridiculous.
It's okay.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That helps out so much.
I really, really do appreciate that support as well.
You guys don't have to give me money.
And Idea Guy, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Put your seatbelts on.
We're driving all the way out to Texas.
And Idea Guy is leading the way.
Now I got to be honest.
When I started this story, I have the vaguest memory of one of you guys suggesting this
story and I don't know who it was.
So if that's the case and I forget to name you in this episode, just shoot me an email
and I'll make it.
I'll make it up to you somehow.
Because I like giving people credit for when they send me these stories.
This story is nuts.
And I have a vaguerock election of someone sending it to me and I read it and go, "Oh,
that's just nuts."
This is just nuts.
And I go, "I don't know.
It might honestly be too weird.
Did this guy make it up?"
But here we go.
We go journeying into the story that this guy either had one of the most bizarre encounters
or he has some sort of substance abuse problem and undiagnosed or maybe diagnosed but he's
not telling us mental problems.
This is nuts.
It's June 17th, 2015.
We're in the town of Red Oak, Texas.
It's 1.30 in the morning and this guy posted this.
He sent this, I believe, to Lawn Strickler for Bandoms and Monsters.
They definitely did cover it.
He might have sent it to somebody else and then Lawn Strickler picked it up but he doesn't
give his name.
We do get an exact date in a location so I'll take that.
We don't have his name.
I'm going to go ahead and call him Tommy.
Tommy is sweeping up his kitchen at 1.30 in the morning.
I don't know much about Red Oak, Texas but I know a lot about Orangevale, California.
If someone's sweeping, if someone is doing any sort of chores at 1.30 in the morning,
meth is probably involved.
But now legally, I'm not saying Tommy is a meth user.
I don't know if he is.
I just know in my life.
I never used it but I just know a lot of people who have had a lot of family members that
have been meth heads.
I do know that if you're sweeping, if you're doing any sort of chores, you're doing a puzzle.
You're doing a puzzle at 1.30 in the morning.
Maybe he can't sleep, right?
Maybe that's just my own life experiences on my uncle repairing.
He's attempting to repair a car engine at 1.30 in the morning.
He found some springs at a junkyard and he goes, "Oh, this will finally let me soup of
that engine, that half engine block that's in grandma's shed.
I'll finally finish building my car."
Tommy's sweeping up his kitchen.
It's 1.30 in the morning.
He's sitting there sweeping, minding his own business.
And his son, Tommy's son, kicks in the kitchen door.
But it takes Tommy back, right?
No one expects that.
I mean, I guess if there's a lot of meth in the house, you know someone's going to kick
in your door eventually.
Sorry, there's the police.
There's people going, "Hey, you got some meth?"
Someone kicks in his door.
Again, for legal reasons, I do not know if Tommy is a meth addict or just does meth or
is a meth aficionado or even knows how to spell it.
I don't know.
But somebody kicks in.
Well, it's not just somebody.
His kitchen door gets kicked in and standing there now in the kitchen is Tommy's son.
Well, Tommy's son is dripping wet.
He's head to toe soaked.
But it wasn't raining outside.
Wasn't raining outside.
So a mystery is afoot.
Tommy realizes something's wrong whenever he sees a relative and they're dripping wet.
It's always a problem when one of your relatives is soaking wet.
Tommy looks at his son and figures that this guy totally has to be on something.
If you looked at someone who came into your house and they were soaking wet from head to
toe and it wasn't raining, what would you think?
I'd figure maybe someone sprayed him with a hose, an extremely exuberant water balloon
fight.
I don't know.
He went to SeaWorld and came back just in time to watch Daddy sweep.
Tommy looks at his son.
He's dripping wet.
Dripping wet.
And goes, "Have you been out jogging?"
Even an actual quote.
"Have you been jogging?"
Well, the son doesn't answer him.
He simply walks up to Tommy, touches his head.
Tommy passes out.
Tommy wakes up the next morning and he had slept so deeply that he actually missed work.
He slept through his entire work shift.
His work shift was not sweeping up the kitchen.
His boss called him up and goes, "Tommy, where are you?
How come you didn't come to work today?
You're in no call, no show.
Not only were you not at work, you didn't tell anyone you wanted to be at work.
What in the world?"
And I imagine this one, the boss stopped himself and goes, "You know what?
I don't even care.
I don't even care what stories about to come out of your mouth."
Because Tommy, the reason why he wasn't able to go to work was because his sweaty son touched
his head, which I imagine is pretty much what he had told his boss.
I imagine the boss just hung up.
He was so deeply asleep after he got his forehead touched he slept through his shift.
Also it turns out that his son came home at seven in the morning.
He wasn't covered in sweats.
He wasn't soaking wet.
So Tommy realizes, "Oh my God, who was that or what was the thing that came into the
house last night?
What was that?"
Because his son's like, "Dude, no, I got home.
I got home at seven in the morning.
I don't know why you're saying that I was all sweaty, Dad.
And I don't know why you're saying I got here at 1.30 and I definitely don't know why you
think me touching your head made you late for work.
This is just getting weird.
Could you imagine growing up in this house?
Could you imagine having a parent who...
Well, that's not fair because a lot of people have paranormal events happen to them, right?
A lot of people have stuff.
We cover them all the time on this show.
The reason why I think I'm going so hard on Tommy is because of what happens next.
Really what he's doing is he's telling the story, trying to prove that something imitating
his son came into his house.
And of course, I mean, obviously I've made a bunch of jokes about...
You know that lighthearted subject, drug abuse.
I've made a ton of jokes about that.
But I will give Tommy credit for this.
He has proof.
He goes, "Listen, I actually...
I don't know how this worked out, but I was calling my son at the exact moment that this
imposter walked into the house.
I don't remember it.
But somehow I had called my son.
So if I had called my son and my son didn't pick up the phone, then there must be an audio
recording of what happened.
You know, because it would go to voicemail and he's holding the phone when this thing
came into the house.
So maybe I'll figure out what happened.
And he said, "Here's the thing.
I played the voicemail.
It shows that I sent a voicemail to my son's phone at 1.30 a.m.
So I got his phone and we played the voicemail and you hear a door crashing open.
And then you hear Tommy say, "Have you been out jogging?"
And then you hear the sound of a struggle.
You hear the sound of two adults struggling and something or someone falling to the ground
and you hear a dog barking.
As the dog is barking in the background, you hear an entity.
You hear some sort of coarse, nearly demonic voice say his name three times.
Tommy.
And you start to hear the sound.
You said it sounded like a radio frequency, a radio channel being changed.
Definitely inhuman, right?
Now the entity quotes, "Said my name three times in a growling, garble voice."
He says specifically it sounded like the voice from the movie "Fourth Kind."
Remember that movie with starring Mila Jovovich?
Or according to him, according to him, "Mia Pultovic."
Maybe it's Mandela Effect.
Maybe he just doesn't know actors.
I don't know.
Mila Jovovich.
"Mia Pultovic."
You know, you're like Jason, now you're just picking on this guy.
You involve people who can't pronounce states' names.
You can't even pronounce major geographical places and you're making fun of this guy.
Mila Jovovich is actually a pretty hard name to pronounce.
Anyways, garbled voice from that movie "Fourth Kind" starring Mia Pultovic.
So you go, "Okay, Jason, at least he has evidence."
Like out of all the stuff you cover, hauntings and UFO, people getting abducted by aliens.
This dude has a voicemail.
Like you've been going hard on this guy.
Basically, all the time I've met that for the first 10 minutes.
This guy has probe.
He has a voicemail.
And surely he included the voicemail when he wrote out this account.
Just attached a little voicemail to the email.
Well, yeah, he would have.
He totally would have.
But the aliens got to his voicemail and they changed it.
So before, the very first time he heard it, he hears a kitchen door getting kicked in.
A voice going, "Him?"
Saying, "Have you been out jogging?"
And then the sound of two adults kind of struggling, a dog barking, his voice being growled out
three times.
But now, he says, "All right, I'm not even going to bother sending you the voicemail because
the aliens got to it."
And what happens is if you hear the voicemail now, all you hear is Tommy, "Gah, imagine
the sun getting this email.
Imagine the sun getting this voicemail."
I mean, you're like, "What in the world, Dad?
I don't want to go home.
Can I just spend the night at one of your guys' house?"
You have the voicemail at 1.30 in the morning from your dad.
All it is, this is all that's on the voicemail now, is Tommy, "Gah, your phone rings.
Let's put it to you.
Your phone rings 1.30 in the morning and you avoid the call because it's your dad and he's
nuts."
Then he listened to voicemail and it's your dad saying, "Have you been out jogging?"
And then you hear like a struggling.
Is it the sound of two men struggling around or is it him struggling with the broom or
struggling to stand up?
You don't know.
You just hear Tommy say, "Have you been out jogging?"
And then a little bit of a struggle noise, some sniffling like Tommy had a runny nose
and a dog barking.
And then the voicemail ends.
I think I need to change my actual voicemail message too.
Have you been out jogging?
Then you can just leave your message.
So the aliens got to it.
You can't say that he didn't provide proof.
He had proof.
It just got altered.
But here's the thing.
I'll give him credit for this.
He has video footage, right?
That's even better than audio.
The man with the podcast says he has video footage.
And along with these articles, there are two photographs of what to me looks a lot like
the demon from Sinister.
What was his name?
Baggule?
Good movie.
I mean, I wouldn't want to pick him up on video in my house, especially video for Baggule.
But he says, Tommy goes, "When I look at him, I see Alf, the lovable, huggable character,
from the '80s sitcom.
Alf, alien life form."
He says he has a big nose like Alf does.
I don't see it.
But I would have to say, I'd feel like we're quibbling over fallen straws.
If I'm saying it looks like Baggule, he's saying it looks like Alf, but it might just
be some sort of interdimensional demon walking around his kitchen.
And he goes on to the video, what he sees is Alf blowing gas into his face or...
This is a pretty big difference between the two, right?
This is a big difference.
Alf was either blowing gas into his face or operating on him.
Huge difference between the two.
If someone said, "Hey Jason, can I blow this gas in your face?"
I mean, I'd probably say no either way, but if someone said, "I'm going to blow some gas
in your face," and before I could answer, they started operating on me instead, I'd
be like, "This isn't part of the deal.
Plus, I should probably get new friends if these are the options they give me."
This entity was either blowing gas in his face or operating on him.
And in the background of this video, you hear the Devil's Rejects.
He was watching the Devil's Rejects.
Okay, so he's confirmed.
I like that Devil's Rejects.
That's like the methiest movie of all time.
He's watching the Devil's Rejects at 1.30 in the morning while he's cleaning up his
kitchen.
In the video, Alf is blowing gas into his face.
You can hear the Devil's Rejects laying in the background.
And then the entity just walks away.
We unfortunately don't get to see the video, but he did provide two photographs of this.
I mean, listen, I wouldn't want this thing in my house.
This thing is absolutely terrifying looking.
It's possible that he just took photos of the television screen, and he was watching
Sinister or something like that.
But I mean, it's interesting because this is one of those stories where he absolutely,
I guess it does kind of look like Alf.
I pulled the photos back up like you can kind of see what he's talking about.
But okay, so he originally reported this to Move Fun, which is the mutual UFO network.
And then Lon Strickler got it from there.
Phantoms and Monsters is a great, great resource.
You go there all the time.
Like here's the thing.
I mean, obviously if you had to categorize this outside of some sort of meth hallucination,
it seems alien because it has the medical procedure going on, the gas blowing and/or
operating.
It's a fascinating story.
This is one of those things, right?
Like is this guy nuts?
Was this a real encounter?
Okay, here's the thing.
It could have been, right?
It totally could have been a real encounter.
In the world of the paranormal, it's such on the verge of madness.
It really is.
Even stories I know that are 100% authentic because either I experienced them or people
I truly trust experienced them, they still sound crazy.
That's the first thing.
When I started really experiencing stuff, I thought it was going crazy.
So there is that border between the real and the unknowable.
That's where paranormal investigation sits.
And you do have stuff like this that is just so insane.
And if you took this story apart and only looked at individual pieces like aliens changing
voicemails or evidence disappearing, that stuff happens in the world of the paranormal.
Shapeshifters, that stuff happens in the world of paranormal.
It's just the character who's telling it.
It's the person who this happened to.
When you look at it in total, it seems like the rantings of a madman.
Did this story actually happen?
Did he hallucinate it?
Was this all a hallucination?
And even when he's listening to voicemails, he was still hallucinating stuff.
Who knows?
Honestly, I think that's the scarier version of it.
Because it's the story of a man who's completely lost his mind.
And I would say if you were some sort of demonic entity, if you were something with nefarious
intent, you would seek out the mentally ill.
We did an episode on that.
We were talking about aliens experimenting on people who can't communicate, right?
They can't communicate.
They're in a medical state where they can't move.
They can't talk.
Would that be the perfect place for aliens to do experimentation?
Because they can never tell anyone about it.
And this would be the same thing.
You show up to someone who's insane, blow gas in their face, and they're like, "You
guys won't believe it.
You guys won't believe it.
Boss, please don't fire me.
Please don't fire me."
I got gas blown in my face by Alph.
But he's going to believe them.
It's actually the perfect target.
That's what I would do.
If I was an alien, I would only experiment on hardcore drug users and the mentally ill.
It shows how inhuman I would be if I was an alien.
Because what are you going to do?
You can't stop me.
But luckily I'm not an alien.
Luckily I do have human morals to guide me.
And idea guy, let's go ahead and leave behind red oak Texas.
I don't think we have enough time for the statue story.
Let's go ahead and I'm going to do a swap out here real quick.
Because this is another story I wanted to talk about.
And idea guy, I'm going to go ahead and touch you the keys of the carbonicopter where you're
leaving behind red oak Texas fly us all the way out to a secret doctor's office.
One of the great things about doing this podcast is I can spend over a half hour calling a
man mentally ill.
And now I get to spend the remaining minutes talking about how I believe that this might
be possible.
This insane thing I'm about to tell you.
I read about it and I go, maybe that will work.
Maybe that will work.
For me it's all about what you can find and what you can't find.
When you come across the conspiracy theory and there are reams and reams of papers, books,
articles, videos, podcasts, whatever it is explaining that conspiracy theory.
It makes me think that's not true.
Maybe a little core of it could be true.
But if it was actually dangerous, if you were actually exposing a group of people or an
ideology or a conspiracy or a cult that was so powerful you would never be able to publish
it.
You would have gotten stopped in the 1800s.
Anyone who talked about it would have just disappeared.
Never heard about it.
That's always been the thing.
When people talk about flat earth, everyone knows about flat earth.
Even if you just have a passing interest in conspiracy theories, especially if you hate
conspiracy theories, you know about flat earth.
You may not know how the flat earth people think the world is, where it's just the flat
disk and the sun and the moon kind of rotate around.
There's tons of theories about what's beyond the article and things like that, but you
at least know the topic flat earth.
So this idea that NASA, the globalists in the most literal form, say that the world
is a globe because if the world was flat it would be proof that God exists.
That's really what flat earth theory is.
If you knew that the earth was flat and either went on forever or had this massive ice wall
and then you went millions of miles and there was another version of earth with their own
ice wall, just millions of miles of ice between, you would have to know that God existed.
The whole idea that planets circle each other and they form these balls and they're like
meteorites and over time all the pressure compresses them into a more circular form.
That is science and science cannot explain a flat earth.
So God must exist.
So that's the core theory of the flat earth conspiracy theory.
Now if that was true this never would have been completely crushed by all the groups.
The second someone started talking about flat earth in the 70s or 80s or even going back
to like the 1880s or what have you.
They would have been shot.
They would have been killed.
And we know that because we know of people who talk about conspiracy theories now that
get killed.
People like Karen Silquid who get assassinated.
People like Gary Webb who get assassinated for exposing the truth.
So when I come across stuff like this I go maybe there's something to it.
This would be super valuable.
This would be a huge thing that you would want to keep secret.
Back in the 1700s there were two esoteric groups.
One known as the, and I'm probably going to mispronounce this, Rosicrucians.
They're pretty big in conspiracy theory in and of themselves.
You see that.
You see a lot of mention of them in the Knights Templar and the early Illuminati, right, 17th
century.
The Rosicrucians and the magnetizers were these two big esoteric orders.
The magnetizers we talked about a long time ago, they were basically founded on the beliefs
of Franz Mesmer, a man who believed that all living things had this magnetic field around
them.
And that's the reason why we use the term Mesmerism or hypnosis is from Franz Mesmer.
We did really good episode on that.
I'll put it in the show notes.
I learned a lot about hypnosis during that episode and I think about it.
That's one of those episodes that I still think about from time to time.
Anyways, they developed this thing called the sympathetic alphabet.
And tell me this would not be world changing, even today, even in everything we have today.
The sympathetic alphabet, what it is, is you get two people to have the alphabet tattooed
onto their arm.
Now I would suggest you make it small.
You don't want to have these giant block letters covering your entire arm.
But imagine a little patch of skin.
You can have it done on your hand as well, probably like the back of your hand.
But you do it on your arm, I think it would be a little bit easier.
You have the alphabet tattooed on your arm, let's say it's just a couple inches by a
couple inches, right?
Fairly small.
You get the alphabet tattooed.
You then slice the skin off of your arm.
Not all of it, just part of the alphabet.
You slice it off and it is then removed from your body.
And then your partner there, he has his alphabet sliced from his arm.
Preferably you made him the same size, right?
Probably a lot of planning that goes into this.
You're not just like, "Oh man, look how tiny my alphabet is.
Your alphabet's huge.
We're going to have these big open wounds."
Because what you do is I take my alphabet flesh and I tear it off and I give it to you
and then I get your alphabet flesh and I put it on my arm and they basically are healed
into us.
So you have a patch of my skin and I have a patch of your skin.
And it is now basically fusing into, hold on questions to the end, okay?
Hold on questions to the end.
Like, "Jesus, this is so impossible.
Who knows?
I think, okay, let me just keep going.
Let me keep going."
So now I have a patch of your skin on my arm and you have a patch of my skin on your arm
and they're both tattooed with the alphabet.
And we take these magnetic needles, these magnetic needles that are actually like synchronized
to each other.
There's like this lodestone that they touch with the needles.
So now the needles are in sync.
The patches of skin on our arm are in sync.
So then you go to Budapest and I'm in Philadelphia and I want to send you a message.
I take the needle and I then begin to tap out the message.
So I say I want to tell you that I saw Avatar 2.
So I go, "I have spilled another whole thing.
Way of the water."
You're like, "Ahhh!"
Because that's what it is.
When I'm touching, I saw Avatar 2, Way of the Water, 3PM yesterday.
You're like, "When I'm poking, really your skin, right?
Your skin is attached to my arm.
When I'm poking it with this needle on your skin, well now you have my skin, right?
So on your open wound where my skin has healed over it, you'll feel little pinpricks corresponding
with those letters.
Because I'm poking, okay, now I realize it honestly took me this long to realize that
how does this work?
I read this so many times, I was like, "What?
This is fantastic!"
Now that I'm thinking about it, it wouldn't matter if I'm poking your alphabet on my arm.
I guess you would...
Anyways, let me keep explaining it.
When I'm poking it, it's corresponding, basically it's like Moriskoda.
It's not Moriskoda, it's like the straight alphabet.
So I can type out stuff, poke stuff in my arm and you feel it in your arm.
And because our alphabets are tattooed the same and in the same place, you be feeling
the pinpricks underneath the letter A. V. A. And you'd be like, "Whoa, he saw Avatar
2, Way of the Water.
If it's all the information I need to know, quit poking me.
I'm doing a full review."
The CGI was perfection.
It's funny because now that I'm saying that a lot, I'm realizing that it doesn't make
a ton of sense, but at the same time, I read that and I was like, "Wow, that's awesome!"
Like that would be Wi-Fi before the corded phone existed.
Like in the 1700s, if you were able to send a message across the planet to somebody, you
need to get a hold of someone, just poke your arm.
That's awesome!
And it kind of makes sense when you think of stuff like quantum entanglement, right?
They say you can take two...
I can't explain quantum entanglement, but the idea is that you take a molecule, you're
just shutting it off, you're like, "Oh, great.
Jason of all people is going to try to explain quantum entanglement.
What YouTube video did you hear about this room, Jason?"
You take a molecule or an atom, whatever it was, and it appears in two points at the
same time.
And if you interact with this point, they both light up, even though the distance is
great.
It is a thing.
I'll try to put a couple videos in the show notes that will explain it in any video, would
explain it better than that.
But quantum entanglement, I'm basically taking your flesh.
It's your flesh still.
It's just on my arm now, but it's like all the little capillaries are giving it blood
and it's healing.
That's the other thing I thought about it.
I don't know if it would heal well.
But let's assume that both of those things are correct.
I can send you a message across the world.
And I wrote this and I go, "Oh, like this was from the 17th century.
This was from two fairly big groups, right?
The Rosicrucians and the mesmerite, or the magnetizers and the magnetizer.
Clearly, there must be tons of stuff about this.
There is zero information about this.
Zero.
All I could find was a Wikipedia article.
I think I was looking up something else and it brought this up.
I thought, "Wow, that's interesting.
There must be a ton of stuff about this."
Nothing.
There was a television show.
I saw on Wikipedia they go, "Oh yeah, this was the plot of a television show.
It was some French show, I think."
But other than that, there's nothing on this.
There's a book where they talk about fact and fable and psychology as a book, extraordinary
popular delusions and the madness of crowds.
These are books.
And then it was like a plot in a French television show called The Nose of a Notary.
I don't know what it's about.
If it's about people, it's about people exchanging their noses and poking them with needles.
I'm in.
But The Nose of a Notary.
It looks like it was a movie, a TV movie.
But other than that, there's nothing.
And this is the type of thing that I could see powerful people wanting to hide.
This is something that I could totally see the elite wanting to control.
You can't hack it.
You can't monitor it.
You can't eavesdrop on it.
You can't stop it.
What's the first thing we see when there's any large-scale uprising in any country nowadays?
The first thing they do is they go after Twitter and then the internet as a whole.
We see it time and time again.
But if everyone just had patches of skin on their arm, you wouldn't be able to stop it.
Now I'm not saying everyone would engage in this.
But I think there would be more people doing it.
Like again, it was interesting.
I wasn't even able to find like jokie articles explaining how dumb this was.
Like those books, they're like, "Yeah, back in time people used to believe you could poke
your arm and send a message."
And then that was it.
Like even the books that I was looking at that mentioned it there, it was just like,
"Yeah, this is something people used to believe."
And I'm not saying you have to debunk everything because at the end of the day you don't really
have to debunk.
Well, you know, I think not debunking flat earth more vigorously is what caused it to
grow.
That and the YouTube algorithm.
It's okay if people want to believe in flat earth.
I actually don't have a problem.
I don't agree with it.
I don't believe in it.
But if people want to believe it, I don't care.
One of those conspiracy theories, whatever.
So you don't have to necessarily like, "I don't need to see a 10-hour-long video debunking
this because I think most people could go, 'Ah, that wouldn't work.
The skin wouldn't heal right.'"
And it's just, "What are we chasing?
It doesn't hurt.
I mean, it's kind of dumb.
It wouldn't work."
But I'm thinking it might.
Because they're talking about this in the 1700s.
And now we know about things like quantum entanglement that when you take...
Damn it.
I just fast-forwarded to this part.
I was hoping he was done talking about quantum entanglement.
He's talking about it again.
You take two molecules and you spread them apart, right?
Two atoms from the same thing.
It's your skin.
And it's on me.
So you're getting that signal to your arm.
I mean, it's basically quantum entanglement at its most base form.
But they've talked about, like, if you wanted to do long-range communication, if you could
use quantum entanglement, you could be halfway across the universe and I could send a message
because I'm talking to this molecule and you're hearing it instantly because it doesn't matter
how far apart it is, they still react at the same time.
Because it's the same piece of matter.
It doesn't matter how far off it's spread, it's still the same.
It's quantum entanglement.
It's crazy.
It's crazy stuff.
So couldn't you do that?
Is it funny you do that with arm flesh?
I know I use the word fascinating at least twice an episode.
I'm trying to actually stop it.
It's so interesting.
And what makes it even more interesting to me is that it's pretty much just out of history.
It's not even like, look at how dumb this is.
People aren't talking about it at all.
I stumbled across it on accident.
And it's so funny, I threw it in my bookmarks and then I came across it on accident like
two or three months ago.
But I kept coming back to it and I kept kind of looking for stuff and I was like, you'll
find a witchinary entry on it.
But no one's really done a deep dive into it.
This is something that I, people are already so tattooed nowadays that why aren't people
trying this, right?
Swapping these alphabets.
That would be a cool tattoo.
If you're looking for an idea, if you're listening to a podcast to get a tattoo idea.
But this is the type of technology that the powers that be would want to limit us from
having.
They would want to suppress this information.
So the only information that's out there is like six sources spread across the entire
internet.
Because it might work.
And if it worked, it would change the way people communicated.
Nothing is private.
We did that episode yesterday about how Google is, with the judge's order.
I don't want to say they're just handing them out, but Google is with the judge's order
giving police all your search information and not your search information.
They'll give the information of everyone who looked for a particular subject.
So a form of communication that you couldn't even be in the other room and listen in on.
Like it truly is impossible to break.
It's a code that you could never intercept.
Because the only two people who know what's going on are the people with the tattoos.
I mean, sure, I guess you could stand over his shoulder and watch what letters he pokes
into his arm.
That would be what you would have to do.
You couldn't even have someone going, "Hey, did you hear what Charles said the other day?"
No.
It's truly secure conversation that can take place instantly anywhere on the planet.
And the people in charge can't allow that.
They can't allow that.
Do I think it would work?
The objections I have to it is the healing of the flesh, right?
And you'd have to like, would you only be able to talk to people who have the same blood
type as you?
Like maybe nowadays with skin grafts, it would be like doctors know how to graft skin better
than they would in the 17th century.
I mean, any objection I have to this isn't the part where they're poking the arm.
It's like how the wounds would heal and things like that.
You got a twig underneath the skin.
You're like, "Ah!"
And your buddy just hears like constant screaming as his arm's hurting too.
That's really my big objection to it.
As a paranormal researcher, I could see this working in some way.
But we would never be allowed to know about it.
We would never be allowed to use it.
It's just too dangerous.
Not to us, but to them.
It's not dangerous because the skin graft may get rejected.
You might get a twig under your skin.
It's because the people on top can't allow it.
You can't have it to the Toletarian government where the people can speak freely.
You can't have any government where the people can speak freely honestly.
But you have to have some restrictions, but this would totally avoid all of that.
You'd be able to send messages.
It would be incredibly dangerous to have this technology, to have this method out there.
But the question always is dangerous to who.
Can I imagine what if you were the commander?
Would you have 18 different alphabets on your arms?
Because you're talking to all your generals?
If it was instantaneous communication across the globe, yeah, you would.
You'd have people with their whole arms, both arms tatted up.
They can keep in touch with people.
I don't know.
At the end of the day, it does sound as insane as anything that Tommy's putting out.
Maybe not. Maybe if I had to choose between this form of communication being crazy from
the 17th century or alph bursting into your kitchen with a gas canister.
That is crazier.
But I just think I'm glad I was able to pair these two stories together because it does
show in the world of the paranormal, crazy is a spectrum.
Because a normal person would have listened to the last 20 minutes of this podcast and
be like, dude, who is this guy?
He's nuts.
He honestly thinks you can take the skin off your body.
You went to somebody else and talk to them?
That guy's nuts.
If you just played that segment, they'd be like, this is what you listen to.
This is what you listen to while you're driving to work.
You're nuts.
It's a spectrum.
And yeah, I guess the skin, the sympathetic alphabet is pretty insane.
It does sound insane and I don't think it's as insane as your son shape shifting into
alph as the devil rejects plays in the living room.
But again, it's a matter of degrees.
It really depends on what you think is insane.
I think it also depends on how long you've been a paranormal researcher because at that
point you've seen a lot of stuff.
Fascinating technology.
Is it real?
Can you do it?
Would someone be willing to test it?
Other than me?
I'm not a tattoo guy myself.
I'm also not ripping my skin off in an underground doctor's office kind of guy.
But I would love to see, I'm surprised people aren't trying this with as many tattoos and
body modifications as they don't know about it.
That would be my guess.
Or maybe, just maybe, this truly is suppressed dangerous technology.
And simply by talking about it on Dead Rav radio, I may not make it to episode one
thousand.
Ten episodes from now will be at episode one thousand.
Will I make it?
Or will the Rosa Crucians and the magnetizers silence this podcast once and for all?
That was them driving by.
That was them driving by in a loud car.
They're letting me know that they're coming.
I'm not a tattoo guy myself.
[MUSIC]