Today is David Lynch's birthday, and if you don't know who David Lynch is, you could say he's the godfather of Dead Rabbit Radio.
Amazing filmmaker.
And today we're going to take a look at three stories that have a lynching twist.
The first off, we're going to cover a conspiracy theory that actually involves David Lynch himself.
A very bizarre piece of information.
You may not know, that's why you listen to this podcast.
Secondly, we're going to take a look at the story of a woman who just tried to enjoy a little evening by herself.
Instead she was interrupted by an alien who acts like someone from a Lynch movie.
And then a family is sitting at home eating a meal.
Everything is going as it should.
But when the sun enters the room holding a shotgun, not only do their lives change,
but reality does as well. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Garminer. I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
This is going to be a special episode. It's going to be extra long.
But it's full of good stuff. It's not filler. It's extra long good stuff.
And speaking of good stuff, great stuff actually, let's give a round of applause to our newest Patreon supporter, Sweet Sweet Golden Goo.
She's actually liquid. She's all like CGI 1990s liquid special effects oozing into Dead Rabbit Command.
And she's also bringing along with her her beekeeper husband, which I'm assuming now that I say that out loud.
I saw that on the notes. Is she the honey? Is that some weird?
Is that some weird thing? He is actually a beekeeper.
She's the Sweet Sweet Golden Goo. So she's going to form into like a solid human.
And her beekeeper husband is just going to be like, "Ooh, yes. That's why I love bees. That's why I found my wife."
Sweet Sweet Golden Goo, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
Just helps read the word about the show. Really, really helps out a lot.
Golden Goo, I'm going to touch you the keys to Jason's Loppy.
Catch him in your sticky fingers.
We are going to head on out to a forest in the middle of nowhere.
[gagging]
It's vague. Just pick any forest. Just pick any forest you've ever wanted to go to.
So as you're looking for any forest to drive through, listen, I know we have a lot of stuff to cover.
This is a jam-packed episode, but I want to start a new segment right now.
And I think this will be really cool going forward. I think this will be really fun.
I get a lot of stuff from emails from you guys, and I see this stuff post online,
of these stupid prophecies that keep popping up all the time.
And you'll see them for weeks. People are hyping them up on these conspiracy boards.
They'll set a prophecy. It's like August 21st, 2020.
It comes, and people are getting worried about it.
People are like, "Hey, man, I really don't know what to do. What's going on?"
And then it passes, and no one ever brings it up again.
And then we see another one pop up.
Oh, you know December 21st, 2020 is actually December 21st, 2012.
And people go, "Oh, no."
You know what? I'm going to start cataloging these.
I want you guys to send these prophecies to me so we can mark them.
And there is recorded proof. It's no longer a forum post that's disappearing.
Prophecy Watch. And this one is timely.
I've seen this one pop up for weeks.
Prophecy Watch, the very first one.
So if you're listening to this episode a couple months from now,
even if you're listening to the episode today, you're like, "What? People actually believe that?"
This is a real conspiracy that people have been buying into for a couple weeks now.
On January 20th, 2021.
So today, what is going to happen?
Obviously, if you're listening to this, it didn't happen.
What's going to happen is you are going to go to turn on the television.
You're like, "I wonder what the Big Bang Theory is up to today."
Click, you turn it on. It's actually going to be something far more entertaining than the Big Bang Theory.
Military Tribunals.
I'm going to read you this because I can't really sum it up any better than darkoutpost.com.
On Wednesday, January 20th, imagine military music playing in the background.
[Singing]
Starship Trooper theme song.
On Wednesday, 20th January, Inauguration Day, the emergency broadcast system will be activated.
The FCC is telling major networks that their programming will be preempted from 8 a.m. Eastern Standard Time
for up to 72 hours. If they don't comply, they will be off the air.
10 days of darkness will begin as mass arrests of over 500,000 individuals is expected to happen worldwide.
On the emergency broadcast system, 8 hour videos will be broadcast 3 times a day for 10 days straight.
Imagine the ratings are going to be great on that.
Hey honey, what are you watching?
The military tribunals are still on?
Yeah, 10 days of this.
The videos will contain military tribunals filled with confessions of high-profile elite individuals
exposed for their crimes against humanity.
So remember when this doesn't happen.
Remember when the National Guard doesn't take contri-
This is the other conspiracy theory.
The National Guard, when Biden is getting inaugurated, the National Guard is going to arrest him.
And then Space Force, apparently, is going to shut off something.
Space Force was created to hit a button.
The whole organization, they hit one button and it's going to take over or melt.
I don't know, maybe Joe Biden's made a wax.
I don't know.
And the Marines are going to be underground and in tunnels or something like that.
I just want you to remember this moment.
The next time someone makes a prophecy, remember this moment.
Remember the military tribunals, the Marines are underground.
They created a military to hit a button.
All of this stuff.
And I think this is important.
We're going to keep doing this prophecy watch.
Whenever these pop up, I can't say I'll cover everyone because they pop up all the time.
But when these pop up, I think it's important for us to cover them and to create a record of them.
So going forward, we can laugh at these wrong predictions and be less scared when they come up more.
Because this segment's gone on a lot longer than I thought it was going to.
But I remember when Clinton was leaving office when Bush was coming in, I was petrified.
I was like 17, 18 years old.
I thought Clinton was going to bring the United Nations and he wasn't going to leave.
That it was going to be this horrible thing.
I was not a huge fan of Bill Clinton.
I was a hardcore conspiracy theorist back then.
And I was scared.
I was absolutely terrified that these blue helmeted weirdos from France were going to show up in Sacramento.
I mean, it's stupid now that you think about it.
But that's why this is important to remember these dumb beliefs.
So going forward, we have less dumb beliefs.
Super long segment, important segment though.
Let's get started with the Lynch stuff.
I look over in Golden Goo and her beekeeper husband wearing blue helmets.
I'm like, oh no, the prophecy is true.
Let's talk about David Lynch.
This episode is going to go long, but I love David Lynch.
He's a huge influence on dead rabbit radio wouldn't exist without David Lynch without Twin Peaks.
Watching Twin Peaks was a huge part of my creative childhood.
I think I was like 12 or something like that.
It's totally inappropriate for a 12 year old to watch, but it was a big show.
It was a big show for me and it was all about like paranormal and conspiracies and how you have a normal world.
I love the idea of the hidden world.
You have this normal world filled with these beautiful people.
The show definitely gave me like my type of woman from Twin Peaks.
But then underneath it, you just have this really like seedy underbelly, this criminal element.
And then underneath that you have the world of portals and demons and secret societies and a group of men coming together to fight this eternal evil.
All that stuff that I really dig in both creative fiction and in my life like paranormal and hot waitresses and stuff like that.
So huge fan.
Now it's funny because every so often I'll find stories and I'll go, that's very lynchian,
which is that idea you have a normal stable world and underneath it, there's this dark underbelly to it.
Every so often I'll pick these stories and what's funny is I'm rewatching Twin Peaks for the third time.
I'm watching it with Sabine.
She's never seen it knows nothing about it.
And I've been having dreams about Twin Peaks and it's very rare that I dream about television shows.
I've maybe had one or two dreams about Deep Space Nine, my favorite television show.
I think I maybe had one dream about Buffy and I love that show.
I've had one dream where I was hanging out with the Transformers.
But since I started watching Twin Peaks, I've had like three or four dreams just in the past month about Twin Peaks.
I actually woke up this morning and I thought, I have all these stories, these lynchian stories that I've been like,
that's very lynchy and I have this kind of interesting stuff.
And it was weird.
I had a dream last night about Twin Peaks and I thought, I think I'm going to do a David Lynch episode.
I wonder if there's any reason for, if there's any justification for me to do that.
And sure enough, no joke.
I woke up about 3.30 in the morning.
I went to bed super early and I had these ideas for these David Lynch stories that I had been collecting.
And it's his birthday.
It's his birthday today, January 20th, 1946.
So I was like, that's weird.
Right.
That's totally weird.
I woke up the idea to do a David Lynch episode.
Turns out that it's his birthday.
Also turns out that it's the day of the military trivenals.
That's great.
It's like peanut butter cups coming together, right?
So let's get started.
That's super long introduction, but I really wanted to set the stage and this is going to be a bonus episode.
Because this man means so much to Dead Rabbit Radio and so much to me and hopefully so much to you guys.
I think you guys should check out some of his works.
It's great.
Golden Goo, take off that blue helmet.
You're really scaring me.
We are headed out to a forest in the middle of nowhere.
Yeah.
This first story I have no sources for because I read it on yesterday's episode.
I talked about how much I love Hollywood gossip.
I read this story on a Hollywood gossip website called blind items.
I'll put the link to the to it in the show notes, just the website itself.
It's just Hollywood gossip and it's really dirty Hollywood gossip.
It's not like you won't believe who Kris Jenner is dating today.
It's like this celebrity murder five people and no one ever found out.
It's like really dark and dirty celebrity gossip.
There is stuff about like Vander Plump rules, reality shows or whatever.
I don't even know that show is but it pops up all the time.
I'm assuming it's a bunch of hillbilly murderers.
How often they pop up on there, but there are stuff like, oh, you won't believe that Cardi B is cheating on the weekend or whatever.
But a lot of it's really like dark and dirty.
A lot of it actually like is elite conspiracy stuff like that.
I actually kind of want to do a segment on him.
There's a guy named him that's been dumping or girl that's been dumping information about sex rings and Hollywood.
So I might do a whole segment on that.
That's real fascinating, but I love Hollywood gossip and the dirty, the darker, the better for me.
So I'm on this website a while back and I came across this little piece of conspiracy info.
So allegedly, we're starting off like this.
Now we're driving through the dark spooky forest.
Allegedly, Jennifer Lynch, she's not alleged, she does exist.
Jennifer Lynch is David Lynch's daughter.
She's a director in her own right.
She wrote The Secret Diary of Laura Palmer, which I read when I was 12.
And then that was the book that I realized how girls masturbate.
Again, it's totally not appropriate.
I remember my older brother bought The Secret Diary of Laura Palmer.
My parents let us watch the show, but they didn't want us to.
They knew it was like on the cusp.
It was pretty rough, but my brother bought The Secret Diary of Laura Palmer and then he let me read it.
Like he read it and he's like, dude, cause he's a huge, he's a bigger, actually a bigger David Lynch fan than I am,
which is kind of hard, but he gave me the book and I read it and I was like, oh, they use a bathtub.
They don't, they don't always have to use a bathtub.
But when I was 12, that's how Laura Palmer masturbates in the book.
And I remember being like, I remember being like, hmm.
So thank you, David Lynch.
Thank you, Jennifer Lynch.
Here's the conspiracy theory, though, without that weird coming of age story.
And I'm reading through these blind items.
They're basically anonymous bits of gossip.
I've talked about them before on this show, but I come across this blind item.
This has had to be like a year and a half ago.
It's mighty to have been been longer.
It might have been before I was doing the show.
I came across this and it basically said that Jennifer Lynch, this is a legend again.
Don't don't shoot me.
Don't shoot me, Jennifer Lynch.
Jennifer Lynch wants to shoot someone in the head is what this rumor is that this daughter of David Lynch, this director,
wants to shoot a man in the head on camera.
She's obsessed with it.
She's been thinking about it for years and years.
She was in the bathtub and she's writing that book in the bathroom.
She's like, oh, you know what I'd really like.
You know, it really worked much better than a bathtub.
She wants to shoot someone in the head on camera.
She basically wants to film someone being killed on camera, but it has to be the fetish apparently is he has to be shot in the head.
It wouldn't like if you fell into a meat grinder.
She's like looking down.
She's like, that's cool, but it'd be so much better if you got shot in the head.
A bunch of birds attack him.
She's like, hmm, it's not good enough.
He has to be shot on the head.
He has to be shot on camera and it has to be like she doesn't want to watch a video footage.
Or like war footage of like some Kosovo soldier.
She wants to see it.
She wants to film it.
Again, a legend, a legend.
And so this rumor goes around that she had actually been talking to people.
She'd been planning to shoot a movie that had a scene where a guy gets shot in the head, but they would tell the actor it was totally fake and the gun was safe.
But the bullet would accidentally be loaded into the gun.
So during the shooting of the movie, she would actually be behind the camera and go and shoot him.
I mean, and action.
And then like the top of his skull would go flying off and he'd die and she'd be like, oh my God, oh my God, what happened?
Did someone put the wrong bullet in there?
And they're like, you're the one who loaded the gun.
You bought it from Walmart.
You brought it to work today.
She's like, who else had the gun?
They're like, nobody.
That's this idea.
This rumor is going around.
This rumor that one person said and now one of the biggest paranormal podcasts, one of the fastest growing paranormal podcasts in the world.
Is now repeating this rumor that I read two years ago.
So what's interesting is I saw that and I immediately was intrigued.
I mean, huge David Lynch.
I'm like, David Lynch, I'm a fan of your work and your daughter wants to murder someone.
He's like, what?
He also, how's your bathtub at home?
That's even a weirder question.
Well, going to his house and taking baths.
I read that and I was like, dude, that's super weird.
Could be true.
I don't know.
I heard that Cardi B just broke up with a weekend.
It's a wacky, wacky world.
But I read it.
I had a little, put a little wrinkle in my brain.
I thought it was interesting.
Huge David Lynch fan, love all of his stuff, even a serial killer daughter.
And then I watched the new Twin Peaks.
So it definitely was, it was pre me watching the new Twin Peaks.
So I would have had to read this back in like 2016, 2017, maybe because I watched it in 2018.
But I watch, I go to my brother, I visit him.
He had the new Twin Peaks and I was like, how is it?
And he's like, I don't get it because I watched the first, he stopped watching after about 16 episodes.
He goes, I couldn't figure it out.
And but we, he watched it all again with me.
It turned my hair gray the night I watched it.
My mom dropped me off from my brother's house a couple of years ago and I was vacationing.
And he's like, Hey, you want to watch the new Twin Peaks?
We watched like the first five or six episodes.
And then the next morning my mom picks me up and she's like, Oh my God, why is your hair gray?
I go because I watched six episodes of the new Twin Peaks.
It's not a joke.
My hair straight up Leland Palmer turned gray.
Ish, it's still dark.
Anyways, we're watching the new Twin Peaks show and the whole show, it basically should be called Twin Peaks.
Everyone's head explodes.
Almost every single person in that show who dies, dies from rather getting shot in the brain
or a hobo squeezing their head until it pops open.
That's, there's a few outliers.
There's the guy whose head is attached to a woman's body.
And then a couple of people throw up creamed corn until they die.
Creamed corn and motorwaves until they die.
But for the most part, their heads explode in some fashion.
I remember watching it and after the fourth person got shot in the brain in a super graphic way.
I actually was like, Hey, Hey, bro, can you pause it first?
I go, let me tell you this conspiracy theory.
I heard a couple of years ago, my brother pauses it and I was like,
So apparently Jennifer Lynch likes heads exploding.
So who knows if that conspiracy theory is true?
Probably not.
But if it is true, I may have actually stopped Jennifer Lynch from murdering somebody on camera.
So you're welcome.
You're welcome because you shouldn't do that.
So there you go.
Your conspiracy theory.
I'm actually because this episode is running so long.
We're going to save the David Lynch alien story for another time because honestly out of all the segments,
I think it was the weakest.
I think it's an interesting thing, but I want to keep prophecy watching here.
I definitely wanted that Jennifer Lynch story in there because she might be playing it today.
She's like, Happy birthday dad.
I'm going to see someone in the head today.
He's like, please don't.
And also you're very clean.
You do take a lot of baths.
She's like, thank you.
We're going to save the David Lynch alien story.
It was just a very surreal alien encounter.
We'll save that for another time because I really want to spend some time on this last story.
Even though I said the show is going to go long, you don't want it to go too long.
You don't want to outlast your welcome.
So as we're standing in the middle of nowhere, I don't know why we're here.
It's just the forest is spooky and imagine behind any tree Jennifer Lynch could be waiting with a gun.
You hear the sound of roaring bathwater and you know, she, I guess I should clarify too.
It's not that she just masturbated in the bath.
Okay.
First, I don't know where Jennifer Lynch masturbate, but people are probably like, dude, who cares if she's a note.
This is what I found out.
It's not like I didn't know girls weren't mermaids and they couldn't masturbate anywhere.
Apparently girls would straddle the faucet of the bathtub.
So the water would hit them like hit their clitoris and be like, uh, apparently they become a vibrating recliner.
When they're having sex.
No, so that I was like, really, you could do that.
Like I knew I couldn't do that.
I know the mechanism wouldn't work the same, but in the secret diary of Laura Palmer,
I eat a secret diary of Jennifer Lynch.
Laura Palmer masturbates using the water pressure from the faucet.
And so yeah, there you go.
You learned something today.
Maybe you didn't know that.
I didn't know that when I was 12.
So it's not that it was just in a bath.
It's the running water.
I just felt like I needed to clarify that.
So Golden Goo is just shaking her head.
Honey is going everywhere.
The beekeeper husband's like, hmm, can't wait to be home.
I'll watch you take a bath.
Honey, I'll watch you take a bath in honey.
Honey.
Golden Goo, I'm going to toss you the keys to the carpenter copter.
We're going to build a little co-pilot thing here.
So your beekeeper husband can help fly it as well.
You guys are working as a team and that's awesome.
We are leaving behind the spooky, spooky force before Jennifer Lynch can get ahold of us before she can get her aim ready.
She has a laser scope on.
We are headed out to Springville, Utah.
Now this just happened.
This absolutely just happened December 23rd, 2020.
It's one of those stories that I read and I go, oh, this is going on a show.
This is so disturbing.
I'm talking about this.
Golden Goo and the beekeeper land the carpenter copter.
And this little suburban neighborhood.
Very lynchian.
Looks normal on the outside, but things just aren't right.
Mike Lopez, he's a 23 year old man.
He's living with his mom.
He's actually living with his mom and his two sisters.
His mother, Victoria Ramirez, is 43 years old.
And his two sisters are Rosie.
She's 14 and Donna, who's 17.
Those names are made up.
We don't have the names of the girl, but Rosie is the youngest and Donna is the oldest daughter, the middle child.
And then Mike is the older brother.
Rosie and Donna and Victoria are sitting around the dining room table just eating.
Eating food.
You know what it sounds like.
I don't need to do a sound effect for that.
And Mike walks into the room.
Mike is carrying a brand new shotgun.
He just purchased that week.
If you were walking into a house and you were used to seeing shotguns, your uncle's always walking around with his shotgun.
He's like, you know, they're going to start broadcasting that military tribunal.
Can't wait.
You want to think anything of it.
Like if your relatives are all constantly walking around with shotguns, you'd be like, oh, they're going out hunting or something like that.
Hopefully that's all they're doing, right?
But this was brand new.
This was new in the house.
It shouldn't have been there.
So immediately alarm bells go off.
Why does this guy have this shotgun?
Now we in that situation would like run or try to fight him for it or pull out our own gun.
Han Solo him.
But the way this family reacts to this is just the beginning of this absolutely bizarre story.
Mike looks at Rosie, the youngest daughter.
And she nods to him.
He nods back.
And Rosie calmly gets up out of her seat at the dining room table and locks herself in the nearby bathroom.
Now Donna and Victoria are sitting at this table and here stands Mike with this gun.
Whatever's going on seemed to be preplanned between the two of them.
Donna gets up and follows Rosie to the bathroom and she's standing outside the door when Mike turns to his mother and aims the shotgun at her.
Victoria looks her son right in the eyes and says quote I know you're gonna kill me and I love you.
Mike pulls the trigger once and the shotgun tears through his mother's neck killing her almost instantly.
At that point Rosie unlocks the bathroom door and walks past her sister Donna.
Mike is just standing there over the body of their now deceased mother.
Very, very quick, painless death.
Rosie walks over and begins to pet her mother's hair.
She's just leaning over running her fingers through her mother's bloody hair.
Mike grabs his sister and lifts her up, wraps his arms around her and they slowly begin dancing next to the corpse of their mother as a song plays on the radio.
Donna has no idea what's going on.
She crawls out the bathroom window, escapes into the neighborhood, notifies the police.
That is a 100% true story.
That actually happened on December 23rd of 2020.
We have a witness of that event.
But the big question isn't did it happen?
Because we have to ask that on this show sometimes as it made up.
Was it you know some alien abduction or something like that?
No, it did happen.
The question we have in this, the question everyone has in this is why did it happen?
And this is where it becomes less of a, well never becomes less of a true crime story, but the focus moves away from the true crime to something else.
The police sweep in and they arrest him, they arrest Mike, and they take Rosie into custody.
She technically hasn't committed a crime yet.
They don't know.
They got to figure it out.
But based on what Donna was saying, whatever it was, it seemed pre-planned.
So the police drag Mike into the interrogation room.
Of course they're going to ask, why'd you do it?
Mike looks at him.
Somebody told me to do it.
I'm so like, you know, is this like, I don't know, some drug deal gone wrong?
Was this something you had to do to pay someone back to chill money to someone?
Somebody told me to do it.
Well, who are you, who's this someone who told you to do it?
Do you have a name?
Like what's this?
Somebody told me to do it is his response.
He leans over to the table and he tells the officers this whole thing, everything, the shooting and this.
It's deja vu.
I've done all of this before.
This, this isn't new.
They're not really getting anywhere with him.
They had talked to Donna and they go, Hey, so listen, your brother, your brother super creepy.
We haven't talked to the little sister yet.
But can you fill us in like he's saying that somebody told him to do this?
You guys owe money to some drug organization or something like that.
Donna goes, listen, he's a big stoner.
He, there are drugs involved in this.
He's a huge stoner, but I don't think it has anything to do with any sort of drug crime.
He was just stoned all the time.
And when they did arrest him, he did have THC in his system.
But there's a lot of people are stoners that don't go around shooting people and then dancing next to the body.
Donnie goes, not only was he a huge pot smoker, but he also would give weed and smoke with his 14 year old sister, Rosie.
And I truly believe that whatever happened, whatever this was is that Rosie knew it was going to happen.
She said, Mike's been getting weirder than normal lately though, like he's a big pothead.
But recently, I'm talking about how much meditating he's been doing.
He'll just meditate all the time.
And he began telling her, he began telling Donna, Donna, it's not just about the smoke and the weed.
It's not just about meditating.
I can, I can travel through dimensions now.
I can move through reality.
You see, that's why I'm meditating.
And I'm not necessarily just getting high and finding peace.
I'm moving from reality to reality.
He also being talking to Donna about quote unquote bad people that he'd been meeting and talking to bad people.
So the police at this point are going, OK, now over the spooky stuff, right?
Never the spooky stuff.
We got to stop interrogating people at 3am.
This makes sense.
He's into weed.
He's talking about meeting bad people saying somebody told him to do it.
Now we're back into the land of reality.
Maybe this was a drug deal gone wrong.
Maybe she was more involved.
So the cops are now feel like they're a little bit more back on track.
Let's go talk to Rosie and see what she knows.
So they bring in Rosie and the police again at this point don't know if she's an accessory before the fact.
If she's just in thrall of her older brother, they don't know.
She could have been the mastermind.
They don't know someone told him to do it.
Maybe it was Rosie.
They're talking to Rosie and again, they shouldn't hold these interrogations at 3am because this is where they truly get spooky.
Rosie says yes, me and my brother have been smoking a lot of weed lately.
That's true.
But you got to understand we're in danger.
We're just not safe.
Cops are looking at each other.
What are you not safe from?
We never slept at the same time.
See, I would sleep and Mike would sit there and watch me sleep.
And then when it was time for him to sleep,
I would stay up and watch him sleep because if we both slept at the same time,
something bad would happen to us.
Cops are like, "What in the world is going on? What are these people so afraid of?"
They ask Rosie, so your sister said that after your mother got shot,
you started dancing.
You started dancing with your brother over the body like,
"What was going through your head when that happened?"
And in true horror movie fashion, Rosie just looks at the officers,
smiles, then she began slowly singing the song that her and her brother danced to.
That was her only response to it.
Some sort of lullaby from the ring.
The police officers were like,
"Can we turn on all the lights in the station right now?"
That was her answer.
She just smiled and then was like, "Shake it off. Shake it off.
Play is going to hate, hate, hate."
I don't know what song it was, but any song saying super slow by a accomplice to a murder
is going to be a rough listen.
She showed no emotion at all during the interview and it doesn't sound like Mike was a font of feelings either.
But this is where we get to all of this stuff kind of being wrapped up in a ball.
This is an ongoing story, so we'll see what else comes from this.
But when the police ask, "Listen, your mom was shot, you're dancing over the body,
you're being super creepy by singing the song, please stop."
What was the meaning of this?
What was all the cause of this?
Why would Mike kill your mom?
And that's when Rosie says, "Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to creep you guys out."
That wasn't our mom.
Police officers are like, "No, no, no, no, no.
No, you see, that's not my mom.
That wasn't our mom.
That was somebody else, but that wasn't our mom.
So we didn't kill our mother.
Mike didn't kill his mother.
I didn't mean to implicate myself.
I had nothing to do with it.
I just knew it was going to happen, but that's not our mom.
So we didn't kill our mother.
Our mother's alive.
This was someone else, not our mom.
This crime happened back on December 23rd,
but the details are really just coming out now,
these interviews and all of these things.
And at this point, there's still no motive as to why they did this.
But I think as fans of the paranormal,
and we're looking at this show,
I think we can kind of figure them out.
I feel like I should be a police officer in Utah,
just for this one case, and then I'll retire and get a pension.
This is my theory.
I think that Rosie and Mike actually convinced themselves
that they were not in their home dimension.
This dimension they're in now, our dimension,
is not where they're originally from.
This is what they believe.
This is what I think they believe.
And so by shooting the mother in this dimension,
they technically didn't kill their mother.
They killed an alternate world version of their mother.
So as far as their concern,
it definitely Rosie that their mother is still alive.
This was somebody else.
So I think that is part of her reaction to it.
But everything else is so weird.
Who are the bad people?
Are these people demonic?
Are they some sort of interdimensional beings as well?
Who told him to do it?
Is that some sort of, I mean, I think it's mostly delusions.
I don't think they actually owed money to anyone
and it was like, kill your mom.
She didn't seem to be into anything like that.
And Donna didn't offer any information on that.
So I think the rational true crime explanation,
it doesn't fit.
But they may have actually thought they were moving
through dimensions and they were meeting these dimensional
entities that may have convinced them that maybe this was
the way to get back home.
Maybe they had traveled too far.
Maybe she was a dark entity herself and they need to
cleanse her.
I think the creepiest part of the whole thing and there's a
lot to contend with on this is the mother's reaction to
seeing her son with that shotgun.
I know you're going to kill me and I love you.
And that's an interesting reaction because he Donna
never said he was threatening.
She goes, he was getting weirder leading up to this event,
but she was never like he was chasing us around knives.
He was talking about killing mom.
She never made any statements like that,
but the mother knew it when he just got the shotgun a couple
days earlier.
The mother knew when he had that shotgun.
She looks at him and says, I know you're going to kill me
and I love you.
Horrible.
And truly a lynchian story.
The family that seemed normal,
a little bit of drug use,
but other than that,
no one saw any warning signs.
Even people in the house just go,
ah, he's getting kind of weird.
But then you have the seedy dark underbelly and underneath
that you may have something even more.
Demented and demonic influence in the events.
Now listen,
I love the idea of dimension hopping.
I love the idea of alternate realities,
portals and stuff like that.
I believe in those things that are possible,
but I think they're unlikely to happen.
I don't think if you smoke a bunch of weed and meditate,
you're able to move through realities,
but Mike most likely convinced his little sister about that.
Definitely convinced himself of that.
Figured they needed to kill her.
I think the tragedy of this other than this loss of life,
this destruction of this family,
Rosie may end up facing charges at a certain point,
but at some point reality is going to hit them.
At some point the drugs are going to wear off,
the psychosis will be stabilized.
They'll be sitting in a cold cell somewhere in the system.
And Mike and Rosie will realize they are in their home dimension
and that they really did kill their own mother.
But I think a darker ending honestly would be this,
that Mike was right.
He is from an alternate universe.
And he found himself in our universe.
But now he's going to be in prison for the rest of his life.
Not only separated from society,
because he's locked behind bars,
but separated from his home reality,
a reality where his mother still lives
and always wonders where her son disappeared to.
He was in his room one night and then
he went missing without a trace.
She would never think to pick up a joint and meditate
and travel through the dimensions to find her son.
But if she did,
she may find herself in our reality.
Standing over her own grave,
and if she stands over her own grave on a cold Utah morning,
she realizes she may have found her son,
but she has lost herself in the madness of the multiverse.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC PLAYING]