English cryptid moves to America and our movies television and music really
conditioning us for a bleak future. Warning, both these subjects give me
headaches to talk about so prepare for a Surly Jason today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Garbner. I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too.
The sound you may or may not be hearing is the sound of me getting some Tylenol
and some ibuprofen. I do have a headache and I know that this episode is just
going to compound that. Originally these stories were, I think they're
interesting stories and originally I was gonna split them up throughout the week
because I was like oh man they give me headaches and I was like you know what I'd
rather deal with one massive headache at the end of one episode than have to be
like oh great I have to record that episode coming up. Now again they're
both interesting stories but man they just drove me up the wall. One one is
driven me up the wall for years but the other one I just found out about. Now
one of them was a request. It was actually a request from a YouTube user
named Zurglejerk and I appreciate the request. I'll go ahead and tell you the
story. Well we'll see how we get through this. Okay so his request, I was
talking about cryptids. I've been doing a lot of cryptid episodes lately and he
said on YouTube he goes I bet you haven't heard of the story of bloody bones
in Texas. I was like oh I'm intrigued that's a cool name it's a you know
cryptid I've never heard of before. I'm sure it's really spooky. Oh my god I
gave me I was oh my god I had the worst headache. Now who is bloody bones? That is
the question right? So to learn that let's go to Texas. Where is Zurglejerk?
Zurglejerk thank you for the recommendation. The fact that he gave me
headache had nothing to do with you. It has to do more with the tail itself. So
let's hop in the Jason Jalopy, drive on down to Texas and find the bloody bones.
Find this cryptid that I've never heard of and when we get there we are told oh
yeah you really want to know about bloody bones. Yeah we kind of have a version
of him here but you probably want to go to the source. You probably want to
figure out like where bloody bones came from and we're like oh okay where's that?
Is that like Dallas or Fort Worth? They're like no England in the 1500s. Okay
great so now we got to go back to Oregon. We get in the carpentry copter. Go
through a time portal. We are now in England the year is 1548. We are out on
a search for the cryptid no one has bloody bones. More like a demon or a ghost
is probably a better qualifier for it. It's old timey England. We go we're
walking around the villages towns kind of at this point in the 1500s. We're
walking around. Actually that was quite far back. I think they were still suffering
from the black plague then. I don't think there were chimney sweep stants in
around 1548 was quite old. Soon it was 1548 is the year we're in England. We
find in this old crone living in a shack. We found her on Tinder and we go hey
this woman's super old and gross. She has to know somebody named
Bloody Bones. I'm sure they run in the same circle. We go in the old
crone's house. We go hey we are here to investigate the mystery of Bloody Bones.
She goes Bloody Bones huh? Bloody Bones you mean raw head and Bloody Bones don't
you? We're like what? No we just we don't care about raw head. I don't know who that
guy is you just mentioned to me. I just want to know who Bloody Bones is. I got a
time limit. I got a daily podcast to do. Just tell me about Bloody Bones. She's
just stirring her cauldron. She's like ah the tail of raw head and Bloody Bones
starts like this. So it's a creature. There's no one to hide in the darkness.
Sometimes it hides under your stairs that lead into your basement. And there's
little openings in between each stair where I can see your ankles coming down
your little eight-year-old ankles walking in front of it. It'll grab you. It'll
grab you. It'll break you. It'll take you away like
Calgon. I don't know how I know that reference I just do.
Stairs are pot a little more. Sometimes the creature hides in a cupboard.
And if it's halfway opened and you look inside and you see it
it gets you. Stirring the cauldron a little more. Or the creature also
lives in bogs and deep pools of water and snatches kids.
Takes them down to Bone Town. Bone Town UK. We're like that is an
interesting story. So is that the story of Bloody Bones?
Which goes no no no no sorry that's the story of
Rawhead and Bloody Bones. So wait wait wait so
are they are I'm getting confused there are there two
different monsters? Well yeah there's Rawhead
who's a monster who has a raw head and then there's Bloody Bones who's a
skeleton who dances. Okay well which one is the one you just
told me those spooky stories about? Rawhead and Bloody Bones.
Which so at this point this is how I felt researching this.
Article after article after article would tell this creepy story.
What I did versions I told you were different versions. In Britain the
original version was that this or them a creature lived in a bog.
And it was again a lot of these cryptids are teaching kids lessons. Stay away
from deep water because Rawhead and Bloody Bones will get you both of
them apparently and has to be a pretty wide pit
for two monsters to pop out of. I have no idea why these guys are so closely
connected. So Rawhead I have in my notes maybe about
three lines down same creature question mark because I can't
figure it out and people may say no no no Rawhead
is different than Bloody Bones and I get that.
But they're always a crew these guys are like
teammates but they never differentiate them. We know that Rawhead
he has a skull that's been stripped he's like a
has a head of a boar that's been stripped to the bone and he bites you
or sometimes it's just like a skeleton dude like who's had all of his skin
ripped off. But Bloody Bones is always a bloody skeleton
and he just dances that's it is that the thing like who
okay who's grabbing you when you're coming down your stairs because I don't
care you there's not two monsters under your stairs
there's not two of them that's not scary. If I was walking downstairs in the
middle of the night the idea of a bloody skeleton
hiding underneath my stairs to grab my ankles would terrify me.
But the idea of a bloody skeleton and then a hulking guy with a boar head
both being able to fit under my stairs at the same time
would is laughable. It's absolutely laughable.
All of these all references to these characters for the most part at least in
the research and again local like Zergljerk his local legend may have
just been about Bloody Bones. But when you look this stuff up
they're always a team they're always a crew.
It's it was driving me up the wall and then
this is their nursery rhyme raw head and Bloody Bones both of them again they
raw head and Bloody Bones steals naughty children from their homes
takes them to his dirty din and they are never seen again.
It says his in the poem takes them to his or which one is doing this stuff.
Is Bloody Bones just like a voyeuristic skeleton?
There's no explanation the weirdest thing is is that
none of the articles were like yeah we can't make heads or tails of this
either. I I've never been so confounded by a cryptid
before. If Bigfoot walked into my living room right now and sat on my lap I
would be less confused than I would be reading these articles.
And then in my pursuit to find out more information about who is actually the
villain in this story I found out there's
Bloody Bones and Goo Goo Eyes in Africa. So that is the story of Bloody Bones and
Rawhead Rex or Rawhead Rex and Bloody Bones.
They're just like a crew who like bumbles around and kidnaps kids and like
eats them or dances with them or turns them into bones
or something. You don't live if you run into these guys
but again super inefficient to if you are a stealth based monster to have
skeletons are the loudest thing that can chase you. They don't even have any
cushioning on their feet. Their bones make noise.
So the Rawhead can't like sneak up on people because
Bloody Bones sounds like a xylophone every time he takes a step.
And then Bloody Bones can't do his thing because he's standing next to a
guy who has the body of Kevin Nash with the head of a bloody boarhead.
That guy is pretty noticeable. A giant boar monster. At least a skeleton can
like sneak around a house put on a trench coat and a hat. Get on the subway.
You wouldn't know unless you looked right at him or his ankles or you heard all
that xylophone music as he was getting on. But then he's standing next to this
giant monster man. So but let's go ahead and norm...
I'll have to end this like I normally do. Is it possible that a creature like
Bloody Bones... What is it? Is it possible that let's
him forget Rawhead for a second? Forget he exists?
Is it possible for a creature like Bloody Bones to exist?
Yeah I mean sure if you... That sounds like...
It's possible. I mean obviously if you had any sort of dark or demonic
entity there's really nothing scarier than a skeleton. Why does it need to hang
off the board? Is the skeleton scary enough? There's another really
scene of animated skeleton is is almost scarier than a zombie.
Because at least with a zombie you could rationalize like maybe it's some sort of
virus or plague or something like that. But an animated skeleton you would go
that's impossible. Like what I'm seeing can never happen.
As no musculature, as no tendons, it can't move. So to wake up and see a
skeleton standing over your bed would be scarier I think than waking up and
especially seeing a guy with a boar head. I would just be like go back to bed Larry.
Like I mean a skeleton moving is so impossible
by any stretch of the imagination that if I was some sort of dark entity and I
wanted to take a form that would absolutely strike fear into the hearts
of children or adults or anybody I would be a bloody skeleton. I mean you
can't beat that. Walking down the stairs in your basement
is quite creepy and the idea of something hiding it's almost like
Schrodinger's cat where there's nothing in your cupboard unless the doors just
partially open and you look in it. If your cupboard's completely closed there's
nothing in there. If it's slightly open and you don't look
into it there's nothing in there but when you do look into it there's a bloody
skeleton. That's pretty creepy. However you knew
not to look into the cupboard because the giant guy with the skin boar head was
riffling through your fridge and goes "hey do you have any cheese?" like
"break up guys" is what I'm saying. Bloody bones you are the Paul Simon of this
group. Go solo and you can take your act to the
stars. Okay so that was a salvage. That was an absolute salvage of I don't know
how much I edited out of that segment but I think I brought it home. I think I
actually got something out of it. Now I took I put my pills out when I
started recording. Now I gotta take them hold on. You guys have it. Oh dude you
know while I'm taking these pills man I'm not I just gotta do have you guys
seen that Joker trailer? Eww Christ that that would dope.
That was awesome trailer. It's not gonna be a little brother about it. I said that
could almost just be a movie. Like if they never released a movie if they just
released that trailer and it was just like a trailer for the character the
essence of Joker I was like it's perfect. It's great if you haven't seen it yet.
Let's go ahead and move on to another conspiracy that honestly is one of the
most aggravating conspiracies. My microphone is vibrating I don't know if
that picked it up but let's go ahead and move on to conspiracy now that
honestly to me is one of the most aggravating conspiracies that I have
to discuss. We've talked about stuff like monkeys
aren't real and nuclear bombs aren't real and stuff like that and those
conspiracy theories are just stupid to me like they're
funny to make fun of but predictive programming and I've
mentioned it quite a few times over the course of the show but predictive
programming is one that really really irritates me because I don't
it's not it's not a very well thought out conspiracy theory
and it's incredibly popular. So what is predictive programming? Predictive
programming is the idea that this that in movies and music and brief
overview you can read whole websites on this stuff but the brief
the brief overview is predictive programming is the idea
that within movies and television and music there are
things that are put in there to desensitize us to the coming changes. So
for example the government wants to have robot armies so they want to
desensitize people to the idea of robots fighting in the
military. So the the illuminati or the powers
that be or the government or whatever they back the movie The Terminator
because it shows how effective a robot would be in combat.
Now I know what you're thinking we'll get to that in a second.
We'll get to that in a second. But another very very popular example
Alex Jones said this was one of the like most blatant forms of predictive
programming or most like extreme form of predictive
program and I remember the exact quote but he went off in this movie he hadn't
seen it or read the book but he'd been told about it and that was the hunger
games. So you know Alex Jones really has a
hard on for like a dystopian society, New World Order, Agenda 21 I think it's
called and you know all this stuff the coming global order and all that.
And so the hunger games really because it was aimed at a young audience
what does it show? It shows a world where one government controls everything
and obviously we don't know what happens outside the borders of the United States
but in within the United States you had one government that had control over
the entire United States and people were put into abject poverty
and their only job was to produce goods for this rich society the elites, the
elites in Washington they made stuff just for them
and the poor people were poor and even Alex Jones was like when the New World
Order comes gladiator games are going to come back.
And so the hunger games by watching the hunger games and having little girls
read these books that starts that desensitization, the cut that starts that
I forgot the word already my head is frowning
it starts to desensitize these young girls so when in their lifetime when
they're daughters so we figured 20 30 years past after the mother reads the
book she has kids and the changes start to come where America starts to
consolidate power in one city and she starts to see like all the economic
resources get drained from her community and as her daughter is getting
prepared for her first gladiator combat she goes ah this is fine because i read
it in the hunger games like i'm used to this now now there are other and we'll
get to i know there's a lot of problems with that one too we'll get to that one
in a second and sometimes there's things called specific
it's not technically called specific predictor programming but
you will see that this is predictive programming but they're just able to tie
it into an event into a particular event so in 2010 i think it's pretty common
knowledge maybe not but the simpsons has been connected to doing
predictive programming for 9/11 they had an episode where Homer went to the twin
towers right so that means they're gonna blow up and
Bart was holding up a in that episode Bart had a magazine that was a
an advertisement for a trip to new york a bus ride to new york or something
like that and it was only nine dollars and he holds the magazine up
and it has the number nine on it for the nine dollars and then the two twin
towers so it says 9/11 and then he's waving money in his hand so you
out that's from alex jones you go see he's waving the money in our face all
the money that the global elite's going to make from the attacks in 2010 of the
simpsons there was an episode called to surveil with love this was an episode
where basically um Homer puts a bunch of radioactive material in a gym bag
which is later described to contain enough radioactive waste to create 17
hulks and one spider-man and the cops think it's a bomb and they blow it up
they release radiation all over springfield and then they have to enact
a police state in springfield they set up security cameras in everyone's homes
and stuff like that but this is from a website that is saying that this
episode actually accurately predicts the next terror attack because it already
predicted 9/11 it's all about looking for the clues so we have the big scale
predictive programming that's just basically showing like if you show a
future where there is strict government control and the people fall into line
you put that in enough movies it'll desensitize the population
so when there is a strict government and the population falls in line we will
accept that because we've already seen it hundreds and hundreds of times
one thing obviously about being desensitized someone who works at a farm
who sees cows heads get chopped off all the time since they were a kid
it doesn't faze them if i saw cows head get chopped off
it would totally freak me out because i'm not desensitized to that it would
it would a live cow just walking and then it's head falling off well that would
worry anybody but you know what i mean like cow guts spilling out i'm just not
used to seeing that stuff so desensitization i can't say that word
desensitizing people is an accurate thing but anyways
that's neither here nor there in the simpsons it's too surveilled with love
when the dirty bomb goes off the clock tower i've got my
heads pounding the clock tower blows into the sky
lands next to Homer Simpson a joke right it's a joke
i'm not particularly funny one but the clock falls down next to him now the
clock hands point to 555 so that's the time it's 555
but did you know did you know if you turn that clock upside down actually if
you turn the picture upside down it's actually pointing to
drumroll 9/11 and you see Homer is looking at the number 10
there's a cloud above the number 12 so we have 10 i should have brought fronds
onto this but my headache was just out of control
so according to this website we have 10 plus 10 plus 2
because Homer's looking at the 10 and then there's the cloud over the 12
but then for some reason they make that a 10 so 10 plus 10 plus see what i mean
dude a splitting headache splitting splitting headache right now
a 10 plus a 10 plus a 2 is 22 the 6 is at the bottom my vision
starting to blur right now the 6 is at the bottom
so we have 22/6 or 6/22 meaning the date of the next terror attack is going to
be on june 22nd 2012 see
obviously that's the problem this was from an episode from 2010 this
blog came out in early 2012 obviously there was no massive terror attack on
june 22nd 2012 so you're like jason why does this
stuff irritate you so much well here's the thing like i said it's super
well known it's really hard to argue with because once you start to break apart
one i've done it before where i've started like i used to argue about this
stuff more in real life and online and once you start to break apart one they
just move to a different movie and then you got to be like oh wait did i see
that move gattaca yeah i guess it's like it was okay like and then you're
starting to think oh where's he going with this gattaca thing but let's really
go back to the original things if the goal is to desensitize people to live
in a future like that you can you name me a movie where a single state a
single government entity ruled every facet of somebody's life and they were
the good guys all of those movies hunger games
equilibrium logans run thx 1138 or two one of those
all of these movies are about people rebelling against the distilled all
movies that feature a one world government all movies that feature even
starship troopers they are a total like lunatic fringe militaristic i love that
movie but you know they're not really made out to be the good guys they're made
out to completely depersonalize the enemy and break down these young men and
women's lives and all this stuff there aren't and that's probably the closest
i've seen of a movie where there is a one world government where it
it has a happy ending with them not overthrowing the government
if these movies are desensitizing you to to do anything it's desensitizing you
to resistance so it teaches you to resist these
faceless entities hunger games does not glamorize the games and it
definitely doesn't glamorize the capital they're the bad guys
terminator okay if terminator movie never came out we would already have
robot in in war i firmly believe that i think movies
like the terminator made you go i don't ever want that to happen terminator
really set up the idea of the ai taking oh and i know it was in science fiction
before that like novels and stuff like that but as far as like mass consumed
stuff terminator basically cock blocked two
different things ai and robots in war because it made both those things look
like absolutely horrible decisions 100 percent that if your
goal was to get robots into the battlefield destroy the movie
terminator don't let everyone ever see it because it makes it look like a
horrifying future so that's the thing when we look at this
oh my god i have such a headache i don't remember if i had a third example
no i think it was just those two so that's the thing with predictive
programming now like i said you can argue this stuff
but there's this thing called the glp effect and i got to talk about this
real brief because my head's throbbing right now and i really
breathe you guys have listened to this episode this long i appreciate it
the glp effect is no and this is just this is just
absolutely bonkers it's glp is this there's a website called godlike
productions it's one of the main forums for conspiracy theory paranormal
stuff i spent probably two or three years on glp forums
that's really back when i was super serious about this stuff
when i was like an 11 true through i believed on all sorts of nonsense i
believed like an illuminati messages and music and all that
i used to believe all this stuff i don't i and i'm pretty open about that i
don't come out and be like oh no i'm so smart i'm like the best skeptic in the
world i used to be fooled by all this stuff glp
effect is this on godlike productions someone would make a prediction
much like this simpsons episode thing they'd say like hey i saw this episode of
the simpsons it had this clock with the numbers and if you do all this you do
all this the next terror attack is going to be on
june 22nd one of the most famous things that they said was that there was going
to be an alien attack at the london olympics and they would show
all of this proof that the london olympics was going to be attacked by
aliens now i remember at that point i was kind of starting to
get out of that i was trying to get starting to get out of godlike productions
and i was like maybe this maybe this is too weird
but the other side of me was thinking maybe they're right
look at all this stuff i mean i was an idiot so anyways
i uh anyways the obviously we all remember the great alien attack
that didn't happen in london for the olympic games
and this is what the whole website did they're like
we stopped it boys we stopped it see we want wrong
deciphering the symbols oh no it was the glp effect
see they put the symbols out there the illuminati the new world order puts
these symbols out there because it's part of their spiritual law they have to
warn us it's part something they have to do no there's no proof of any of that
either but anyways that's what they have to do and then we decoded it though
before the act see the simpsons was afterwards that didn't help but we were
able to decode the time and date of the next attack and those
evil illuminati went dang it he got us again we got it we got to shut it down
if we launch the attack now these armchair researchers will expose our
long-term goals shut it down call the aliens off
shut down blue beam it's over now let's hide some messages in arthur and then
you got to watch a bunch of episodes at arthur and hopefully
decode that that art what is he like an art farc or something he has that weird
looking nose i don't know if he's a doll or whatever but
anyways that weird looking dude and that that fat weird looking dude are like
shaking hands but it kind of looks masonic and then and then godlike
productions is digging into it trying to go obviously that is circular logic
obviously that is completely ridiculous you predict something's going to
happen it doesn't happen your prediction was so right it stopped it from
happening glp effect to this and that was back and like i said i was more into
that back like in 20 probably from like it was probably longer than two years
it was probably from like 2009 to 2012 i i i i don't know about the mayan
awakening but i definitely had a awakening
in the year 2012 i remember thinking this is absolute garbage
all of this stuff is just absolute garbage still get a lot of entertainment
value out of it but when i say i used to be like a 9/11 truth or
it was i was i would have irritated myself back then
and i definitely was wholeheartedly i wholeheartedly believed in
most conspiracies except for lame ones like jfk in the moon landing
anyways so i've been in the trenches with the people who believe in predictive
programming i believe in predictive programming and then when i got back out
i'm thinking like come on boys there's a world of knowledge out there that we
can discuss without all this nonsense and i turn around and the trenches are
still full they still got their helmets on and they're like
no we're gonna stay in this trench it's safe in this little bubble
so you have these people who really believe this las vegas carnivore actually
he watches the show on youtube las vegas carnivore's comment was this and i'm
paraphrasing the spiritual law thing is dumb
the spiritual law thing is stupid where they have to warn us before they do the
action but it's possible that they're using these
messages in movies as some sort of hypercigill to almost force
reality into their view and i said oh now that is
interesting i hadn't heard that theory i hadn't heard that take on predictive
programming before i've heard of the stories that
iluminati put the codes in there to warn the other members of the iluminati
stay out of london for the olympics alias are coming
i've heard that they use it to desensitize us to the coming changes i've heard
that they use it because it's part of their spiritual law they have to warn us
but i've never heard that it's almost like brute force magic and then what's
scary to that to the people who believe in predictive programming is that it
once again removes the power from them one of the reasons why i think predictive
programming is so popular is because it basically gives
the average person the ability to warn others of upcoming attacks so you have
the hidden knowledge component and it gives you the
power to fight back against the faceless iluminati and that's the glp effect
so it's a very attractive conspiracy theory
las vegas carnivores take on it completely removes that power
whether or not you decode the messages at all
it's going to happen because it's basically the secret
but instead of you living the secret or you having positive thinking or you
doing hyperstitial working it's every member of the audience doing
that towards this other goal great theory great theory
it's interesting to think that movies might not just be a form of entertainment
there could be i don't subscribe to the theory currently that there's a single
iluminati i believe that there's multiple groups
some name some unnamed that are vying for control
of the planet or large swaths of it i do believe there's people in power who are
trying to enact their goals over the whole population i absolutely believe
that i just don't think it's one faceless
organization and they're all connected because it just doesn't make sense
i believe there's this group here and this group there and this group there
and what if the war that's going on between those groups
used to involve spies and armies and assassins between these groups that
have existed for hundreds of years hidden from the general population
and the little wars they waged that eventually sometimes would flare up
into full-blown wars but then all those wars just kind of started to die down
the global wars ended really in the 1940s
and then the bush wars went on for a while but they
they got a little bit less than the 80s you had like south america flare up and
you but it was no longer this huge these huge conflicts
maybe they weren't needed anymore because we had world war one and we had
world war two but weaving its way through both of those was the
technology of film and radio and what if these groups
wised up and they thought you know what we don't need to fight this war with
guns or bombs anymore we can reshape reality itself
we can go in and make these movies and not just have a movie with a gay
character in it and then 20 years later people are fine with their neighbor
being gay i'm talking huge societal changes
massive some of them sure maybe dystopian future to them it would be good but to
us it would be dystopian other ones maybe a future that focused on
technology and the great things it can provide
maybe another group just wants a future where every man looks like matthew
mccanae and he always gets dumped within 10 days
these groups decided to stop fighting in the battlefields
and begin fighting on the silver screen
it's nothing you can predict it's nothing you can decode
there's no real secret message there
but it gives real meaning to the term the magic of the cinema
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address you can also hit
us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @jasonlcarpenter
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
you don't have to listen to it every day but i'm glad you listened to it today
have a great one guys