Today we take a look at the best and worst aspects of humanity.
First off, we meet a woman who has an encounter with a grey alien who's laying there helpless.
So what does she do? She takes him home and nurses him back to health.
And then we travel to the United Kingdom to meet a man whose reign of terror lasted almost 20 years.
A man who would sacrifice animals to Satan, put on a wig and a rubber mask,
and then adorn himself in nails so his victims felt pain even if they tried to escape.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are having lots of fun. Hope you guys had fun right before you listen to this episode.
Are having fun during it and have even more fun after it.
First off, let's give a shout out to one of our returning Patreons, Elkie.
Elkie, thank you so much for supporting the show, long time listener.
You're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode. If you can't support the Patreon,
you know what to do. Just help spread the word about the show. That helps the show grow.
That helps so, so much.
So Elkie, let's go ahead and hop in that Jason Jalopy. We're going to take a cross-country journey.
We are headed out to Douglas, Georgia. So go ahead, control all those. You know how to drive a car,
stick shift, steering wheel, things like that. There's also a little time travel button, Elkie.
Go ahead and hit that. We're going back to the year 1992. Elkie's driving us through the time
stream. We end up in Douglasville, Georgia. It's 2 a.m. in the morning. Our little car is driving
out in the middle of nowhere. We see a trailer kind of sitting on the outskirts of the outskirts
of town. It's very isolated out here. Driving nice and slowly. In this trailer is a woman.
We don't have her name, but we'll call her Nancy. She's sleeping with her husband. They're trying
to get some rest. But then she realizes there's a bright light outside of her trailer. So she
gets out of bed. Her husband's fast asleep and she walks outside. The noise changed because
she's closer, I guess, or I just forgot how I did the original noise. She sees out in this clearing.
That's where the light is emanating from. So she's like walking through stuff. She's like moving
corn stalks away. Apparently she's in the middle of a corn field because it's extra creepy. She gets
to the clearing and she sees a mushroom-shaped object hovering about 50 feet off the ground.
And she's like, "I know my mushrooms. They normally don't hover. They definitely don't emit
bright light." She begins walking towards this flying mushroom. I'm gonna say it doesn't give
the size, but I don't think it's the actual size of a little mushroom. I assume it's UFO size. So
let's say it's about 50 feet around. Pretty big, right? She's walking towards it and as she's getting
closer, she hears a voice telepathically go, "Turn around." There's a real creepy command, right?
No one ever tells you to turn around when something good's coming. It's always terrifying.
Burglars tell you to turn around. Axe murderers tell you to turn around. Just run in those cases.
But when an alien voice in your head tells you to turn around, nothing good's gonna happen, right?
You would think you turn around and the next thing you know, you'll get a holographic sack cloth
rubbed over your face with holographic, holographic chloroform on ya. She turns around though and
none of that stuff happens. She turns around and I don't know if she stepped over it the first time,
didn't really see it. She was so distracted by this giant UFO, mushroom UFO. Or if it teleported
there afterwards, I'm not for sure, but she turns around and laying on the ground. This is a little
great alien. He's just motionless. Just laying there and she's like, "What? I didn't see that.
I wouldn't have to turn around if I'd seen that first place." Little gray aliens in there.
She says he's about four feet tall, laying down technically. He's four feet long at this point,
but she also had an interesting observation. His fingertips were like little octopus, not like
what are those octopus arms called? Octopus arms? Tenderles? They were normal fingers, but at the
end of the finger were little suction cups. She thought that was kind of weird. And also the fact
that there's a four foot long gray alien laying in the grass. She's then given instructions from
the ship. She's looking at this little alien dude and the ship says, or whoever is in the ship says,
telepathically, "Take care of him. Keep him warm." So she says, "Yeah, okay. Okay, voices in my head.
I will do this." She picks up this little alien fella, takes the alien into her house, and her
first thing is to keep it warm, body heat, which makes sense, right? She tries waking up her husband,
her husband won't wake up. So this part is actually pretty invasive. This part's pretty messed up.
She puts the alien in bed next to her husband. Her husband's all spooning this alien. He's like,
"Oh, baby, you lost so much weight." He's saying in his sleep, "Oh, I love the feel of your skin.
It feels like plastic and your octopus suckers. He's having a great dream." He's like, "Oh,
you finally got that surgery I wanted." And she's like, "What are you talking about, weirdo?"
She puts the gray alien in bed next to her husband, and then she crawls into bed too. So they're like,
cuddling this alien, trying to keep him warm. Again, against the husband's knowledge,
she can't wake him up. That's pretty common in alien encounters. Like, only one person can wake up.
Obviously, a skeptic would go, "She's either dreaming or she's making it up." And she goes,
"Oh, yeah, my husband was asleep the whole time." But we'll dismiss those two because they poop
over the whole story. She's snuggling up with this alien, this gray alien, and her husband's
snuggling up with it too. He's like, "Oh, yeah, I love this little... I love what you've done with
your hair. I love how your bald and your head has gotten massive." And she's like, "Oh, my God,
he has some weird fetishes." But she realizes the alien doesn't seem to be getting any better.
He's just still just laying there, emotionless. So then she goes, "Okay, sandwiching him between
two homo sapiens didn't work. I know what I'll do." So she takes him out to the couch. Also,
probably her husband was probably burping and farting the whole time. She's like, "Oh, Gary,
you're a horrible representative of humanity." She takes him outside. The alien wakes up long
enough to be like, "Be you." And so she takes him out of the bedroom and puts him down on the couch.
And then she makes food. She takes some saltine crackers. She's crunching them up. She pours
in a little bit of warm water, which is gross, right? No one wants to eat that. No one wants to
eat that. But you figure, this is probably what you give a baby or you give someone. It's the least
toxic ingredient you could find. You wouldn't want to be like, "Yummy, yummy, yummy, strawberry milk,
made straight out of a cow's booby." And give it to someone who might be lactose intolerant.
Might not even seen a cow. Actually, they have. They've been abducting them for 100 years. But
you can't go wrong with crackers and water, right? So she's making this. And the alien's laying there.
And then she gets a little spoon and she holds it up to his mouth and he goes, "Mmm."
He eats some of it. So she's like, "Huck rock, goodbye alien. In your spaceship.
Don't know the rest of the words." And she's just feeding the alien this stuff. And then she says she
loses time. She's feeding the alien the saltine and water. And the next thing she knows,
she's standing outside in front of this object again. And the alien is now standing up.
He's standing underneath the ship and this beam comes down and he goes,
gets teleported into the ship. She's like, "You didn't say thank you for all those crackers.
You didn't even pay me the money, man. You know, that was what I'm supposed to put in my soup tomorrow."
But she doesn't say that. She looks over and she sees five other great aliens. And she said,
they were lined up in military style. So like shoulder to shoulder, I guess. And they all just
stood there staring at her. She's looking at them and she's like, "Well, I could go buy more crackers
if you want." But and she said the aliens would turn and then one by one walk into the beam of light
and get teleported back up into the ship. The next one to walk up. And then after the fifth one had
been sucked up into the ship, she said the ship disappeared with the sound of a thunder crack.
C-CRAP!
She's like, "What's up with the thunder crack? What's that? I didn't sound like thunder crack.
Sounded like some guy like playing NBA Jam or something like that. What was that? Boom shaka
lock out the ship takes off." And so that's the end of that story. I think it's a interesting story
because you have, this is one of the stories that you can really put yourself into the place of the
person. Like some of the stories people get abducted and they're like strapped down and aliens
putting needles in their brain and they're so extreme. Like you would think what you would do
in that story but most of them come down to, you really don't have much choice, right? The aliens
have teleported you aboard their ship. You're in a cage. Oh, let me out. Let me out. The cage next
to you contains a bear. The cage to the left is some hysterical person. Your options are pretty
limited. You can stay in the cage or they take you out of the cage and they run experiments on you.
This is a story where the person has a lot of options and I think it's such a uplifting story.
I think this is what would happen in most cases. We covered a story a couple weeks back about the
lumberjacks who came across an alien who was dying in the river and he's like, "Don't touch me. Here's
my, here's how we do our final rites and stuff like that." The lumberjack was just kind of listening
to him trying to console him. I think those stories are how a lot of, if we weren't in an
abduction scenario, I think most, yesterday we even talked about a woman who gave an alien an
exorcism. I think in the most case, humans are very benevolent. I think that we do tend to do
terrible things, but in a vacuum, I think humans tend to do the right thing. I think if an alien
came to you asking for help, I think one, if a normal human came to you asking for help and you
didn't think it was some sort of scam or setup, you would help them. If you honestly believed
that they needed help and you didn't think that they were trying to rip you off, you would help them.
And I think an alien, obviously, he's not like, "Hey, are you going to have some money?"
You're like, "Are you going to spend it on space drugs?" He's like, "Uhhh." And the next thing you
know you're abducted, you're being turned into space drugs. If an alien is just laying there and
he's like, "Uhhh, I'm super cold and I need help. I've been wounded." I think most people would
take care of it. In a vacuum, obviously, if you're a professional alien hunter or if you need some
new alien skin boots, you might chop the dude up. But actually, now that I say that, we've covered
a ton of stories where aliens seem to be able to know who to appear in front of. So if you're
never seen an alien, it's because they're choosing not to be seen by you. Even if you haven't seen a
UFO, they're choosing not to be seen by you. It's supposed to a ghost, which simply just manifests
in an area. Aliens seem to be a little more picky, so they may have been flying around Douglasville
and this alien's like, "I'm not going to make it, dude." They're like, "No, no, we're going to fly to
TaiPet. We know this guy out there. He's totally going to be good at it. He's all, "Blehhhhh." He's
like, "I'm not going to make it, man. Just pick someone. Just pick someone." Finally, they were able
to psychically select this woman who they knew would mother this alien rather than smother this alien.
This was the only two choices, right? Elkie, let's go ahead and hob in that carboner copter. We're
going to wave goodbye to Nancy. I noticed Elkie has a new pair of alien skin boots. I'm like, "Elkie."
We're getting in that carboner copter. Elkie, take us out of Douglasville, Georgia. We're headed
out to the United Kingdom. I'm going to warn you guys as he's taking this flight. This is one of
those stories that's a little dark. It's a little depressing, so if you've been having a great day,
you might not want to listen to it. It's not uber dark, but it's pretty intense. So if that's not
your cup of tea, I'll see you tomorrow. If it is, if you're some sort of weirdo who likes reading
and hearing about this stuff, stay on board the carboner copter. Elkie's like, "I don't have a
choice." I was like, "No." Carboner copter is headed out to Groville. That sounds like a place
from Sesame Street, but it's a real place, apparently. Groville, that's on the island of Jersey
in the United Kingdom. It's 1957. Carboner copter is going to land in Groville. And as we're walking
into town, we see an orphanage. There's a woman. She's waving to all the kids. She's like, "Where
are we going? We're orphans." She's like, "Oh yeah, come back. Come back." They're like, "Oh."
I'm sure they go to school. I'm sure eventually the orphanage is like a prison
where you just have to watch Annie 24/7. You're like, "Oh, this is the real torture." I think,
you know, you go out to go to school and stuff like that. But anyways, she's like hanging out
with all these kids and stuff like that. We're walking by the orphanage and we see a bunch of
kids having fun. We see the woman who runs it and then we see her husband, Edward Paisnell.
He's 35 years old and he's building a little room on the side of the orphanage. Because he's a
construction worker. This is the sound of a hammer. Now, both of them are pillars of the community.
She's super well known. She's a great surrogate mother to all of these children and he is just
known as being a great guy, all-around great guy. He needed something built. He was there. If you
provided you had money, he doesn't run a charity. His wife runs a charity. And when he's not out
doing construction work, he's just someone you kind of want to hang out with. Both of these people
were examples for how people should act. He actually, every year, played Santa Claus in town.
That was his reputation. But it was a false reputation. At the house, he had his own private
room. There's a place that no one was supposed to go. And that wouldn't re... To me, that would be
very suspicious. But I guess that's a thing. Sometimes men have like... I get that men have
like the man cave and they have like stuff in their houses. They'll have their den. But it's
never like, "Don't go in there!" It's like your wife goes in to like ring you a magazine. What are
you doing here? Like, I've been in houses with dens. I don't think my family ever had it. My dad
had like a workspace because again he was a minister. But like, we'd go in there and make
photocopies and stuff like that. He wouldn't be like, "What are you doing?" He's like,
crawling on the ceiling. His head spins around. "Get out!" It was just a place that he went to work,
but it wasn't off limits. This dude, Edward, has a room that was off limits to everybody.
And he would go into this room sometime just to work. You know, he's a handyman. He's going to
go in there. He's just going to try out those new nails he's heard so much about. These nails have
points on both end. So he goes in there and there's this red curtain against the wall.
But he ignores that for now. It's not time to unveil the red curtain. He opens up a box
and inside it is a rubber mask. He pulls it over his face.
[gurgling]
There's a blonde woman's wig that he is now wearing as well. He goes to his closet
and there sits a heavy trench coat. It's studded with nails. He puts on his cuffs
that have nails sticking out of them as well. Then he turns to the red curtain, throws it back.
It's his altar to Satan. At that point, I guess this episode's darker than I remember it, at that
point, there's a cage rattling in the corner of his dark private room. An animal he had caught
days before. A rabbit, a cat, a lost puppy. He reaches in to the cage and pulls the animal out
and sacrifices it on the altar. That's just the beginning of his night.
His reign of terror started back in 1957 and what he would do is late at night when he'd see a
young woman standing at a bus stop waiting for a ride. He'd sneak up behind her and throw a noose
over her neck and pull it tight. There's no fighting back from that. There really isn't.
He would then lead them like cattle off into the outskirts of town and sexually assault them.
Even if you could somehow struggle against the noose around your neck, I mean that would
cause such a shock to your system. Even if you're somehow able to maintain your sanity
and fight against the noose around your neck, he was studded with nails. Every time you pushed
against him, every time he pushed against you, you would be poked, you would be scratched,
you would be pierced. His entire body was a weapon. But like we see with all of these sickos,
he doesn't end there. They can go back and they can always say this peeping Tom, the reason why
they're so hard on peeping Tom's and people who expose themselves in public, some people go, "Hey,
I was just peeing and now I'm a registered sex offender." The reason why the law is so harsh on
them is, one, it's gross, but two, a lot of times it leads to other actions. The peeping Tom isn't
satisfied with just looking in the windows of coeds while he was in college for four years.
It escalates. He starts off by doing this. He's attacking women at bus stops. And these are women
who are 19, 20 years old, old enough to be standing outside waiting for a bus late at night, getting
off work, leaving a friend's house, something like that. This guy's derangement, that's not enough.
He needs to make sure no woman in the city is safe. Anywhere. He would begin to stake out houses
during the day, which would be very easy for a construction worker. It's one of the few jobs.
Electrician is one that you can do this. Obviously, like police, you could do this super easily, but
as far as civilian jobs, construction workers, electricians, plumbers, they give you access to
houses. But also, if you see a carpenter, if you see a construction worker, if you see an electrician
working on something for a prolonged period of time, it's not even going to ring a bell. If you
saw a garbage man outside your house for five hours, that would be kind of weird. But if you saw
an electrician poking around your neighbor's house, he gets hired to work in your neighbor's house,
he'd seem to walk in back and forth between his van. You're not really going to think anything of it.
He will be able to stake out your house, and you really wouldn't even think about it.
He begins to watch houses. He begins to keep track of the houses that have young girls.
He begins to keep track of what rooms these young girls sleep in. So in the middle of the night,
in the place where you should feel the safest, Edward would crawl into these young girls' windows,
wearing a rubber mask, a blonde wig, and an outfit covered with nails.
There was 13 no-one attacks that he committed, combined with the bus stops and the house invasions.
This went on from 1957 was his first attack. It wasn't until July 10th, 1971,
that he was finally caught. Police were obviously looking for this guy, but they had no description
of him. You could probably get a height description. His costume, his uniform, served two purposes. One,
it completely concealed his identity. Secondly, it was terrifying. And I can almost imagine at
first, when he was first attacking the adult women, I'm sure the first one or two, the police
probably didn't even believe it was true. It's so insane. But it was true. July 10th,
1971, Edward is driving down the road and there's an officer who sees him commit some sort of routine
traffic violation. Just making a turn without turn signal, not having a tail light. It was
something super routine that should have just been, "Here, Edward, pillar of the community,
Santa Claus every year. Here is your ticket. You're free to go." That would have been the end of it,
but Edward had something in his car that would elicit more questions. So when this cop turns
on his siren, Edward hits the gas and a high-speed chase ensues. At this point, the police are like,
"I don't care if it's a bus or tail light or not. You're out running us. We're bringing in everyone
to get you." So they finally are able to get this guy to pull over and lo and behold, in his car,
is a trench coat with nails sticking out of it, a rubber mask and a blonde wig. There's actually
photos of this and it is as terrifying as you would imagine it. You can look in the show notes
and see photos of this. Now the police obviously had been looking for this guy for, again, almost 20
years. They'd attacked 13 different people. Edward, okay, there's routine traffic stop.
You're speeding away. We thought that was suspicious, but what is that doing in your car?
Why do you have this outfit now? He goes, "Oh, that? What? That? Oh, sorry, officer. I'm just on my way
to an orgy." It was his actual excuse. And here's a little tip, not to help out future criminals,
but if you get busted, don't name something else gross, right, as your alibi. I mean, I guess,
I always had a rule. Like, if I wanted to call in sick to work, I'd always tell him I had diarrhea,
because no one wants any follow-up questions to that. You just go, "I have diarrhea," and they just
totally let you go. I guess that's the equivalent. The difference was that I was calling in to work.
I wasn't trying to outrun the police. I don't think the cops are going to be like, "Oh, diarrhea.
You're free to go." So they bust this guy. They take the suit and they search his house,
and they find the altar. And they're like, "They don't really need any other evidence at this point."
I think the cops are really just like, "We want to know why he was doing this stuff. We don't really
buy his orgy theory. We know all the good orgies in town, and there wasn't one that night."
They find the altar. They find the remains of these animals. They start questioning the wife,
and they're like, "Why would he be going out and doing this stuff?" And she said, "We never had sex.
Like, we'd been married, but it was in name only. We have never, ever had sex."
So the cops are like, "Okay, well then, yeah, he didn't do this because he didn't have sex.
It's not her fault." But it shows that he couldn't be intimate in a way that wasn't ultra violent.
And if he had done that to his wife, his ruse would have been exposed.
He gets sentenced to 30 years in prison. So good job. I always complain about the
justice system in England, in the United Kingdom, because they're constantly letting people go all
the time. Oh, wait. He only served 10 years. Sorry. And he did serve 10 years, and he moved back to
that town. He goes, "Hey, everyone, remember me? Edward, pillar of the community. I'm out now."
That's nothing for 13 attacks over the course of 20 years. He serves 10. He got good behavior.
England's really good about just letting people go because they're nice in prison. They're like,
"Well, you didn't kill anyone in prison where there's guards everywhere, and everyone's your
physical equal. You did good here. Let's put you back out in society, dude." So anyways,
he's walking around. He was eventually, he was very quickly run out of that city. The people
in town did not want him there. He ended up dying three years later. He lived, they didn't let him
live there. He moved to the Isle of Wight. So maybe they have a lower, maybe they have a lower
threshold for sickos, or they just didn't get the newspaper. That's the story of Edward, or it would
be, because those are the 13 known attacks that he had. In 2008, they were doing renovations at the
orphanage where him and his wife lived. And while they were doing renovations, they found a child's
skull buried there. There was actually reports of several missing children in the area, but they
were never solved. And over a 20-year time span, especially if the children who went missing were
orphans, cases just slowly went cold. This man who got caught for 13 brutal assaults, did 10 years in
prison and returned home, may have actually also been a murderer. And it wouldn't really surprise
any of us, right? A man with that much darkness in his heart. He's sacrificing live animals.
He's breeding fear in a community, snatching women from bus stops, breaking into young girls' homes.
That would all just be a prelude to the act of taking a child's life. Darkness never stops.
It is never satiated. It will always push you to get darker and darker and darker until you exist
in a world that is so black you never knew you could be somewhere so devoid of light. A place
few humans could even imagine. And even when you stand on that precipice, you still want more. Evil
is never satisfied.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadravoradio. Twitter is @deadravoradio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]