put down that bowl of stewed tomatoes because today we're gonna take a look at
a Chinese artist who did whatever it took to make a point or so I don't even
know what the point of his thing was but he did something super gross and then
we travel to the bedroom of a young boy who's trying to catch some peaceful
sleep instead he finds himself thrust into a world of the afterlife where
nothing is as it seems today on Dead Rabbit Radio
hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I'm your
host Jason Carpenter or I'm having a great day I hope you guys are having a great day too
I hope you guys have already eaten because if you are eating while listening
to this episode Godspeed to you I would not recommend it but one thing that I
would recommend is coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now they're eating a
big bowl of stew mmm this is extra chunky it's Nigel King everyone give a round of
applause to Nigel King he's walking in with stew he made it for all of us but
he's the only one eating it Nigel you're gonna be our captain our pilot this
episode if you guys can't support the patreon I totally understand just help
spread the word about the show really really helps out a lot now Nigel I hope
you brought some cornbread because I will eat that cornbread's always delicious
a little bit of butter a little bit of jelly this isn't a cooking podcast this
is a paranormal podcast that often just becomes grossed gross stories podcast so
Nigel I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durchable we're
leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command we are floating all the way out to China so in
China there is a little restaurant actually sorry about to get a lot of
trouble actually we could get about to get in a lot of trouble with various
governments over the world we're actually starting off the story by heading to
Taiwan
Durchable kind of turns a little bit right we're headed to Taiwan in Taiwan in
Chaiye City in Taiwan there's a little restaurant and we walk into the
restaurant ding ding ding little door little doorbell and we sit down at the
tables and the cook comes up to us and he goes I know what you guys are here for
you guys are here for the special you guys look like a bunch of disgusting
human beings you guys are here for the most special food I have and he goes to
orders of yin yang fish that was the sound that was the sound of a couple
people shutting off the podcast because they know exactly where this one's going
the yin yang fish it's this real delicacy and this is how you perform it so
now we're back in the kitchen we're watching him cook this and he goes and
he reaches into a big bucket of water and he pulls out a fish like a carp like a
big old fish right and it's like breathing if it's not breathing that's
the thing it's a fish he pulls it out of the water it's trying to breathe but it
can't it's just breathing in oxygen and so then he goes guys you guys are gonna
love you guys you guys are sick you guys are sick individuals right you guys
are gonna love this he then takes the yin yang fish and he starts to scale it
descale it while it's still alive and we're like looking at each other like
oh it's kind of messed up like does that hurt he's like oh fish I don't know does
anything hurt does anything hurt he has no nerve any since he was born without
the ability to feel pain he starts descaling himself he's like look it I'm
not feeling anything he's bleeding all over the kitchen we're like oh he
descales the fish while it's still alive and he's like and then he takes out
like a filet knife and we're like oh no and he starts to gut the fish while it's
still alive and we're just looking at his little mouth going ah mama then he
takes the fish and he holds it up by its head and he dips it into boiling oil
all the way up to its head and it pulls it out this guy has now been completely
burned but you can still eat it if you still have an appetite and the yin yang
fish also known as the dead or alive fish is served to you and it's been
cooked alive gutted alive descaled alive and while you're eating it its head is
looking at you and its mouth is moving there's videos of this which I'm
unfortunate enough that I was reading the article but then I was like well I
gotta see I gotta see a video of this and sure enough it's exactly how I
described it so let me describe it to you again in graphic detail I'm gonna
watch the video and talk along with it so here's the thing so this video came
out and it went viral and people were really really upset the fact that you
were eating this fish while it was still alive which I don't know what's more
horrific being cooked alive or being cooked half alive and then like you're
sitting there you're like remember that old Tom Petty music video this video
terrified me as a kid that old Tom Petty video where Alice in Wonderland is
trying to run away from Tom Petty and then he turns her into a cake and then
they eat her that I that movie that oh my god that terrified me as a kid but
anyways and she's looking she's like no no they're eating me no I need my thighs
what would be worse to be cooked alive or to be cooked just enough that you can
watch yourself be eaten I guess actually that's not even the one where you're
watching yourself be eaten is the worst but these people are eating this fish and
he's like looking at them imagine I don't know why he tried to put you into this
hellish position but someone takes a spoonful of you and then you see the
spoonful of you move past your eyes into someone's mouth that's what I'm trying
to get at that's what this fish is seeing absolutely despicable now the chef
says listen he's saying this from behind bars they get ready to execute him no
no he actually had a little bit of blowback from this but apparently they
still sell it he goes listen you idiots you guys are morons the fish is
obviously dead the fish died when I removed its guts right it died it
suffocated from not being able to breathe what you're seeing is simply the
synapses what you're seeing is the nerve endings you see it's just simulating
that it's an undying agony it's actually been dead for a while that's his
defense now again imagine you were corpse I was joking imagine you were a corpse
and someone is pretending you were alive we did that episode a long time ago I
don't even remember what it was where people were putting soy sauce in the
octopus brains and would make the octopus dance around on your plate and I
thought what if you could put a soy sauce helmet on a captured soldier and
you'd turn him into a zombie and have him run across the battlefield like what
a psychological weapon that would be it would be super convainting you have the
special forces they're bringing along all their gear and then they also have this
giant industrial sized soy sauce packet they're like trying to tear the tip off
and just squeeze into some dude's brain but what it work the point is is like
whether or not the fish is alive the fish the fish it looks like it's an
agony it's a horrible all around so I read about this yin-yang fish and it's
just gross and there's a video of people eating it and it's looking at him and
maybe he's still alive maybe he's not but then that led me to look at more
disgusting stuff so now we're headed to mainland China so hop back in this
dead rabbit dirgeable we're going to Beijing to meet a man known as Zhu Yu in
the 90s he became super popular and you know like there's different types of
art schools like there's like hi I'm a cubist so like I draw pictures and
everyone looks like Minecraft or I'm like gothic so it's like I make pillars
and hide-and-sme-clothes and like gothic art everything super spooky in the
candles or like you just walk around candles through spooky houses and then
there's like modern art which is like here's some dust you walk into the
exhibit they just throw dust in your eyes that'll be $500 please that's art
you have all these different schools of arts Picasso did something I think he
was like cube cube I think he was a cubist as well I did take an art history
class in college technically I took a heart is art history class I never went
though it's super boring there weren't enough hot girls in the class to keep me
interested but anyways so all of that has led up to that monologue there's
different types of art but there is a school of art known as the cadaver school
and that is where your milieu your genre of art is body part stuff there's
enough of these people that they have their own school it's not like Hogwarts
it's not like there's like a physical school you can go to or is there but you
go to a mortuary and you walk in between the fourth and fifth body and then you
end up in the cadaver school it's enough artists worldwide that they use that as
their template they use that as their canvas the blood is my paint in the
sin you'd flesh is where I put stuff it's not just one sicko there's enough of
these lunatics out there that they formed their own school and so Zhu Yu in
China is one of these guys and he had here let's look at some of his art
because I've learned from doing the show that I love going through performance
art I would never attend one in real life I think it's super boring but I love
reading about them because they're super lame so anyways here's this guy he'd
made a art one of his art pieces was called skin graft where he had skin
cut from himself and put on a giant flank a giant cut of pork he could chase
this awesome you're telling me I can go to an art show and watch a man get his
skin cut off no I don't think so I think he just brought the most interesting
part is him screaming in agony he's like this is all for the cadaver school as
he's cutting out this piece of skin no he just shows up with a big piece of
pork and goes that's my skin on there that's super lame dude then he has this
thing this is better this is better I might go to this one go to this one just
to pull pranks he had a thing called pocket theology in 1999 he had got this
room and he had a long coiling rope pretty much covering every inch of the
floor so there's just a rope everywhere and then the rope is hanging so it's like
all this rope on the ground and then the rope is hanging from a severed arm a
severed human arm is holding onto this rope and the arm is stuck on a meat hook
that's hanging from the ceiling so it's this decayed rotting arm holding this
rope and the art exhibit is you have to walk over the rope as the viewer it's
like in the middle of this museum so basically you're walking you get to
this room and the only way to continue on to the dinosaur exhibit the only way
to get to the gift shop you have to walk over this rope now and when I first
read that I got laughing to the thought of this smelly human arm hanging I
thought that would be creepy because you're not just walking over any rope
you're basically walking over an extension of this rotting arm it's an
interesting trick it was just a rope on the ground some other lesser lame or
artist out there right would be like oh this is called rope it's called the
tangled of the masses pay me ten thousand dollars and I'll throw this rope in
your museum like I don't have a lot of appreciation for modern art and it's so
funny because I happen to run in circles of people who've loved this type of
garbage and it's just a miracle of sociology that I can get along a lot of
my friends would be like oh my god tangled of the masses is coming to
Portland I can't wait anyways it doesn't involve body parts or
Optimus Prime I am not there so zoo you also have this this is what he's most
famous for and if you didn't shut off when I said ying ying fish I'm sure a
lot of people shut off when I said zoo you this is what he's most famous for in
the East Link gallery back in 2000 in Shanghai China there's this art
exposition it's supposed to be all of this like outsider art like really in
your face art at the East Link gallery in 2000 and zoo you shows up with a set of
photographs but what the photographs were were disgusting and really I think
disgusting is probably underselling it zoo you have this exhibit it was called
eating people and what he did a lot of people have tried disputing this but he
has never disputed it people have tried changing and saying oh no no he later in
life he said that it wasn't true I could find no record that he ever denied this
snopes ran a big article about saying oh no no it's not true it's not true he
has never denied it and even in the snopes article they were saying well
well what he did might have been true but we think it was this like people have
been going out of their way to dispute something that he has never denied doing
eating people is zoo you it's a series of photographs of him sitting there
eating a six-month-old human fetus these photos went viral and what it became was
this thing and you might have seen these photos back in the early 2000s they were
saying this huge thing like look at what they're eating in China they're eating
babies here's a photo of just a normal Chinese guy sitting down for a delicious
breakfast and so people were debunking that and that's where snopes came in and
they're like normal Chinese people are not eating babies this is a photo that's
attributed to a performance artist and snopes goes on to say we don't even
believe he's eating the baby we think they took a duck and put a doll's head on
it I don't know much about human anatomy but I know it doesn't look a lot like duck
anatomy anyways he does not deny it he came out and said there's nothing wrong
with cannibalism and he's he puts it out like this there's another wrong with
cannibalism as long as it can be done in a way with that does not end in a crime
being committed so if someone is willingly giving their body in his mind I
think it's disgusting right I'm not giving him any wiggle room but he's
saying as long as you can not commit a crime while committing cannibalism is
there anything wrong with cannibalism he said that he said it's not forbidden by
any laws or religion which I'm pretty here's the thing I don't know if that's
true it may is it against a lot of eat people I know they have things like
abuse of a corpse is a law so you and they could classify cannibalism of that
if you someone dies of natural means but then you turn them into a marionette
puppet that's a crime right if you eat them and there there's no survival
situation that would be a crime as well I don't know honestly if in the Bible
they talk about cannibalism and it's weird because they were constantly
starving to death back then I think people were eating each other I do
remember reading books about ancient warfare ancient Hebrew warfare is real
Israeli warfare and there would be sieges and people would eat each other
back then but I don't know if in the Bible it specifically says don't eat
people what's so bizarre is he views his artwork as a protest he's protesting
people he's protesting people who don't like cannibalism so he's basically
protesting everyone here I'll tell you exactly what happened with this dude so
you exactly what happened to this dude he says he he almost threw up a couple
times all he's getting ready to eat this baby but he finally was able to eat it
and he's never denied it nowadays he's like painting pebbles and rocks and he's
doing like art art he's doing Jason art he's doing art and Jason would consider
art I think he just wanted some attention I think there is my two scenarios
here's my three scenarios one he's a groundbreaking artist who would stop at
nothing no matter what taboos were in front of him could have been doing that
to he could just have been an attention seeker I think that a lot of
performance artists are comedians who stand up comedians who have stage fright
so they just do wacky stuff and they do stuff out of the sight of others and
take photographs and things like that of it or this was some sicko sex thing as
well right we can't discount that he's just always wanted to eat somebody when
he was a young kid he saw that movie alive about the Brazilian soccer players
crashing into the mountain and he's like that's me I want to do that someday in
his entire life he was going to enter any job possible that would allow him to eat
people first off he tried playing soccer that didn't pan out and then he tried
becoming like an adventurer hoping he'd get stranded with a bunch of people in
a cave and then maybe eat them but people got a little worried because he never
brought like survival gear he just brought a fork and knife everywhere and
then he goes you know what I'll do I'll just be a performance artist then I'll
eat a baby like okay that last one might be the most convoluted of the three he
probably sees himself as the taboo breaking artist but I so weird and
gross right eating the baby eating the baby if it's a little more intense than
just listening to an M&M song so when you're talking about art and pushing
buttons that just seems too much I have since we're here no let's go on to the
next segment let's go ahead hop in that dead rabbit durable let's head to London
England because I'll cover this guy as well he's another performance artist he
actually beat out a zoo you by a couple years he'd been doing this stuff before
his name is Rick Gibson and he back in 1984 made a set of earrings that don't
tell me I don't know why all this stuff I really don't know why I found all this
stuff in the same two or three days the Google algorithm must be doing my job
for me or it just must be possessed by MOLOC Rick Gibson decided to start wearing
these earrings I don't know if he wore him around town I don't know I might for
all I know he made him and took a photograph of him and show that the
museum it was matching earrings and each one was a 10-week-old fetus so it's
like hey he's dancing he's like hey ladies what's going on they're like oh
my god it's the most disgusting thing ever so then he's like I shouldn't wear
these out to pick up women or women who do go home with them that's just wrong
right they're like oh I really love your earrings in that then he had this weird
down slide he had this weird down slide he did that that's a big show stuff right
like how do you where do you go from wearing fetus earrings in 1986 he stood
in front of government buildings in England holding a rat he had this rat
and he would hold it up in front of the doors because get it like government
officials are rats oh that's lame dude I'm not saying I'm not saying go harder into
the fetus stuff but what a come down he's holding up the rat get it they're
rats but then he came back he came back swinging hard July 23rd 1988 he's in
London everyone's like oh great he's doing the rat thing again boring he's like
oh no I need something super crazy he cannibalism he goes the cannibalism
route he's eating a canape you know what a canape is I didn't it's a crack it's a
cheese and cracker right it's that's what we would just call it hey can I have
some cheese and crackers but I guess I guess if you want to spend $50 on a
cracker after you've gone seen the tangle of the masses you take a cracker you put
some cheese on it maybe like a tomato or some basil or something like that he is
standing in the middle of London and he has one of those and he's like doodododo
and he puts on top of it this is so gross this to me is grosser than the fetus
because I can't really comprehend that right like I have seen pictures of fetus
I've seen the photos of this guy eating the fetus the zoo you guy but it's all
alien it's an abstract thought to me I've never held a baby I've seen them from
afar they terrify me what I do know I do know a lot about because I'm constantly
looking at my throat because I always have sore throats is tonsils so this
dude has this cracker and on top of it he has human tonsils and he eats it now
that's hard that's relatable no one likes tonsils right there everywhere
they're constantly coming out of mouths you can eat that I would have been I
would have been Bravo Bravo then he had to updo that right you your performance
artist you're an artist you have to keep doing better and better April 15th a
year later 1989 this time he shows up and the police are ready for him because
the fetus earings were gross but it's like 1984 and people are like what
huh it's just super bizarre and then the rat thing was so lame but now he's just
ate some human tonsils the previous year it was this huge uproar the police
are looking for this guy they're looking for him he's like constantly hanging
outside a dentist office he's like more delicious tonsils this time he shows up
and he eats so he has two of these to eat he has two of this segment is going
on way too long but I'm getting way too much enjoyment he has two of these to
eat so start thinking about body parts that you can eat two of and you can put
in your pocket we'll say so it's not feet which have really big pockets he
sits there and he has two of these and he eats the first one and people are just
sickened they're outraged what it's so gross and the police move in and they
arrest this guy and during the scuffle he drops the second one and rolling around
the truth story rolling around in the streets of London falls out of his hand
a human testicle so it ain't the first one no problem you can always eat at
least one testicle no one can stop that first swallow but when they saw him go
oh and then they saw him reach into his pocket to pull out the other milky white
I imagine they're like giant wall I imagine it's like oh if you took a wall
nut and dipped it in milk maybe white paint maybe for a little more viscosity
but they have this we have this walnut size thing and it's rolling around the
ground and I can just imagine as the cops are cuffing him he's like no lefty
no he's watching this left testicle kind of roll down the streets getting close
to the sewer will it fall in no it doesn't actually apparently one of his
supporters can you believe this guy has fans one of his supporters must have
scooped up the testicle good old lefty because this dude I don't remember his
name it's too busy talking about what he's eating Rick Gibson gets taken gets
arrested gets taken to jail gets released right with not a big deal the judge goes
there's really not a crime against eating human testicles we're assuming
it's from a willing donor and then a year later he shows up that exact same
spot he has that other testicle all he eats that one as well what's worse
what's really worth eating a human testicle or eating a testicle that's
been sitting out for a year right that's discovered makes it even worse I
don't think he was just sitting in his cupboard next to his top rom and it's
like slowly getting moldy and it's like getting harder and harder he's like oh
now really is like a walnut yes he's a nutcracker to get to the juicy goodness I
don't know I don't I'm so he put it in the fridge then you got to worry like
did he get freezer burn did it ruin the flavor did he really get the full
flavor of the testicle a year later Nigel let's go ahead and toss you the
keys to the carbonicopter we are leaving behind all of this madness in London we
are headed all the way out to a tiny little house in the middle of the
suburbs to the story online very very interesting story with really bizarre
implications let's kind of dig into this real quick here there's this young boy
young 12 year old boy let's call him Robbie Robbie has a best friend named
Devin who's about to turn 10 years old but shortly before Devin's 10th birthday
he's killed in a car accident little Devin little nine-year-old Devin is
walking down the street there's a driver has a seizure she loses control of the
car it jumps the curb and runs him over now Robbie didn't know that this had
happened the day that it all took place he wasn't there and his parents didn't
know how to tell him like this is the first real loss as a child is losing
one of your friends like that they didn't know what to do so they actually
asked his aunt hey would you mind taking Robbie for a couple days we need to get
some stuff settled here yeah yeah sure of course and that day when he gets home
from school he actually packs up and goes to stay at his aunt's house for a
couple days he has no idea what's happened to Devin and that night that
very first night after Devin had passed away Robbie has a dream he dreams he's
in a department store like a JC Penney's so you got the linoleum floors that give
you a guided pathway through the store and then the carpeted areas where all of
the fixtures are at you have racks and racks of clothes the perfume counter
those pillars that kind of dot the landscape and then you have the clothes
on the circular racks you'd always see a sea of those as well you would just sit
there and you kind of flip through the clothes like you're looking through a
magazine page by page and they'd be on these circular racks and these racks if
you've ever been in a malls which I kind of have to say because not everyone
gets the opportunity to go in a malls or department stores anymore that they
exist less and less but there was all I mean shopping is super boring rather go
see performance art and go shopping but I was always dragged going shopping with
my mom standing there and those circular racks were always creepy to me
because they were child height and you never saw was on the other side of them
now it was kind of that mixed bag like sometimes we like to hide in them it was
funny for us to go in there as children and be like who wonder where I'm at play
hide-and-seek and in a crowded department store we did that back in the day but
it's also creepy because they're the perfect size for a kid to get lost in
their perfect size for a kid to get pulled into who knows what's in there
so there's this weird fascination I think that you have with those circular
racks in this dream Robbie is seeing these circular racks and out of one of
the racks Devin pops out sticks a little head out of the rack of clothes
Robbie goes hey Devin what's going on hey how's it going and Devin snuck back
into the rack what Robbie's looking here and he's looking in this department
store and people are just kind of shuffling around shopping and he sees
Devin poke his head out of another rack of clothes just kind of looking at Robbie
Devin what's going on hey man how's it going we play hide-and-go-seek who's it
I'm assuming I am since you're the one he ducked back into the rack of clothes and
so Robbie begins to walk through the department store and every time he gets
to a circular rack he sees Devin's head pop out of it but as he gets closer
Devin disappears back into the circular rack and appears at a farther off one so
no matter how far Robbie's moving through the store he's always not able to
catch up to Devin and this happens Devin keeps getting farther and farther away
in these racks of clothes he's popping out farther and farther away and then for
the first time in this dream Devin speaks he says I have to go
Robbie wakes up later later that week Robbie is told that Devin had passed
away Devin was killed in that accident and so that dream kind of sat on Robbie
was obviously a difficult dream and when he found out that that was the night
that Devin had died made it even more impactful six months after this whole
thing he's visiting Devin's house for the first time since the accident he went
there and he's talking to the stepmom and he's talking to Devin siblings and
they're just kind of reminiscing and when I'll detail this whole thing that
Robbie was saying was so weird was that the stepmom Devin stepmom showed him a
little container full of teeth and she said I got these from the accident scene
when Devin got hit by the car and knocked out some of his teeth I saved
him she's holding out this little container for Robbie to see so just an
odd a detail to it a grief you know the grieving process so Robbie was really
creeped out by that but he was even more creeped out by the fact that he's
talking to the stepmom and the stepmom goes you want you want to know the
weirdest thing about all of this I'm you know other than the teeth I'm collecting
I had a dream about Devin after he died I had a dream I was in this big
department store you know normal typical department store the clothing on those
circular racks and I'm standing in this department store and Devin popped out of
one of the racks and no matter how close I got to him he was always just out of
reach
it's an interesting creepy story it makes you wonder about what the natures of
dreams are are they a way for spirits to communicate with us what's really going
on the fact that he didn't know that that's pretty standard in ghost lore and
dream lore people having no news of an event that has happened and then in
their dream being alerted to someone who had died earlier that day a long time
listener of the show Beatrice sent me in a story that's very similar to this about
her grandmother who passed away came to her in a dream and she wasn't aware that
the grandmother had died in the sleep so and it's very standard for good thanks
for sharing the story Beatrice as well it's very standard for ghost lore stuff
so a standard interesting ghost story it correlates with the lore the things that
we know about ghosts what when I was reading this story though what I was
thinking was like we all got the imagery right when I described it you could
almost you can imagine the lighting the right lighting for this JC pennies you
can imagine exactly how it's laid out here's my question I've been thinking
about this a lot kid poking his head out from the turnstile of the clothing the
rolling racks that's creepy right no one liked being around those things because
they were creepy you would always think someone would get out and get you I told
the story about Beatrice's grandmother who came back to say it's okay honey I
love you after the grandmother had passed away and Beatrice didn't know
about that I left out the part where Beatrice's grandma is floating is like
floating down the hallway here's my question do ghosts know they're being
creepy do ghosts understand because he used to be alive they should be fully
aware that floating floating down the hallway doing inhuman things is going
to scare us appearing to us late at night popping out of the turnstiles of
clothing just until your friend gets a little bit closer and then you disappear
and then do it out another one not only is that terrifying you're kind of a
jerk do ghosts understand they're being creepy now sure we could say the
malevolent ghosts the demons things like that that's their goal what about the
time so little little little Robbie I think his name was recording this way
recording this hours later the original ending went on for a long time and it
wasn't that good this is my second take what do we call I think it was Robbie or
is that that's the kid from the first story from Mexico he's like hey for
yesterday's episode is the factory still haunted anyways the point is is that
imagine imagine you were the narrator of that story and how distraught you you
don't even know your friends dead yet and how to start you would feel you know
something's off and you're trying to just say hi you're being led in your dream
and he gets disappearing why would Devon's ghost choose to do that twice he
did it to his stepmom too he's like that was so funny what I did that other kid I
totally forgot his name that lame oh he's still alive I don't even remember who
he is I had so much fun doing that I'm gonna do it to my stepmom and give me my
teeth back you weirdo that's so weird that's like it's just a sad detail about
collecting the teeth having the teeth but anyways I mean that that's how real
people in real life are creepy but let's talk about how people in the world of
the dead could be creepy and I don't know if I've given them credit yet this all
came from an online post written by couple technical 16 795 so couple
technical if I haven't given you a shot out yet I apologize but yeah just to
wrap it up like when I'm reading the storm thing and does Devon know how
creepy this is do ghosts choose to do creepy things or do ghosts live in a
since they're in the afterlife and they live in this different dimension is it
so irrational like they think they're things when he's doing is totally normal
he's in a brand new reality thinking about like floating a couple inches off
the floor of the hallway at night coming through the doors being like I love
you I'm just gonna tear anyone I mean it was a beautiful story of a grandmother's
love piercing the veil but would you choose to do that if one if you passed
away and you had to greet one of your loved ones we're like what's the heaviest
chains I can borrow what's the spookiest time I can't appear no you would show
what like I would show up right and I'd show up how everyone always remembered
me unwashed jeans and a t-shirt and I would walk and I would sit there they'd
be like do it'd be like in the middle of lunch or something like that they're
trying to work they're on their commute to work and I'm like hey guys what's up
sit in the fast food seat ah I would show up and I'd be like hey remember me it
was of course you remember me I'm totally awesome and they're like they're
holding their noses they're like uh you just don't wash your jeans in the
afterlife either I was like listen hey man I really loved you and I wish I
could have told you one last time how cool you were but I died horrible
harpoon accident so here I am I just have this giant harpoon sticking through my
heart I'm dripping ectoplasm all over your staking eggs here I am I just
came to give you hug and I chased you around the house trying to take you
with me that's probably what I would do that's probably what I would do if I was
a ghost I guess that answers the questions ghosts know they're doing
creepy things and it's hilarious
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is gonna be your email address you can also do
stuff at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Tiktok is at DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to
it every day I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys
[Music]