Today, we take a look at a series of harassing phone calls that turned into an unsolved mystery.
And then we take a look at the Back to the Future movies.
The Power of Love, Trying to Bang Your Mom.
There's a lot of good things that came out of those movies, but War those movies actually
a code trying to warn us about 9/11.
We'll explore that and more.
We're just gonna do those two stories, but we'll explore those two stories today on Dead
Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
It's snowing.
Whatever.
I just gotta deal with it at this point.
However, I do have something to gripe about.
I watched Love Never Dies.
Love Never Dies is the sequel to Phantom of the Opera.
I'm not gonna do a whole Dead Rabbit Recommends on Phantom of the Opera, but it is an amazing
movie.
It's directed by Joel Schumacher.
And Batman and Robin and stuff like that.
I don't really think he was trying to go for like a comic book vibe, like super comic
bookie.
But man, he really hit a home run with Phantom of the Opera, with Gerard Butler as the Phantom.
It's an amazing story, amazing soundtrack.
I had knew nothing about it.
I was in my mid-20s.
I was blazed out of my mind.
This was back when I smoked weed.
Absolutely bait.
And I think I had got it from Netflix back when they still did stuff in the mail for
whatever reason I had got it.
And I put it in.
Two minutes later had it turned on the subtitles because the whole thing is singing.
And what is it?
Two and a half hours later I was sobbing.
It was the most beautiful story.
And it's a straight up horror movie.
It is a gothic horror movie because the Phantom is a lunatic who kidnaps people and murders
people.
Blackmail's people doesn't care.
Super insane.
Basically the ending is, spoiler alert, it's basically Columbine in an opera house.
He doesn't use guns, but it's a massacre.
It's a brutal film.
And he is the love interest.
Well she has to choose between two guys.
The noble and kind of boring Raul or the violent psychopath known as the Phantom.
Very very interesting movie.
And then she, then they made a sequel.
20, 30 years later Andrew Lloyd Webber made a sequel to this movie or to the play.
And I'm watching it.
I'm such a big Phantom of the Opera fan.
I've never seen it live.
I saw the movie multiple times.
Stoned and sober. That when Love Never Dies came out when it was released at the Broadway
or it was never played on Broadway.
But when it was being played at theaters I thought I'll never be able to see it about
the soundtrack and sat at home and listen to the soundtrack.
And I'm like, oh my god, this is not very good at all.
Imagine if on after, imagine they did a sequel to Nightmare on Elm Street where after Nancy
survives the slaughter of all her friends and gets away from Freddy Krueger.
And the second one you find out 10 years later they banged and had a baby.
It's super bizarre.
It totally is one of those sequels that you're like this actually retroactively kind of ruins
the first one.
And even Andrew Lloyd Webber is like, eh, it's just a different story with same characters.
Even he's saying it's not really a direct sequel.
Andrew Lloyd Webber, it's weird.
He's, I think he's brilliant, especially his early stuff.
But I didn't know this.
In theater circles he's considered the Michael Bay of musicals.
He's not very well liked.
He is a middle class audience guy.
He gets the middle classes there who go see like rent, no he doesn't do rent.
They go see Cats and they go see Phantom of the Opera.
He's the Michael Bay of the theater world.
I think he's really good.
This wasn't very good.
But Phantom of the Opera is absolutely brilliant.
I recommend checking it out.
11 over 10.
You can take it or leave it.
But I'll give Andrew credit.
Although songs are stuck in my head.
I just didn't really like the plot.
Songs are good.
Can't get them out of my head.
Anyway, so I think I've spent enough time talking about my obsession with Phantom of
the Opera.
Let's go ahead and get started with the episode.
So we're going back.
Ooh.
We're going back in time but not in the way that Marty McFly would.
No.
We're going back to the year 1980.
I was born in '76.
So I'm four years old.
Imagine me in kindergarten during this story.
Oh my God.
I actually, oh okay.
This story takes place in Anaheim, California.
I lived in Anaheim at the time.
I may actually suspect for this story, little four year old baby Jason.
But we're going to go back in time.
We are going to, we don't need the carbon decopter.
We're already here.
We're, oh no.
We forgot.
We're in Oregon.
I'm not in California.
So we're just going to go back in time.
We're going to bar the DeLorean.
We go back in time.
1980, May 28.
There's a woman named Dorothy Jane Scott.
She has three names.
That means one of two things.
She's either a victim or a serial killer.
Whenever the news reports a middle name, that's usually what happens.
Dorothy Jane Scott works at a head shop.
Where they sell pipes and stuff like that.
Paraffinilia, drug paraffinilia.
And one of her coworkers, they're having a company meeting.
And one of her coworkers goes, "Oh God, my leg.
Ah."
And they're like, "What is it?
A cramp?
You need some calcium?
You need some milk?"
He's like, "No, no.
It's not a cramp.
Ah."
He got bit by a spider during a company meeting.
And you know you work for a really crappy company.
When you're sitting in the back of the company having a meeting or in the front, or just
walking through the door and a spider bites you.
I've never gotten bitten by a bug.
Ever.
Definitely not at work.
But anyway, so he gets bit by a spider.
I don't know why.
And I don't even know what type of spider.
Oh, it was a black widow.
Or as I wrote on my notes, a black widen.
Anyways, so it's 11 PM.
Now he's at the hospital.
Dorothy Jane Scott and her friend and the spider bite victim go to the hospital.
Now, first protocol when you get bit by a spider is the first thing they do is see if you can
crawl on walls.
And if you can't, all the doctors get really disappointed and they're like, "Dang it."
Let's just treat him for venom then.
He's not an actual Spider-Man.
But anyway, so he gets treated for it, but it was his leg.
He wasn't feeling really good.
And Dorothy goes, "You know what?
I'll go get the car.
I'll go out to the parking lot and get the car.
I'll come up to the front of the hospital and we'll all get in the car and we'll go
home."
Everyone's like, "Oh, that's a great idea.
You know, because my leg got bit.
Spider might be nearby."
So, they don't want to get assaulted again.
They see Dorothy walk out to the car and then they're chit-chatting the friends in the hospital
kind of like, "Hey, how's your leg?"
And he's like, "What do you think?
I've been in the hospital for my leg."
She's like, "Oh yeah, I forgot."
And then they see the car start to drive through the parking lot and then it gets on the road
and drives away.
And they're like, "What?
That's weird."
It's almost like when you're watching a zombie movie and the guy's like, "Here, give me the
keys.
I'll go out and get the car."
And then he gets in the car and drives away and the survivors are like, "No.
That was our last hope."
But this was real and it involved zombies, just spider.
A couple hours pass and the friends are still sitting in the hospital and now they're concerned.
They're like, this was before the era of cell phones.
They're thinking when they first see her drive away, they're thinking, "Maybe she went to...
Maybe she saw another spider and got panicked."
But after two hours they start to think, "Okay, that was really weird.
It's not like Dorothy to just take off.
She's supposed to pick us up."
So they tell hospital security, they're like, "Hey, this is what happened."
And then they call up her parents and say, "Is Dorothy home?"
"I don't know.
She's not home."
Because she just left us here stranded at this hospital and we thought that was really
weird.
The next day in an alleyway, her car is found on fire.
She's not there.
Cubs automatically begin investigating it and they're thinking, "This is super bizarre."
You know, they get their first major lead.
As they just start investigating it, they get word that she had been receiving harassing
phone calls and they weren't just like, "Show me your boobs."
They weren't just like creepy pervert phone calls.
They were phone calls describing what she was wearing, what she had done the previous
day.
There were stalker calls and it wasn't again just, "Oh, you look nice in that blouse.
I saw you touching cantaloupes yesterday."
This is actually one of the quotes that she had told her friends that the caller had said,
"When I get you alone, I will cut you up into bits so no one will ever find you."
Click.
So these are very, very threatening phone calls.
And this was going on for weeks before she vanished.
A newspaper starts doing an article.
Obviously, they're like, "Okay, we're going to cover this story."
They get a phone call, a very threatening phone call to the newspaper.
They're like, "It might just be a prank caller because we get those, but we're going to tell
the police."
Two weeks after she disappears, her mother gets a phone call.
Mom picks up the phone.
I got her.
Click.
Almost every Wednesday, the mom would get a phone call.
And the phone call wouldn't come if Dorothy's dad was home.
So whoever was making these phone calls knew when the mom was home alone.
On a Wednesday, Adelina.
The phone calls would either say, "Is Dorothy home?"
Click.
Or, and I don't know the exact quote, but she basically it was, "I have her prisoner.
I'm holding her prisoner."
Or, "I murdered her."
So she would get these different phone calls.
One teasing her, one saying that she was basically still alive, and then one saying that she was
murdered.
One time, one time the phone rang, this went on for quite a while, the phone rang.
The dad picked up the phone.
Instead he happened to be home and whoever was making the calls didn't know that.
Stopped calling.
Stopped calling the house.
Game was over.
He wanted to harass the mom, but once the dad picked up it ended.
Now obviously the cops were trying to get a trace on the line, but the phone calls were
so short.
Four years after she went missing, in the Anaheim Hills, a set of bones are found.
Cops are like, "Well we gotta identify the body."
So they do dental records and it comes back as Dorothy's body.
After the bones are found, ring, ring, ring.
Mom picks up the phone.
"I killed her."
Click.
The phone calls started up for a short time and then just petered off.
Unsolved mystery.
No one's ever been arrested for this.
There's been a few suspects.
One of them is there was a guy working in an auto shop across the street from the head
shop.
Now to be fair, that's not an official suspect.
I was doing my research, someone on Reddit was saying, "Well you know there was this
auto shop next to it and it could have been someone working there."
But no one was ever arrested for it.
No one was ever convicted for it.
Totally unsolved murder.
It's creepy because that means that guy's still out there.
And who knows, the next time your phone rings, you could be getting one of those calls.
I can't imagine getting a call saying, "When I get you alone, I will cut you up into bits
so no one will ever find you."
If I got it now, I would automatically assume it was a lark that someone was messing with
me.
But just being a normal person moving about the world and getting a phone call like that
would be quite chilling.
And then for it to actually come true, creepy.
So the next story we're going to talk about is a little more lighthearted, a little more
lighthearted even though it eventually involves the death of 3,000 people.
But the journey there is more lighthearted because we're going to take a look at a preposterous
theory called, I'm going to call it Back to the Truth-er.
Ooh, I just came up with that.
I'm always so pleased with myself when I come up with stuff like that.
Back to the Truth-er.
Did the Back to the Future movies directed by Robert Zemeckis actually predict 9/11?
And just quick heads up, we're still in Recommends Week or Request Week.
I don't know what I titled it, but this was actually a request via email through Justin.
So Justin, thanks for the request.
Now imagine you're sitting in your living room.
You're sitting in your living room and you have your VHS copy of Back to the Future.
And for whatever reason you think, I'm going to watch this tonight.
I haven't watched it in a while.
I could watch it on DVD.
I could watch it online.
But no, I'm going to put in my VHS copy.
So little flap closes.
That's your audibly loud VCR.
And right when it's getting started, right when it's going to-- you can't wait to hear
some Huey Lewis in the news.
You can't wait to indulge in your incest fetish.
That mom was very, very hot.
Props to Marty McFly for resisting.
But anyways, you're getting ready to start it.
You got your popcorn.
You hear a knock at your door.
You're like, "Oh, no, no, dude.
I just want to watch my movie.
I just want to watch my movie."
And underneath the door, you know, you have a little cap under your door.
You see these two long arms, kind of like Slenderman style slide under your door.
Fold up and unlock it from the inside.
It's Franz.
He's showing up quite early in this season.
Because this is definitely a story that needs a little bit of Franzinian.
Because it's a lot of just weird facts.
So Franz just sits down with you on the couch.
Franz is our resident conspiracy theorist if you're a new listener.
With audibly long arms.
He sits on the couch next to you, throws his arm over your shoulder.
And it's long enough that he can still reach in and get popcorn and put it into your mouth.
So as you're trying to move your mouth, as he's trying to shove popcorn into your mouth,
he says, "Ah, back to the future, eh?
Watching some back to the future?"
You're like, "That's a weird voice.
You don't know I'm going to say, 'Ah, yeah, I know my voice changes from time to time.'"
Did you know?
Did you know that Doc Brown and Marty McFly, when they first time traveled, do you know
where they time traveled from?
You're like, "I don't know.
It's been a while."
The Twin Pine Mall.
Sounds familiar?
What other things are there twins of?
You're right.
Twin Towers.
You don't even respond to his answer.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
And, here, let me pause it.
Give me the remote.
Pauses it.
What time does it say?
People really believe this, by the way.
People actually, there's several videos and resources on all this stuff.
I should start off by saying that.
What time are they at the Twin Pine Mall?
You look at that.
You look at it.
It's a digital clock.
It says 116.
You're like, "Oh, it's 116."
Oh, no, no.
You have to look at it upside down.
He gets up and he takes your television set up and sets it on the upside down.
What time does it say now?
And you're like, it says 9/11 when you turn it upside down.
Exactly.
9/11.
He puts the TV back.
Urgh.
Sets it back up.
Right?
You're surprised because it's a CRT TV.
It's quite heavy.
Now, let's fast forward a bit.
So, he has this car that goes back in time.
Hence the title of the movie.
And he goes back in time.
A farmer who lived on that land that would eventually become the mall describes the car
as an airplane without wings.
Sounds familiar?
Oh, yeah.
The plane crashing into the Twin Towers.
I guess that sounds a little familiar.
You're right.
You're learning.
You're learning from me.
I'm glad he's become more like Gollum at this point.
Now, he gets away from the farmer by crashing into a tree, a pine tree.
So in the future, the mall is named One Pine Mall.
You're like, oh, yeah, I guess.
You see?
Proof.
That 9/11 was caused.
Was predicted by Back to the Future.
Not Cosmo Back to the Future.
That's a different conspiracy theory.
Now, there's other things that people tie into this conspiracy theory.
One, that Muslims are the bad guys.
That Muslims are the ones who attack Doc Brown and Marty because Doc Brown had them smuggling.
Oh, no.
He got money to get plutonium, that he was going to then sell to the Libyans, and he
was going to use it for his own time travel device.
The Libyans show up.
The Libyan car crashes into a building as they're trying to-- something happens during
the shootout.
The Libyan car crashes into a little building, knocking it down.
That's proof of 9/11.
The fact that they were Muslim terrorists is proof of 9/11.
So that was a weird thing for me because, hey, Franz, I thought that 9/11 was an inside
job.
It was brought down by bombs, and the Muslims had nothing to do with it.
So why does this movie highlight the fact that they're Muslim?
Well when most conspiracy theories believe that it was taken down by bombs, and Osama
Minaloud was completely innocent, Franz just shifts his eyes from side to side and just
sits there silently.
You can't have it both way conspiracy theorists.
You can't point to evidence of Muslim involvement in Back to the Future and then try to convince
me that the Muslims had nothing to do with it in the event you're trying to reference.
But that's an odd part of conspiracy theory.
So Mayor Goldie Wilson was a black guy who was running for mayor in the present.
This slogan "progress is his middle name" you'll remember Obama's very, very famous campaign
slogan "progress."
It wasn't that, it was hope.
But apparently there's some sort of comparison between that.
Predict the rise of Obama.
Because whoever thought of a black politician before President Obama is weird, "Did you
know?"
Franz interrupts us.
"Did you know this?"
And there are comparisons of Donald Trump in Back to the Future too.
Yes, I know that that's actually a really common joke.
No, no, no.
It's not a joke.
Because when the Marty McFly is fired, he looks like Donald Trump too.
What?
What are you talking about?
I don't remember that scene.
And his fax machine prints out his pink slip?
Guess what it says on the pink slip.
Does it say you're fired?
Mm-hmm, say proof.
It predicted the future.
That's what you're missing, Jason.
That's what you're missing.
This movie, it's not just about 9/11.
It has all these other little things.
But the most chilling point of all these movies, the Back to the Future trilogy is what I call
it.
But so then, yeah, Franz, okay.
So the nonsense goes on and on.
There's a lot of little connections between, you can take a little piece out of the movie.
One of the connections is the Libyans were the people trying to get the plutonium.
And 25 years after the movie came out was Arab Spring and it started with the Libyans.
So when you take three movies of any trilogy, you could take the Princess Diary movies and
isolate single scenes and compare them to world events and get something.
I mean, you may get something.
You're a loser in the end because you had to watch a bunch of Princess Diary movies,
but you can find anything and anything if you look hard enough.
Now I said yesterday when I was hyping the story up that there was one thing that I found
that was super, super bizarre.
It is most likely a coincidence.
It's almost 100% a coincidence.
And I don't know if Robert Zemeckis, if Robert Zemeckis did it on purpose, he's a mad genius.
I think he may have just liked the visual.
And if he did this on purpose, he may be insanely... it would blow my mind if he did this on purpose.
So the climax of the movie is this, of the first one.
They have to...
See you later, Franz.
You'll be back shortly.
I'm sure you'll have another story you can share with us.
But he walks away.
His knuckles dragging on the ground.
He leaves.
So there is something that is super bizarre.
So the climax to Back to the Future is they have to rig a wire from a power line onto
the clock tower.
They know precisely when the clock tower is going to be struck by lightning.
Marty McFly needs to be going 88 miles an hour and hit the cable at the exact moment of
the lightning strike.
He then is allowed to go back to the future, hence the title.
So they're rigging the wire.
Doc Brown's rigging the wire.
Marty's getting his car, banging his mom, something like that.
I don't remember the details of why he's late or almost late.
And he shows up and he gives Doc Brown a letter.
The letter is warning that Doc Brown's going to be killed by a Libyan.
But Doc Brown goes, "What is this?"
And Marty McFly goes, "You'll know in 30 years."
He then gets into the car, gets into the delorean.
He hits 88 just the right moment.
The flaming lines appear on the ground.
And then there's like an autolube shop called Nine Autolube or something.
So you have a nine on one side of the screen and in the middle of the screen you have these
two flaming tire tracks.
So it looks like 9/11.
That's utter nonsense.
That's not what I was hyping up as saying he was a mad genius.
That's just stupid.
So 30 years, 30 years after the release of Back to the Future, Robert Zemeckis directed
another movie called The Wire.
And it was about a man who, and I didn't come, I don't want to take credit for this.
This actually, this thing I'm about to tell you, comes from the same source of all the
other nonsense I've talked about.
So I don't want to think like I came up with this, but it's quite ingenious.
So despite all the nonsense of research I had to go through, all the videos I had to
watch to get to this, I thought this was pretty ingenious.
So I'm giving the credit to the guy who did this.
I didn't write his name down because you know, it's just crazy conspiracy theorists.
But the YouTube links are being in the description.
So 30 years later, from 1985, Robert Zemeckis directed a movie called The Wire.
The movie is about this guy wants to walk a high wire act from one of the twin towers
to the other twin tower.
So the plot of the movie is him trying to attach a wire, that's not the whole plot of
the movie, but the climax or what he wants to do is he wants to attach a wire from one
tower to the next and then walk across it.
And you're thinking, okay, that's just a weird coincidence.
And that is just a weird coincidence.
They both involve wires that comes out 30 years later.
He is wearing the exact same clothes as Marty McFly in that final scene.
The exact same clothes.
The exact same outfit.
So in that scene and back to the future, when he travels into the future, he comes back.
He's wearing a black jacket, a burgundy shirt, or a red shirt, and dark jeans.
So we see him disappear in part one.
In part two, he comes back into the past.
He's wearing the black jacket, the red shirt, and the black pant.
We see him come back at that very moment.
In The Wire, the guy who is walking the wire from one tower to the other is wearing dark
jeans, a red shirt, and a black jacket.
Now again, I'm thinking when I'm watching the clip, the rational part of my brain is
Lincoln.
I think Robert D'Amicus just finds out a really dynamic color set.
I think he finds that he must, he must, those colors, that combination of colors must appeal
to him, making a human look like a black widow must be a pleasing color set to him.
But seeing those two scenes back to back the way the YouTube video intercuts them, it does
look really bizarre.
And so the implication, and so I'm looking into that, and I'm thinking either Robert D'Amicus
did this on purpose as some sort of troll, or he just really likes that color palette.
The YouTuber seems to think that what the story actually is, he goes in quite in detail
in this.
And back to the future, he travels back to the future at the end of that.
He then goes 30 years into the future, not the 1985 future from the 1950s, but he goes
from the 1985 past to the 2015 future, then walks, no joke, walks across the twin towers
in the movie The Walk, and then travels back in time.
The YouTuber thinks that Marty McFly is in The Wire.
So as much as I think that's a really compelling piece of "evidence", I think it's just a
really really bizarre part of the story that somehow matches up.
I don't think the character in The Wire is Marty McFly, because I'm pretty sure The Wire
is based on a true story, and we know what happened to Marty McFly when he traveled after
because there's a sequel.
So it's super bizarre because the people who believe this conspiracy theory, they really
have to leave a bunch of stuff out.
Like where's all the 9/11 references in the third one?
Why were the Libyans involved and not Saudi Arabians?
Which is actually what happened in 9/11.
And again, according to you, the Muslims had nothing to do with 9/11.
So it's this weird mishmash of conspiracy theories, but I think these people watched these videos
where we're watching a VHS copy with Franz at one night, and they started to see these
scenes, and then they just got rid of everything.
I don't remember Osama bin Laden trying to sleep with his mom.
Like there's key plot elements in those movies that are not a clue to 9/11 at all.
So why are you just picking out these little things?
And you know, that's the thing, that stupid predictive programming thing.
People go, "Well, before the Illuminati can commit a crime, they have to warn us about
it.
I'm gonna do a whole segment on predictive programming, but it's utter nonsense.
We'll cover that later."
So that is the story.
Oh, and this was the thing that I thought was interesting about 9/11, and I could be totally
off base with this.
But 9/11 really, really only appeals to two age groups.
Baby boomers and millennials.
Baby boomers are like, "Oh my God, my security in my country is broke."
It was a tragedy.
I'm not saying it wasn't a tragedy.
It was an absolute tragedy.
3,000 people lost their lives, thousands and more families devastated from it.
But the cultural significance of 9/11.
To millennials, it was their cradle being shaped, and they're like, "Oh my God, this
is the reality of the world."
To baby boomers, it was their cradle being shaped, and they're like, "Oh my God, I thought
we were safe."
Gen Xers really don't care.
Really.
I looked at the human toll of it, and I'm like, "Oh my God, this is a tragedy.
It's horrible that that happened."
But I gotta take my shoes off at the airport.
To me, it wasn't this huge, significant element.
And generally, when I talk to other people my age, they don't really give it much social
weight.
They don't give it a bunch of societal weight.
We go, "Yeah, they don't make movies like She's All That anymore."
It did kind of change stuff.
But I think 9/11 truthers, they tend to either be older or younger.
Because I just think that people my age are just kind of like, "Eh, it sucked."
Just like a house burning down sucks, but it wasn't the biggest event of our lives.
It's kind of weird.
I think it's just part of that whole Generation X being like, "Eh, the so what generation,
the why generation, the grown generation, we just don't care."
Generally, it's older people and younger people who are really looking for this 9/11
connection truth or stuff.
The rest of us old timers are like, "Pfft, whatever man.
If I can live through Kirk Cobain blowing his brains out, nothing else matters."
Which is the name of a great Metallica song.
So, but anyways, that is the story of, back to the future, predicting 9/11.
Did it predict 9/11?
No.
But is there even more bizarre evidence that I couldn't fit into the quote, again, quote
unquote evidence that I couldn't fit into this episode that you can enjoy yourself by
watching these videos?
Yes.
I will admit, the costume thing in the wire and the wire and back to the future and the
tower and the back to the future and those connections between those two scenes does
seem very, very, very coincidental 30 years later.
Movie 3, I get it.
There's a lot of stuff packed into those two scenes.
And to be fair, if that was the only evidence that was presented to me, I probably would
have been a little, I still wouldn't have believed it, but I would have been a little
more forgiving on it.
But that's the thing with conspiracy theories.
They overdo their Sunday.
Sometimes you just need the plain vanilla.
You need the one scoop.
Blop.
It's human trafficking.
That's what's going on.
But then you get the other people like, "No, no, that's boring.
We got to put on like some satanic chocolate syrup and some sprinkles of reptilians.
And we got to get this cherry out of the demonic workshop."
And then eventually the real conspiracy is buried underneath all this nonsense.
Maybe that's the point.
Maybe the best way to hide a bizarre conspiracy theory is to make it so bizarre, it's unbelievable.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)