Two of the most bizarre, true crime tales we've covered so far.
First off, a man driving down the freeway at 10.30 in the morning dies in a car accident.
Simple tragedy, suicide attempt, the police don't know, but it is odd that both of his
nipples have been cut off.
And then we travel to Spain to chase a truck full of sulfuric acid as it barrels down a
winding mountain pass, eventually crashing and spilling acid all over the road.
But as cleanup crews and police investigators look at the scene, they realize that underneath
the acid is a deeper mystery today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You know, I've had actually a great series of days and it's thanks to you guys.
It's actually thanks, well it's thanks to you guys in theory, but it's thanks to one
of you guys in particular.
You know, a lot of times when I'm talking about the Patreon, I say, "Hey, if you can't
support the Patreon, that's fine, just get the word out about the show."
I've never supported a Patreon and I've been a rabid listener of a lot of podcasts.
I've just never really been in the position to have enough money to support them.
So I appreciate it when people support my Patreon.
But if you can't support the Patreon, help get the word out about the show.
I pitch that all the time and I mean it very sincerely.
There is a Reddit thread recently about the conspiracy theory iceberg.
There was a Redditor who goes by the name "AbsolutelyFat" and they said, "Hey, there's
a guy who's done a couple episodes on this conspiracy theory iceberg and you should check
it out."
And then someone asked for the link and he sent the link.
So those two posts on Reddit within about 36 hours got me 500 new subscribers on YouTube
and my podcast downloads doubled from a thousand a day to 2500 a day.
More than doubled.
Two posts.
I blew the show up within 36 hours.
So that's all it takes.
That's so awesome.
And you know, if you don't use Reddit or you don't use computers at all, just get the
word out about the show.
We got flyers you can print out from the show notes.
Talk to your friends.
Talk to your family.
Harass people.
Knock on doors.
Really, really helps a lot.
Stewart and Meatball got banned from Facebook for three days for harassing people.
So again, you don't have to go to those links.
But I really, really appreciate you guys getting the word out about the show.
It really, really means a lot.
So absolutely fat.
Today, we are going to give you the keys to the Jason Jalopy you're going to be driving
us around this episode because this episode is interesting too because I normally don't
go true crime heavy.
I normally only do one or two true crime stories a week, but both of these are so bizarre
and they both are related because we're going to hit some horror on the highway.
And so we're revving up the Jason Jalopy.
Let's all hop inside.
Absolutely fat.
You got the keys.
We are first going to San Antonio, Texas.
The year is 2003.
It's a sunny spring morning, April 16.
Jason Jalopy does not sound like that, but I'm in a good mood.
Normally it's all, it barely works, but we got it souped up for this episode.
By the end of the episode, maybe back to normal.
And you think if we're going to be hitting the highways, we're going to be going on
these races, but first we have to make a stop.
We're going to stop outside this house and we're just going to sit in an idling car.
We're going to look.
And there we see the house of Air Force Colonel Philip Michael Shoe.
He's a 54 year old staff psychiatrist.
He's drinking his coffee.
Wife.
Great coffee.
Glug glug glug.
He's sitting there, he's drinking coffee.
And then he goes, you know what?
Tracy, my wife, my beautiful wife.
I have to go to work.
And she's thinking, that's weird.
It's an hour earlier than you normally leave, but she doesn't say anything.
She doesn't say anything.
Gives her husband a kiss.
He leaves.
It's 5 30 in the morning at this point.
He's like, we're like, you have to duck into the car as he's walking out of his car.
He's like, that's weird.
Why is it that old time he car sitting in my front yard?
Oh well.
And he gets in his car, he starts driving away.
Now we're not going to follow him because we don't know what happens for a while, but
let's go into this past.
So Phillip Michael Shue, Tracy's his second wife.
He was previously married to this woman named Nancy.
And there was an odd relationship.
She was also apparently like a psychiatrist and she specialized in people who were into
S&M, which doesn't seem like something you'd go to the psychiatrist for.
You're like, oh, I really enjoy rough sex.
I got to stop this.
Like I don't know why you would go to the doctor for that.
If only I could get over my crippling addiction to sweaty anal sex.
I don't know why.
Is that a thing?
Do people complain about that?
I guess the person receiving it might.
They're like, please make my husband stop.
The point is, is that that was her specialty.
And that's important.
That may be important actually.
Phillip was married to this girl Nancy before.
The relationship was getting rough.
Apparently the relationship was not physically rough.
He's not coming home and getting whipped.
Actually, we don't know.
It's an interesting thing.
So she's a psychiatrist for this S&M stuff.
He's married to her.
He's a staff psychiatrist as well.
He starts to have some paranoid issues.
He starts to believe that people are after him.
And a big component of that is that Nancy has a $1 million life insurance policy on Phillip.
And he is like, that sounds a little dicey.
It sounds a little weird, right?
And he's also getting like threatening letters.
I'm going to get you.
I'm going to totally like beat you up and tie you down and chain you and whip you.
And he's like, what?
These sound awfully familiar.
But he's getting actually vague.
It doesn't specifically say, read 50 shades of gray to find out what happens to you next.
It wasn't specifically S&M stuff.
But anyways, he ends up divorcing Nancy and saying, hey, you need to cancel that.
I didn't know this was a thing.
He goes, so we're not married anymore.
You have to cancel your life insurance policy on me.
And she goes, no, I'm not going to do that.
So apparently I can take life insurance policies out on just random people.
Is that a thing?
Or I can like date a girl for a couple months, take out a life insurance.
That would actually be a good thing.
No, not a good thing.
It would be a cruel thing.
But what if you only dated girls who were in extreme sports took out life insurance policies
on them?
I'm not going to finish that sentence.
But like you don't do anything.
You don't like you're not put there again ready to base jump and you're like, whoopsie
and you push them off.
I guess no, then they would have a parachute.
But they'd be like, wee, thanks Jason.
You know what I mean.
Poke holes in their surfboard or whatever.
That's even possible.
This should be an Adam Sandler movie.
He's trying to kill his extreme sports girlfriend, but she's just getting more and more extreme.
She goes to a piercing parlor and he's like infecting the needles.
He's like taking hobo blood.
He's pours hobo blood all over the tattoo artist stuff and the tattoo artist doesn't
notice.
He's like giving his girlfriend a tattoo and then it turns out that hobo's blood actually
had these awesome antibodies in it.
She gets stronger.
Adam Sandler's like foiled again.
Not only do I not think that's an Adam Sandler movie, I don't think any film studio would
ever make that.
But if you do, James Wan, I know you listen to this show.
If you do, give me credit.
Anyways, the point is apparently you can have a life insurance policy on just random people
or people you are in relationship with.
So he divorces Nancy and he tries to get her to shut it down.
She won't do it.
He remarries Tracy and he...
It's interesting because he dies.
Spoiler alert.
I think I mentioned that in the intro, but there's this huge psychological autopsy thing
written on him because the military really had to investigate this.
Really goes into a lot of detail like his mind states at certain points.
I recommend you guys reading that if you want to get into the real nitty gritty.
I'm glossing over a lot of the stuff that happens in between Tracy and Nancy.
But anyways, now we're back with Tracy and we're back to April 16th, 2003.
He left the house an hour earlier than he normally does.
It's now 8am.
We're on a freeway outside of San Antonio.
So we're driving down the Jason's Lopi down this road and then all of a sudden...
Car flies by us.
Whoa, whoa.
We almost get hit and we're watching it.
We're trying to catch up to it.
Apparently it's a TIE fighter now.
It goes and it's like dodging cars and then it...
You know like freeways normally have like the one lane and then there's like grass and
then there's the lane going the opposite direction.
The car goes off the road, drives between two light poles, hits something in the median,
goes airborne.
Whee!
Damn Duke boys on the run again.
The car then crashes down on all four tires.
The driver corrects it.
Keeps going.
You know there's no brake lights on at any point here.
So we've basically just seen this guy do a Mad Max stun.
The car's coming and it hits something, flies him in the air, lands.
He's able to regain control of the car, keeps going, leaves the interstate again, smashes
into a tree.
Call 911 bro.
We are you.
You do it.
Come on.
Do it.
The rest of us, you have to call 911.
We have to call 911.
This is what makes this story so weird.
When they take him to do the autopsy,
I don't know if they noticed it right there,
because there's pretty much blood everywhere,
and smoke, and all this stuff,
but maybe one of the rescue personnel goes,
"Hmm, that's weird."
His shirt has two little bloody, bloody circles,
right, where nipples would be.
When they do discover this,
he has, he doesn't have a head,
or his head's bashed in,
so that is what killed him.
But this is what else they notice.
He has, both of his nipples have been cut off.
Not, and there's no car accident thing,
unless he's like juggling razor blades
while he's driving.
There's no way you're going to be in a car accident,
and you're like, "Oh no, my nipples,"
as like your seatbelt is like,
"Sling!"
Shafing them off.
That's not possible.
I mean, I guess in an infinite universe
of infinite possibilities it is,
but not in ours.
He has a six inch long gash in his chest.
Now, not six feet deep,
because that would basically be through him.
No, not six inches deep either,
because I think, how big is six inches?
I should know that.
But, um, yeah,
that would still probably be deadly
if you had a six inch hole in you,
for, you know, in your chest,
is what I'm saying.
So anyways, the point is,
is that he had a big cut in his chest.
That took way too long to figure out.
Thirdly, which is possible,
car accident, you know,
thirdly, his pinky was chopped off.
Now, again, you could be in a car accident
and you could be like having your finger in the vent.
You lost the penny in your heater vent.
You're trying to get it and you look up
and you crash and you lose your pinky.
But they could not find his pinky anywhere
out of the crash thing.
Or his nipples, by the way.
Again, it wasn't like his nipples
were just like floating around.
They're like, "Oh, here they are.
They're underneath this can of Mountain Dew."
They're gone.
His pinky's gone, his nipples are gone.
And to make it even more bizarre,
if that's not weird enough,
because again, you could go, "Well, maybe like..."
He was juggling raise-blade Jason
and his nipples got cut off
and they flew out both windows.
And I don't know,
seatbelt and the pinky just kind of disintegrated, right?
You could possibly say that.
But he also had duct tape wrapped around both wrists
and around his ankles,
like he broke free of something.
So the police look at all this information
and they go, "Hmm."
So we know that this guy had a life insurance policy
of a million dollars with a ex-wife
who treated people with S&M, apparently.
Again, they're like, "What? Really? That's a disease?"
And, you know, sergeants like it.
Some people don't like it.
And then, easily bruisable people,
bananas don't like it.
And then, so they know that this guy looks like he suffered.
It looks like he was tied up from somewhere.
He left home early.
Maybe he was having an affair.
Maybe he went back to his ex-wife.
She has this million-dollar insurance policy on him.
We've got to keep bringing that up.
Maybe something happened.
However, the police look at all the available evidence
and they go, "Oh, suicide.
Why did we even investigate it? Suicide, obviously.
Stamp. They have a big stamp that just says 'suicide' on it.
Hit the court document. Case closed."
And his wife, Tracy, is like, "That's totally impossible.
There's no way that this guy killed himself."
Not saying that he couldn't kill himself,
but how-- where are his nipples?
Where are his nipples? Where is his pinky?
So this is where we get into the psychological examination,
the psychological autopsy.
Oh, also, the duct tape had no fingerprints on it
and there were no-- no gloves in his car.
So whoever put the duct tape on it wasn't him
or he did it and then threw his gloves away
and then it was like, "Oh, it threw my nipples away too."
As he's driving on the road.
He was-- he was being seen by one of his colleagues
and other psychiatrists at the area
because he was dealing with some issues,
but he had no suicidal ideation that at least was spoken of.
He was planning on retiring in October of 2003
and starting his own career.
He was really looking forward to that.
He actually told his psychiatrist six months before his death
that he had this feeling or this dream that, quote,
"His car went out of control on his way to work.
Great violence was done to him."
So it could be a premonition.
It could be him setting the stage for something he was going to do.
Obviously, the psychiatrist wasn't like, "Isn't that spooky?"
The psychiatrist wasn't standing like that,
but that could mean that to a rational person,
that means he was setting the stage for his eventual suicide.
But anyway, so the police ruled it's a suicide.
No crime took place.
This guy duct-taped himself and ripped his own nipples off
and all this stuff and then purposely drove his car off the road
into a tree.
He didn't hit the brakes. It's a suicide.
If it wasn't for all the missing body parts,
it would just have been a normal suicide.
Tracy, though, she can't really fight that.
She sues Nancy and the insurance company to say
she shouldn't be able to get the million dollars.
She shouldn't be able to collect on the life insurance.
She sues Nancy for just being Nancy.
She sues USAA for not canceling the contract
even though he kept telling her to cancel the contract.
And the judge in this civil trials,
they're going through the whole trial,
Nancy's doing her stuff, Tracy's doing her stuff,
USAA's doing her stuff.
After the trial, the judge finally goes,
"Okay, it's time for my verdict.
You lose, Tracy. I'm not going to..."
The USAA was in their right.
This is apparently some weirdo policy
where you can have a life insurance policy on someone.
So you lose the trial.
And Nancy, you will get your million dollars in life insurance.
You will.
Tracy, you get 1.2 million dollars
in her life insurance policy
that she had separately or something like that.
And the judge goes, "He was murdered."
Absolutely. This was not a suicide.
This guy was murdered.
And everyone was like, "What? That wasn't even part of your trial."
And he's like, "Yeah, yeah. This guy was obviously murdered by somebody."
And that's been it.
The Attorney General of Texas goes, "No, he wasn't.
We're not changing the ruling on his death certificate.
It was a suicide. Case closed. We're not looking into it anymore."
What I think happened,
I know that you guys have been waiting with bated breath,
is I think he went, he was either having an affair,
he got into some S&M stuff, he was tied up.
And I don't know if Nancy was involved in this,
but I think he was probably having an affair.
Don't haunt me, ghost of Philip Michael Shoe,
but this would be my scenario.
Probably having an affair.
Got out of hand, he got tied up,
he got his nipples off and he's like, "Hmm, this is going a little too far."
And by the time they were like cutting his chest open,
he broke out, "Ugh, I'm out of here."
And he runs, he gets in his car, he's driving,
and then one of two things happened.
He succumbs to the 6-inch gash in his chest,
which was probably unlikely. It wasn't like his guts were coming out.
Or he could have realized that maybe it was even like a gay affair.
It's one thing to cheat on your wife with another woman,
like you can kind of tank that hit.
You can be like, "Yeah, you know, whatever, I had a moment of weakness."
But if you're a man and you're married to a woman
and you have a saintomasticistic affair with a gay man,
for a lot of people that's a lot harder to tank.
That's a lot harder to be able to excuse as just a dolly on.
So he could have been driving on the road and he's like,
"Oh no, my nipples are missing, how am I going to explain this?
I'm just going to kill myself."
So in the end result, it may have been a suicide,
but that's my take on it.
I have no proof of that just based on the hour of research I did on this topic.
I think it was a suicide, but...
Because I don't think like you're not like,
"Oh, my nipples only got 10 minutes left to live."
Like I don't think his wounds would have killed him.
I think he's the one who eventually killed himself,
but he killed himself because he was going to get found out.
Either he was having a heterosexual or a homosexual affair,
and he was like, "I can't deal with this."
So that's my personal take on it.
But I do think it's weird that you can't cancel it.
I can get insurance policies against people.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story here.
Now for our next story, we're still on the freeway,
but this time we're going to Spain.
We're going to the mountainous region of Spain.
And this one takes place in the year 1986.
So I was a little kid when this one happened.
I always think it's so weird.
2003, that's not long ago.
I mean, I was in college back then.
But like 1986, I was like running around playgrounds
when this story took place.
Most of you guys didn't even exist, but I existed.
1986, I was just child.
I was about 10 years old, discovering girls for the first time.
And this story happens.
Now, this is 1986, it's June 25th.
There's a truck full of acid, right?
Which is obviously the best way you want to start.
One of these stories.
There's a truck, this guy is hauling acid up the SOMO Sierra
mountain pass.
It was a well maintained truck.
I don't know why I'm making it sound like Frankenstein's
in the engine, but this truck is going up this mountain pass.
This is in Madrid, Spain, that area, headed towards the Basque
region.
So, woo, yeah, Basque people, let's go, let's go.
So there's this, it's a try, it's not like a semi.
It's a, I don't know anything about cars.
This is what it is.
It's a Volvo F12 truck.
So I'm imagining it like a, not necessarily a pickup truck with a flat bed
and there's just acid spilling everywhere.
But I don't imagine it as a big semi in this story, but it is hauling
an awful lot of acid.
It's hauling 5,600 gallons of 98% pure sulfuric acid.
So it's a lot of stuff.
This stuff is not watered down.
This is not your, this is not your grandpa's sulfuric acid.
This truck, I don't know why you make it sound like that.
It goes up the mountain, right?
And we're driving behind it and you're like, "Jason, do we really have to be behind?"
I'm all like removing the windows.
Like yes, smell the fumes, smell the fumes of the acid.
The truck's going up the mountain.
It gets to the top and then it basically just starts barreling down the mountain
and it's not a straight shot.
It's not like a slalom or a solemn, you know, what skiers go down?
Which a mountain.
It's going down this mountain, right?
And cars are like, "beep beep," they're like getting out of the way.
At one point, a car gets ran off the road from this truck.
It's just, "yep."
Car gets ran off the road.
And a white car, like a white van pulls up behind the car that gets run off the road
and two people jump out of the car and they're like, "Are you okay?
I just saw that truck almost ran you off the road."
And the guy's like, "Yeah, that lousy idiot."
The woman, so it's a man and a woman jump out of this van and they're like,
"Yeah, yeah, I know, he totally sucks, right?"
"I'm a nurse. I'm just one of the women," says this, not the dude.
Not like it matters, but the woman goes, "I'm a nurse."
The dude's like, "Mmm-mm, men aren't nurses.
He has arms crossed. Uh-uh-uh."
And the woman's like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
I'm the nurse. I'm the nurse. Are you okay?"
And the dude's like, "Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, but just stop that truck."
So they jump back into these, man and this woman jump back into the van.
They're driving down the road.
Now, the truck also hits a car and knocks off its like side view mirror.
Yeah, keeps going down the hill.
The white van stops, man and woman jump back up out again.
Guys now wearing shirts. This is not a nurse.
The woman's like, "Are you okay?"
So that car hit your car and knocked your mirror off.
And then the guy's like, "Yeah, yeah, it really startled me."
But stop that truck. That's the new game show in Madrid, Spain.
Every week they get a truck full of sulfuric acid and just push it down a random mountain pass.
Truck keeps going down the road.
And eventually, it's like going 86 miles an hour, it's a windy mountain road.
Eventually, everyone knows what's going to happen.
The driver loses control of the car.
It tips over and all over the roadway is 56,000 gallons of 95% sulfuric acid.
Now, there are some shepherds in the area because it's the Basque region
and that's the number one job over there.
They're sitting there with their shepherd crooks hanging out, eating shepherd's pie,
hanging out with some sheep.
And are you a shepherd? Do they only do sheep?
Is that what that name means?
Can you be a shepherd of goats?
Are you a goat herder at that point?
Like shepherd, sheeper.
Anyways, as they're debating that, they're like, "No, I swear.
I swear I can start raising goats.
You can raise goats, dude, but you won't be a shepherd."
As they're having this conversation, they watch this truck full of sulfuric acid.
Throw sulfuric acid everywhere.
And basically, they're like, "Whoa, dude."
The white van pulls up, man and the woman jump out of the van.
They go to the wreckage of the car, of this truck that sulfuric acid is coming out of.
They take a box out of it, jump back in the van, and leave.
The shepherds are looking at each other.
They're like, "Hmm, that was interesting."
Rescue crews show up.
Now, at this point, sulfuric acid is completely leaking everywhere.
Rescue crew has to wear respirators.
Even then, you're having people who are having breathing problems.
The acid's getting in their lungs.
You have to be careful because I guess the fumes could ignite.
It was this whole entire ordeal.
They go into the cab and they see the driver.
It's this dude named Andres Martinez, and his wife is also in the car, Carmen Martinez.
They're both dead and they're both just bubbling and boiling away
because a bunch of the acid came into the cab.
The investigators are thinking, "Must have lost control of the truck."
They died in the car accident.
Hopefully, they died in the car accident.
The acid is just doing what acid does best,
acid-ing stuff, eating them away.
Obviously, it would have been much worse if they were like,
"We survived that car accident."
"Aha!"
They're just as acid was filling up the cab.
The investigators shut the door and they're like,
"Don't look."
They're telling the other investigators, "Don't look."
And they're like, "It's totally gross."
They're pouring lime, stuff, quick lime.
And they're pouring sand to kind of help neutralize the acid and stuff like that.
Everyone's clapping because they finally stopped that truck.
This show's been going on for three seasons and no one ever done it before.
They're putting it out.
Now, it gets to the point where their cops are like,
"Okay, now we got to start notifying next of kin."
These are the only people who died in this car accident.
They get a hold, they find out who these people are.
I'm assuming they look to their wallets because they're all gross.
They're all acid-y, right?
It's not like they can go, "Hey, I know that guy."
And then you call up like somebody worked at Acme Chemicals and you're like,
"Hey, I think your uncle died in an accident."
And they're like, "Uncle Joker, no way."
But no, they found...
They didn't identify based on the horrible acid wounds.
They found the driver's license or license registration.
Somehow, that's not the point.
Somehow they track down Carmen's mom.
They make a phone call and they go, "Horrible accident."
She's like, "That's a hell of a way to start a phone call."
I'm with the police department.
Their daughter and her husband were driving down a road in a truck full of sulfuric acid.
And they're dead.
They died on impact and they have melted now.
They're quite melted.
And she goes, "So that's a hard phone call to make."
And I'm sure he was a little less blunt than that.
He was totally gross.
Your daughter was all melted.
Here's what's left.
It's like a tune being dipped in acid.
She's like, "No, my daughter was Betty Boop."
Anyways, anyways, it's a horrible story.
I don't know why I'm making all these jokes.
Horrible story.
So the grandma gets this phone call and then she says words that change the course of the entire incident.
The grandma says this is a quote, "And the boy? Please tell me the boy is all right."
The cop is like, "Uh, yeah, let me get back to you on that. Sorry, phone's breaking up. Reception's really bad. Hangs up."
Turns to the other cops and they're like, "Did you see a kid in that car?"
And cops are like, "No."
Now, they're calling the next of kin within a couple hours that this is going on.
So now they look over at the scene and there are pounds and pounds and pounds of sand and lime all over the crash scene.
They're like, "Put your respirators back on, boys. We gotta dig and we gotta see if we can find this kid."
Because when they looked in the cab, there was no kid.
They also then they go, "Okay, let's see if the kid was somewhere else."
Because he's a truck driver, all of his movements were tracked.
He had this little tachometer in his car that like, "Show, it's this thing. I think in Europe, I know in Spain they have it."
But it like, "Show's how the car's running and where it makes it stop."
They're able to start doing all this investigation over the next three days.
This is kind of what it comes about.
In the first one, they go to a local restaurant and the guy's like, "Oh, no, no, no, they all three were here."
The son was here with them. So they go, "Okay, so we know the son was with them very, very recently."
And then they realized that when they were looking in the car, they saw kids' clothing and like music, like raffy music cassettes and stuff like that.
And they're like, "No adult would ever listen to this garbage."
So that was another clue that the kid was in the car.
But where's the kid now?
The first thing was maybe he's buried under all the sand and the quick lime.
So they're digging all that stuff up. They can't find him.
The second theory is that maybe he just melted.
Maybe there was nothing left of him.
And so they ran that by some scientists and basically got laughed out of science school.
Because they're like, "It would take five days before the bones got eaten by acid."
Like, acid doesn't work like that.
Like, yeah, they actually said if you took him and put him in a pit of nothing but acid,
it would take five days.
If you just had him in a car and he got splashed with acid, there's not even a chance he's going to melt.
You're going to find hair, you're going to find teeth, you're going to find most of them in the amount of time they've been talking about.
Another theory is that he didn't have a seatbelt on.
They could say that based on where he would have been sitting, he didn't have a seatbelt on.
It's possible he got, when the car crash happened, he flew out of the car and landed somewhere and then simply got up and walked away.
That one, they go, "It's... okay, actually."
They think he might have gotten thrown out of the car and like fell in the river and died, or just like fell down a ravine and is still there.
That is a theory.
The other one is that he could have gotten thrown out of the car and survived and just walked away.
Because that has happened.
Now they said due to the violence of the accident and the copious amounts of acid,
he wouldn't have walked away and been like, "Oh, I don't remember who I am, but I'm going to become a blacksmith in this village and just build this new identity."
He would have been like, "Oh, I don't know who I am. Also, ah, my face!"
As I'm covered in acid and even if he did wander to the next village, they'd be like,
"He's not like, 'Here, I don't know who I am. I want to be a blacksmith.'"
He'd be like, "Hey, I don't know who I am."
"Ah-ha, and they'd take him to the hospital."
So they don't really know.
The weirdest thing is the people in the van.
So the people in the van appear to have been following this truck.
It stopped when the one car got ran off the road.
It stopped when the car got hit and the rearview mirror got knocked off the site.
And then it stopped and it retrieved a package from the ruckage before things got really acid-y.
It got out of there.
And the police, that last story, what happened was police were saying,
while they were investigating this, people were like, "Oh, yeah.
I talked to these two shepherds like right after the accident."
And they said the car stopped and these people got packaged out and then they took off.
And they're like, "What?"
And then other people were like, "Yeah, yeah.
There was two shepherds who were up there and saw that."
When the police went to question the two shepherds, they questioned every shepherd in the area
and none of them said that they saw that.
Which means one of two things.
It was some weird urban legend that started within hours after the accident.
Or the two shepherds who saw that disappeared.
There's a lot of French theories about this.
One is that they were being pursued.
That white man was actually chasing the acid people.
And maybe they were dealing drugs or, and that was the package that was retrieved.
Possibly.
I think if you were pursuing a mental thing, you would stop at each side.
You would be a really terrible drug dealer if you're chasing down someone who's stolen your drugs
and then they mildly inconvenience someone and then you jump down and you're like,
"Hey, look at my face and look at the license plate of the car I'm driving."
You're like, "Okay, perfect. I'm gonna go fight these other drug dealers. See you later."
Like that would be a really bad tactic for a drug dealer.
But did they take the kid?
Like where's the kid?
What was the car doing following it?
It's such a bizarre story.
And it's so bizarre I don't really have an explanation for it.
Like if the kid was last seen weeks before the accident, you could think maybe something,
maybe they accidentally did something to the kid or hurt the kid or left the kid
and they were so guilt-ridden they decided let's just commit suicide.
Because he wasn't breaking when he was going.
And that's the thing, people describe the truck as being out of control
but when they started looking at the tachometer of the truck, they're like,
"He was totally in control of the truck. He seemed to be meaning to drive that fast down that road."
The brakes worked perfectly fine.
He just wasn't using them.
It's possible that the white van had already done something to the kid
and was chasing the family to finish off the job.
Who knows? Really, who knows?
We just know that two people are dead and a child is missing.
I think the best case scenario is that that little dude, his name was Juan Pedro Martinez,
is still alive.
That he got thrown clear of the vehicle and like, there was like a pillow.
There's like an old dirty mattress just out of sight of all the investigators.
He's like, "Ugh."
I mean that would be the best scenario.
Worst case scenario is something awful happened to him before the events of this day.
I think the middle-play scenario would be he gets acid on him.
"Ah!"
And then he jumps out of the car and runs before the white van shows up
and then he like, rolls around in the dirt to like, neutralize the acid.
He's like, "Ah!"
And then he looks and he sees the white van and they're like,
"Ha ha ha ha ha."
Because they caused the accident is what that implies.
And then they take a package and he's like, "No, not the package."
This little boy.
And his parents are dead.
And then he wanders through the like, grasslands of Spain and he's training every day.
He's like picking up, he has these weights full of sulfuric acid.
He's just like lifting them.
And it's good because if he drops them, then he gets more acid on them.
So it makes it so he doesn't drop the weights like plant a fitness.
And he's just like, "Ugh yeah."
And he's like working out every single day.
And then he basically like, a sheep herder.
Those two sheep herders, they meet him and they're like,
"Hey dude, you look all messed up."
And he's like, "I know, I know, but help me train."
So then he learns the ways of the sheep.
He learns the fighting styles of the sheep.
All of his fighting styles are just head butts.
He just head butts people.
And he's building up to the day where he's going to find these people in the white van.
He's going to get revenge against them for killing his family.
So his costume is just all wool.
It's all wool.
But he doesn't never hides the scars on his face.
Because he wants those two people.
He wants that guy who doesn't think men should be nurses.
And the woman nurse to recognize him when he shows up.
And then he can head butt him.
So after eight years of training, he's going to turn 18.
And now he's ready to go out and seek out vengeance.
And his weapon is a shepherd's crook.
And one night he's like crawling around on a rooftop.
And there's like a big she-glass window.
And he sees there's a white van parked in this drug dealers headquarters.
And these guys are like, "Ha ha ha!
We've cornered the acid market.
Sofiric acid.
You have to use this stuff to make gold."
And then he knows he's at the right spot.
And then he jumps through the stained glass window.
It's not stained glass.
It is now.
It's a church.
The Vatican's involved in this.
Shhh.
He jumps down.
The Pope's like, "Oh no!
It's the acid dude."
He doesn't have a name yet.
He's fought some low-level crooks.
No one knows who he is.
He starts throwing his shepherd's crook around.
He's throwing it around people's necks.
And then he pulls them towards him and he head butts him.
And then he head butts the Pope.
And the Pope's like, "Oh my hat!"
And it falls off in his hat.
Actually, it had a bunch of acid in it.
And then the end.
I think that would be...
I basically...
I don't know.
I hope Juan's alive is basically what I'm saying.
And having a life full of adventure.
Maybe not headbutting the Pope.
It might have been too much.
But DeadRabberRadio and gmail.com
It's gonna be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio
Twitter is @deadrabberradio
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[Music]