One man goes all out for the ultimate cosplay and
Then we join a group of stranded sailors on a rocky island in the middle of nowhere
They thought they were gonna starve to death on this deserted island and that would have happened
If it hadn't been for a crashed UFO today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*Music*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carbner and I'm gonna cut to the chase here guys
Let me give you a little bit of advice
Life is too short
To work a job
You don't like
I'm gonna say that again because a lot of people need to hear this. Life is too short to work a job
You don't like if you're not being fulfilled by your job if it's not your calling if you don't have a passion for it
Why are you doing it?
I know this young woman her name's Tiana. She's 16 years old. I've known her since she was 10
She hates her job
And I realized when I was talking to this young woman, there's a fallacy in life
That you're supposed to work jobs you hate. It's okay to work jobs you hate as long as you're making money
Putting food on the table. It's okay, and I say no to that. I
Say you need to work a job you enjoy at the very least a job you enjoy
So many of us work jobs that we don't like have you ever been going to work and think I hope I get in a car accident today
Because then I won't have to go to work
That's a sign you need to change your job and it is this lie
That society tells us and that we tell ourselves that we need to work crummy jobs now
There is a caveat to that one of my favorite movies transformers dark of the moon transformers 3
There's a scene in it where John Malkovich tells Shia LaBeouf and this is this is an important caveat
Shia LaBeouf is about to get a job in a mail room John Malkovich has this company
John Malkovich says I know this isn't the job you want you want the job after this
But you need to do this job first
If you're on your way up the ladder
And you need to work this job to progress
Fine do the crummy job, but guys really I want to reach out to you
And if you take nothing else from this podcast from this show anything
Just to know that you are better than a bad job
so
Start dusting off that resume
Start looking for something that will excite you. I know it's scary
To change make these big changes make a list of the things you need in a new job
Make a list of the things you want in the new job
You don't have to do this overnight
But if you are miserable in your job life is too short to work in misery
You're on your way to your job and you're frustrated and you're gonna hate it
And you hate your co-workers and you hate your job, but you make good money
You got good benefits and as you're going to this job that you hate
You have all this negative energy swirling up inside of you
You have a heart attack and you die. You're killed in a car accident
Rogue rogue elephant crushes you as you're pulling into the parking lot. How will you feel then?
Your last thing on earth you are going to a place that gives you nothing but negative energy
Find the positive job. It doesn't even have to be a great job. I love retail
I love stocking shelves. I love working with customers
So doesn't have to be a flashy job. Just look for the job that you love life is too short
To work in misery
We take nothing else from this podcast nothing else from 777 episodes
Remember that there is only one of you you have one life
Make sure you're working a job that you want to work
Don't just work for the paycheck. Don't just work for the benefits
You find yourself in that situation when as you're traveling to work you wish that someone rear-end you
So you'd get the day off. It's time to dust off that resume. It's time
To find the right job for you
Let's go ahead and welcome in today's legacy patreon supporter coming into Dead Rabbit Command give it up
It's Matt Sprinkle everyone give a round of applause to Matt give him a high five while you're doing a round of applause
It's all totally confusing you accidentally punch him in the eye
But you can't sue me Matt because you've already given me patreon money
So you're gonna lose that's in the law. Did you not know that Supreme Court ruled on that if you give me money
You cannot sue me Matt
You're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode you guys can't support the patreon
I totally understand just help spread the word about the show really
Really helps out a lot now Matt. I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We are driving all the way down to
Brazil
Matt is perfectly driving us down there. He's been in the vehicle. I think once or twice
He's been a supporter for a long time Matt knows the way. He's totally like oh Brazil
I totally know where that's at. Do do do do do we all go down there?
You guys longtime listeners of the show know I'm a huge fan of urban legends. I think that is really
Powered like my childhood belief in ghost of front. I'm like, oh no, there's a man with a hook is gonna come after me
I'm not making out with anyone in a car
I actually don't think I've ever gone old lovers lane now that I think about it make out in a parking lot, right?
It's a little as romantic if you're in the parking lot of like a movie theater
But you know the whole story lovers lane and the hook for the hand I love urban legends
Those are the first scary stories that I think kids really hear and they sound believable
I remember there was a story that I used to be told that in
Orangevale which Orangevale, California is one of the flattest places on earth
You can literally stand there and you're like hello state capital
You can pretty much just see for miles and miles, but I remember my brother told me a story
There are these two Native American people. I
Did not use that terminology didn't use that terminology, but there are these two Native American
People and they were madly in love
They're madly in love with the chiefs of the different
Oh, they're from different tribes to do that would make sense if they're just like hey
We're in the same time. Let me back up here because this will make it more dramatic and accurate
There's two rival tribes of Native Americans and you have a dude from this tribe
And then you have a girl from this tribe and they were in love with each other
But the chiefs of either tribe goes no you cannot be together. How dare you marry that?
Oh, they were also they were also the kids of the chiefs. I guess I'm a little off track here
You're like Jason at least like edit that stuff out. No, don't tell me how to do my show a long long time ago
There were two Indian chiefs right one of them had a son
Well name him Johnny and the other chief of a rival tribe had a daughter named Daphne and
Johnny and Daphne were in love with each other, but the rival chief
I know the water room. Me. Oh, Julia. Just get to the stupid urban legend part. So anyways
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay
Maybe you do know how to run a podcast better than I do the point is is that because they couldn't be together
They went to a cliff a cliff in Orangevale, which doesn't exist the much you'll get is maybe a goalie
But anyways, they went to this cliff in Orangevale and they jump both jumped off to their deaths
I
Guess I have to have the sound effect that made it quite brutal
But so you're like that's not an urban legend Jason
That's just like Romeo and Juliet
But this didn't happen in the end of Romeo and Juliet if it did it would be awesome
My brother told me and to this day if you go to this cliff in Orangevale that cliff that doesn't exist
I was so scared as little kid. I'm like, I don't want to go no towards any cliffs ever
I don't even want to see Clifford the big red dog the go to this cliff to where the two natives jumped off and made that sound
If you stood on the edge of that cliff their faces like their faces got cut off some
I don't know. I was a kid. I didn't understand a legic
But apparently their faces got sliced off on the rocks when they fell
so if you go to this cliff their
Skinned faces would float up and they're just be like it would be like if you cut off leather face cut off their face
And so they had no eyes. They had no mouth. It was just these two bloody
skin pieces of skin floating around going
That's terrifying right absolutely terrifying it would have been one thing if just their ghost showed up and they're like walking through the woods
It's their skin got faces floating after you. I remember a I remember
Being told that story on an overcast Orangevale morning back in like 1982. It's one of like my earliest memories
Urban legends. I love them. They terrified me and
Still don't go towards cliffs because you never know you never know what cliff it was
So I love urban legends and when I can't the only thing better than an urban legend
Is an urban legend like the one we're about to discuss and I got to give a shout out to
Nelsilius because Nelsilius brought this to my attention. I never heard of this one before let's take a look at this
Have you guys ever heard of a show? I'm sure some of you have called. I think it's Naruto and
I don't really know much about it. It's about like some cat ninja
Right, isn't that guy like half cat because he has like whiskers or something
But I see a lot of people dressed up as him when I'm walking around just town everyone's like hi
I'm Naruto running like him that that's really what I know
He has a headband and then I think he has whiskers and he runs with his arms behind his back
That's all I know about Naruto, but now I know something else about Naruto. There's a dude named Kan Kuro on the show
and he's a shinobi ninja and
I guess he's a puppet master ninja
So he I don't know my research ended was like Naruto headband shinobi ninja
I didn't watch any episodes of this but apparently he's able to control
People or he can create constructs like puppets and he like marionettes them has him dance around on I'm assuming
They do niggas so I'm assuming he's not putting on a puppet show for the bad guys
I think he like makes the the puppeteering kick people in the nuts or something like that
I'm not for sure. So that's the background of that character. He let that deep dive research
I does something with puppets
The reason why we're in Brazil is in 2005
There is an anime convention called anime friends 2005 and this dude shows up dressed up as Kan Kuro
It's his favorite Naruto character
his name is Tarsisco Felix and he shows up as this dude and
He brings this puppet with him like he has like this giant casket thing
And he's like all the the marionette puppets in here
And I guess on the show the guy has something strapped to his back or he does carry around this thing that the
marionette dude is in
So I lost all my Naruto viewers are there already furiously type in some on YouTube
You're like Jason you literally could not have gotten any details more wrong than he did
But the point isn't that I'm gonna get flooded by anime comments
The point is this he shows up in this costume with this casket and people are like dude
That is one of the best Kan Kuro costumes I've ever seen and there's a guy's in a next-time dress that was like
Oh, I was Kan Kuro too. They're like you just look like some dollar store ninja
He actually is going around the convention people like you're really this is real cool
Gonna get a picture with you and people are like well that was weird right something smelled bad
An anime convention, so I'm sure the B. O meter was off the chart
But every so often someone when they'd walk by to Risco they would go hmm. I don't smell too good
They eventually have this
Like lineup on stage. He actually for the entire convention. He's one of the finalists for best
Cosplay
So he shows up and he's lined up on stage with all these other people and this is the first time he's standing still
I'm sure maybe he's still to go to the bathroom or when he's in line to buy a hot dog
But usually he's walking around the floor, but now he's on stage with all these other people you got these bright lights
You got the guy on the microphone announcing everyone and people are like dude that really stinks
Like whatever whatever your costume is really really stinks and they start to think maybe in his
casket his backpack is whatever it is
There's a dead animal because it smells like it's dead
the
Judges actually get alerted to this and people are like okay. We need to actually see you could you bring like spoiled food and
Tarsizos like it depends on your definition of food, right?
So they make him open up this casket. That's part of his costume
They find a dead body
So the urban legend goes like this
There was a man who brought a dead body as part of his costume
To an anime convention in the year 2005 in Brazil and when they force him to open up
They find this dead man and it turns out that Tarsizo was actually a medical student
and this dead body was a
Homeless person who had been dropped off at his college
That you're supposed to be working on so I go know my finals do tomorrow. Where's my homeless dude? No
So Tarsizo had it if he failed Brazilian medical school in this year
It's probably cuz Tarsizo stole your buddy
He takes his body puts it in this coffin for his costume
And I'm wondering if anyone said hey man, can you make your puppeteering thing?
And I wonder if it crossed his mind and he thought yeah, I'll pull it out and he starts like making this
But because anyone would have automatically realized this was a real dead person
I don't know why he put it in the casket if he wasn't showing it off
but
The entire event was canceled
Anime friends 2005 everyone was sent home because this one jerk ruined it by bringing in a human corpse
On the face of it, that's a great urban legend right it goes right
I mean it totally it fit here. This is what's interesting about it
It fits what we know about people who go to conventions. They're weirdos and I'm speaking of one
I go to conventions as well when I can it's been a long time since I've been able to go one but
Generally if you're going to anime convention. I comic I used to go to comic book conventions all the time
Back when I was younger it does attract a certain segment of society
The weirdos the ones that would think it might be okay to bring in a human
Okay, they're not saying all anime fans thinks it's okay to bring in a human body
But you know what I mean? It does attract a certain segment of society. I'm not putting them down
But they're weirdos and I'm a weirdo too because I go to these conventions as well
But so the stereotype already fits the socially inept
Scientists doctor who thinks it's okay to smuggle a human body out into an anime convention like it doesn't
Defy logic right you could see this happening with so many goes others nothing wrong with this dude dress up as a comic book
They're dressed up like Thanos. I'm gonna carry around this World War two veterans body and say that I killed Captain America
And I read this and I go what's fascinating urban legend of course
There's no way we can actually prove it anime friends 2005. It was what 16 years ago
Anything is going to be in a foreign language
And so I read this urban legend and it actually was posted on the urban legends forum
And I thought whoa dude. It's really cool and then and
then
As a follow-up post Nelsilius
showed proof
He took a screenshot of a magazine
That tells this story
There's a photo of this magazine the photo was taken back in 2007 and
My Spanish is non-existent, but I know a
Submission of Latin and I can kind of make out what's going on
It appears that this article is saying hey yeah back in 2005 some nudge
I brought a human body into anime friends a Brazilian convention. It's written in Spanish
The best type of urban legends are the ones that are true
Now just the story alone is just a fun story right because you can see it happen
But this apparently actually happened and I will say this the only
question I have is
What did that magazine come from like where?
Was it a magazine of Brazil's best urban legends or was it a magazine about weirdos and in
Convention culture wasn't just a magazine about conventions in general and this was a highlight story
But it appears that this story is actually real that a man
student did actually
Smuggle in a human body into an anime convention and not show it. That's the weirdest thing. He didn't show it to anybody
It's like he just wanted the realism of having 180 pounds strapped to your back. It is dead homeless man
Fascinating story the best urban legends are the ones that turn out to be true and this one's super obscure
I hadn't heard it before but yes a man apparently did
Bring a dead body into into an anime convention and they shut it down and who knows what happened to the guy right?
I'm assuming
The very least he got kicked out of school. I don't know maybe they just gave him a demerit. They're like Teresa
Teresa you keep still in human bodies. We're gonna mispronounce your name every time we say it
But yeah, I really love urban legends and you can't get any better than one
That's true and pretty disgusting right you love the disgusting urban legends
Matt I'm gonna go ahead and touch you the keys of the carpenter copter. We're leaving behind anime friends 2005
We're saying goodbye to all the weirdos in Brazil. We are headed on out to a
deserted island in the Indian Ocean
to
Now hold on tight guys huge storm in coming
Winds blowing rain rain we have the window sets and we don't worry about the rain
I guess the helicopters a little wobbly because of the wind, but we're actually pretty comfy in there
We're drinking hot cocoa, but to anyone else alive in this area. It's a miserable day. It's September
22 and we're in the Indian Ocean and we're watching this huge storm just royal the ocean
Now in the middle of this Godforsaken area
There's the boat Christine
It's a Danish ship and the people on board are trying to do whatever settlers do to avoid dying in the water
They're like, I just don't drown. That's rule number one
So guys like oh, I didn't forgot that rule is he's flown away
Christine a Danish boat is out in the middle of this ocean and the wind and the water and the waves are tossing every each way
People throw ropes throw ropes somewhere. It's not really good captain. Where do we throw them? I don't know do something
Sailory splash people are getting just washed over
People were singing a jaunty tune they're not singing it anymore. They're just like lashing themselves to stuff
And it doesn't help it doesn't help the boat is out of control and they see this rocky outcropping this island in the middle of nowhere
Look out. Don't go over there the captain
You gotta give us better better instructions, dude
This boat
crashes on this deserted island and it's just I mean
Falling in an island is probably I mean the basic definition of an island. It's land in the middle of the ocean
But what it is it's just jagged rocks. There's no coconuts
There's no like far-sight-esque characters already trapped there
it's
It's death
It's a bunch of jagged rocks in the middle of the ocean the boat is
absolutely destroyed and everyone starts jumping off of the boat and
Basically like I can either be in this boat when it sinks or I can climb on these rocks and slowly starve to death
And so the people decide to climb on the rocks
Now these rocks they're not just like you can walk around there's like cliff sides and things like that
It's just inhospitable to human life
And so they actually have a good amount of water because it's raining and it's collecting in the gullies of the rocks
So they got that but they have no food at this point everyone's eyeballing each other custom of the seas brother
Who's gonna draw lots first? They're like, dude, we've only been here for 10 minutes. We don't want to start have to cannibalizing right now
But no food the boat sinking they're probably getting some rations off of there, but not enough not enough
And the men are sitting there
kind of just
They know they're gonna die. It's just one of those situations. You know, you're gonna die. Nobody knows you're there. It's 1862
The chances of another boat finding you is probably as high as that boat then getting stranded on the rocks themselves
more man meat to eat
But you know, you're not gonna get rescued right your best hope is that more and more boats
Crash there and you can just keep eating the survivors of those wrecks. So the men are sitting there and they're thinking we're dead
And what's worse is that we have all this water to drink
So we're just going to be able to prolong our lives until we all slowly start to death or start eating each other
And that is when they see
Something in the sky
A massive UFO
Is plunging through the clouds
And the storm is so violent they're actually watching the ship wobble now
This is 1862 they have no concept of a UFO even today
This would be the most spectacular sight you could ever hope to see in your life a UFO a UFO
That is estimated to be as big as a modern battleship
This isn't some tiny three gray aliens piloting this thing
This is a huge craft and it's coming down and even that the storm is so violent. It's battering the ship
The men realize this thing whatever it is
Is headed straight towards them
What do you think is gonna get any worse?
A giant vehicle from the sky
Is headed right towards you they start to scatter trying to look for shelter on these rocks
*Metal noise*
The UFO smashes into the side of the cliff and then there is no sound but the storm
The men start to approach this vessel and it's mangled there's massive holes torn in the side of it
It's sitting there now on the beach
But it's not in the best shape it hit this thing going god knows how fast
And this ship has created a new hazard outside of the twisted metal
Scattering the landscape the water around this craft is boiling
This ship's hole is so hot
The water is boiling
The men enter the craft
I love this story I just came across this one the other day. I really really enjoy it
As they're walking inside they see machinery of unknown origin
They don't know what it is. They can't make heads or tails of it. This is 1862
This is pre-industrial revolution the most technological thing they probably saw was like a loom or an astrolabe
But it wouldn't matter it smashed to bits
They're looking at all this stuff. Oh no my space loom doesn't matter smashed to bits in the impact
They see these metal boxes though
That have a strange type of writing on them these glyphs
And they're large but they can open them
So they see these large crates and they pry it open and inside these crates
Food
So the men I know they're all sneaking up behind each other with a fork and a knife and then all of a sudden
They just start devouring this food because again now they've only been trapped on this island
We're like I have our this point, but
Maybe they were super hungry on the way to get there
Who's going to turn down some good old mysterious food in a metal box that you can't read the labels?
These people are eating this food
Have all this food now they know that their problems have been solved. They have food
They have the water that they can collect from the rain and the rocks
They don't still have no idea what this is, but you would think at this point it must be god's mercy
some sort of angelic
gift and then there's one atheist sailor is like, I don't know maybe uh
Maybe none of that stuff exists and this just came from another planet people are like boo you we're gonna you work when this food runs out
We're eating you first
But they continue to explore the ship
And they walk into this room
And the sailors find them
They find more than a dozen bodies
strewn about
More than a dozen bodies
These men had dark bronze skin
With long hair
Long beards
But the most spectacular thing about these bodies
They were all 12 feet tall
The sight of giants
Giants from the sky in this great machine that smashed against our planet killed all of them
None of these posed any threat. They were all dead, but the sight of these 12 inhuman beings
Sent the sailors running
Some of them it drove them mad
One of them was so insane from this site. You can't comprehend it
You're seeing a non-human entity for the first time. You're seeing a bunch of them
When he ran out of the ship
He jumped into the boiling water
Cooked himself to death
Now I know the cannibals the cannibal contingent of the sailors were like, oh, right. We're gonna get that guy later, but
They didn't they didn't need to I know cannibals. They really want to eat this guy. They didn't need to
Because they had enough food
Fra I know I know they're super disappointed. Oh man. The thing is
Is they left the food in the ship
But they refused to go back in there they refused to go back into the ship
Because who knows what these things were this was not a place for man
A place for gods a place for devils
But not man
But they were starving they're on this deserted island in the middle of nowhere
This delicious smell of that cooked human keeps filling their nostrils eventually they do go a while without food and they say guys
We need to go back in there and get those containers
We need to go back in there and get that food
So after starving for a bit and realizing the only way to stay alive was to visit this
This cemetery
They go back into the ship
They began eating the food
They decide to drag the bodies out of the ship
They throw them into the ocean
Now they have food
Now they have water
Now they have time and strength
to escape
Because you can't just go out on the high seas you could build a raft day one
But you're not going to survive that journey
But now that they have this food they can build this raft and they know we're going to be on the ocean for god knows how long
But we have a chance now
So they eat they regain their strength
They build the raft they take provisions for them and the survivors get on this raft and leave this deserted island
Eventually
They reach civilization
There's a really cool book and a couple of you guys sent this to me a long time ago
There's a really cool book called albert rozales
Or albert roe sails one of the two humanoid sighting reports
And it's a lot like that website think about it docs.com where it's just brief
Overviews of these amazing stories
And they got this story from gerome clark who wrote it for fate magazine back in september 1990 now
And so the question is is
It's a fascinating story. I love this story, right? It's really cool
But the question that I always go back to is how true was it or is it true?
And I actually found out on wikipedia. They have a list of
shipwrecks by year
In september 1862 there was no boat that matched this description that crashed in the indian ocean
Although I figured maybe the dates wrong. I looked at october
1862 I did find a boat called the christine. That was a danish ship
And it does say it says that the brig was wrecked at jedaren
Which I wasn't able to I don't know what that means to try to look that up on a map
I brought out all my nautical maps at jedaren. Her crew was rescued
It says she was on a voyage from asgard to montrose forfenshire united kingdom. So I don't know
Why they would be going from the netherlands
To britain and end up in the middle of the indian ocean
But I was able to find at least a little bit of details. Does that mean the story is true?
We don't know right whether or not it's true. We can't determine that but this story is so
Awesome. I really love this story and the idea
We think of when sailors crash on these deserted islands
And that hopelessness, you know, you might be able to scrabble some stuff together to get off there
You may slowly eat each other away
See you I take a bite out of you you take a bite out of me
We'll just keep doing this until the first person dies
But you could have a 10 people die on an island and they're constantly hoping to get rescued and then they
Turn on each other and then you know eight are left and then a couple die of disease and then all of them end up dying
Their bleached bones are never found their family and their employers and everyone
Never is able to figure out what happened to these 10 sailors and that's so part of human nautical history
When we look at what humans have done crossing the oceans that is what we're doing when we look at the stars
It's the almost the same level of technology to build those galleons back in the day and to cross
The ocean was such a monumental task and if you messed up you died
Water is just as hostile as space
Right if you're
Mucking about in space and you float out of the space station you're gone
You're just going to keep floating and floating and floating away until you get sucked into the orbit of something
Or burn up in the sun and the same thing if you fall out of a boat
I'm almost gone bro. If you fall off of a cruise liner
You're done
It's so inhospitable nowadays. We're like, hey, let's hop on a cruise line
Let's hop on a disney cruise and drive around and baby Yoda will come out and help feed us oysters at the buffet
Maybe some and I believe someday space travel will be like that
We'll look back at the this era of space travel the same way that we look back
400 years ago in nautical travel you're like well, we'll get in a boat and maybe we'll make it
Maybe the crew will mutiny. Maybe they'll never know what happened to that boat
Maybe that entire galleon could sink and have all this treasure in it. We don't even know what happened to it
And that's the same idea of an alien ship crashing on earth
It's some backwater in the middle of nowhere if you have this galactic civilization, right
past Alpha Centauri
And you have this craft that you build with the top technology of the time
You say goodbye to your alien wife and to your alien children
And you hop on board your ship
And you fly across the galaxy
You're leaving behind that civilization. You see the last lights of the colonies
Disappear on your view screen
You go farther
Than the farthest outpost and now you're in the middle of a galactic nowhere
And your ship crashes on a mud ball
On the edge of the milky way
It's the same thing I find that so fascinating
The idea of an alien crashing here would be the same thing if we crashed on a rocky shoreline
You go well, there's people here. That's not good for them. What would you rather do?
Crash on a deserted island or crash on an island full of hostile people
Like you're probably gonna die anyways. Maybe you'll make friends
with the people there
Or maybe they'll just kill you because you're some weirdo outsider walking around
You look like a devil to the humans
You shouldn't be there. You're a trespasser
Fascinating story and I've always loved the connection between the nautical
and
the galactic
We are all just explorers
Trying to find our way through the universe trying to discover new things about reality about ourselves
But those type of adventures
They take blood
They take bodies
You got to lose a lot of ships
To explore the world
You got to lose a lot of ships to explore the galaxy
But it is through that loss it's through that struggle
That you gain knowledge
That is a little
soulless to the men and to the aliens
Who die
And no one knows where they are
Little soulless to them
But for civilization as a whole
We wouldn't be where we are today if it wasn't for the explorers
Who risked their lives
To get us here
Exploring as part of human nature
And from all the stories we've covered
All of the visitations all of the events all of the crash landings
I think exploration is part of alien nature as well
And hopefully that common theme unites us
And that our comrades deaths will not be in vain
And we will all someday explore the stars together
[Music]
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio
TikTok is @deadrabberradio
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and truth-fram podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you guys listen to it
You guys don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you guys listen to it today
Have a great one
[Music]