Is the movie The Conjuring Haunted? Yes, I'm still looking for a haunted movie.
And then we look at a book that was so mysterious.
A man asked an angel for a translation.
The book goes missing for 400 years.
And then things get really weird. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. I'm having a great day even though
I just recorded this episode and then ended up being an hour long with two additional stories.
And I was like, there's no way I can edit this down.
Scraped it, moved a couple stories around. I like this version better even though I just
started recording it because sometimes it's, sometimes I record an episode. It's almost like
a rough draft. And as I'm recording it, I'm like, I'm just not feeling it. I'm not feeling this
episode. I need to do it again. Now I got all my, I don't know, bees in my bonnet. What's the thing?
Ducks in a row, ducks in a row. Now I have all my ducks in a row and I'm ready to go.
This one will not be 56 minutes long either, by the way. I want to let you know I woke up this
morning and guess what was laying on the ground next to my couch, aka where I sleep? Yep. My black
boxers, they turned up now. Did my boxers disappear? Did a ghost steal my boxers and then return them
because they heard my podcast? Or did I just not see them the other times that I was looking for
them? Who knows? Completely valid. Obviously I probably just didn't find them. And you know,
a couple people who listen to this podcast have been over to my apartment. I'm sure the past two
days they've been yelling, just clean your apartment. You won't have to worry about your clothes
disappearing if your apartment is clean. My response to that is you should come over and help me
clean my apartment. It's a win-win. I get a clean apartment and you get the knowledge that all the
clothes that I'm wearing are 100% clean because they're not missing it somewhere in my house.
Ghosts, if you stole my boxers, that was awfully mean of you, but also thank you for giving them
back. If I had just misplaced them, ah, no harm no foul. Let's go ahead and get started on with
the episode. So what we're going to talk about right now is I'm going to start off with the book
of Soy Good. Book of Soy Good. There was two copies of this book. We're back, well let's go back in
time to the 1500s. Now there was two known copies of the book of Soy Good and what it is, it is a
magical text. What makes it interesting is that it is focused on the Christian Kabbalah. So you go,
what's the Kabbalah? So what Kabbalahism is, it is a Jewish mystic practice. It's basically like
magic. It would basically be religious magic. It's kind of a bastardization of what it is, but
that's what it is. It's magic that comes from God, not from any sort of dark sources. I think you
could argue that maybe Moses was practicing Kabbalahism when he threw a staff turn into a snake,
and it's based on like the, what is it, the seraphot? That's like the nine orb tree thing. It kind of
looks like the big, it looks like the nine realms from Thor. I mean that's probably the best comparison
I can have it. Anyway, so you have the Jewish mysticism, which is Kabbalahism, and Christian
thinkers and philosophers and particularly magicians wanted to have their own versions,
so they created Christian Kabbalahism. So you took all of the Christian beliefs, then added in all of
the old Jewish mysticism. It was the rage of Europe for a short time, but it really didn't catch on.
Christians don't like magic in general, but anyway, so this book had, was full of Christian
Kabbalistic imagery and spells. It had the names of angels, which you very rarely see.
Generally we have books that are like the names of the demons, but this book contained the names of
angels, so that made it very rare as far as the knowledge inside of that. It had something in
it called the Book of Rays, and it allowed you to understand the evil forces of the universe.
And then it went into things like about the humors, which is like blood, bile, mucus,
something else, and then the four elements and stuff like that. So it was basically like this
overall mystical magical text, and you're thinking, Jason, places were full of those things back in
the 1500s, but there was something particular about this book, not just the names of the angels,
which again made it rare, but the book ended with 36 tables of random letters, 36 tables,
36, and each table had 36 rows and 36 columns, and it was just random letters,
and no one could make heads or tails of it. They knew it was important, but they couldn't
make heads or tails of it. No one knew who wrote the Book of Soyga, but it fell into the hands of
John Dee, and he was the one who really, really made it famous. Now John Dee at the time, we're
still in the 1500s, was a preeminent scientist and rational thinker of England. The Queen used him
for a long time, and he was the one who proposed building a public library. He says, "You know,
we have all these rich people who have all these private libraries. We should have a place where
our libraries, where everyone kind of puts their books together for, I can borrow this one and
people can borrow this one. It's for the public, it's for everybody." He was a main proponent of
that. At the same time, he was really into magic. He was really into astrology. He was into scrying
and mediums and things like that. He saw them as much as he was a scientist, like a mathematician
and an astronomer. He felt like science and magic both had the same goal. It was to understand the
workings of the universe. He comes across the Book of Soyga, and he becomes obsessed with it.
He reads the book, and he's like, "Oh, that's pretty good. It's Page Turner. Has all these
mystical thoughts in that? Names of the Angels? Things like that? Book of Rays? Always want to
read that?" He's reading it, and then he gets to the end, and he goes, "What is going on here? The last
36, there's just a bunch of tables. It's like, basically, I'm going to call them 36 pages, but
basically the end of the book was just these tables, 36 pages of 36 columns, 36 rows." He's like,
"What does this mean?" He begins to drive him mad in a way. So he hooks up with his buddy, who's a
medium, and he goes, "Listen, I need to find out what these tables mean. Let's contact an Angel."
So they contact the Angel Uriel. Now, everything I've told you before is fact. It's historical
fact. Now we're going to get into the weird stuff, the beginning of the weird stuff, actually. He
contacts Uriel, and Uriel appears. So if you're a skeptic, you're like, "That's lame, but anyways,
let's accept this for a second." So Uriel appears to John Dee, and John Dee goes, "What's up with these
last 36 pages?" And Uriel goes, "Those were given to Adam from God." What? Okay, that's cool, but I
mean, what do these pages mean? Uriel goes, "The only person who knows what those pages mean
is the Archangel Michael." And then John Dee goes, "You know, I heard a legend that if you are able
to decipher the last 36 pages of this book, you only live for two and a half years. And Uriel
responds, 'No, you'll live to be a hundred and some odd years.'" And he's like, "Oh, okay, great. That's
great, but can you help me in Uriel's like, 'Peace!' And he leaves, right?" So John Dee really doesn't
get the answer that he wants, which is what is in the pages. He doesn't get a little more information
that God gave them to Adam, and that only Michael can translate them. Now, why he didn't then summon
the Archangel Michael? I don't know. Maybe he didn't know the summoning spell for that, or maybe he
tried. What we know happened after that factually is things did not go well for John Dee. He ended up
running into some money trouble and had to sell parts of his library. He ended up leaving England
for a while when he came back. Someone broke in and stole a bunch of his books. And he eventually
passes away. But because of his reputation as such a deep thinker, people for 400 years tried to find
this book. His name was linked to the book of Soegah, because like I said, he was obsessed with it.
People knew he was researching it. People knew that he highly valued this book, and they knew there
was only two copies. And at this time, there were no copies. Nobody could find them anywhere.
They were gone. People thought they're in some private person's collection,
or it was destroyed, or who knows. But the books didn't exist, and people looked all over. They
would go to the British public library. It has a real name, but like the Royal Library. And they
would look for, look under S for Soegah. They couldn't find it. They'd look under B for Book of
Soegah. Couldn't find it. So they're like the government, they don't have a copy of this.
The main library doesn't have a copy of this. It's gone for 400 years. No one sees it anywhere.
In 1994, there was a researcher. She was looking into John Dee and, of course, the book of Soegah,
because they were so closely connected. And imagine this. I keep saying like he's close
connected. Imagine if, let's say, Stephen Hawking in his later years, his past 20 years,
said he found a book that explained the secrets of the universe, and it's called "Alebaster,"
and then he dies. People are going to try to find that book. And that's basically what John Dee
was considering the book of Soegah. He was not just this weird mystic dude. He was an amazing
scientific mind who also believed this wacky stuff. And then he just dies and the book goes missing.
And so you had mystics looking for the book and you had, you know, philosophers looking for the
book, historians looking for the book. No one could find it. In 1994, Deborah Harkness is a
researcher who, again, is researching John Dee and the book of Soegah. She's going through his diary.
In the Royal British Library. She's going through his diary. And she sees an entry
where for whatever reason, he changed the title of the book from the book of Soegah,
which is what everyone knew it as, to Alderia, and then officially changed the title of the book
to "Alderia Civ Soegah Vocor." She's looking at it and she's like, "What? Oh, she go- no joke. She
goes look in the section for A's in the historical manuscripts, sitting on the shelf, or maybe behind
glass. I don't know. But she goes to the section where the A's, and there it is, filed away, "Alderia
Civ Soegah Vocor." She takes the book. It's the book of Soegah. He had changed the name. And so when
people had gotten it, it has moved around libraries and stuff like that. It had a different name on
it. So when it finally did filter into the Royal British Library, I don't know if that's the official
name, but it was there. So they have it. They found it and they're able to translate it. It was
originally in Latin. Now it's in English and does have that information and the names of the angels,
the book of Rays. It's all complete. But of course, what everyone is curious about, because all of
that stuff, I mean, other than, you know, the angel names, most of it is pretty well known. The 36
tables, the 36 pages. This is what people were looking at. So they're looking at it and they're
like, "Yeah, it's just random letters. This doesn't make sense. Why is this even in here?"
Okay, so now we're going to jump ahead to 2006, where we have another researcher named James A.
Reads. Now James, Jimmy, I'll call him James, James is, loves breaking codes. He loves getting into
these, his fingers dirty and looking into these mysteries. He had previously been working on the
Voynich manuscript. What the Voynich manuscript is, it is a book. We don't know who wrote it. We
don't know really when it was wrote. We don't know where it was written. It's written in an
indecipherable language. It's a whole book. And there's drawings of weird herbs and animals in it.
And people are like, "What is this?" Some people thought it was just gibberish. Other people think
it's some crazy code. Most people have tried decoding it. All have failed. He was working on
the Voynich manuscript and he goes, "You know what? I think I'm going to try something easy.
Let me get a crack at the book of Soega. Let me look at those tables."
Now luckily, nowadays, we have computers. This is amazing. He was able to take these random sets
of letters and ran all these computations through them. He basically, it came down to,
there was, between all 36 pages, there was 46,656 letters. 36 pages, 36 columns, 36 rows.
And he was able to crack the code. So on the pages themselves, we just see the 36 columns,
36 rows, and random letters. But each page had a purpose. The letters weren't random. They were
each attached to a magic word. A magic word forward and backwards was the key. And he'd go,
"Well, how do we know that?" Because when he was able to crack the code, he was able to link 24
of the pages to the Zodiac. So each Zodiac sign had two pages. So if you put in, there were specific
words that were used, magic words equated to those Zodiac signs. So Aries was Nisram. So you'd
have one page that was just Nisram, Marsyn, Nisram, Marsyn, Nisram, Marsyn, all the way down the 36
rows. And it matched up. And then you'd have another page for Aries, which was Marsyn, Nisum,
Marsyn, Nisum. They matched. 24 pages for the Zodiac signs, seven for the planets that were
known at that time, four for the elements, and one for something called the Magistrate or Magistate.
The letters weren't random. They were able to be matched to known mystical words of that time.
The question is why? The fact of that, you could create this code. 36 columns, 36 rows,
36 pages. Numerology was very, very important in Kabbalistic theory. And so was names and languages,
names particularly. 46,656 letters. A code created by hand without a computer
that was unbreakable until we had a computer that appeared completely random until you found out
the magical phrases that unlocked the code. Why? Who made it? This is where it gets weird.
Let me give you a little precursor, though. If you've ever played Minecraft, there was the option
for what is known as a seed. There's a little seed option. You type in a word, it will randomly
generate an entire world based on the algorithm of that word. If I typed in or numbers, whatever,
if I typed in 111, I will get one world. If I type in 112 or 111, I don't get a slight variation
of the original world. I get an entirely new world. So keep that in mind. This is from the website,
blog of wonders. The article is "Soyga, the book that kills." So this is the blog that puts this
theory forth. And I think it's the closest thing that we have to understanding what the book of
Soya, what those 36 tables are supposed to be. So I'm reading this article and they quote the
Gospel of John where he says, "In the beginning was the word, the word was with God, and the word
was a God." The book of Soya, this is the hypothesis here on this blog and it's quite amazing. The
book of Soya, the 36 tables, they're universes, they're realities, they're futures, they're
something blank. The 36 columns of 36 rows are blank until the word is entered in, until you
give it the seed and then it generates and it would continue to generate infinitely.
If you went more than 36 columns, if you repeated that magical word over and over again
across a thousand columns, it's going to keep spreading. What we see in these tables in the
book of Soya is a glimpse of these other worlds, of these other realities. A book of tables given to
Adam, showing him not just the power of God's creation but the power of words, the power of
language. Enter the word, you're given the code. The question is, who came up with the code?
Was it to hide something or was it to reveal something? If we knew the code, we have the seed.
I can put in Jason and it would say Jason, no such, Jason, no such, Jason, no such across 36
columns or 36 rows. It would say Jason, no such, Jason, no such, Jason, no such across 36 rows and
it will populate a random set of letters. But are the letters random? Do they show something else?
Why create such an elaborate code if it was completely random? The only thing I can think
of is to create the code is if you thought that it was revealing something or hiding something.
And maybe it doesn't. Maybe the person who created the code was off their rocker and they were just
smart enough to come up with this code. But if the code was completely random, how were we able
to match it up to the astrological symbols, the four elements, the seven planets, and the magistrate?
If it was completely random, we should have gotten no answers for it. There was a purpose to the code.
Is it if you speak that magic word, if you view the universe through that magic word,
through that seed, the page being blank is a blank reality. But when the word is spoke,
as God spoke existence into reality, are you basically seeing realities and futures on these
tables? Is there something mystical about this code? Is there something scientific about this code?
Is it random? Did an angel tell a leading scientist that this book was giving from God to Adam?
Who knows? I mean, obviously the logical answer is no. But even if you dismiss,
even if you dismiss the angel helping translate the book, even if you dismiss the creation story
of Genesis, what we are left with is a mathematical code that really shouldn't have been possible to
create over four or five hundred years ago. And to what end why it was created. If you spent
enough time, you might have been able to do this, but who and why? But the bigger question is what
does it mean? I can see why John D was obsessed over these tables. I get it. Because if you think,
if he had a hint of the truth that if you had these mystical words, the table would quote
unquote make sense, you still wouldn't know what it meant, but you would know why it existed.
You would know why the letters were there in the first place in that order.
This is blowing my mind, honestly, because I think about it on two levels. One, I think about it
on the mystical level that are these basically visions of other worlds and other realities where
that word was spoke. Instead of whatever word was spoke that created our universe,
if instead of saying earth, they said Nisram. But then on a scientific level, the fact that
somebody could create such an advanced code that wasn't random but appeared random, chaos theory,
basically. Fascinating stuff. Fascinating stuff. But then again, do you break the code,
do you die in two and a half years or do you live to be a hundred? There's just another weird mystery
on this thing, Book of Soyga. I don't know, man. It's blowing my mind, honestly. It's blowing my mind.
So, you know, I don't even know if I have time for another story.
I think I'm going to save the haunted movie thing for tomorrow because I think this kind of is
just going to exist in its own episode. You know what, yeah, we're going to call it here.
Conjuring can wait. Haunted movie one can wait. We're going to go ahead and end it here because,
again, this story is just blowing my mind. Who wrote it? When? Why? How?
It's a mystic. The goal is a scientific. I don't know. Talking about the Conjuring being haunted
film seems a little anticlimactic after that. So we're going to go ahead and end it here.
Hopefully you guys don't mind. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also
hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @JasonOCarvener. DeadRabbitRadio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today. And check out their website and check out those
codes. Maybe you'll see an alternate reality of your own. Have a great one, guys.
Bye.