You steal a man's iPad.
You find horrible images.
What do you do next?
And then we take a look at two stories.
The implications are chilling.
Is it possible that human beings aren't simply being abducted by aliens,
but we're being lured to areas to make it easier for them to get us today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm here. I was Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You're like, Jason, I can tell you're sick.
I can tell. I've been listening to the show for a long time.
I can tell when you're sick.
Yes. Yes. There's a lot of episodes where I've gotten sick
and I always get allergies this time of year.
It's nothing to panic about.
The problem is, when I lay sleeping on my back,
it all gets into my esophagei.
Because I'm a dude, so I have an esophagei.
Women have an esophagus. I bet you didn't know that.
And it just gets all gooey inside there.
So I'm miserable.
But that doesn't mean I'm not having a great day,
because I am having a great day.
Just have a little bit of a head cold.
I went outside for a little bit, man.
I did some steppin'. I got on a stair.
I just walked up and down it 120 times.
And just staying moving.
I think I'm going to do a home workout routine,
because I'm self-isolating.
I'm self-isolating here.
So here's where we're at right now.
Not talk about me. This isn't Jason's video blog,
or vlog, is what you kids call it.
This is Dead Rav Radio, where we talk about crazy stuff.
So let's go ahead.
That was a tour. That might have been the worst segue I've ever done.
But whatever.
So let's go ahead.
I was supposed to talk about this story yesterday,
and I ran out of time for it.
But I've actually, this is a story that I've kind of...
I've told variations of this story throughout the years.
It's not like I made it up.
It's not Goldilocks and the Three Bears,
and I'm slowly refining it.
This happens every so often.
And each time you get different results from the people involved in it.
But recently, let's hop on board the Jason Jalopy.
We're driving up. The borders are closed.
Let's hop on board the Carvener Coptor.
We're going to Canada. We're going to Regina.
That's in the Saskatchewan province.
In Canada.
It's February 23rd, 2020.
So like just a couple of weeks ago,
Dude walks into a police station.
And he's sweating.
"Oh my God, you don't have the coronavirus, do you?"
And he's like, "What? No, that's not news yet.
It's only February 23rd."
The cops are like, "Oh yeah, yeah. We're not taking it seriously over here yet."
And the dude's coughing on him.
Touching all their paperwork.
He goes, "So, officers, I have a problem.
It's not a respiratory illness. I have another problem.
I'm being extorted."
The cops are like, "Oh, you've piqued our interest."
You know, a lot of times, police work.
It's boring.
Traffic stuff. And then you got domestic disputes,
which is like super dangerous work.
And you know, it's just a bunch of boring stuff.
You want to be driving around in cars,
shooting bad guys.
But this isn't that. You're not driving around shooting people.
But it's something different than
this guy's playing really loud rock music.
Can he tell him to stop? This guy comes in and says,
"I'm being extorted. I'm being blackmailed."
Police officers go, "Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Police officers go, "Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
It's like my Kindle. I'll never know what happened to Bella and Edward.
Jeremy goes, "Oh, no, no, no. It's none of that stuff."
It's full of child porn.
It's just full of a bunch of child porn is all.
And she's threatening to release the child porn
to all of my friends and family
if I don't pay her X amount of dollars.
And so the cops go,
"Okay, yeah, that's a whole extortion.
Whoa, blackmail. That's like the worst crime
we've ever heard of. We actually have a division
dedicated to just stopping blackmail.
Why don't you come into this room
and log on to this computer here
and show us the emails she's sending you."
And they're like, "Oh, I'm so glad I thought you guys
were going to be mad about all the child porn."
And they're like, "No, no, no, what? No way, dude.
Here's your email."
And they're like, "I'm so glad I thought you guys
were going to be mad about all the child porn."
And they're like, "No, no, no, what?
No way, dude. Here, just go ahead
and log into this official police computer."
Yeah, go ahead. Okay, get the camera right here.
So we show your face
and fingers at the same time, type in your password.
Okay, good, good.
He pulls up these emails from this woman
saying, "Hi, I sold your iPad
and I found all the child porn on it.
Pay me X amount of dollars
or I'm going to release all the child porn."
And in the email were photos
from his iPad of child porn.
And the officers go,
"Oh, are those the photos
that are from your iPad?"
And he's like, "Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, those are from my iPad."
And, "Okay, sir, you're under arrest.
Why under arrest?
Because you have put child porn on your iPad."
He just told us that, "Oh, dang, now it.
I thought you guys took extortion work seriously."
Well, the cops did
because then they pretended to be the guy
they emailed her, the person who stole the iPad,
and said, "Hey, I got the money.
Where do you want to meet?
I'll pay you the money."
And the woman goes, "Oh, that's so perfect.
I'm so tired of having to email people child porn."
She meets up in the middle of the park.
Cops arrest her.
The one dude gets charged with child porn,
which is obviously a horrible thing
to get charged with. It's a horrible thing to do.
She gets charged with extortion
and distributing child porn
because she emailed it to him.
So the reason why
I've told the variations
of the story throughout because
there's a heartwarming version of the story
that I've always loved to tell.
And this is that. There's an old story.
This old story. Some kids
broke into this dude's house,
checked all of his stuff,
stole his laptop, stole a bunch of his stuff,
left. And then when they were
back at their little hideout, back at their
where the footclan hangs out,
it's like an arcade and a skate ramp
and all this stuff. The teenagers are using
his stuff. They turn on his laptop full of child porn.
They call the police and say,
"Listen, dude, we broke into this dude's house.
We stole all of this stuff,
but..." And we admit to all that,
"But this is super gross."
And the cops took the computer
and didn't charge the kids. And the dude went to prison
for like 20 years, because there was like a ton of it
on there. There really doesn't even have to be a lot.
Any small amount can get you a serious time.
But I always liked that story. That's what you should...
First off, don't break into people's houses.
But if you ever have a hankering to like
smash a window and steal something, and you
happen to find this stuff, don't then try to
blackmail the guy. Just turn it over to the cops.
Like what was her best case
scenario? That she was going to meet a guy
and he was going to give her like $10,000
or something like that. She was going to give him back this
iPad. And then she would know
that this guy, this grody dude
is walking away with his collection of
child porn. And she's like,
"Ha ha ha! I got all this money!"
That's blood money right there.
But anyways, they're both facing
massive charges and all that stuff.
Gross, if that ever happens to you,
not that your child porn collection
gets stolen, but if you ever like
stumble across someone else's stuff, turn it over to the police.
So there we go.
A story of two gross people
running into each other. She should have just
turned it in. She would have been a hero.
But instead she's a zero. Just like him
in jail. Don't do drugs.
You know, this, I mentioned
a couple episodes back. I said,
"This is an episode of Bad Transitions."
A couple episodes back, I said,
"If this show's too dark for you
because everything else is going on, I don't mind
if you skip a couple of episodes
or stop listening to podcasts all together and come back later,
or whatever."
You're under no obligation to listen to me.
I really enjoy it, and I really enjoy spending the time with you guys.
But I also wanted to give a shout out to another
podcast that I listen to.
It's called the Black Heart Cinema Podcast.
It's a group of dudes who do, they talk about movies.
And they basically do about one movie and episode,
some episodes they've done two.
It's one of those things that, one of the things I like about the podcast is,
they talk about the movie,
but you can tell they have a passion
for film in general.
Because first off, they did an episode about,
this also set them apart.
They reviewed a porno movie, so that obviously
set them apart.
Recently though, they did an episode that they
gave a shout out to me. I want to return the favor.
For the movie, "Triple X," starring Vin Diesel.
And as they're talking about it, you can tell
they have a passion for film because they just start going,
talking about like 90's,
early 2000 action movies in general.
They started talking about the genre and how it changed.
And we saw that
change from "Triple X" to
the new James Bond versions
in the comparison. These guys know their stuff,
is what I'm saying. Some people can just
sit and talk about movies, read an IMDB
page and call it a podcast. That's not these guys.
They actually seem to have a passion for it
and a knowledge about the movie. So I recommend you guys
check them out. Also, dude, they need some
subscriber love. Right now, they got 15
subscribers over there. They got 66
episodes out, so they've been putting in
work, it comes out every week. They've been doing
it for a long time. Let's get them some subscriber
love over there, Black Heart Cinema
Podcast. They're on
EveryWaryListener Podcast and YouTube as well.
Now, I want, let's
move on to our next topic. Our next topic involves
two different stories. And I'm going to tell you up
front that this is
a, this is something similar we've
covered before. So I don't want to feel like
I'm ever repeating myself, but this is
similar to something we've talked about
before. But I think it's important. It's more
information involving a phenomenon that
I mentioned a long, long time ago.
But let's go ahead and strap
in here. The first story
we're going to look at, I don't have
a location for, I just have a month.
So, take with a grain
of salt is what I'm saying. That's, that's
might be the least amount of
information I have for a story.
But it's been backed up by other stories
that I've told in the past and another story I'm going to tell this
episode, so we're going to go with it. It's January,
it's 1989, at night
there's a husband and wife. And
they're sitting at home just kind of doing their own thing
reading the newspaper, wife's cooking dinner,
or let's not be sexist, maybe the man
is cooking dinner and the
woman is baking.
So, anyways, they're doing their own thing and
they both get, they both
get a hankering
to go to a movie. So they're standing
in the kitchen, he's cooking, she's
getting her cookies ready, and they look
at each other and they go, let's go see a movie.
Now it's 1989, so what are they, what are they
watching? They're watching the Deep Six,
what is that, Deep Star Six?
It's 1989, what's at the theater? Terminator
2 hadn't come out yet. They
decide to go see Deep Star Six.
So, they get dressed up, they're going
to cosplayers, they dress up in underwater
suits, and they get into their car, and they
drive to the
movie theater, and they watch Deep Star Six, and they're like
"Eh, I was okay."
You know, a decent creature feature,
I guess.
You know what you're going to do. So,
they walk out of the theater, they get in their car,
they leave the theater,
driving around town
at night. A town that they live in, by the way,
they didn't travel 500 miles
to go see Deep Star Six opening night in Hollywood.
A town that they live
in, driving around at night.
And they're trying to get home,
right, that's what you do after a movie.
You drive, and they're coming down the street,
and there's construction set up,
like a roadway block, and they're like
"Oh, that's..." They must have started
building something in the two hours
we were watching the sci-fi
cinematic masterpiece
Deep Star Six
Do-it-you-turn, start driving the other way.
Coming down another road,
flashing yellow lights,
road crew equipment there. No people!
Just the
barricades in the road.
What? That's weird.
They start to realize
that everywhere they turn
there's construction.
But there's no one actually
doing anything there. They also begin
to realize they don't remember
how to get home.
They're driving around
for hours.
And then finally they get home.
A weird night, obviously.
They get home, they're like
"The movie was mediocre, the most exciting part
was the fact that the city seemed
to surround us, but we're home."
And as years went on
they'd always kind of be like
"That was so weird, remember when we went to go see Deep Star Six?"
Apparently this episode
is a plug for that movie.
And they go "Yeah, it's so weird."
But I don't remember
everything was blocked off and they'd be like
"Yeah, I just have a hard time
really remembering anything about the movie."
Except for the lukewarm performances
of George Clooney's cousin. And I think Clint Howard
was in it too. And she's like "What?"
He's like "I don't know, I don't know. I'm having
vague memories about Deep Star Six now as well."
Years later they decide
to get hypnotized. Now this makes
sense because
we have hypnotism, regression
stuff like that. It's always been
in vogue, at least since the 70's
80's. I remember when I was a kid a lot of people
were doing it. Not a bunch of kids. Kids were like
"What do you want to do for your birthday party, Billy?"
"Pass life regression!"
You have sort of a clown that's hypnotized
me and like "You used to be a monk."
But it was in, when I was
a kid I would see people on television
talking about getting hypnotized and stuff like that.
Hence the name of Biggie's hit song.
So
they decide to do the hypnotism thing.
And this is what they remember
now something more concrete about that night.
They left a movie theater.
They drove to a church parking lot.
They remember that.
They remember
a flying saucer
hovering above them in this empty church parking lot.
They have flashes
of gray aliens reaching out to them.
Of being pinned down
to medical tables.
Of painful procedures
of painful procedures.
And
they notice something later as well.
In the real world, outside of their memories.
The wife
she used to have a blood clotting disease.
It's now gone.
Now you're going Jason, that story is kind of ridiculous.
You don't have a place.
You don't have names of people.
You're missing key parts of information.
You can't even tell us the town it took place.
That's fair.
And you think
if you got abducted by aliens
or you went to see deep star 6
she got lost. You don't know where you're at.
You get home. And then
between that and getting hypnotized
she didn't realize that her blood clotting disease was gone.
I mean I don't think you feel it.
I don't think you're like oh the clots.
The clots they hurt. I don't think it works that way.
But if she was a hemophiliac
and her blood didn't clot
did she not get caught. It's suspicious.
But it's an interesting story. Because if you will remember
long time ago
and I tried to remember
in what episode it was I couldn't.
I talked about a thing called disguised abduction.
It was a short story
where a woman got in a car crash
and
she had a hard time remembering
which will happen after a car crash.
But there was like a car crash or she saw a car crash
and she couldn't
drive around it or something like that.
I vaguely have memories of it. I don't know if the aliens got to it too.
But the point is that there was a weird
I think it was a car. That was it.
She was driving on the road and there was a car crash
but there was nobody in any of the cars
and she was like this is weird.
And she was kind of like looking around the car crash
and then eventually after a period of time she drives away.
And then she had
she remembered
through hypnosis there was a UFO
the car crash was completely made up.
There was a UFO that abducted her
and experimented on her. And the theory was
was that
the aliens we've always heard this
story of like false memories
and it's kind of the idea that
you get abducted
and then you get put back on earth and you're like
oh I don't remember all of this horrible stuff.
It turns out the aliens may actually
be able to
create completely false memories
in you. Not you go to bed
you wake up you don't remember being abducted.
You go to work
and you go into the bathroom stall
you get abducted and then you remember
the rest of your day at work.
So when you wake up at home
this morning you're like oh that was weird.
Of course then there's other people there
and be like dude where'd you go you went to the bathroom stall you disappeared
for like 10 hours. You walk in here you're all sweaty
you've something sticking out your butt you obviously got anal probed
what? Oh I didn't even notice that.
But if you were in a
solo environment or like in this case
husband and wife together
both going out and
that's the other creepy thing.
But we'll get to that in a second.
We'll get to that in a second. Let's take a look at another one of these stories.
February 11th
Levittown Long Island this is 9pm
we're getting some more information on this one.
There are these two
musicians in their apartment who I can only
assume are the Beastie Boys
hanging out in their apartment in Levittown
I think they're in the Bronx it doesn't matter.
These two guys these two musicians
were fighting for their right
to party making music
in this apartment. I'm sure the neighbors
loved these guys I'm sure they were totally awesome.
And they start to hear
weird noises. Noises
that are weird because they're not making them.
Someone else is being annoyingly loud.
And both dudes run to the window
and they look and they see four
military helicopters
cut across the night sky.
In the four helicopters are not flying
in a line they're flying in formation.
They're flying in a box.
And in the middle of
the helicopters
is what they describe as a massive
shiny vehicle.
Saucer shaped?
We don't know.
But definitely not
human.
Not identifiably human.
These two dudes look at each other.
Whoa dude. They run
they get in their car and they begin driving through
the city of Long Island. That's a city right?
They're driving through
the area known as Long Island
Levittown. And they're looking up
through their windows and they can see the four helicopters
and the
metal ship flying in formation with them.
They start to get on the expressway
and then all of a sudden
the four helicopters
break formation and start to fly away.
The metal ship becomes a flaming
ball.
And then both of them black out.
The next thing they know
they're turning onto a bridge.
What?
What was that? I don't know. You saw that right?
Yeah, yeah, the helicopters and the
shiny vehicle. There's multi-colored
lights flashing all around it. Yeah, it was
weird. And turned to fireball.
You say, "Yeah, yeah, yeah, but weren't we just on the expressway?"
Now they're just silently
they're not silently they're talking but now
they're driving across this bridge
in Long Island.
Later on, months, years later, we don't know
but later on one of the young men
remembers
things.
He remembers
being in a room
with gray aliens.
And he remembers seeing
hieroglyphics everywhere.
The hieroglyphic motif
is, I'm starting to see
is very common
in alien lore. Now I don't,
I am not a proponent of ancient aliens.
I will say this.
I think it's possible that aliens have visited
us in the past.
I don't believe that all of our
great wonders are because of aliens. I
believe that humans
are so uniquely advanced.
We built the pyramids. We built
these temples. We built all
of these things without any alien
intervention. So
I don't think they're necessarily Egyptian hieroglyphics.
A lot of times people say they're hieroglyphics
and then when I did that story recently about the scientists
Deep Prasad
he said they were hieroglyphic. Look,
if I saw weird symbols
that seemed to be showing
some sort of, like a guy
walking, I would describe it as hieroglyphic.
It doesn't mean that it's actually hieroglyphic.
Deep Prasad said
it reminded him of hieroglyphics.
Deep Prasad is a quantum
scientist. He has the language
for these type of things. If I just saw him and said
they're hieroglyphics, I don't necessarily think aliens
were messing around with the Egyptians
helping to build temples. Because if that was
true, hieroglyphics is a really, really
primitive way to write things.
So if the aliens were coming down
and teaching the Egyptians how to write, they sucked
at that. I think what we're
seeing is their language.
Well, now I'm kind of knocking the aliens language too,
but maybe they do have a sucky language.
Or maybe the best way we can look at it
is a hieroglyphic. And really
it's this super advanced thing. I don't know. But anyways,
Egyptian hieroglyphics aren't the most
advanced writing form on the planet.
I don't... they're not
even in my top ten personally. And I'm a big
writing dude.
I love cursive.
Whatever the steady... stenography.
No, that's not it. Doesn't matter.
The point is, is that both of these stories,
and the story I told in an earlier episode,
have some chilling things
going on. One, it's the idea that
you can be abducted
and you're given
this memory that
halfway makes sense.
That's weird. It's almost like...
and it makes sense from an alien point of
view. If the alien is trying to
replicate the human experience, but doesn't understand
the human experience,
it just says,
"Oh, we need to keep... we need to fill
your brain with memories for a while."
And we know humans drive down
roads,
so we're going to put
barricade... but see, that doesn't make sense.
Like, as a human, you'd be like, "Why are there all these barricades here?"
If a human was going
to implant false memories in somebody else,
you would go, "Oh, they're dry...
We'll have them driving down the road,
and then we'll make them remember taking a turn
off and going to the old place they used to make out,
and they drive out there for a while, and they...
they make out or whatever, and then they come back.
Apparently, I'm the pervert.
I'm putting in perverted stuff.
I'm like, "Oh, yeah." Then he was kissing his cat.
"Ooh, he loves it." They're like, "Jason,
quit putting in gross false memories."
My point is that a human
could come up with better ones, and alien would just be like,
"Oh, bunch of stuff,
a bunch of random stuff to keep you from getting
home. Here's your false memories."
With the two musicians,
they didn't necessarily have a false memory,
but they... actually,
that's the second part that makes it creepy.
Both of these groups of people,
they were lured out of their houses.
The couple at home
going, "You know what? Let's go see a movie."
And they drive to the...
They had no... who wants to see
Deep Star 6 in the theater?
Really. I don't know if that's exactly
what they saw, but the story
goes they were just standing there
and they go, "Let's go see a movie."
Like, it popped in both their head at the same time.
They drive out to watch the movie
when they go to go home. They're trapped.
And then eventually they have
these memories of being abducted.
With these two young men,
they already saw Deep Star 6.
They don't care about that. What's going to get
two young dudes out of the apartment?
You could have had a bunch of curvy. You could have some gray aliens
wearing wigs and like tight dresses.
Like a Bugs Bunny cartoon. They're like, "Hey boys!"
Or...
Because I've done this. If there's a bunch
of cop cars flying by, I will
follow them. Not anymore, because I walk.
But I used to have a car. I used to follow
cop cars all the time. I always used to...
police helicopters searching the area to go out to the area.
Just hang out.
See what's going on.
With Sacramento too, so that happened a lot.
But that's going to get you out of your house.
You see four military helicopters
escorting a UFO. That's way better than a police chase.
You're going to go out there.
And you have to think
they're seeing it.
But this was never reported in the mainstream
media.
So that makes me think no one else
in the city is seeing this thing.
It was unique to them.
And it wanted to get them to a location
where it could abduct them.
So not only
is it possible that people are being abducted
and never even
knowing about it.
They're just that time you went for a walk.
And it's not like you walked out
your house. The next thing you know
you were standing in the middle of Virginia
wearing a raincoat. You're like, "Well, what?"
You walk out of your house. You're walking down the street.
You see a cat. You're like, "Oh, look at this.
Cool little cat." You walk a couple more feet.
You see a squirrel. You're like, "Oh, that's cool."
Then you walk a few more feet and you see the squirrel
riding the cat.
What?
And then you... that what?
Did I just see that? And then you turn the corner
and you go back home.
And in that time period
was basically an al...
you get abducted and an alien going,
"Well, we have to account for these 10 minutes
that we have this due."
And cowboys ride horses
and squirrels look like cowboys
apparently to an alien.
Let's make them ride a cat. That's normal, right?
So you have to think
about all those times you've ever seen...
What if the actually seen a UFO
is the anomaly that's being put
in your brain? Everyone's being abducted.
But that's not
the only scary part about this, because I covered
that on a past episode. The scary part is
is that you can actually be taken out
of your safe space
by your own
"free will"
to get you in a better position to be abducted.
Both of these stories involved people going to places
they wouldn't have been going at that moment.
Both of them
either seeing something or sensing something
to get them to leave that place.
That's scary.
That's scary. Because
it didn't seem weird to any of them.
Well, the UFO flying over town was weird,
but their own instinct to follow it
was normal.
That's creepy. Because I think
the thing that we can count on is
if we're ever in a position
where our lives are in jeopardy,
we can make rational decisions.
But what if that's simply not true?
What if you could be safe at your home
and then go,
"You know what? I want ice cream."
"I have ice cream in my freezer,
but I want a particular type of ice cream
and it's across town at this particular
ice cream shop."
You're driving over there,
you get abducted.
Creepy.
But then let's take it to 11.
The aliens
are ready to make their move.
Whatever their overall goal is,
the aliens are ready
to make their move against humanity.
What will any of our technology matter?
What will any of our military matter?
If they can simply
trick us
into walking outside,
we may want
an Independence Day war with the aliens
to take our planet back,
but when the moment comes,
we may all just walk outside.
Because that's what we want to do
in that moment.
Or at least
that's what we think
we want to do.
[Music]