queer ghosts and queer ghost hunters
bees
Interrupt your civil rights in Britain and
Then we take a trip to the farthest reaches of space with the Mandalorian conspiracy today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too
I know I often say that this is gonna be a short episode because I'm not feeling good
This is gonna be a short episode because I'm not feeling good and it's funny because every time I say it's gonna be a short episode
It ends up being like 35 minutes long
I think you can tell from the sound of my voice that I'm really on my last leg as far as
Sore throat health I need to go to bed as soon as I can but I wanted to get this episode out for you
And I previously just got then recording 15 minutes of stuff and was like yeah, I don't like it
So I'm starting over I'm starting over for you guys my friends
Yesterday's episode I finished off with the story about queer ghost hunters
I teased you he gave you a little tickle little little tickle tickle about queer ghost hunters and what's interesting
We're not gonna spend a ton of time on these guys because I kind of think it might be a joke. It's really really hard to tell
Queer ghost hunters you go. Oh, it's a bunch of queer people that are hunting ghosts. That's interesting
Well, they are that they are a bunch of queer people interviewing not interviewing
Investing what am I what's oh man? I'm so tired
Hunting ghosts queer people hunting ghosts. That's the name queer ghost hunters. They're not queer ghost interviewers
So they're not just queer people who hunt ghosts. They're queer people
They're queer people who hunt ghosts, but the ghosts they hunt are
Gay like they hunt gay ghosts and and lesbian ghosts and stuff like that
Which oh which brings up a whole bunch of questions and I'll get to those in a second, but
This is their logic when ghost hunters show up at a place
They're like how many women have you slept with and the ghost will be like oh five or whatever little EVP farve
And they said well, that's weird that every time someone shows up
They ask a ghost if it's a man if he was married if it's a woman they ask if it was a husband now
What's funny is I'd have never really heard that I've never when I used to watch a lot of ghost hunting shows
I never hear them show up and be like so
Did you like blonde or brunette women like I think that might be something that they perceived was going on
But I don't know I've never seen that at least, but I'm not saying it's not happening. I've just never been aware of that
And they said that if you think about this why I thought was kind of funny
If you think and it's true in a sense if you think about the most haunted places
It's places where gay people
hung out the most
you have
theaters like big ballrooms and stuff like that and a bunch of gay dudes hanging out there
Operas stuff like that theaters operas big fancy mansions
That one's a little more iffy because big fancy mansions were just where rich people hung out insane
Asylum's in prisons though
Which I mean there was a point in time where if you were gay you did get sent to the insane asylum
And it was you know sodomy was a crime now those last two
Here's the thing this is the thing I this is the thing really that's the most interesting thing about this
They self-identifying 4.5 percent of the population I self-identifies as LGBT queer people
So even in a in the world of the paranormal you're still gonna scale that in
So in the amount of which which not every human being leaves a ghost just right off the bat and
Out of those ghosts you would figure five maybe high-ball at 10% of all the ghosts that can be encountered are
Queer so you're actually making it even harder for you to find ghosts
But they have this YouTube show
Like two and a half seasons long. They're still trying to get new episodes
Where they keep running into gay ghosts and you go Jason. How do they know they're gay?
Well, they have these
dowsing rods and they go
Are you gay and then the rods move and they're like oh lesbian lesbian ghost
Which again, I think the whole thing might be made up
They did raid third they they did raise $35,000 on Kickstarter and they currently have a patreon going
Part of me part of me thinks it's a parody
But it could be real but here's my questions about it one first off ghosts are incredibly hard to hunt hunt in the first place
You're making it even harder if you only want to find queer ghosts secondly
What's the ethical ramifications of outing someone after they're dead?
Because they don't I mean a ghost from the 1800s. They'll be like we're gay. They went to a
They went to a nun graveyard and they go there's a bunch of lesbian nuns nuns
They were a lot of lesbian nuns out there, which I don't know statistics on lesbian
I don't know the Venn diagram between lesbians and nuns
But anyways they go to a nun graveyard and they're just walking around the graveyard going we're gay
We are gay so feel comfortable talking to us come to the back of our van
Sit in our van and talk to it if I was from the 1800s and I was a gay nun
I could be like oh what and I and they're doing in the middle of the day
Which was weird too like oh and then you crawl out of your grave your little ghost crawls out of your grave
And then you're like telling them yeah, I'm gay and then you go back to sleep or wherever you go
They don't understand they're on YouTube. They don't understand video cameras or anything like that
So outing someone after their death is that there was one where the guys was like
Who do you think is cute in the group or do you think Mike they're talking to a guy ghost and there's three guys in the room
And they're like which one of us do you think is cute and it's like
Mikey and he's like oh they just see they're
Well, I think that parts made up to like that's the whole that's the weirdest thing about this like
It's so hard to get a ghost to just admit what its name is but this one is like giving it relationship advice
Being like I love your shirt like though. I think it's a setup. I really think it's a wind up
But it raises some interesting questions one
Does your sexuality go with your spirit I
Think there's a lot of stuff
That we assign biological traits to that would have no
Relevancy to be in a ghost. Let me say this to
John Jack London did not write cannery row. That was John Steinbeck. I looked that up afterwards
I had a sneaking suspicion while I was doing some editing. I go great. So
Jack London did not write cannery row that was on yesterday's episode
But on yesterday's episode I said that ghosts may just be these forms that then we put a physical
presentation on top of that's why famous people
Show up looking as you remember to Marilyn Marilyn Monroe's ghost is an uploaded fat gross
Blob because she has she laid in her own organ
She what's that thing called when you get all purple not not holding your breath
Well, that happens when you die too, but rig a mortis if you saw her ghost, she'd be all glamorous. I
Think the idea of like there might be some forms out there that we're putting thought projections on and
That's why we would see a white ghost as a white dude and a black ghost as a black ghost
But why would the soul matter in that case the actual soul
The the energy that is existing outside the body would if it's black or white
Then what if the ghost as a living person had Down syndrome does the ghost have Down syndrome if
the ghost was
If you had somebody who had both their arms chopped off and they died their ghost wouldn't have both their arms chopped off
I'm thinking that right because otherwise everyone who died would basically it'd be like Beetlegees
She would be the death you'd be a ghost of your
Of your body, so I don't it's so why is it that you would see a oh an Asian ghost
Appear like an Asian man and a white ghost appear like an Asian man
No white ghost would appear as a white man
But how does that of that's your that's the physical body that shouldn't affect what the soul looks like I
Don't imagine if a guy who's three feet tall his soul is not three feet tall
So if the biological and that and I you can you can we can argue about that because obviously that's not what we see
When you see a ghost of George Washington
It looks like George Washington, but I think that is just our representation or our perceiving the energy that's actually there
So extrapolating that further
Sexuality is who we are your your your sexual preference. I guess it should say is who you are attracted to
It's who your body reacts to
When I see an attractive woman walking down the street my body reacts to that whether it's my eye my eyes go
My blood pressure goes up whatever like I'll see an attractive woman
I will feel an attraction towards her like physically and I'm not talking about pop it
You know, I'm not talking about you know getting a boner
I'm talking about I can feel my body react to a beautiful woman in my presence or a beautiful woman walking 50 yards away
But those are biological markers. There's it's a biological thing. That's happening when I'm seeing a woman. I want to mate with
my ghost
Would my ghost be like a
Little cartoon ghost eyes. I don't think so. I don't think your sexuality is
such an important component of
Your soul
Because your soul if you imagine if you think about something like the Tree of Life
We're not getting to the other two stories
By the way, you talk about something like the Tree of Life that we've discussed before
The soul exists before your body and
Then your soul is in your body and it may exist by
Millennial or it may exist by simply moments, but your soul goes into your body and then it leaves when you die
so your soul is
Beyond sexual preference. It's be if in
Living times if while I'm alive. I love to eat chili beans and rice and then I die and my soul is has that same dietary preference
And but all that's there to eat is nothing because I'm a ghost
The dietary preference doesn't carry over either. I don't I this might this might sound super rambly
But I feel like I'm trying to put my thoughts together while we're constructing this you're like Jason
This might be the least funny episode and I apologize for that also. I'm sick, but
the
idea of your preferences
existing before or after
you die seems
Universally such a minute thing and then I feel the same thing what about race or or your sex or your gender I
Feel that none of I feel that the soul itself is
Neither male nor female or both
It's neither white black eastern European Persian. It's all of those and nothing
Most likely nothing is most likely not both male and female. It's simply transcended that
So I don't think you could have a straight ghost or a gay ghost
You could have a ghost of someone who was gay who died
But I don't think the ghost is still like search, you know going on grinder the same way
I don't think that a straight ghost would be going on Tinder
I
Course I have absolutely nothing to back any of that up. I just find it in I find it interesting that
In the realm of ghosts these questions don't really get asked
Let me ask you this - this is an interesting question if a trans woman died
Would her ghost
be a trans woman or a woman who was born a woman?
There's tons of questions
Because what would be the what would be the represent?
Let's say I'm totally wrong with my idea that souls have no sexual preference no dietary preference no race
Nothing like say I'm totally wrong and all that and if you're a white dude and you die your ghost is a white dude in
That theory if you're a trans woman or a trans man and you die is your ghost that of a trans woman or trans man or
a
Woman who was born a woman or a man who was born a man. How would your ghost?
Be what is your ghost? What is your soul on that level?
So as much as I think the queer ghost hunters is a parody because and they don't seem to be fair
They seem like a lovable bunch of ragamuffins and they don't seem to take themselves super seriously
And I think that's why I keep leaning on the parody thing because in the beginning the like during their credits
They kind of do the serious pose like the ghost hunter shows and they kind of start laughing so you're like they don't take themselves
That's you seriously
But they raise a whole host of questions
What survives death
What survives death and it's one of those things that will never know obviously
But I guess as long as you have groups they're not as far as I saw I watched a couple episodes
So they're not actively and asking these questions as far as I saw but having these kind of groups that are kind of
Not traditional ghost sending groups
It is it does kind of make you think about the stuff on a different level
So I congratulate them for that. Maybe we do have time for the last two stories here
But I do have to go soon because I'm super sick
Bees
Let's leave behind the queer ghosts the queer ghost hunters. We're gonna go to Britain and
There's a bunch of bees flying around right I'm gonna try to get a little bit of humor in this one
Cuz that one was just sounding like like I was super stoned and just going off the top of my head
Which to be fair I was going off the top of my head, but not super stoned
Here I don't even need to do bees. Yeah, I've already told you that right bunch of bees flying around
Here is the thing this might
I'm so tired. Okay. Where did you go bee be notes? I actually had to take notes for this hold on in
1980 Britain the the most police state in Europe. I swear to God these guys are so brutal in 1980
They enacted the bee act
Which means
If the authorities think there are bees in your home they can go in without a search warrant
Not only can they go in your home it is it is it is specified
They can also go into any vessel
boat
Hovercraft aircraft what are they chasing down co-ver commander or vehicle of any other description
In which he has reasonable grounds for supposing there are or have been bees or
Other things subject to control under an order under that section. So probably like wasps hornets
Yeah, all they have to do is show a badge if they think be if they think you had bees in your hovercraft aircraft
They just show a badge and then they kick down your door and get in now. Hopefully
I'm just about to give up on this episode
Okay, let's move on to our next story
You know what jokes bad when you don't even finish it
Let's just get on with the next story so I can go to bed
You'll have to email me and you'll have to say hey Jason
We would rather not have an episode than an episode where you're one clearly dying and to
Barely trying so let me know in the comments like share subscribe this video
Share it with your friends. Maybe not this one
Mandalorian the Mandalorian
You know you guys hear me talk about this is our last story
You guys have heard me talk about Disney in the past
Usually I taught I say I watch a lot of Disney stuff, but every show often I'll make a comment like they're I
Said that they were I
used Disney of
Faking death threats against theater that were showing the Joker I
Reference that Mickey Mouse may be a representation of the ultimate evil a summoning spirit. That was a long time ago
all sorts of stuff and I also
quite often make fun of
The new the sequel trilogy Star Wars movies both on the show in real life. I've never seen any of them
I've never seen Force Awakens the last Jedi. I've read the plots and they sound super stupid and
I never saw Rogue one
I have seen that Darth Vader scene quite a few times like near near when he's walking on the hallway and
I watched a little bit of Han Solo
And I thought it all pretty much sucked except the Darth Vader scene was cool
But I had no interest in watching any of the Disney Star Wars stuff. I was a huge fan of the original trilogy
I'm actually a fan of the prequels and
So
But I really wanted to see the Mandalorian and I do watch a lot of Disney stuff
So I recently signed up for Disney Plus Disney Plus is the service that you too can subscribe to for just 699 and one
If you use the promo code dead rabbit
You'll get nothing off because it doesn't exist. Anyways
So I got Disney Plus
I got it because I wanted I was really curious about the Mandalorian
But at 30 years of Simpson episodes plus all the other Disney Channel stuff
I watched all that stuff is included in their basic package for 699 a month
So I watched the episode of the Mandalorian now what was interesting was I began to snoop around and check out stuff
see what other people thought about Mandalorian YouTube videos Easter eggs stuff like that and
Just clicking on randomly I found a couple of them and they said the comment. Hey listen man not a fan
Basically what I just said I'm not a fan of the new sequel, but this
Mandalorian show this Mandalorian show reminds you why you love Star Wars this Mandalorian show is a love letter to the fan
And I heard that on a couple different YouTube videos and I thought
Disney's paying people to say this
Like this is weird because they're using kind of the same terminology
Now I have to say two things to this one obviously I have no proof of that
But it seems like it's right up a wheelhouse Disney totally screwed up Star Wars with the last Jedi
They were already people were okay with the Force Awakens. I thought it was stupid that they just told the same story first order
Resistance rebel I thought all this stuff was dumb thought all this was super stupid
I thought it was a total fake out or they made it look like Finn was going to be the next Jedi and then he's like
Or and then Ray gets the sword you're like what like even on the posters he had the lightsaber really kind of just a weird
I stormtrooper being a Jedi. I thought was an interesting concept
but anyways I
Totally screwed it up with the last Jedi to the point that Han Solo was a huge flop and
The last Jedi didn't make as much money and no matter how much they spin it people are now coming out and saying how much they
Don't like that movie even though these same people at the time were defending the last Jedi
Which again makes me think that Disney was pumping money into these YouTube people
To prop to prop it up and to say if you don't like last Jedi
It's because you have a defect of a personality the last Jedi is actually this totally great subversive film this slow-speed chase
Through space that takes place in about eight hours. What a great epic Star Wars movie, but anyways
Mandalorian comes out and all of a sudden the thing has changed. Oh those sequels boo
This reminds you why you liked Star Wars this reminds you why you like sorry and that's actually a perfect marketing thing and
Disney's always had this conspiracy around them that were not always but fairly recently
That they're manipulating
ratings and rotten tomatoes and
basically social engineering people Batman vs. Superman
Civil war yay, and you look at all the reviews and people's reactions saw this up Batman vs. Superman is
200 times better than Civil War
now
It wasn't a very well constructed film, but what it tried to do is basically the difference between
watching someone try to jump the Grand Canyon and
Only making it halfway
Versus someone on a three-foot slip and slide in the backyard
that's the difference between Civil War and and Batman vs. Superman
This idea that you shoot for the stars at least she'll hit the moon Civil War was basically like oh remember those dudes
Anyways anyways, I think Disney does prop up their properties and now they realize that the last shit
I sucked they have to admit to that I think they knew it early on but anyways now they're telling people
Hey and subscribe to Disney plus six ninety nine a month and you'll get to watch this new show if you're a true Star Wars fan
This is this is what it is. I think that Disney is
Do and run in the same game, but now they're actually pooping all over their past properties to get support for this one
Because people are using that same terminology
What's weird too is that
They're kind of right
like I really really enjoyed the Mandalorian and it reminded me of
Old Star Wars it reminded me of the original trilogy the way that it looked the way that it felt
so really really well put together television show and
It's not doesn't dumb stuff down
There's a scene. This isn't a spoiler Mandalorian walks into a room. This takes place like five or six years after return
Mandalorian walks into the room and there's a guy sitting behind a desk
There's four stormtroopers and their armor is totally dirty and scuffed up not battle scarred like actually dirty
And they're standing around and one of them looks a little skinnier than you would imagine a stormtrooper to be
That's it
They just kind of stand there and there's this little meeting and
Then he leaves
Now a dumb television show before he went there. They would have been like hey look out about this guy
He's hired rogue Empire soldiers after the fall of the Empire
They needed something to do and you'd be like okay
So they're actually like old stormtroopers or a guy could have said yeah the guy rolls with stormtroopers
Turns out it's just a bunch of bandits who found some armor
But still they might shoot you in the back and you'd be like oh then these guys are you you don't know the movie
The show is really good at just like putting you in a room
Using terminology you don't know and you're kind of like well, I guess I guess that means a bucket
I guess that means something you put it in I don't really understand what they're talking about
So the show is actually pretty smart as far as that goes but
Yeah, I and the whole episode is like that. It's just it assumes you are a resident of this galaxy
So you should know what they're talking about very very well done show
But does that mean that
There is no conspiracy doesn't mean that Disney is not I just realized that this has nothing to do with the topic of the show
I just am talking about Mandalorian at this point
Does this might honestly be this I'm not even going to title this episode anything
This is a this is an episode. This is a spin-off for a new podcast
This is the lost episode
Does that mean that Disney actually is a spin-off for a new podcast?
Does that mean that Disney actually isn't pulling a conspiracy? I
am almost for certain that Disney is paying people to say
All of our other stuff sucked
But this is the good one and the sad thing is is that they've been working on this bounty hunter show for like 10 years
I remember hearing about HBO going to have a star war show focusing on bounty hunters
If this had come out first
And it was a hit which I am sure it's shaping up to be
It would totally change the whole dynamic of these prequel these sequel movies that are just rehashes
Death stars and stuff like that totally would have changed look. I think it's directed by the guy who did a lot of the clone war stuff
But anyways, it didn't it came out after we had to sit through princess layoff flying through space
and all that other stuff so
Is Disney committing a conspiracy?
To get people to watch their show probably it's it's actually now that I say it's not a conspiracy
It's called marketing. You know what?
This episode has completely gone off the rails. I apologize, but
Here's the dilemma. Do I release this episode?
Knowing that it's it's it's barely functional as an episode it barely works
or
Do I put a message on twitter saying sorry guys not feeling good. No episode tonight
If
You're hearing this episode
Then you know which decision I made obviously
I'm going to get a good night's sleep
And I will be back monday with it with a relevant episode an episode that makes sense
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be your essay shake my head dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily
queer ghosts be
And mandalorian podcast you don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]