A terrifying haunting at a high school reminds us that even though we think someone's head
has been cracked open, they might still be alive.
It's very specific advice, but it might be applicable someday to you.
And then we travel to outer space to try to figure out if we're a crewmate or an imposter
in the popular game Among Us.
But is the popularity of this very simple game natural?
Or is Among Us actually a CIA plot to get us to vote out the unvaccinated?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter here, I'm having a great day, hope you guys are having a great
day too.
Hope you guys had an awesome weekend.
We've got a ton of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away walking into
Dead Rabbit Command.
Everyone get on your feet and give a warm round of applause to Colin M. Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in Colin M. Come on in and look it.
He brought a guest with him.
A super sexy alien, huh?
If you guys were wondering what I'm talking about and you can't see the cover art for
today's episode, for my birthday Colin sent me a statue of a sexy grey alien, I gotta
admit.
I might betray humanity.
For this level of alien booty, very very sexy alien, I'm gonna make sure that she appears
in our live streams coming up.
Like please don't Jason, it's bad enough to see him looking at the photo.
Actually I don't know yet, am I gonna take a photo from the front or the photo from behind?
She's quite sexy.
I guess I shouldn't out myself with so much as an alien pervert.
This is your first episode, but if you've listened to the show long enough you know
that I'm truly an alien pervert.
Colin you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode, if you guys can't expose my
fetishes, that's okay too.
Just help spread the word about this show that really, really really helps out a lot.
Now Colin, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Give us all the way out to Newport Beach, California.
Nice leisurely drive down to Sunny Sunny Newport Beach.
Specifically we're gonna head out to Newport Harbor High School.
Now at Newport Harbor High School, there's a building known as Robbins Hall and that's
where war headed.
So put on your Letterman's jacket, grab your backpack.
We're basically pretending to be high school students and we're all these people walking
around.
Clearly we're adults but they have really bad security there.
We're walking around, we go into Robbins Hall and it's just a series of classrooms like
most buildings on a high school campus, who would it be?
But Robbins Hall also is home to Loats Theater.
We walk in, we're like oh look at what great stage plays could be performed here.
You could probably do some Hamlet.
You could probably do Cats.
They probably just do high school musical over and over again.
But we're walking around this theater.
It's actually quite grand, a 700 seat theater.
Now in its heyday, this would be the place you'd go to watch a play and to sit in the
cheering section of the playhouse.
But over time it began to get invested with rats.
There was rats everywhere, cockroaches everywhere.
They toured the building down in 2007.
It doesn't exist anymore.
However, there was a time when it did.
And when this theater was there, it racked up like all theaters seem to across the country
and I'm assuming across the world.
Loats Theater also had a ghost story associated with it.
One day these three boys broke into the school.
They're like it's our summer break.
Woo!
What are we gonna do?
Let's go to school.
They broke into the school to drink.
Which I figure you know you're probably out of prionizer.
I didn't say how old these kids are but I'm figuring like teenagers or I don't think they're
like third graders or anything like that.
Three kids are sitting there drinking in Loats Theater and they're on stage.
They're goofing off, it's dark and they're drunk.
It's a bad combination.
Well two of the boys fall off of the stage.
This is actually kind of hilarious.
I'm probably the worst person to talk about kids dying and becoming ghosts because I always
find it so funny.
These two teenage boys are goofing off on stage.
They're drunk.
They both fall off the stage and crack their heads open when they hit the ground.
Now stages can be fairly high.
They're normally not like two stories or anything like that but you're talking about like you
try falling off to defend these idiots now.
You try falling 10 feet into an orchestra pit or just onto the hard ground of that front
row of chairs.
Both of these guys fall off and they both crack their heads open and they're both laying
in the darkness going...
Well probably not saying anything right.
Their brains are smashed.
They're probably not talking at all but who knows.
They're laying there and the third dude is so scared by what happens when he sees his
two friends fall in the darkness and fall off stage and smash their heads into the ground.
He takes off running.
Not running to go get help.
Not running to a pay phone to call 911.
He just went home.
He's probably going to go get help.
And as you're sitting there bleeding next to your buddy and his blood's like pooling
and it's like making a bigger puddle of blood.
Happy Halloween, guys!
You and your friends' blood is like pooling together and making an even bigger pool.
You'd be laying there in the darkness and after 20 minutes, then 50 minutes, and then
two hours, you're waiting for your friend to come back with help and you're just laying
there in the darkness going, "Where is he?"
Like, I could literally see that being somebody's last words, right?
They're waiting for their friend to come back with help.
He never did.
He never told anyone that this had happened.
It's a terrifying story.
I mean, like really, when you step back, you put your bagel down and you think about it.
Like, I could imagine someone's only hope, just ditching them and you're just waiting
for them until eventually you bleed out, right?
Terrifying story, terrifying ghost story.
We don't know how much of it's true.
The theater's been torn down now.
That has never stopped hauntings, though.
We've covered stories.
I always try to remember exactly where this took place, but there was a three-story building
that had a haunting on the third floor.
They ended up demolishing the building and building a two-story building and you can
still hear the haunting, but like you can hear it a couple feet above the roof of the
new two-story building.
So simply by demolishing the building, wouldn't get rid of the ghost if it happened in the
first place, right?
Like, I'm gonna find any proof of this, but a scary way to start off another spooky week
of the month of October.
Call in M. Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Carbentercopter.
We are leaving behind Newport Harbor High School.
Take us all the way out to deep space.
[imitates carbenter]
Maybe we're gonna meet some sexy aliens.
I don't know while we're up there.
You never know what's gonna happen on an episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
We're headed into deep space because we're about to board the ship known as the Skelb.
That is the ship that is world famous among elementary school students, world-round, as
to where the game Among Us takes place.
Or one of the maps.
The Skelb is a ship.
If you guys aren't familiar with Among Us, you guys are just waking up from a coma because
you split your head falling off of a stage.
Among Us is a video game.
Among Us is a video game and it's basically the movie the thing in video game format.
I guess there's also like card games or party games called like Mafia and Werewolves attacking
me or whatever.
Stuff like that, but Among Us is basically you have let's say eight people.
You have six people who are trying to repair the ship and then you have one or two imposters
that are killing the other players.
So it's kind of like a mystery game where you come across by, I don't even know why I'm
bothering explaining this.
I think everybody knows what Among Us is.
Anyways, the video game Among Us, it came out, this is very interesting conspiracy theory
because this is one of those ones that I think we can argue on the details, but there might
be something here.
I think we can argue, not on the details, I think we can argue on the motive.
Let's take a look at this.
Among Us, it's a video game.
It's about paranoia.
It's about not knowing who to trust.
Everybody looks the same.
Everybody can act the same, but you have a murderer among you whose only goal is to kill
off everybody and take control.
But is there a darker conspiracy behind this game Among Us?
It is one of the biggest games in the world.
Is there something more maniacal pushing this game into the forefront?
Was it just an accidental success like we see sometimes in the world of entertainment?
Or was this government planned propaganda?
Let's go ahead and take a look at this new conspiracy theory that I just saw on the
export the other day.
The theory is this.
You had the COVID-19 pandemic really starting to hit the national headlines in March of
2020.
I think it was in the headlines before that, but that's when like, first it was like, "Oh,
new disease, whatever.
How many of these pop up a year or two?
Oh, I can't leave my house?
Like, this is new.
Like, I've lived through swine flus and bird flus, but I was just, you know, like, walking
around, I was walking around, eating pigs and eating chickens.
But now I can't leave my house.
Like, it really started making waves in 2020.
And the conspiracy theory is this, is that the powers that be said, "Okay, here's the
game plan."
I'm so glad I'm not on YouTube anymore because if I was on YouTube, I would just know this
video would get, I'd get hassled with this video.
But to Spotify, who also likes to rattle my cage, this is not my conspiracy theory.
Okay.
Simply reporting on it.
The powers that be, the government, the new world order, the Illuminati, whatever you
want to call them said, "Okay, we've now done stage one.
We've released this disease that we created.
Stage two is we want everyone to get this vaccination."
We probably should have started with promoting something like that.
I don't know why we're waiting so long.
But anyways, we've released this disease.
It's all over the world now.
Now we want people to take the vaccination.
How do we get people to get a vaccination, right?
We're having people put something in their arm that really, they're going to be nervous
about.
It hasn't gone through long-term tests.
So somebody in this powerful group of people said, "How about we find a video game, specifically
a video game?"
This conspiracy says it wasn't about finding music or movies or predictive programming.
They said, "What if we found a video game that started retraining people's brains to
look at other people suspiciously?"
And we use this game to start to program people to say the majority of people are the vaccinated
ones who are vaccinated against this COVID-19 disease.
And the people who don't get vaccinated are literal monsters who, by simply being around
us, can kill us in any moment.
In short, ladies and gentlemen, they'd be sus.
I'm CIA and the Illuminati and everyone's clapping.
So they decided to do this.
They decided to take a video game to promote this ideology.
And they happened to find the perfect one.
They didn't...
The conspiracy theory is not that the government created among us, is that they started looking
for a game and the game they found was Among Us, which had come out in 2018.
And that game has a really interesting pedigree.
It was created by a small group of people called InnerSloth, that's the name of their
gaming company.
It came out in 2018, it was an app, and it was a total bomb.
At a certain point, they were like, "Why are we even doing updates to this game?"
They were losing money on the game.
I was reading this Wikipedia article and they were saying, "We had enough money in savings
that let us keep going, but the game wasn't selling.
We weren't making any money from the game."
However, we had a super dedicated fan base.
They said their concurrent players at any one time back in 2018 when the game first
came out was only 30 to 50 people.
They really, really liked the game, so we kept pushing updates and fixing bugs and stuff
like that, but we're like, "Wow, this game is not taking off at all."
And it doesn't until mid-2020.
Now the conspiracy theory is that the powers that be found this game.
They found a game that nobody was playing and they went to InnerSloth and they said,
"We will give you the capital.
We're going to give you this massive cash influx."
However, we want you to make some changes to the game.
One of those changes was that the original version of Among Us had no sound effects.
And InnerSloth, the company said, "We didn't have sound effects because we didn't want
to give away."
Like if something was happening in another room, if you heard the sound effect, then
you would know that someone just got killed over there and you could run over there.
So originally the game had no sound effects, which is funny because nowadays all the sound
effects in the game are iconic.
The theme song, the sound of the doors, the sound of the killings, the heads getting chopped
off, they go, "We want you to put in these sound effects."
That's one of the things we want you to put in the sound effects.
And according to this conspiracy theory, the sound effects were, quote, "MK Ultra
Audio Bites."
So these weren't just random sound effects that were being generated by the studio or
they were getting to license or anything like that.
These were actually given to them by the government.
The sound effects, again, here's the thing, I've never heard an MK Ultra Audio Bits.
So I mean, for all I know, this is how they programmed Britney Spears.
They made her listen to doors opening for hours and hours and hours.
Who knows, right?
But anyway, so that's part of the conspiracy theory that the sound effects are actually
MK Ultra Audio Bites, which I mean, if that's the case, then I guess they're using 8-bit
sounds to do all this stuff.
But they promised, interstil off a ton of money, they said, "Listen, we want to use
this game because it's all about paranoia.
It's all about punishing the people who aren't part of the majority."
Because again, the crewmates always outnumber the imposters and it's the goal of the crewmates
to vote out, to get rid of the dangerous people among them.
That's why they called it that.
Then you have that done, right?
So they go to interstil off and they say, "Hey, we're going to pay you a ton of money.
Get this game fixed up.
Put in some new party hats and you need to put in these MK Ultra Audio Bites."
The other part of this thing, because that's a super fascinating conspiracy theory, right?
I don't know if it holds any water.
Probably doesn't.
I read it on the X-word last night.
A couple of people, we'll get to that.
A couple of people talked about it too, but everyone's anonymous.
Who knows what's the truth?
Interesting conspiracy theory, but that would only be half of it, right?
You can have the CIA or MK Ultra groups or Illuminati or whatever create something.
The question is, can you sell it?
That's always the big thing.
I see music videos all the time with full of satanic Illuminati imagery.
They totally flop.
I can name artists you would have no idea who Ivy LeVon was.
You're like, "Who?"
Who?
But I mean, if the Illuminati thing is true, her video's full of it.
She has this video called Biscuit where she keeps talking about you going down on her.
And it's the weirdest thing.
I think maybe once a month I watch this video, because it's so bizarre.
I'll get back to the amongst thing.
But Ivy LeVon is all full of the satanic imagery, and yet every so often a little biscuit shows
up with arms and legs like an egg McMuffin minus the egg and it's dancing.
And she's like, "Kiss my biscuit.
Kiss my biscuit.
Kiss my biscuit."
And I'm like, "What?"
I remember when I first saw it like 10 years ago, I go, "What in the world is this?
This is like pure Illuminati."
I might have even seen it on Vigilant Citizen, which always goes over these music videos
and shows all the Illuminati symbolism, but she's gone nowhere with her career.
I mean, she's a lovely woman.
Her music is fine.
I don't necessarily want to kiss your biscuit.
But you can put all this Illuminati stuff in that.
You can have all this government-controlled stuff.
If that's true, I mean, again, she could just really be in a witch and have this spooky imagery.
But what I'm saying is like, you can create, if the government creates a product that doesn't
necessarily mean it's going to sell.
Doesn't necessarily mean people are going to buy what you have.
So you need to do the other thing.
So Inner Sloth now has this, allegedly, has this infusion of cash from these dark forces
of the government.
I know I keep using these words kind of interchangeably, CIA, and the powers that be.
Next step is to sell it.
But the game had been out since 2018.
You couldn't really market it as a new game.
People would know about it.
So what they did is they really did the best thing they could do.
They began to pay off streamers.
They began to locate Twitch streamers.
That's not hard to locate, right?
You know exactly where they're at.
They have channels.
And you said, "Listen, we're going to pay you X amount of money and you're going to play
this game and you're going to talk about how awesome it is."
Now that happens, right?
That already happens.
Other companies all watch Omerekker a lot playing games.
And a lot of times they'll be like, "Hey, this company wants me to play this game."
And he's like, "Wee!
This game is so awesome!"
You know, because you're getting paid to play the game.
It's a way to advertise your game.
But again, Inner Sloth had been around.
This game was losing money.
And then all of a sudden you have all these streamers playing it.
And the idea is they weren't paying streamers to play it.
Some other group was.
And so in August really, it was July, August of 2020 is when among us just skyrocketed
in popularity.
Everyone was playing this game.
It was being played by all the major streamers.
It became a hit.
And the whole purpose of this was ramping up to the release of the vaccine.
And it was all set up to brainwash people into not only getting the COVID-19 vaccine,
but to hating those who don't.
It's an interesting conspiracy theory.
I just saw it pop up.
It's not the only one.
It's funny, as I was getting ready to record this episode, I was talking to St. Strand.
He was in the live chat.
We do the live episodes on Sunday.
And he said that he had heard another conspiracy theory linked to among us as well, that it
was all setting us up for the election, the 2020 election, specifically voting people
out.
You know what?
The whole thing was to train people to, for you to win, you have to vote people out.
So it's training people to go, "Let's get rid of Trump."
We got to vote him out.
You don't win the game by voting people in.
You win the game by voting people out.
And so it doesn't matter what candidate we run against.
Trump, if we can program an entire generation of people to win by voting out, then we can
win this election.
These are all really interesting conspiracy theories, right?
And then there's some less interesting ones.
Also on this same post someone said that Five Nights at Freddy's was designed to make people
want to have sex with furry robots.
Okay.
So now I can.
Like, I don't know anything about that conspiracy theory.
But again, eventually people just, it's, it's, whenever you look at conspiracy theories,
they tend to get goofier and goofier the more you look at them.
But anyways, we have two conspiracy theories here.
The first one is, was Among Us designed to get people to not only get the vaccine for
COVID-19, but to hate people who don't?
It's a super interesting conspiracy theory.
I personally don't feel it holds a lot of water because Among Us is a totally different age
group of who was originally getting the vaccine or those first waves of vaccine.
Like you couldn't, you couldn't design a game that would turn off boomers more than Among
Us.
And yet they did.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like if the vaccine was, if those first waves of vaccine were targeted at kids and teens
and young adults when they weren't, they were targeted at people my age and older.
Like you need to get it now or you're going to die.
Like that was that first wave of vaccines and it was all for like public service workers
and healthcare workers and airline.
I actually think the airline pilots thing came later.
But in the beginning it was like, you work with the public, you have to get this.
If you want a certain job with the government, you have to get this.
And it was people who were so far removed from the Among Us game by age, by interest level
that I don't think it really holds water.
As far as that goes.
I know nowadays that younger people do get vaccinated, but that's not the conspiracy
theory.
The conspiracy theory is that it was getting ready for vaccinations in whole.
And I don't think that it did that.
Again, that game was targeted so young that I just don't get that.
But I think the conspiracy theory is interesting in the, oh, and let me give InnerSloth a little
more credit too.
And actually, like I said, I was reading about InnerSloth, they actually did lay this out.
They said, yeah, our game was not selling well until the streaming community took it.
And they said, and really it happened in Mexico, South Korea and Brazil first.
The streamer, they said the game was always more popular in those countries than it was
in the United States.
Streamers in those countries started streaming it.
And then late into the game, you had a U.S. streamer called Soda Poppin in July.
He started playing it and then other people started playing it.
And I remember, I was watching the Among Us stuff and I was thinking this is a really
good game for COVID because again, in July, August, September of 2020, people were still
really iffy about being around other people, social distancing.
What can you do?
Schools were shut down.
And this was a game you could get on where you could be with your friends.
It was a social interaction game.
It was a party game.
So actually, like watching the streams and watching these people have fun, watching my
virtual friends hang out, I understood the appeal of it and I can understand why specifically
kids and young adults, you know, teenagers were in on it because their social network
had been completely destroyed.
You had people still working and maybe they were working from home and stuff like that,
but the kids, they had nothing.
Their schools were all shut down.
So I understood like from a social aspect why the game was so popular.
But going back to the conspiracy theory, I don't really agree that it was a push for
the COVID vaccine because I just don't think the age groups line up.
However, if we want to put on our conspiracy caps, it may be a push for something because
it did come out of nowhere.
And again, I was surprised to find out that the game was a couple of years old because
that's very, very rare that a game starts off a dud for two years and then becomes a
huge hit.
Just say the same thing.
It's hard for movies to do that.
It's hard for albums to do that.
Unless it's like from an artist, like a classic artist who put in an album that bombed in
the 70s and then it's rediscovered in the 90s.
That type of stuff does happen or you have an artist like Meatloaf who blows up in the
late 80s and then all of his old stuff becomes good again.
Not good again, but people go back and rediscover it.
You have stuff like that, but there's usually some sort of spark.
It sure could have been the people streaming the game in Brazil and South Korea and Mexico,
but it's rare.
It's rare that this happens.
Not impossible, but it's rare.
It could be that the game is designed for something.
It definitely is something that I think some sort of other group entity would want to put
its weight behind.
But I just don't know what.
I don't know what it could be.
I do kind of like that idea that it was about voting somebody out.
But even then the game skews so young.
It's not like that seventh grader's going to be like, "I hope I get to vote this election."
Because they didn't.
They didn't get to vote the election.
There's no doubt in my mind that a lot of our entertainment is funded by government entities
or groups that have a unstated purpose to us.
They know it, but they're not telling us.
I do think, and people could say this is a conspiracy theory, I do think though that
there is a connection, there's a through line between the war movies of the 50s, 60s, and
70s, the war cartoons like G.I.
Joe and Transformers and stuff like that, the 80s and the 90s, and then the first person
shooters of the early 2000s to today.
I think it, I do honestly believe that the government encourages that type of media to
be created and helps disseminate it to create the new generation of future soldiers.
It's the reason why the U.S. government will work with Michael Bay to make a Transformers
movie.
You're like, "Why do they care?"
Yeah, Michael Bay has a bunch of American flags in his shots, but why are they giving
him jets?
And a lot of the military in the Transformer movies, specifically those first three, you
see, are active duty military.
Why is the U.S. military helping out these Transformers movies?
Because it gets people to sign up, it makes war look cool.
And I like those movies.
I like G.I.
Joe, I like first person shooters.
I'm not sitting on a pedestal saying all this stuff is bad.
I enjoy all that entertainment too, but I also feel I know what the motivation is behind
it.
It's not just, "Let's create some cool entertainment."
I do believe the government does make those things and encourage those things to create
the new generation of fighting soldiers.
And among us though, it would be a more sinister thing.
I guess going war and blowing up people is pretty sinister too if you're on the other
side.
But among us is all about, it's not about, you know, G.I.
Joe is saying the other is this terrorist organization trying to destroy peace around
the world.
Among us is, you don't know who the bad guy is.
They want to blow you up.
They want to take over the ship.
They want to destroy peace as well.
But they look exactly like you.
They act exactly like you until they eat you.
And the main strategy of the game is to lie to your friend's face.
If you're playing with your friends, which is the way the game I think is kind of designed
to be played, people that you know very well, you have to lie to them and convince them
you're not the imposter.
So why would, if this conspiracy theory is true, why would the government do that?
Why would the government or some sort of shadowy organization want to promote you lying to
your friends?
And I think the answer really is simple when you state it like that, is that I think every
government benefits from a paranoid population.
Not paranoid against the government, not Mel Gibson from conspiracy theory, but paranoid
against each other.
Right?
If you can't trust your best friend, you guys are playing a video game and he lies to you
and he tricks you and you lose, sure, you're just like, "Oh man, you got me.
I totally believed you."
But I think that does put a little wrinkle in your brain.
I think it actually does over time make you trust your friend less.
Because this isn't a party.
I mean, I keep calling it a party game, but you know, a party game, I went over to some
buddy's house a couple years ago and they had this card game called Secret Hitler.
We sat around the table and we played it twice and then we went and like drank an eight chips
and listened to music.
People spent hours playing among us.
Hours lying to people, being fooled, right?
Being tricked by someone you trusted explicitly.
Because before you guys started playing the game, you guys were talking about movies and
stuff like that.
You played the game, you guys are probably going to be playing Warhammer or something
like that.
But while you're playing that game two, three hours, you're being lied to and you're lying
to people who in any other situation, you would trust them explicitly.
But now you're in a game where you're lying to them and you're trying to fool them.
And when you succeed, their trust level of you goes down.
If it was a party game you played once a year, it wouldn't affect you.
But if it's a game you're playing over and over and over and over and you're getting
better and better and better at it, it will change the dynamic.
It may not even be noticeable at first, right?
But over time, you would stop trusting your friend.
And when it came down to something when your friend said, "Hey, no, no, no, you got to
trust me."
Even though you know Among Us is just a game, you would think, "Maybe."
And you may not even be able to connect to you.
You may, I don't think you would logically say, "Well, listen, you're telling me to
trust you right now, but you lied to me three months ago when we were playing Among Us.
I don't think you could connect it like that."
But I think it would do something to the trust center of your brain.
And you would go, "Your best friends would have become less trustworthy."
You would become less trustworthy to them, because the way to win is to become the best
liar possible.
So it may not be a conspiracy theory to get us to take the COVID vaccine, because that's
done.
That whole, like, that's pretty much done.
Everyone who wanted the vaccine's gotten it, and it's pretty much over.
The mandates are gone, everything.
People don't even make you show your card now when you walk around.
Like, that's over with.
But the game's still running strong.
The 2020 election, it's over with.
The game's still running strong.
But a game that inspires you to not trust your neighbor, to not trust your best friend,
and to also look at your best friend and lie straight to their face.
You both deceive and are deceived, build a paranoid society.
Not paranoid at the machinations behind the halls of power.
Not paranoid at the conspiracy theories that threaten to control the entire world.
But paranoid of the people who you spend every single day with.
That doesn't just sound like any old video game.
That sounds like a blueprint to slowly take over the world.
[Music]