A man makes a horrifying discovery in the middle of the road.
Another man dies in a horrible way.
And then we take a look at a...
It's kind of hard to describe.
First off, we're going to look at a conspiracy theory that wind turbines may make people
kill other people with a hammer.
And then we take a look at the broader conspiracy that there is a war on for your mind right
now.
The Battlefield?
The Movie Theater.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You know, I was looking at my notes for this particular week of shows.
Man, all the episodes, okay, all the notes are super depressing.
All the story ideas are super depressing.
Now I'm not going to do a bunch of depressing stories this week.
I gotta go find some more lighthearted ones.
So I will.
I'll find those.
They will show up.
But in the meantime, let's talk about some horrible human tragedies.
This first one was recommended or sent to me by James Milne.
I feel really bad because James, he recommended a story in the past and I asked how do you
pronounce your name and he told me and then I promptly forgot.
It's James Milne or James Milne.
I apologize, James, but I really appreciate the story idea.
So I keep saying story idea.
Like I'm writing short fiction.
This happened in real life and what happened was September 30th, 2019.
So not too long ago, this dude, walking down the street in Anchorage, Alaska, doesn't have
a care in the world.
I don't know.
He actually probably could have owned a Fortune 500 company.
It could have been super stressed.
Doesn't matter.
He's not the subject of the story.
But this dude's walking down the street.
He finds an SD card.
Now I've done that before.
Well, I'm sure everyone's found stuff in the road.
But when I come across like SD cards or cell phones, I always try to look at them.
I always try to see what's in them.
Now this one actually was labeled.
It was not labeled Scarlett Johansson, parentheses, topless.
Must watch underline, underline.
Gone wrong.
It's not labeled that.
This one is a hundred times worse than that.
SD card that's labeled homicide at Midtown Marriott.
So the dude puts the SD card in into his port.
He's a cyborg.
He's like, "Ear, eliminate worries, no worries, insert card."
He takes it home, presumably.
Puts it into his computer.
Not into his own mainframe.
And it is actually what it says.
There's 39 photos and 12 videos of a man brutally beating and killing a woman.
So he calls the cops.
Now, you may think, "Hmm, this could just be someone's snuff collection that they found."
But it probably would still be a good idea to call the cops.
So he does call the cops though.
And the cops watch the video.
They come over and they're like, "Hey, how's it going?"
The cyborg's like, "Boot up."
Walking slowly towards the door.
Initiate officer shake hand protocol.
They're like, "Dude, just give us the SD card."
And you're saying, "Jayson, just continue the story."
Fine.
Card eject.
So anyways, the cops begin watching the video and they recognize the guy in the video.
His name is Brian Steven Smith.
And what's interesting, he was currently being investigated.
The cops are currently watching him for something else.
They haven't revealed what else he was under investigation for.
But he was under investigation.
That's why the cops recognized him.
Now he was arrested for being in this video footage of him killing this woman.
On October 2nd, the body of that woman, that murdered woman, was found and he admitted
to killing another woman.
And as far as I know, her body has not been found yet.
So Brian Steven Smith is currently being held for the murders of two women.
Creepy.
Now, that's just a standard serial killer story in one aspect.
But then you can look at it like this.
First off, I would find it bizarre if he labeled that...
Okay, we're going to put on our little paranormal conspiracy hats.
Did he actually label the SD card himself?
And you're like, "Jayson, that's...
Of course he did.
Were you saying that a goblin, a murder goblin, labeled it?"
Well, no.
But I mean, I think it would be kind of dumb.
If I was a jewel thief, I wouldn't take...
I wouldn't write on...
I wouldn't take one, I wouldn't videotape my crimes, and then two.
But I guess you don't have a fetish for stealing jewels.
Most people don't.
I'm sure someone...
Some jewel thieves walking around all turned on the whole time is like, "Ooh, I can't wait
to get home and remember this event."
But for the most part, it's like a financial crime.
I guess a serial killer or a killer in general would videotape it to relive it.
But still, why would you label it?
Secondly, like, the fact that it fell out of wherever he was holding it, his pocket,
or maybe he's walking around with it in his hand looking at it, being like, "Ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh, once I get home, I'm going to watch you."
Like, that is a miracle.
Because here was a man who had already murdered two women.
And proof of his crimes showing his face murdering a woman, it wasn't just his face.
This whole body murdered the woman.
But his face in the video.
That's a miracle.
Because who knows how many other women he would have killed.
So it's not just the story of a serial killer.
It's the story...
It's this total perfect storm of a serial killer losing proof of his crimes, which again, is
something the little rascals would do.
That's quite stupid, but he loses proof of his crime.
It's not destroyed.
It's not swept away.
Some kid doesn't pick it up, he raced it and put an Xbox game on it.
And yeah, I know that's not how Xbox games work.
But my point is that the right person found it at the right time.
If my mom found an SD card, she wouldn't even know what it was.
She wouldn't be able to take it home and put it into a computer and decipher it.
Now, because it did say homicide at Midtown Marriot, she probably would call up me or
my brother and have us do it.
But you know what I mean?
It was the right person.
It fell in the right place that it didn't get destroyed.
And it had just enough information to actually nail this jerk for being a serial killer.
So divine intervention or just a series of fortunate incidents.
Huh?
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
Now, our next story is part of our calvocade of depressing stuff.
Although this one you might be able to say has a happy ending if you like money.
If you love humans, it doesn't have a happy ending.
The year is 2012.
We're leaving Anchorage, Alaska.
Let's hop in the Carbentercopter.
I don't think we've used it this season yet.
Hop in the Carbentercopter.
We're going to fly all the way down to Santa Fe Springs, California.
And as we're flying there, I want to remind you guys the Minecraft server is now open
to the public.
So if you want to join us playing Minecraft and unlocking the secret mystery of the giant
black spaceship that is just floating over spawn, join us.
The website, the login, whatever you call it, whatever you kids call it, is in the show
notes.
Go ahead and put that into your Minecraft game, gamermajig, and join us.
It's a lot of fun.
So after that pitch, after that, I'm not making any money off of it.
It actually cost me money to run the server.
Anyways, we land the helicopter.
Everyone's like, "Dude, I don't even play Minecraft, dude.
I just like listening about ghosts.
Why are you always hawking your Minecraft server?"
I'm like, "Come on, man.
It's fun.
Let's play."
Anyways, as we're walking, we're walking into a bumblebee tuna plant.
So put on our worker uniforms, our hard hats.
You're like, "Why do we need a hard hat to be around tuna?"
I'm like, "You'll see.
Unfortunately, you'll see."
Scammy little badge.
Beep.
Okay, we go in.
And working there is a man named Jose Molina.
Now, this is where they basically do tuna stuff.
I don't know how tuna works.
I know that it's a fish, and then you kill it, and then you eat it out of a can.
But I didn't know they cooked it or how they'd prepare it.
I just imagine they were ripping fish up, throwing fish into a grinder, and then it
[imitates fish] shooting out into a can.
I've developed a taste for tuna.
I don't like it when I do taste for tuna.
That's the cool name of a band.
But I never really was into tuna as a kid.
That has nothing to do with this story, by the way.
You may not like tuna after this story.
Jose Molina was, I think he was like 56 years old.
He had adult kids and all that stuff.
There are chain breaks in one of the giant ovens.
Talk about divine intervention.
This one's almost the opposite.
Jose goes in to fix the chain.
Now, this oven is 36 foot by 54...
Okay, now I think this might be a typo, honestly.
Because I haven't written down as a 36 foot by 54 inch oven, which would be the world's
biggest rectangle.
I'm assuming it should be 36 feet by 54 feet?
It doesn't matter.
We're already halfway done.
Either he's crawling through...
How big is 54 inches?
That's about four feet.
So he'd have to crawl through on his belly.
It doesn't matter.
The point is he's in an oven.
He's in an oven trying to fix the chain.
Now, his coworker has another job.
His coworker's job is to hit a button and to dump tuna into the oven and to turn the
oven on.
So the coworker's walking around the workspace and he goes, "Hmm, where's Jose?
I don't know.
He's probably in the bathroom."
Boop.
And then at that point, 12,000 pounds of tuna fall into the oven.
And the coworker turns it on.
Do... turns up the heat.
Pssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss
Now, I don't know at what point they realize that Jose's not in the bathroom.
They do end up opening the oven and Jose is dead.
Now I know you were hoping that it was some superhero origin story.
I know you were hoping that it was a man who became tuna man who had the ability to talk
to only tuna, but no, he died.
Now this is the horrifying part of this.
You're like, "Jason, that whole thing's horrifying.
A guy trying to do his job crossing an oven."
The tuna, 12,000 pounds of tuna did not kill him.
When they did the autopsy, the tuna did not kill him.
He was cooked to death.
He survived what?
Which I find odd that the tuna didn't kill him.
But I guess if you dropped like 12,000 pounds of like wet, slimy, slidy stuff, it would
just hit you and like slide down your head.
Like it's not like a barbell, which hits your head.
Path of least resistance, your head is the least resistance.
If I threw 12,000 pounds of feather on you, wouldn't they just like tickle you?
Sure, you would like suffocate, but you would be able to like move them out of the way as
they're falling on you.
And now if it was only four feet tall, that might be kind of hard.
Again, I think it was 56 feet tall.
But anyways, the 12,000 pounds of tuna did not kill him.
He got cooked to death.
This is the happy ending.
His family ended up suing the company, Bumblebee, tuna company, and they made like millions
of dollars off of it.
And I get it.
You'd rather have your relative still alive.
They made millions of dollars off it.
The state got millions of dollars.
They had to put in all these safety checks and everything like that.
So a happy ending, not really, but you know, they did get held liable for it.
So when you get cooked to death, it's horrible.
This is horrible thing.
I'm not going to go too much into detail about it, but you boil your stomach acid boils.
I think that is horrible.
I think the whole thing's horrible and it's pretty slow.
That's the big problem with it.
I mean, not like I'm pro, not like I'm pro the other things that being cooked to death,
but apparently it takes a while, your stomach acid boils, and the last thing to really get
cooked is your brain.
But yeah, so it's quite the journey.
I mean, there's a lot of horrible ways to die.
Being cooked underneath a bunch of tuna is probably not one of them.
Like I said, dude, I'm sorry.
These stories are kind of depressing, but let's move on to one that's a little less
depressing, unless you find people being murdered with hammers.
I'm sorry, guys.
But at least this one starts off with a fictional death.
Now I was watching a bunch of movies recently, and I'll usually watch like, when I get in
a movie binge, I'll watch like five or six in a day, because I'll watch like 10 minutes
and go sucks, click, sucks, click.
I just get rid of them.
I started watching a movie called Turbines, and the tagline for the movie is "green, efficient,
deadly."
And it was kind of being billed as a thing where wind turbines are killing people.
Now I imagined it like a sci-fi channel movie, like at night the wind turbines were like
jumping off, chopping people up, or the government put some sort of beacon or something in the
wind turbines that were making them kill people.
That's how I imagined it.
The truth of the matter is this, what the movie is about is a young family is brought
out to basically the government says, "We will pay you to move out to middle of nowhere
and help maintain this wind turbine farm."
And they do.
And then we start to see the effects of the wind turbines on these people living here,
i.e. they become hammer-wielding murderers.
And it's weird, so you're watching the movie, and it's like you can see the guys getting
a little tense.
And then there's a five-year time jump, and a group of young teenagers, not teenagers,
but like young college students, they're doing their grad work on wind turbine syndrome.
We'll get into that in a second.
So they're the slaughter.
They're like the standard cabin in the wood type thing.
They show up to investigate these.
The guy takes a hammer, starts bashing their heads, and this guy is like John Wick with
a hammer.
He'll take on like four or five people at a time.
He's like taking on like two or three cops at a time with this hammer.
He's murdering everyone.
And then he murders his wife.
I don't know if he murders his son.
I don't really remember.
I wasn't really paying attention to that point.
And then I guess it turns out there was two hammer-wielding murderers.
It's like, "What?"
And then the movie ends.
This is not a Dead or Ever recommends, by the way.
The movie was beautifully shot.
Like it definitely had its strengths.
But when you watch the trailer, it says, "Based on a true story."
They're like, "What?"
So this is the quote-unquote true story.
Apparently, there is a...
I don't know how to put it.
Some people say it's pseudoscience.
Some people say it's a conspiracy theory.
But windmills are actually...
There's basically two levels of this.
At first, people were saying that wind turbine windmills can cause cancer and can cause people
to go and murderous rages and commit suicide and things like that.
That's ridiculous.
You're gonna get those things in any community whether or not there's a windmill.
People were saying, "No, no, we think there's more of them around windmills."
But it's interesting because they've walked that back now.
What happened was a bunch of medical studies came out.
25 medical studies.
Peer-reviewed medical studies.
You'll hear that phrase often looking into this.
Saying that windmills cause nothing except green energy and wind.
They don't cause the wind, but they do stuff with the wind.
They don't do anything to your mental health.
They don't cause cancer or anything like that.
Then the anti-windmill people said, "Okay, okay, okay.
Maybe that was ridiculous at first."
But it does cause you to wake up.
It causes insomnia, migraines, ear pressure, visual blurring.
It's infrasound that's going into us.
And at that point, the medical people go, "Listen, it may annoy certain people.
Some people may be able to pick up on the noise and it may annoy them."
So cities and governments started saying you can't have windmills.
These wind turbine windmills too close to the houses.
Because people can't hear the noise and there may be some sort of health effect
as far as annoying people making them want to leave.
So it's a weird conspiracy theory because the anti-windmill people
reached really far from the stars in the beginning.
And that was easy to be shut down.
They're like, "No, it's causing no cancer vectors.
People aren't running around with hammers bashing in people's heads."
And then they kind of walked it back and said, "Yeah, it's just kind of annoying
and it's hard to sleep."
And the people go, "Well, that might be the case,
but that's not enough to cause a disease."
Wind turbine syndrome is something made up by the anti-windmill people.
It's not a recognized disease.
So I had never heard of that syndrome before.
I never heard of that before.
It's an odd, very, very geographically limited conspiracy theory.
It's not like anti-vax or anything like that, which is like a global thing.
This is limited.
You would only care about this if you lived near a windmill.
But that's not the point of this topic.
The point of this topic is the movie itself.
I'm going to go half Alex Jones right now.
I'm going to go half Alex Jones.
I'm not going to go full Alex Jones, but hear me out on this one.
We have reached a stage in human development that is the perfect combination of access
to filmmaking equipment and general human lunacy to the point where somebody can sit
down and make a movie based on a conspiracy theory, set up a horror movie based on a conspiracy
theory and present it as based on a true story.
Now, I know what you're thinking.
You go, "Jason, this isn't anything new."
People make movies about aliens.
People who believe in aliens make movies about aliens.
But no, this is something new.
Because yes, people who believe in things like ghosts make movies about ghosts, and then
people who watch those movies may tend to believe that ghosts are real.
People who believe in aliens make movies like communion, close encounters with the third
kind, E.T.
People who watch those movies go, "Maybe aliens do exist.
Maybe aliens are visiting us."
This is different.
This is the... those aren't weapons.
Those are saying, "These are beliefs that I have, and I'm making a movie."
When you go to see a Christian movie like Fireproof or God's Not Dead, that movie is
made for people who already believe in these things, who already have a general working
knowledge of Christianity, or aliens, or Bigfoot, or what have you.
Things like Turbine are a stealth weapon, because it's not marketed towards people who
believe in wind turbine syndrome.
That doesn't come up until halfway through the movie.
It's not in the plot synopsis.
Nowhere in the marketing for the movie that I saw would you think this movie is for people
who already believe in this stuff.
Obviously, if you're watching God's Not Dead, you watch the trailer for that, you go, "Oh,
this is a Christian film.
It's made to appeal to Christians."
Now, obviously, someone who's not a Christian could watch that, and they could debate it,
or they could go, "Oh, I believe in Jesus now."
But the movie itself is not the weapon.
We are getting to that level.
Think about it this way.
If you went back 10 years, before the whole anti-vax thing really, really took off, and
you had a series of horror movies, or series of sci-fi movies, you'd probably be better
for that.
Imagine a movie on the level of The Matrix.
As far as popularity goes, but one of the key things in it is the government controls
you by putting a vaccine in your system.
They show Neo go, "Tch, and he's like fighting, fighting the vaccine."
All this stuff about red pills and blue pills and being woke all come from terminology from
The Matrix.
And you could argue some of it farther back, but from that, that's really what popularized
it.
Instead of taking the red pill or the blue pill, Morpheus goes, "Well, now we gotta
suck out that measles, mumps, and rebu- uh, whatever."
MMR vaccine from your arm, Neo, that's how the government controls you.
You would have, I honestly believe you would have more people who are anti-vax.
The makers of these movies who have an agenda to push forward are constantly fighting for
your mind.
Most, I would say 99% of movies really don't have an agenda at all.
You could go, "Oh, predictive programming, Illuminati's putting eyeballs in everything,
and Michael Bay has an American flag in every movie."
I don't, Michael Bay does not have an American flag in every movie, but I dismiss the whole
predictive programming thing like that.
I think most movies are there to make money.
They are there to continue the corporation going on, continuing the consuming of their
products.
That's their main goal.
They may in a movie throw, and hey, you know, we wanna have, show how badass women are,
so we're gonna have a female, a lead female character who's stronger than the male characters.
They could definitely do that.
Or you could have, we wanna make money so we can make "God's Not Dead 4," but we
still wanna make this movie, it's gonna have this message, but we still also have to make
money doing it.
So, you can have movies with messages, but I think most movies don't have a message outside
of maybe the theme of the movie or something like that.
But we have reached a level now, where, 'cause this movie, "Turbine," it wasn't a bad movie.
I'm not knocking it all.
The acting was good, the cinematography looked great, super low budget film, looked beautiful.
It wasn't the best horror movie I've seen, but there was skill in front of and behind
the camera.
And we're reaching a level where now anyone can get this technology and put their conspiracy
theory out there.
If anything, if really if anything the last year of doing this show has really taught
me, it only takes about 10,000 people to get a conspiracy theory off the ground.
It really does.
It's not a lot of groundwork to do.
Imagine yesterday I talked about my conspiracy theory involving plastic bottles and bottle
caps and how recycling is a scam.
Imagine if I had $5 million in the team of people to make a movie about that.
And let's say the movie actually was good.
I could rack up 10,000 people to believe that in a year, a year or two, if I really wanted
to push that conspiracy theory.
I guess it never really occurred to me before how easy it is to get your conspiracy theory
out there in a stealthy way.
If somebody put online, "When mill turbines cause cancer or cause people to kill each other
hammers," most people are going to dismiss them.
The idiots will be like, "Oh, really?
Yeah, my cousin got killed by a hammer and there was a fan going on in the background."
So that might be that.
But when you can wrap it in a piece of entertainment like that and put it out there and people
watch it and then halfway through the movie they mention the term "When mill turbine syndrome"
and you're like, "What?"
And then maybe you catch the trailer and this is based on a true story and you start researching
it for yourself.
It's so much more valid to the human mind that way.
I don't know why it is, but it is.
That happened to me with the Mithras conspiracy.
The movie is called The Conspiracy.
Highly recommended.
It's a fake documentary, a mockumentary.
I don't want to call it mockumentary because it's not, that sounds funny, but it's a documentary
about a conspiracy involving the secret society.
Now it has enough truth in it that when I went to research it I found all the stuff about
this thing called the Mithras society and I was completely enthralled.
Stuff that I would have completely dismissed out of hand if I hadn't seen that documentary
first.
It was a documentary, it was fake.
Knowing what it was about, it still made me more interested in conspiracy theory that
I would have completely just not been into.
This is the weaponization of entertainment and conspiracy theory combined into one.
Now mainstream media has been doing this for a long time.
They want to get an idea out there, they wrap it in entertainment and I'm not dismissing
that.
They actually do that.
They want to push a message, they can make it entertaining.
But now anyone can do that and it's dangerous.
It's dangerous to everyone involved.
I believe we're on the verge, not of a civil war where the nation splits in half and we
go to war, but a civil war of the mind.
We are becoming so fractured as a global society where people are believing their own conspiracy
theories now and I don't see a way back from this.
I think it's going to get worse.
I think we're going to get to a point where most movies have hidden conspiratorial messages
but they're not the big Illuminati messages that people like to pretend as all seeing
group is pushing on the media.
It's going to be the bizarre beliefs of different directors and different writers put in these
movies to the point that other people working on the movie may not even know that they're
there.
We've moved past conspiracy theory.
The world is now in a phase of conspiracy belief.
The world is now not a global society but 7 billion people all with their own set of
facts and it's absolutely frightening.
But the hardest thing to admit is that I would do the same thing because if I had the money
to make a movie, I'm doing it with this podcast.
How many times have I put out conspiracy theories that I'll say I don't have anything, I don't
have any proof to back this up but this is what I believe and I'm spitting that out to
1,800 to 2,000 people a day.
It doesn't take many people to start to upset the public discourse.
10,000 people tops and you can start a thought revolution.
There weren't many Flat Earthers 8 years ago.
It was a minority of people and now you got hundreds of thousands of Flat Earthers within
8 years.
What bizarre conspiracy theories are floating around out there that are just on the cusp
of breaking into the mainstream?
Are we one blockbuster movie away from more people questioning whether monkeys exist or
that mountains are actually dead trees?
Who knows?
But I think we're going to find out very, very soon.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)