The man who smelt so bad that they had to ground the flight and then we'll
revisit the resistance of light today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone this is Jason Carpenter. Well this is Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm Jason
Carpenter. A quick clarification, smelt. If somebody smelt so bad is it actually
smelled so bad? I'm not for sure. I'm not for sure. I'm barely holding on. I got a
pretty bad sinus, some sinus stuff going on. Funny because I have to listen back
to the episodes and I was like, "Oh man it sounds like I'm getting a cold. Like I
could hear my voice getting a little more horse-aged episode and then sure
enough I'm having full-on sinus pressure today." But you know doing my thing, taking
medicine, sleeping, I'm fasting for it too, which you think would make me more
miserable. But once you get used to fasting it's it's it's pretty normal.
Heads up to my friend Veronica who went and bought me some medicine today. That was
nice. Well that was homebound. I got, before we get started here, because I know
I'm always so succinct in my beginnings, today I got my copy of Stephen King's
Shot John Lennon by Steve Lightfoot. I paid $10 for it and I'm gonna tell you
guys right now, I'll put the link at the bottom below. This was easily worth $10.
There's no sarcasm in this whatsoever. One, he autographed it. I
don't know if he does that for all of them, but he did put a message on here.
"To Jason, thanks for your vital concern, Steve Lightfoot." Like I said in the
two episodes regarding Stephen King's Shot John Lennon, I've been following this
conspiracy theory for probably about two years now and to be able to to me hold a
piece of conspiracy history. It's quite amazing. It's quite amazing. Now those two
episodes, I think they're episodes five and six. What that would, I think I'm going
to, we're gonna keep covering that conspiracy theory, but if you listen to
those two episodes and you weren't a huge fan of it, blame it more on the format,
not on the subject matter. I found the subject very fascinating and I kind of
did a dramatic reading of his writings. I don't really know how now that the show
has, you know, 10 episodes later, I think the show's kind of found its tone a
little more. So we're gonna be revisiting that, but I don't, I'm not gonna go over
today because I just got it and I really want to read through it, but I'm
telling you, it is, I'm not disappointed. It looks amazing. Covers a lot of the
same detail, but I'm going to say this. So you know, like I said, I've been
following it for two years and his website's just kind of spiraled out, but
the, in this one he actually has a, he has a back-to-back picture of Chapman and
King and then they do kind of look alike. They do kind of look alike. It's kind of
weird. So we're gonna probably handle that on Monday or Tuesday because I got to
read over that. I got to play practice a bunch of stuff too. Okay, let's go ahead
and get started here because I got two really good stories, so I don't think we
need much introduction. This first story I saw was fascinating just because it's
one of those situations. It's sad. I feel really bad for the guy, but it's one of
those situations that I think we can all empathize with, kind of on both levels.
So you're a passenger on a plane and you get up in the plane and the planes
flying now. Everyone's trapped on this plane and you're sitting there and you're
reading your in-flight magazine or you're, you know, playing, I don't know, what do
people play on their phones? I don't know, Fortnite, whatever. You're a kid, I guess,
in this scenario, but all of a sudden you start to smell something. Now, it's, you
can't really place it at first. It's not, it's not body odor. Does it smell like raw
sewage? No, no, no. It's worse than raw sewage. And you kind of look around and
either just the smell is feeling, filling your nostrils. You just feel it
burning, burning your nose and you kind of look around and you notice other
people, they seem to smell it too because they're also kind of looking around
like I haven't, looking around the plane. Can't figure it out. Everyone's kind of
looking at each other and the smell is getting worse and worse and worse. Now
imagine the worst smell you can imagine. It's kind of hard because scent is such a
different type of scent memory. We can remember like the physical reactions we
have to smell, but it's hard to actually remember the smell itself. But you know,
we have stuff like rotten eggs or poop or stuff like that. But no, this smell is
worse than all of them because you're on this plane, you're up in the air, you're
30,000 feet in the air and what you're smelling is rotting human flesh. You're
smelling flesh rot off of a living person sitting four seats in front of you.
It's overwhelming now. The air is just getting circulated. You have no escape.
You can't open a window. So you plug your nose at first, but that's no. Available.
People begin fashioning little masks for themselves and coughing, retching almost
because the smell is just filling the cabin. There's no way for the odor itself
to escape, so it's only growing as more and more flesh is rotting off of this
guy. So passengers begin throwing up. Now that's not how to help me the smell
either. So passengers are throwing up. The man profusely apologizes and he feels bad
that he's rotting. He's rotting in front of you. Pilot is smelling it too and the
pilot comes back and he assesses the situation. You're still your innate
year old boy in this scenario apparently and you put your phone down and you see
the pilot and he's talking to the stewardess and they walk up to the
man who looks normal. He looks a little sick because he's rotting away,
but they didn't notice anything wrong with him. It kind of sounds like a zombie
movie actually, but so they say well let's lock him in the bathroom. Maybe that
will stop the smell and then we can get to our destination. And the guy's like
yeah, no, fine. I'm super sick. I have no problem with that. So he goes into the
restroom and they lock him in there and it doesn't work. The smell is just too
overpowering. It's still that it's just creeping out from underneath the bathroom.
The whole cabin's full of it. They have to let, they make an emergency landing. So
what happened was this guy named Andre Shillen, Shillian, Shillian, 58 years old.
He got an infection and he, what happened was he was suffering from tissue
necrosis. His flesh was rotting on the plane and we're gonna go ahead and post
the article here. People were fainting from the smell and unfortunately is that
he's passed away now. They landed the plane and they tried to get him, get him
treatment but it was too late. Too much of him. It kind of rotted away. And it's
weird. So this was his response. It's not after he died obviously, but this was his
after emergency landing he wrote on Facebook. "The tragic and comic component
of this whole situation is that I caught a disease which, let's not say how and
why, makes a person quite stinky. As a result, a group of passengers may demand
the captain for you to be removed from the plane." So I think it's weird that
they don't really, like he doesn't state what it is and I didn't see on the
article what caused him to have that infection. But they tried their best. They
did multiple surgeries. You couldn't stop it. Now this guy, this Andre Shillian to us,
or to me at least, he's just a guy with an unfortunate accident. Apparently in
Russia he's like would be like their version of Jimi Hendrix. He was like a
guitar god. He was considered one of the top guitar players in Russia and was a
pioneer of rock music in the Soviet Union. So that's tragic. You know one of
those things, the smells are impossible really to get past. I always
ask questions of people and if you have, if you're wondering, is this an act? Is
Jason just, is this like a bit he's constantly doing for the show or does he
actually act like this? I act like this all the time. It's not a bit. But I'll
ask people I'll go, this is one of my like thought experiments. I say you meet a guy
or girl, whatever. You meet the person of your dreams and they're everything you
wanted. Everything you wanted. If you want them to be rich, they're rich. If you
want them to be successful like a writer, that if you want them to be like six,
seven feet tall, whatever. But his face is completely busted up. He's totally ugly
and you can't do any sort of repairs to it. And people always go well how ugly
are we talking? And I'm like well I mean like on a scale of one to ten let's put
him in like a three or four. So he's not like if you look at him you want to
vomit but he's not good looking by any means and even you don't think he's good
looking face wise. Would you date him? And people generally go yeah, yeah everything
else is perfect. If he's kind or funny or if he's a you know domineering or
whatever whatever you look for. Then I ask the same question. I go what if he's
everything you look for, everything and he has a beautiful face or whatever type
of face you want but he smells like wet garbage. Would you date him? And most
people that that gives them pause. We can look past physical differences. You can
see someone and they're everything's perfect about them but they have some
you know like their face was burned off or something like that. And you could be
like I can make this work but if they smell like wet garbage and again you
can't do anything to fix it. That changes the answer. Smells are super important
to us. They're completely overriding and we can't really do anything to stop
them. You can't put a bag over a smell. Now here's a gross smell story that I have
and I've always I'm sure there was some sort of scientific principle here but I
used to when I had an apartment in Sacramento. I had these really nice
neighbors. They were from another country and they made like this super
pungent food and it actually smelled pretty good. It was all like you know
rice and sauces and stuff like that. They were really good neighbors and just
around dinner time you would smell the food through the walls of the apartment
because it like I say was very pungent but it wasn't it wasn't offensive I
never really cared. One day I went to the bathroom and it was super hot so I had
the door open. I was living by myself but I like needed air flow in there so I'm
going to the bathroom and they start cooking their food in the next
apartment and the smell of my poop and the smell of their food created a I
almost threw up. It created the most noxious smell I've ever smelled in my
life. I couldn't even describe it to you. I couldn't even try to compare it to
something. It smelled like a chemical weapon. It smelled like I was going to
die and I was trapped because I was still going to the bathroom and I remember
going and I almost like looking back at that I imagine like the molecules the
two the two smell molecules like binding together into a third unheard of
smell or uns smelled of smell like it only existed in that one moment of time
they had to be cooking that exact meal and I had to be deprecating at the same
time it was disgusting. It was disgusting and what's funny is that I could
probably like I could probably recognize that smell but I couldn't describe it to
you. It was absolutely just awful. So I think that's probably my worst smell
story. I don't think oh you know I did look this up the other day so you know
there's I guess you know where I'm going with this. I don't know I'm doing a
lead-in but you know there's speed of light and there is speed of sound. The
other day I thought what's the speed of smell what's the speed of touch and taste
of course you know the internet wasn't the you know the greatest help on that
but I did find out that the speed of taste there is a speed of taste they
can measure. I could have really find anything on the speed of smell but I have
to think that the speed of touch has to be faster than the speed of light
because you figure if I touch a hot stove the signal has to travel from my
fingertip all the way up to my brain and then all the way back down to my hand to
move it away and that is almost instantaneously because that you don't
get burned you're out you know and I think that the distances involved on
you may go well Jason your fingertip to your brain and back is much shorter than
you know from here to a light you're out. However I think relatively the
distances are the same I mean my brain doesn't know and there's I'm gonna try
to find this article I found a couple things about how your brain actually
registers pain before you feel it and they can't figure out why like technically
you shouldn't if you touch it there should be a delay between the time you
touch it the signal going up to your brain and signal coming back to your
finger and you're removing it but when we tested it's far faster than it should
be so they can't really figure that out anyways anyways anyways I don't know
speed of smell speed of smell so I'm thinking the same thing with the speed
of smell speed of smell I just probably faster than the speed of sound because
you got to smell something like not I'm not talking about the little like wavy
lines like you see in cartoons that reach my nose those are the speed of wind
but once it hits my nose it has to go to my brain and then back to my nose I
don't know and I guess that's probably as fast as the speed of taste I'm gonna
say both of those are stronger faster than the speed of sound and I also think
speed of sound is stronger than the speed of light because I can shut a door
and light can't pass through it oh no no sounds is stronger than light is what
I'm saying because if I shut a door there's no more light but you can shut
10 doors and still hear music so light is faster but sounds is stronger which
makes me think we shouldn't be trying to build laser guns we should be building
like big sound guns and just like knocking stuff out of the sky with sound
that would be the noisiest war ever though if you think about it did you
know bombs have whistles on them that's what I heard when I was a kid I probably
heard it from that same encyclopedia that told me whales live to be 500 years
but apparently bombs have whistles on them so when they fall they go to that
that they normally don't do that like if you just dropped a metal out of a plane
but you put a whistle on the end of the palm and so the wind blows through it so
it makes everyone scared and look up and it's like traumatizing I probably should
Google I should probably Google a lot of stuff oh and I did Google can a mountain
be tall enough to reach the atmosphere the other day when I was editing that
episode and like 10 articles came up so that's ridiculous I said oh I can't find
it and then I googled it and it's all over the front page anyways so now we're
gonna get to what I think is becoming if Steve Lightfoot if Steve Lightfoot the
architect behind who shot John Lennon is becoming almost like the anti-hero of
this podcast where he's he's he's a mystery then I'm starting to think that
the resistance of light may actually become our mini-boss because I was
look I was listening back to that episode earlier today and I'm like these
guys are so ridiculous the resistance of light is so ridiculous I need to look
into these guys a little bit more they're the ones who have like the three
sectors and I'll have I think they're on no place like space episode I think
they're on episode 8 but anyway so I went and did did some more digging into
them and they're just absolutely ridiculous so first off I did was looking
at some of the stuff that they sell and they sell like tachyon water water that's
been bombarded with tachyons at 36 bucks for like a leader and they sell
tachyon protectors for your phone you can buy little gems all that stuff and
I'm like okay you know what you can say hey listen I got this water and I've
bombarded it with some science stuff and you don't know if I did but you know
trust me I have you has a resistance of light ever lied to you and you're like I
guess not you pay 36 bucks for the water but one thing I also came across was the
sin Tom and a stones sin tonnage stones so there are these little these little
rocks and they say that around 30,000 kilograms of diamonds are mined around
the world each year whereas only 50 kilograms of centanami stone are found
yearly well that might be true but probably because no one's looking for it
like they're looking for diamonds but anyway so these little rocks which is
what they are it says I'm just gonna call them sin stones a sin stones is the
stone with the highest vibration of all stones no and I'm okay source source
needed but it awakens you to your mission strengthens your inner guidance and
contact with your higher self and dissolves implants and outdated belief
system so I guess basically you hold it oh and these ones have been tacky and
eyes as well anyways you hold it and all your implants will fall out which if you
are a porn star is probably not a good idea these little rocks and that's what
they are for a four to seven gram rock fifty euros so what is that like sixty
US dollars and then it goes up fifty euros sixty euros it for a gem grade
stone whatever that means it's polished they probably through through a fifth
graders rock tumbler hundred euros and if you want a gem grade stone that's seven
to twelve grams it's 200 euros so there you go these people are totally ripping
people off it does appear that they have a lot a big following in Asia which the
website boasts like I was looking at their web counter and I'll put the link
into the description but they say they've had 42 million hits which is
possible I mean scams do get to be very popular they currently have a petition
now now this is a group that's talking about global enlightenment and so I
saw that they had a they were raising money for an African village or a kid or
something like that and so they're the fur global enlightenment they're for like
helping out of the people's and selling rocks they find itself like that so they
have a petition and so here's the question you think okay so what's this
petition about is it about like in world hunger is it about you know save the
endangered African panda rhino whatever no it's for planetary liberate
now so you sign this petition and you're you are basically it says we are all
aware that there are forces within the banking establishment military industrial
complex and also on the non-physical planes that do not wish humanity to be
free they have stolen our money they have poisoned our food they are trying to
take away our freedom they are trying to take away our happiness we will not let
them so I don't know how the people in the non-physical plane are going to see
this petition like if they're like ethereal ghosts floating in the void and
being like oh have you checked out their web page their web presence lately
anyways so they're trying to get 144,000 people to sign this because that's the
biblical number in book revelation they have 25,000 people have already signed
it or 26,000 close enough and what's funny is that they've stolen our money
they've poisoned our food and then they say they are trying to take away our
freedom if these dark ones are so powerful why haven't they already done it
that's always the big question if the Illuminati are so powerful why haven't
they made their move yet I do believe their private groups trying to control
parts of the public sector I do believe that but I think the fact that we're
still freer than we're supposed to be under their rule is a sign that they're
not doing things right and the same thing with these these non-physical plane
creatures they've stolen my money and they poison my food but they're trying
to take away my happiness they haven't got there yet that's pretty that's pretty
bad on you ghost overlord so I found this and I thought this was awesome so
anyways it's awesome and it's sad at the same time okay so I saw this and this is
their entry protocols for the underground resistance which again we talked
about earlier now this is both hilarious and sad first off the website that we're
going to for this is 2012 portal dot blog spot com now one if you don't care
enough about your idea to register a domain name for 1499 a year through Go
Daddy it's probably not that important to you really secondly if you're talking
about the planet being liberated now and these are all this is all recent stuff
if you're talking about the planet being liberated liberated liberated now and
you're any day now the pleidians are going to show up and we're going to need
you to fight the dark ones and it's going to happen it's going to happen soon
why is your website called 2012 six years ago and here's the thing if they
bought a domain name and they had linked it to this I never would have known but
this is what they call themselves 2012 ridiculous the ascension past dude you
got left behind like the rest of us so apparently a dream has gone out to the
people this dream has gone out to people who are not yet in the resistance of
light but are being called up it's their destiny you're a loser in your real life
you got nothing going on don't worry because there's a super secret fantasy
war coming up and you too can be a part of it if only you follow us then you'll
know your true mission in life and everyone who has ever mean to you
they'll be like you know what Jason Jason was the hero he's the one who fought
those space ghosts in the battle of Hood River because he had that dream and he
followed the entry protocols this is this is them this is what they sell to
go above people anyways so this is here goes if you if you are selected for
pre-event entry into the resistance the entry protocols are as follows step one
you will be physically contacted by a resistant agent very near to the place
where you live so I'm he will he or she will be wearing plain civilian clothes
and will emanate very positive energy he she will introduce herself himself
okay that's gonna get annoying he will introduce himself to you and ask you if
you're willing to enter the resistance it will be explained to you after in
entering the resistance you will not be able to have any physical contact with
the service population so let's let's unpack that for a second you're walking
on the street somebody walks up to you in normal clothing who just seems to be
really happy and they're going to say hi I'm Jason would you like to join the
resistance and your answer if yes you disappear you will no longer have
physical contact with the service population if you say yes you basically
go missing and become a missing person that is step one step two clarifies that
because it says you will be given between five and fifteen minutes to
collect your personal items to bring with you you will be asked to bring
objects of personal emotional value wedding rings why would you have more
than one wedding ring of photos of loved ones etc because all other objects
clothing food gold cash ID documents can be easily reproduced with replicators
you will be given a small bag and all your items will need to fit in that bag
size and weight requirements will be very similar to requirements astronauts
have had for their personal items on a space shuttle now what's funny is that
then they include a link to how much weight a astronaut can carry on a space
shuttle so again people buy into this nonsense and I'm sure people reading
this started carrying around photos of their loved ones and their wedding rings
plural and they're like well this is what I'll take with me because this is what
who clicked on the link to find out how much an astronaut can carry and why a
space shuttle why do we even have space shuttles anymore I think they got rid of
them anyways why five to 15 minutes what if I'm not by my house it says it'll be
near the location I live but what if I'm in the middle of eating subway and this
guy comes in and says are you ready to join the resistance and I'm like yeah
sure but I'm only like two inches into this foot long sub I can't finish this
in 15 minutes and I got a pocket full of wedding rings I got like eight of them
because I own a pawn shop anyways step three the resistant agent will escort
you to the entry point into the resistance this will usually be a service
store in the cellar or a basement inside a commercial building close to home
they're gonna murder you they're telling you follow me no one will ever see you
again just walk into the basement please then it says there there he and it's
weird cuz then they dropped the whole he she thing about halfway through this
cuz even they really got tired of it there he will there he will guide you to
descend a set of stairs that will lead you 30 meters or yards it says both
underground to the top most level of resistance the stairs will look somewhat
like this and it's just a picture of a manhole disappearing into the darkness
it's like a creepy ladder and I'm like I hey man I'm totally on board to find the
dark ones I also hate non-physical entities coming into our plane but I'm
not crawling down that I'm not crawling down that so but they want you to so you
go down there and it says step four when you reach the resistance level you will
approach a high-tech door that will lead into a structure that looks somewhat
like a shower cabin and then they have a picture from a video game to show you
what the resistance is going to look like it's it's from a video game so I
crawl I made a stranger that I've never met before just like a normal person
asked me if I wanted to join the resistance gives me five minutes I can't
talk to anybody he takes me to the basement has me crawl into the sewers
and get into a shower cabin now it's very typical to say you can't make this up
this is the this is what these people legit believe because we're gonna get
to the comments soon you think I'm just you know taking the piss out of this
website the comments are heartbreaking at this point the agent will ask you the
last time if you're willing to enter the resistance if you refuse you will be
brought back up to the surface and never be contacted again I mean you do ask me
that before I climb 30 meters down a ladder like it just or before I go into
your crazy murder basement if you accept the agent will leave will leave you
alone and you'll enter through the high-tech door by yourself you'll be
asked to take off all your clothes wait a second if he's if I'm by myself who's
asking me to take off my clothes it's just like a voice in the dark take off
your clothes it's a voice in the dark sewer while I'm standing in the shower
cabin you'll be asked to take off all your clothes and leave the bag with your
personal belongings in a special tray then you will be asked to enter the
shower cabin where you will be disinfected from all nano technologies all
nano technology and from most viruses and bacteria why not all those - why not
all viruses question 5 you'll exit the shower cabin on the other you'll exit
from the other side of the shower cabin into the resistance proper refresh and
disinfected at this point you will feel much better with bursts of inner joy and
will feel very alive and full of energy you'll get a new set of clothing let's
see if there's anything else here a doctor shows up they'll give a they'll
cure you of any possible diseases you'll be given your own room and there's like
a detox process and blah blah blah so anyway so there you now you know how to
get into the resistance step 9 last step is after you accept it after you are
accepted in the resistance you will not be able to go to the surface contact the
surface population or even use the surface internet / cell phone network
except in extremely rare cases that will be directly related to your mission you
will only be able to make direct contact with surface human population after the
event victory to the light so here's the thing again I'm reading this this is
nonsense I think it's a money-making scam you're listening to this I'm hoping
that you're on the same page or at least you just think it's gollible or made up
and I obviously it's made up but there are so many people whose lives are so
empty to them and they feel so directionless and meaningless to them
that they buy into this they buy into it hook line and sinker and that's one
thing I've seen in the conspiracy theory world I it comes across all the time
people have dedicated their lives to fight in the Illuminati and they they
feel like that is their goal that's why they were put on this earth because
otherwise they have to realize they're just an accountant or they're just the
teacher or they're just some unemployed kid you know they're stuck in a bad
marriage whatever it is whatever it is these things give people meaning and
purpose and it's the one thing that everyone is lacking or thinks they're
lacking in life that direction so instead of just being a nobody who everyone
just walks past because everyone wants to be someone everybody wants to be famous
that's that I like that song by who's that band how can I not remember them
they're like one of my favorite bands big-time rush big-time rush you want to
be famous but anyway so that's besides the point so you know people don't want
to be nobody they want to be somebody and not everyone has the skills the
talent the drive to become somebody or the luck to become quote-unquote
somebody big so they buy into this nonsense now again you're thinking okay
that's all nonsense hit let's look at some of the some of the comments here on
this okay here's a couple of the first ones I'm ready to be part of the
resistance I would gladly give my life to make the event happen quicker the
event is the coming war between the dark ones and the Pleiadians and the
Arthians and these lunatics here's another one assuming if I was selected I
would join the resistance movement if my mom was financially taking care of
during my mission she can't make it on her own without me financially because
she is elderly that's sad here's this guy who believes this like but what's
holding him back he's like but you know if I join the resistance and I fight for
the world and I fight for the resistance of light who's going to take care of my
elderly mom I'm the only one supporting her that's his dilemma absolutely
terrible let's see let's find another one okay here's one it's definitely a
great opportunity I guess it's like someone has to choose to just disappear
within 15 minutes I wonder how the family members friends co-workers would
react call the police I'd be okay with it if everyone on the surface would
simply forget about me but they won't someone disappearing could be
traumatizing for close ones just saying that's not positive energy I hope no one
gets kidnapped by fake agents either that's that's or real agents anyways I'll
keep training as usual he goes on to say or she so these people actually believe
it and they're like trying to figure out like oh how would I balance you know the
realism of me wanting to fight this fight this war with having to say you know
say goodbye to people are just disappearing and I think this is
probably the most harsh heartbreaking comment it's in all caps but I'm not
gonna yell it at you Cobra is the author of the article so they're gonna start off
by saying hello Cobra I am following you since 2013 five years waiting for the
event I live in Venezuela it's not good I would like to go with the resistance
but I have two children two children five cats that are my children and only
the death will separate me from my cats not her kids okay cannot disappear in
15 minutes this does not make sense one how to know that the agents are of the
resistance that's a good question question number two they would have to
notify us about 15 days before to promote our family I have to carry at least
three of my cat the most in in defense three how our family is going to know if
we are okay if we do not communication with them we need a lot of information
and new protocols victory to the light so here's this poor woman who's been
following this nonsense for five years religiously and she reads this and her
heart breaks and she's like what about my kids what about my cats how am I going
to help I this is the one thing I believe in this is the reason why I was put on
this planet was to help the resistance and I have to say goodbye to everybody
and you can just imagine her like being concerned about this pouring over this
the fact that she has to send this email out and then she decides to choose from
her cats like imagine oh imagine somebody who's so torn mentally from all
this nonsense at one night staying up thinking how many cats can I take and
how many will I leave for the dark overlord now to us that's funny that's a
funny suggestion but to her that that was a real problem she had to face and all
of these people here are really like how will I do this like oh no if I leave
tomorrow how's my mom gonna take care of herself I really want to join the
resistance this is why I was put on this world these people are disgusting and I
cover a lot of disgusting people and no these people aren't on the level of
some of the people we've covered this is gross you're taking advantage of people
and you're selling them rocks for a hundred bucks and you know that they're
selling you know that they're selling if this group is really getting 42 million
hits in the past you know six years on their website someone's buying these
stupid rocks and their stupid water and all of that stuff they're taking
advantage of people and they're selling fanfiction as if it's real and while
there simply they may go well I'm just getting money from them some of them may
actually believe this at the top but you know they're like well what's the harm
in just getting money from people are staying up late at night worried about
which cats they get to take into their resistance and which cats get left behind
to be destroyed it's that's horrible you're tricking people you're emotionally
manipulating people for what for monetary gain it's awful these this website goes
on and on and on and on and this may just be the beginning of me looking
into this group they may decide to to use their light lasers and positive
energy to come after me and all of a sudden I begin getting harassed oh wait
no no actually I would to them I would be on the side of the space ghost army
they the space ghosts would protect me from these people I would be basically
in league with the dark ones according to them maybe I am highly unlikely I don't
think dark ones suffer from sinus pain but I mean this is ridiculous and
honestly I'll tell you this to you guys this is the tip of the iceberg not just
in relations to this group but there are other cons groups like this that are
selling the spill of goods to young men and women and old men and women - yeah
these they're just taking advantage of these poor people and I find that
despicable but on the other hand I'm getting a lot of fun taking the piss out
of them and I'm gonna continue to take the piss out of them and groups like
this as long as people can can laugh with me and and through making fun of
these people and laughing at them we can start to break away at this at this hold
that is your mission you were chosen by the rabbit league you and only you can
help me take on the resistance of light that was why you were put here that is
why you listen to this podcast in the first place you and me we are chosen
that is why you are here that is why you were born on this world to help the
rabbit league fight the resistance of light are you ready I'm gonna come to
your house and I will lure you into a basement of a place you've never been
before and have you take your clothes off and only then will I know for sure
you're ready to join the rabbit league send me a hundred dollars for a rock
my name is Jason Carpenter this has been Dead Rabbit Radio