A conspiracy so weird, so deep that you can't find anything on it.
Today on Dead Ravvo Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome to another episode of Dead Ravvo Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
We've been running into some technical issues.
Some audio issues the past couple episodes.
We've missed an episode because we were working on them.
Because of that, and because I want to make sure that we can correct these issues,
I'm actually going to keep this episode short.
I've actually already recorded it twice.
There's still something going on, so I think we might have figured it out.
But again, I've recorded two half hour versions of this episode,
and I'm taking a bunch of stuff out, and this one's going to be shorter than normal.
I'm not super short, but we're just going to do some quick little story bits,
and then get into this conspiracy that, you know, I like to source my stuff.
I like to have my, say, these are the links for all this stuff, but it's gone.
It's gone from the internet.
I can't find the sources that I used to have on this.
Quick, quick notes.
You guys can let me know if you're interested in this or anything.
So the other day, I was reading this article about the, there's a group called,
there was a cult called the Children of Thunder, and there was a guy in it named Justin Helzer.
It was a cult, it was three guys.
It was two brothers and the younger brother's girlfriend.
But Justin Helzer was so enthralled to his older brother, he would do anything for him.
They believed that they were going to be able to kill or take over the Mormon church.
They were either going to kill the leadership of the Mormon church,
or simply just take over the Mormon church.
They were going to use it to spread joy, peace, and love.
They had a bunch of crazy schemes with getting a bunch of underage girls from Brazil
to have sex with people and a black male for money to raise an army of, again, Brazilian orphans,
to lay siege to the main Mormon temple in Utah to wipe out the leadership and to take over.
They eventually ended up trying to extort some old people for money.
They murdered about five people over the course of a weekend through a bunch of body parts
and some duffel bags dropped them in the river.
They're caught.
There's all having it back in 2000.
I remember when the duffel bags were being floating through the river
because that was in California and I was living in there at the time.
Not in the river. I was living in California at the time.
That aside, the reason why I was thinking about this was so just then I found out
that he, Justin Helzer, the younger brother, he hung himself in jail.
And I'm reading the article and again I've talked about bearing the lead
where you kind of put the important thing in the middle of the story, not at the beginning.
The article saying, "Yeah, he hung himself," and I'm kind of reading it and stuff like that.
It's kind of the wrap up to this whole story.
Then it goes, this comes on the back of a previous suicide attempt
where he ended up blinding himself and I thought,
"How do you blind yourself committing suicide? Electricity can happen."
People try to electrocute themselves and they go blind
or a big electrical shock can fry your eyes out.
He tried to kill himself by sticking needles in his eyes.
I know suicide methods are not easy to come by in prison,
but I don't, I mean, how long would those needles have to be
to go through your eyes and to your brain?
And why would you try both eyes if one has already failed?
I mean, that, I guess he really wanted to kill himself.
He was obviously mentally disturbed if he killed five people over the course of a weekend.
But I mean, you're sticking those needles in your eyeballs.
You stick the first one into your right eye and you're in incredible pain
and you're still alive and you go, "Well, must have to go through the left eye too."
How a blind man kills himself by hanging himself is how he eventually did it.
I'm not entirely for sure, you know, but maybe he had help
or maybe he was just super determined.
The reason why, so for whatever reason that I was like,
"Pit needles in the eyes to kill yourself. That's horrible."
Then that reminded me of something.
I don't know if this is something I particularly want to do
because it's gruesome, but some of them are hilarious.
So Marquis de Sade wrote that book, 120 Days of Sodom.
And I've read the fourth section of it.
And now, see, Marquis de Sade wrote it while he was in an insane asylum.
And Marquis de Sade is where we give the name Sadism.
And the book, it's an escalating list of terrible acts.
So the first three are kind of this narrative flow
where I think it's like four or five of elite, these elite Italians
or French aristocrats go to this castle and they engage in the most pervert--
and when I say perverse, I mean perverse activities and they get worse and worse and worse.
And the fourth one, he was never able to finish,
he basically just wrote a list of tortures.
They would make the producers of saw wet.
These are the most gruesome tortures ever.
So some of them are actually kind of hilarious because they're so ridiculous.
So if you guys want me to do every so often throw in a funny Marquis de Sade torture,
I will, but again, it can be a little heavy.
It's all fictional, none of this ever happened.
But I always thought one of the funny ones, there's some dark ones too,
so maybe they're not all funny.
But one of them was, he wanted to put two-- he wanted to take two pregnant women.
This is where we're going, guys.
He wanted to take two pregnant women, curl them together like the ying-yang symbol,
put them in a cannon, like a cannonball, and shoot them out of the cannon.
It's just bizarre.
It's completely bizarre.
And I'm reading these, like, there's a ton, there's basically I think 40 per section.
So I think there's 40 of these.
I remember reading that and thinking this would be perfect for a saw movie.
It's like, you have to choose.
There's three pregnant women in the room.
Only one will leave.
There's a key, a new floating in this big fetus carcass in this river of shit.
The person who finds the key will not be turned into a cannonball.
I don't know.
Maybe actually, now that I say that, that might actually be the funniest one.
The rest of them are pretty disturbing.
One of them is you throw a woman and her kids in, they find like a poor woman and her, like, her like, destitute kids.
You lock them into a cell and see which one she eats first.
So maybe, maybe I guess I think I've already probably exhausted the funny Marquita Stott tortures.
It's a cannonball one.
The rest of them are pretty grisly.
But if you are a producer of a saw movie or any sort of movie like that, I would, I don't want to recommend reading them because they're pretty disturbing, but it does give you a wealth of ideas.
So we're going to go ahead and get on with the episode here.
Now, this is a weird one because it's going to deal a lot with a bunch of broken links, misinformation, and a simple phrase that I remember and have seen repeated a few times.
But now is changed or gone.
And this is about an alien race called the conformers.
Now, who are the conformers?
Well, nobody really knows.
Supposedly, the information that I came across, and I think this is back like in 2010, I heard about an alien race called the conformers.
Now, what I heard was that one, they are the only alien race humanity has ever made contact with.
There are no grays, there are no reptilians, there are no Nordics.
The rest of that stuff is made up.
The only ones that we have ever run into are the conformers.
Two, they're silicone based.
They are not carbon based.
They are giant rocks.
Three, when they talk, you know, quote unquote, it sounds like pebbles dropping into a mess.
Dropping into a metal bucket.
Four, they are extremely violent and cruel.
That was the information I came across.
I was instantly intrigued because it was different than any other type of alien race I had heard of.
And I remember researching it back then, and I found a couple resources and they all had pretty much that same set of information.
There's not a lot of stuff out there, but it all had those thing steps.
And it always stuck with me because the idea of, I think one thing that a lot of people forget, or a lot of people don't understand is that
alien and alien, if they're not from Earth, if they're not like I've said before, UFOs may be from this planet,
I think that's more likely than coming from another planet.
But if they come from another planet, their DNA would be completely different than ours.
The idea of somebody evolving, a race evolving on another planet, having two arms, two legs, two eyes, a mouth is statistically improbable.
Here's the thing, if you look at a tree in the fall, if you look at a tree with no leaves on it, with the trunk and then the branches turning into other branches
and turning into other branches, it looks identical to a human's nervous system.
When you look at a human nervous system that's been stripped of everything, they have those photos, and it's just like a cadaver, but it's just the nerve endings.
That's what a tree looks like because we share a DNA, we share an evolutionary path.
Everything on this planet has shared resources, has a shared origin.
It wouldn't be the same on another planet at all.
There's different biological factors, there's different environmental factors, everything's different.
It's another planet, the only thing that's the same would be dirt.
The fact that it's a ball of matter, and even then if it's from a gas giant, then again, all that's out the window.
So the idea of these reptilians, even though they're reptiles, showing up and be like, "Hello, stranger, I also have fingers," and all this stuff, it's completely ridiculous.
But a rock creature, I don't know how they move. See, that was again, there wasn't a lot of detail on these things.
Now, I always found that very intriguing. I wanted to do an episode on it, and for about the past week, I've been gathering resources and I realized something.
They're gone. There's two types of web pages that deal with the conformers.
There's dead links. When you click on them, this page has been removed, this blog no longer exists, which happens.
I understand that. But what's weird is some of them are actually like UFO Digest, like some of them are actually like UFO Report.
These are websites that are dedicated to this. I get the blog not being around anymore, but the website's still up, but the page you requested does not exist.
And these websites, they catalog this stuff. This is what they do. The rest of their pages are up, but nothing on the conformers.
So that was very suspicious. And also, resources, any information on these guys is incredibly rare.
So there was a group of, there was a duo of brothers called the Pickering Brothers, and they met with someone they called Source A.
Now, right now, the Pickering Brothers are the only, and Source A are the only way you'll find anything about the conformers.
And it's different. The information is different than what it used to be.
So the Pickering Brothers say that Source A says, "Yes, there are a race of beings called the conformers. They're 90% silicone, 10% carbon. They have arms.
They sound like pebbles dropping into a metal bucket, but they're also jelly, different colored jelly. They're not no longer a rock creature.
They're known as stinkies because they communicate via smell. They smell like burnt popcorn, and they can change the smell they emit to communicate with another stinky.
They hate the grays. They're ultra-religious. They've been here for 6,000 years, and the grays are trying to get them to leave Earth,
but the stinkies have decided to stay because their religious God wants them to convert or destroy us.
That information is wildly different than the information that that was out 10 years ago.
Wildly different. A little more detail in some places, radically changed than others.
Even though the information is out there, the Pickering Brothers are saying, "Yes, yes, they are an official, the quote-unquote "official race" now.
Most UFO investigators have never heard of these guys, and I know what you're thinking.
Jason, they've never heard of them because they're fake, and they're made up, which is possible, which is likely, let's be fair.
But again, it's weird because people whose job is to catalog this stuff and people who make money by hyping this stuff up,
you think they would be, "There's a new race. They're called the conformers," or "Aka stinkies."
These guys don't exist. These guys, there's nothing. When I say "don't exist," I mean on the Internet.
There is almost zero resources on them.
And the main resources we have now are completely, completely different than the resources from before. Why?
Why? Even for the people who make money believing in this, or for the people who are making it up to make money?
They don't know about them. They don't exist.
The Bigger Ring brothers are really big in the disclosure community, so it's not like these are just guys who are...
You know, it's not two guys with a YouTube channel. These guys are actively pushing disclosure, so they've acknowledged the conformers,
but nobody else's. They're not in these big lists. The webpages are going blank. The information's been changed.
What's going on?
To be honest, I debated whether or not to cover the conformers, because I don't believe...
Whenever I come across stuff and people be like, "You know, we wrote this, and the government revealed that this was this,"
but then the government took it down so you can't prove it like golf rumors.
They said the political article was up, but then it was removed from the Internet.
And in that episode, I was like, "You can't remove stuff from the Internet. It's out there."
This isn't here anymore.
The resources that I had aren't there anymore.
The Pickering Brothers account is close enough, so you still see those key details.
They also say it sounds like pebbles dropping in a metal bucket.
They're not rocks now. They're gelatin. They're not the only species. They work with others, but the initial idea of them being silicone...
The name, them being silicone in the way that they make that sound, that's all the same.
So obviously, they saw the same source I did. They added stuff on.
Did they do that for disinformation?
Did they do that because the myth has simply evolved?
Or did they do that?
Is it possible that this story is being suppressed by somebody?
Is it possible that there is a race of aliens called the conformers that are the only alien race we've met, they're silicone-based, and they're incredibly violent?
I mean, anything's possible.
But before I started researching this again, if you told me that stuff could get scrubbed from the Internet...
And you couldn't find anything on it after eight years, I'd go, "Well, you know, yeah, blogs can go out and web pages can go out."
And you go, "No, no, no, Jason, I mean, it's gone or changed."
I should say with this caveat that I was able to find bits and pieces of the original description of the conformers online, but again, bits and pieces.
And they all... I found some resources that talked about them being rock-based and stuff like that.
One of the websites I had to consult was a foreign website that I had to translate.
It was like a Spanish website that I had to translate into English, and that article is very dismissive of the idea.
They don't like aliens, and that's fine. It's good to be skeptical.
But it's just one of those things, like...
I'm kind of speechless.
I don't like to do stories that I can't source, but this one's just going to be a bunch of websites that contradict what I've said
or just have a simple paragraph of what I said or not much of anything.
I would ask you guys to help me on this one.
See if you can find out any more information about this race called the conformers.
And let's see if we can dig something up.
It could have been erroneous information.
It could have been completely made up.
But if both of those things were true, why can't we find anything on it anymore?
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be the email address.
So yeah, send me anything you find there.
You can also hit me up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
You can also hit it, get us at Twitter, which is JasonOCarpenter@jasonocarpenter.
Let's see what we can find out. Let's make this a team effort.
Because I would love, honestly, if this turned out to just be some big scam and it came out,
that would be awesome.
Again, just an answer to the mystery.
So if we can trace back to see if somebody made it up,
if we could see that maybe the Pickering Brothers made it up and they've just changed,
they've tooled the myth as time has gone on, let's find out.
I don't mind getting dismissed.
You know, getting saying, "Yo Jason, this isn't true."
And let's be fair.
Again, I'm not a big proponent of aliens coming from other planets.
I think that's very, very unrealistic.
I agree more with aliens coming from another dimension or aliens already have been here.
But if they did come from another planet, they would be completely alien to us.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
[Music]