A man pulls out a gun and shoots a world leader for the first time in history.
And then we meet a grieving young mother.
Her younger sister who she loved so dearly has recently passed away from a drug overdose.
And her sister used to be a ghost hunter and she's decided to continue her crusade on the
other side today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I'm your host Jason
Garbner I'm my days going okay I hope you guys are having a great day if you're a new
listener you're like what that's the weirdest intro I've ever heard I just want to be honest
I usually say I'm having a great day I'm still struggling with this little earache ear infection
thing going on I can only eat bland foods my tongue is swollen you're like Jason go
to the doctor don't record don't record a podcast it's not swollen it's just a little
red but anyways thank you for your concern probably should I actually ordered some stuff
up Amazon to treat it myself speaking of treating speaking of speaking of segues let's go ahead
and introduce our one of our live stream supporters this is someone who gave a live
stream donation back in 2019 it's taken me a long time to get to you guys and this guy's
also a huge supporter of the show Patreon supporter been listening to it since like episode 20
or 30 it's Barfee man everyone give a round of applause to Barfee man he's walking into
Dead Rabbit Command doing cartwheels throwing up throwing up everywhere Barfee man you're
gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't financially support the
show through like the patreon or the merch store that's fine just help spread the word
about the show that also really really helps out a lot Barfee man I'm gonna go ahead and
toss you the keys to the which which vehicle sound effects is gonna make my throat hurt
the less I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys I'm gonna go and toss you an ore to
the Dead Rabbit Robo we are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command we are headed on out to
the Dutch Republic Splishity Splash Splishity Splash Barfee man is courageously leading
us all the way across the Atlantic Ocean we're headed back to the year 1580 as well so let's
make sure we navigate into that time portal over there it's 1580 so it's old timey all
of a sudden we're wearing like old timey clothes they're super like itchy and heavy I bet you
I bet you they are the most uncomfortable people on planet earth back in the 1580s because
like cavemen were running around and like leopard skin so this documentary once called
the Flintstones I know what it's like they're wearing like saber two tiger pelts and it's
very breezy nowadays you know we wear like yoga pants and tank tops but in the 1580s
everything was so heavy and woolen and super itchy and like then they're like hey we need
to go into battle here put on like 80 pounds of steel you're like oh man I hope I get
killed right away so that way I don't have to keep running around all this heavy stuff
I bet you totally suck but it's 1580 we take all our clothes off retired walking around
in these itchy itchy clothes and we're in Spain and there's this dude there and his name is
King Philip and he's like you know what it sure is fun being the king of Spain officially
I'm going to outlaw clothes but for now I'll allow them I'm King of Spain I'm also King
of the Netherlands but I'm having some trouble up in the Netherlands you see there's this
guy named William first of orange and he's this Dutch independence leader and he's really
getting my goat which is literal literal back then because everyone had goats and William
took one of King Philip's he's like listen you got to take care of them they're calling
this guy like father of the fatherland I'm King so many to take care of William but
William was such a beloved resistance leader that no one wanted to do it and King Philip
stomped around the courtroom for a while and he issues a proclamation at a certain point
he goes listen if you kill him I will give you 25,000 crowns that's money it's not just
a bunch of crowns that you're like oh now what do I do with these I'm not king of 25,000
countries 25,000 crowns was the currency you also gain a peerage which is like a class
upgrade it's like a real life role-playing game and you get a house an estate it's not
like some busted old Shrek house it's like you get fancy grass and put your own goats
you get all sorts of goats and you get a big house so this goes on he makes his proclamation
and in July of 1584 there's a dude named Balthazar Gerard he's a 26 year old man I know a bunch
of history majors just shut the podcast off before they turn their ground out of fast
forward because they know exactly where this story is going but for the rest of you ignorant
goons strap in Balthazar Gerard 26 years old he goes I want that man I want the fame I
want the fortune I want it all like Sharpey he heads out to Difft that's a city in the
Dutch Republic but he gets there and he's like oh man you know what I'm missing I want
to do this so I make money but I'm too poor this is a real problem I never thought about
this before he's too poor to assassinate somebody.
He's too poor to assassinate somebody because you need like a weapon right and you need
a weapon that will kill someone you can't walk around like a little dagger I mean you
can and that'll kill someone but this guy has protection this guy has an army really
is a resistance leader not really going to be all go up and shank this dude in lunchline
he's like I don't have enough money to kill him I this is this is quite the conundrum
but once I kill him I'll get all this money but he starts trying to borrow he goes all
I need is 50 crowns if you guys got like 50 crowns laying around that's all I need and
they're like what a foreign he's like to donate to somebody else what you think I'm here to
kill William and they're like we didn't think that until you said it he's walking around
and he can't get the money now he's dressed like a bum and this isn't this isn't a clever
disguise of his he's a bum he's a bum he's just he's just a little down on his luck he
just wants to murder a man make his dream come true at one point he's hanging around
outside Williams house which is called the prizenhof it's just very very elegant mansion
it's still there today he's outside the prizenhof he's this hobo and he's like oh man he's
all doing he's picking flowers he's like I'll kill him I'll kill him not I'll kill him he's
just wistfully dreaming of the day he will assassinate William and get a class upgrade
he's like no more bum for me he's he's a bum though he's a bum he's outside this mansion
so a royal guard comes up and goes hey you gotta get out of here no bumming around about
the start tells the guard look at my rags look at how bummy I look and I know that's
why he came over to accost me but I want to go to church man I want to find my peace with
God before I kill William they're like what what's that last part oh nothing you think
you could lend me some money so I could buy some new clothes so I could go to church and
the guard goes ah I don't get paid enough for that but I know someone who may lend you
some money so the guard goes to William and says hey there's this hobo outside he wants
to go to church but his clothes are gross and they super stink and William says you know
what I will give that young man 50 crowns so he can go to church guard gives Balthazar
the money and he goes and he buys two pistols click click click click click yeah he goes
by some non stinky clothes he's like whoo that guard was right I smelled he buys himself
two pistols now remember we're in the year 1584 so firearms are readily available I mean
they're part of military arsenal but 1584 what we're about to get to and I kind of gave
it away in the beginning but this isn't the whole crux of the story 1584 we're about to
witness the very first execution of a world leader by firearms now Balthazar didn't want
50 bucks just to buy the guns he actually has a plan not only to execute but to get
away with it because that's the key he's not a martyr he's not there to actually go and
like a perform this for a cause he wants money and a class upgrade and that nice new house
this is his plan he's going to go into the palace jump out surprise Balthazar surprises
guard shoot him twice that's why he has two guns he wants to make sure this works he then
bought a pigs bladder I never would have thought of this Balthazar straight up and first off
that's pretty dope name secondly James Bond of the 1584 he buys a pig bladder and apparently
I didn't know that Looney Tunes actually were real physics a pig bladder I'm assuming he
inflated it but this was his plan he was going to run jump off the rampart of the palace
land in the moat this is old timey they still had all this stuff and the pig bladder would
help him float across the moat he has a horse ready to go and before anyone can really even
process this because no one has ever been executed a royal figure had never been assassinated
with a gun before that alone would shock everyone he's going to be on his horse he's right in
a way he's eventually going to get back to Spain he's going to get back into the safety
of the king and he's going to get all this up he has his planned out July 10 1584 William
is walking down the stairs with his guards Balthazar jumps out shoot some twice hit some
twice kills William father of the fatherland William the first of orange he starts to run
out the guards are flabbergasted and they're all sitting around with like pikes and things
like that they probably have their own pistols but you would it would be this equivalent
as if you were sitting at work and someone walked in and vaporized your boss with a laser
beam and then ran out you would you'd be like wait what that can happen these things exist
well they knew guns exist and they never thought they would see a leader of any sort of affluence
die of one Balthazar's running he's busting loose from the castle he has his pig bladder
ready to go he looks he sees this little horse winking winking on the other side of the moat
he's getting ready to jump off the rampart into the moat he trips he trips on a pilot
trash they didn't plan on and he falls to the ground not doesn't fall to the ground
off the cliff of the building he just kind of tumbles in the ground the guards catch them
and they beat the crap out of them it was after this I'm not done with the story if you guys
are like oh that was kind of underwhelming that was just wrap this up though that was
the first time a gun had ever been used in a political assassination and a gun was not
used again until a 200 years later very very interesting they're so practical for assassinating
people okay CIA agents in a state listening to that I did not mean what you think I do
not mean exactly what I said they're so efficient but I think there is an in elegance to it
but yeah between this now the use of all the time because it's where less civilized age
but that happened and then it was another 200 years before someone goes you know what
we should do what Balthazar did we should shoot our political leaders in the face but
this might be there may be a reason why they didn't do this when they never shot anyone
again because although his target died that is not the end of the story of Balthazar Balthazar
is sitting in prison and this is prison in 1584 so they go but let the torturers begin
so they some guy comes out of retirement he's like oh dude I've tortured all my life I tortured
all those people and you know it's time for me to just it's time for me to hang up the
human skin and become a farmer but now that this guy is killed William he has he deserves
the worst torture possible so yeah this is what we're gonna talk about this is when history
majors left this is what we're gonna talk about for the next seven minutes he's hung
on a pole and he's whipped watch and then this is what's so weird one I think a lot
of this torture stuff is exaggerated I think a lot of these historical torturers we covered
one before about a guy who had to sit in a red hot chair and they use red hot clamps
to pull off his thumbs and his toes and stuff like that and I go with the chair would have
killed like the shock from sitting in the chair would have killed him on the spot and
so on because when I put that episode on YouTube I had a bunch of torture porn aficionados
been like no it was real man it was totally real don't ruin my dreams and I was like it
probably wasn't they probably got a red hot chair he would have had a heart attack for
even gotten to the chair I know what was coming I think a lot of it or he's dead at that point
and they're like and then we did this and did that so I think a lot of this torture
stuff is exaggerated to this stuff is so incongruent like you tie me to a pole and you whip me
I'm not having a good day right I'm not Rihanna it doesn't turn me on but then okay so this
is this is okay so starting off right from the beginning supposedly this is all really
happened but jigsaw would be like really dude really that's a little that's a little ridiculous
they whip him with a whip then they smear him with honey which would be so soothing I have
a sore throat I would love honey right now but they smear him with honey and which you
think if it helps your throat it would also help the bleeding wounds caused by the whip
then they bring out a goat and describe this goat has a sandpaper tongue I don't know if
I don't know if all goats do I don't know if this goat was specifically bred for honey
torture but they bring the goat out and the idea is is the goat with its sandpaper tongue
is going to lick him and it's going to hurt and that's why the honey's on him so goat
will lick what type of torture is that just whip him for another 10 minutes think about
all the work that goes into that there's some guys like autos like hey guys they came over
I had this crazy dream last night how about we cover him in honey and we have a goat lick
it off of him and think about how long it would take to cover a human being in honey
lead the goat in and then he's like ow ow what like eventually like when it isn't hurt
it tickles I don't care how rough a goat's tongue is you just got whipped you just got
whipped and the goat doesn't lick up the honey this is all historical this is hilarious
the goat makes some historian had to write this down and go wait what the goat the goat
didn't even do anything the goat didn't lick him do goats even like honey what's going
on here the goat does not want to lick him now they never say that it washed they washed
him off I'm assuming they didn't I'm assuming they were like well that didn't work let's
wash the honey off of this political assassin will assume he's covered in honey for the
rest of the time which would be super sticky of punishment in and of itself they then tie
they take him this is ridiculous they take him and they roll him into a ball they roll
him into a ball and tie him together so now he's like a ball now he's like a human ball
of yarn I don't know if they covered him completely in rope where they're like the guards are
like hey where's Balpas are and they're like that's him you're like what oh I thought it
was a giant ball of yarn I think they just like hog tied him I don't know if they completely
covered him up Garfield is playing with him they tie him up in a ball so he can't sleep
which I'm gonna take a stab in the dark no pun intended I think being whipped I think
being whipped a lot and being afraid you're gonna get tortured the next day that's gonna
keep you awake too I could probably fall asleep in a ball shape actually people sleep in the
fetal position all the time so you could totally do that he's already had this whore I can
almost guarantee you this is the rest of the episode I don't know if we're gonna have time
for the other one but he's maybe we'll do a second shorter story for the next three
days about this are now it's public humiliation right now that they've experimented with the
goat and that didn't work now they're bringing them out into the public they strap them to
a pole and they mock him boo you suck man boo you're super sticky he's like that's not
my fault they make me sticky they're like no no excuses the buck stops with you you're
gross you're gross that I would be like why for three days I mean it might hurt my feelings
a bit I bet you you can't fall asleep as a ball I can throw his balls you're like oh
I wish I could be free in a ball but that's nothing dude like really what could you say
to me over the course of three days that would be worse than me getting whipped well they
haven't tied up and they're mocking him for three days and then they take the against
bizarre escalation like okay is everyone did everyone say something mean about this guy
okay you good you in the back you said something mean about okay now let's move on to the next
stage they should have just done this they should have done this for three days they
took 300 pounds of stones and tie them to his big toes that's torture but logically he
would have no toes he would have no toes at this point they let these 300 pound weights
hang for 30 minutes my toes my toes shut up complainer they're like no no the mocking
portion is over sir you can't mock him this is the stone on the top or sorry sorry I didn't
know that for 30 minutes during your pounds on your toes I weigh almost during the pounds
I put a bunch of weight on my vacation I did put on some weight but imagine me hanging
on two of me hanging on to a dude's toes me stepping on a guy's toes would be incredibly
painful imagine him hanging from a pole and me being like you get up there as I'm pulling
on his toes for 30 minutes then they have a real feet thing over in the Dutch Republic
I don't know if it's still a thing that they have this weird fetish feet fetish thing but
in back then they definitely did if you're pulling on his toes then they go bring out
the shoes bring out the shoes and he must be like I'm not from around here maybe they're
really fancy shoes maybe they're the shoes of forgiveness maybe they'll let me go they
bring out shoes and they're well oiled uncured dog skin shoes and they're too small who cares
someone was just hanging on my toes who cares if the shoes are too small well you didn't
let me finish you take these uncured dog skin shoes and you put them on your feet and they're
super tiny and what happens is he's then hung over a fire again that's enough right just
hanging someone over a fire don't have to mock them you hang them over a fire and these
shoes they dry and they start to get smaller and smaller and smaller eventually these
shoes tightened up until he had no more feet because the the okay now I don't think that's
possible I've come across other torture stories where people get sewn into cow hides and then
the hide is put out in the sun and the hide crushes them as it dries and that's a little
more believable because you can suffocate someone by simply putting pressure on their
chest that'll kill them they can't breathe but you have all sorts of foot bones and stuff
like that I don't care if you put small shoes on me and they slowly cooked you think they
would just crumble away you think there's like a path of less resistance the human foot
that's genetically engineered to last 80 years and run across savannahs in the pursuit of
wilder beasts or or dog skin or dried up or non dried up wet dog skin that's slowly dries
they could just fall apart but now he doesn't have feet they've been crushed they're nothing
but stumps due to this scientifically dubious torture method then they take his shoes off
and I'm assuming he's got my shoes my new shoes no I came to love those things they
take his shoes off and they brand his armpits they take his shoes off I only have a few
more of these okay they take his brand new shoes off he's like no I'll always remember
the times we had together he has a scrapbook he has a scrapbook and spritters of his feet
getting smashed and then they go put your arms up I think his arm I don't think they
asked him politely I think he's still like bound with his arms up they take a hot branding
iron and brand them under his armpits it's a picture of his shoes you'll never forget
your shoes I wasn't going to anyways I love those shoes they brand an image of the shoes
underneath his arms then it said that they so so bizarre how did you picture this guy
the whole time I pictured him like old timey clothing like maybe he just has on underwear
like they're not naked because they're probably Puritans but he's probably wearing like rags
for underwear that's about it I mean how do you dress a man for public torture they soak
his shirt and alcohol and I spread that ago he's still wearing his shirt they didn't catch
on fire they didn't get all bloodied up apparently he still had on a shirt this whole time they
covered an alcohol and then it was weird right they covered alcohol you think what are they
going to set him on fire if he's going to die eventually Jason is this man being tortured
to this day they take because that's what I would have done if I had to cover someone
in alcohol I would have thrown matches at him and would have like taken satisfaction
to knowing nine of the matches out of the ten will actually extinguish as I'm throwing
them at the person I'm not a torch I actually despise torture but if I was torturing someone
this is what I would do I'd keep throwing the matches because I know eventually one's
going to light it but most of them won't and there's a psychological torture so I think
they're going to do something like this right now I don't think they even had matches back
then they cover his shirt and alcohol and then they pour bacon fat boiling baking fat
all over his body just skip the shirt just get the shirt dude if you have boiling pig
fat just laying around I'm sure they boiled it specifically for this just do that just
do that you don't have to go well first let's get his shirt all nice and juicy anyways that
happens then okay just one two three can it's only only five more I mean they really went
to work on this guy they really really went to town on this guy you're like he's just
such a despised torture and yet you seem to be awfully entertained by this again I think
a lot of this stuff is exaggerated and in the case in point he just had boiling pig fat
actually looking at my notes it said burning pig fat so maybe the maybe the burning pig
fat was to soak mechs with the alcohol and the shirt but I mean like that's saying like
if someone's like spilling like lighter fluid around your house and then they bring in a
bunch of napalm you're like you didn't have to use the you know these lighter fluid you're
gonna bring out the napalm so maybe he's like ah but he's burning or boiling one of the
two it's super painful no matter what then they go let's put nails let's get some nice
metal nails and shove them underneath his fingernails and his toenails the man's boiling
pig fat at this point ah and then some guys like whoa put it out put it out put it out
you know what I explain them down you know what we should do we should put like metal
nails and people like what that's such a deescalation just keep covering them in pig fat but anyway
so this on a red this and I go wait a second he has toenails still doesn't have toes doesn't
have foot how are you gonna so stuff like that I go they're just making stuff up but
anyway so then boiling pig fat metal steel underneath your nails now it's execution day
this has been going on for a while they have all the balloons they release a bunch of balloons
their little skull faces are floating through the air kids are ready they have their popcorn
it's the day of execution this is what they do they take his right hand I don't know why
because he killed him with both hands but they take his right hand and they burn it off
ah that was my second favorite hand ah then they get some metal pinchers you're like just
skip to the end just skip to the end they have metal pinchers and they rip they described
it as they ripped off his skin from six places which begs the question which six which six
and you go Jason nobody's asking that question this poor man has been suffering for days
but it's like if you had like obviously if someone came at me with metal pinchers and
says I'm gonna pinch off six pieces of your skin like I would go okay get a little bit
get a little bit of my thigh maybe some now you won't want your butt because you gotta
sit down on that but like there's places in your body you'd be like no I'm fine you can
like take out like the webbing between my index finger and my thumb because I don't use
that too often I mean that probably grows back maybe a little bit of elbow so which
six this guy this guy's not worried about whether or not you can play video games he's
gonna be executed by wonder which six places did it have any significance it doesn't matter
because he is eventually quartered or you rip off your arms and your legs he's disemboweled
they rip his heart out while he's still alive because you know getting your getting your
he would listen he would have died long before this of just infection and shock but let's
assume that the Dutch the Dutch people in most prolific liars and have a foot fetish
he disemboweled him he's still alive they cut his heart out he's still alive they throw
they throw his own art in his face while he's still alive he gets to feel the sensation
of his own heart hitting him and be like that was less weird than I thought it would be
honestly thought it would be more shocking and then they chop his head off and Balthazar
Gerard 26 years old is finally dead finally got the punishment for the execution of William
the first of orange very very interesting story I honestly didn't expect it to last
that long I just got such a kick out of it maybe maybe because I'm going through my own
mildly uncomfortable pain that I could sit and look at the pain of another man and chuckle
that's not true I found that story I found that story on a day I felt great and I still
had to get laugh about it we don't have enough time to do the second story about the girl
whose sister was a ghost hunter that's a really cool and we're going to see that one for tomorrow
let me take a quick look though and see what I got ready to go that's relatively short
it's interesting in a different way let me it's interesting in a different way than
I'm used to covering so let's go ahead and get started on this one Barfee man I'm gonna
toss you the keys to the Carbenter copter we are leaving behind the Dutch Republic we're
saying goodbye to Saint Balthazar Gerard we are headed on out to Mount St. Helens Washington
and I got this story from a good friend of mine Sabine and she was very excited about
it she was like Jason I have a story for you might go oh cool you like the enthusiasm
Matt it's May 18th 1980 and Mount St. Helens erupts lava is going everywhere I don't think
there was lava I don't think it was like a Hollywood movie but there was ash that was
the big problem a lot of people were killed by the ash very very deadly I think it might
be the most deadly volcano eruption in modern US history I'm pulling that I'm pulling that
out of my butt so if that's not true please save the hate mail but 57 people were killed
it caused 3.5 billion dollars in today money the largest landslide in recorded history happened
when part of Mount St. Helens fell apart but that's all pretty interesting right volcanoes
I think the very first episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I talk about volcanoes I love the topic
of volcanoes that's not why we're talking about it that's not why we're adding this
episode adding this tail into my torture porn episode that I just did people believe that
not only did Mount St. Helens cause all this death and damage but it also released the
bat squash I never heard of the bat squash before so when Sabine told me about the bat
squash she read about it in the Guardian I believe and I go what I never heard of the
same must be fake if I didn't hear about it if I Jason Garvin I didn't hear about it but
I didn't think it was fake but I go that's weird I never heard about it I'll have to
look it up my interest was peaked Mount St. Helens volcanic eruption bat squash comes
flying out of it sounds pretty interesting I was I was wrong I was wrong this topic is
dumb it's super dumb and that the it's so funny because I've been wanting to talk about
this but this is actually great this episode might run a little long but I've been wanting
to talk about this because it's dumb I didn't really know how to fit it in because I didn't
want to build up the topic like in a way that I'm doing now and then reveal and think about
it how many times do I cover style cover stuff that I think is dubious factually I'll say
I don't know if this is true but let's put on our conspiracy calves but I never really
covered topics I think that I personally I think it's dumb until now and that's the reason
why I want to talk about it I it's this let me tell you briefly what the back of the
Squatch is originally I was hoping to get this done in like five minutes but I can already
tell it's gonna spiral out of it and don't leave because you go it's stupid Jason
says it's stupid so it's not in good the bad Squatch is described as this it's nine feet
tall it weighs as much as two grown grizzly bears I have no idea I have no idea how they
got that estimate but it weighs as much as and the multiple sightings of this thing blue
fur odd detail right it's blue has a wolf like muzzle and it has bird like wings that
span out to 50 feet now it's unlike the mothman because when she was telling me about this
I go so it's I am thinking it's like the mothman it's connected to this disaster it's connected
to Mount St. Helens it flew out when you look at any account of the bat Squatch they talk
about it being related to Mount St. Helens this is what's so weird about this I read multiple
articles on this hoping the story would get slightly interesting and it got dumber and
dumber I think there has to be something else going on here there has to be something else
going on here people every article basically states that this thing came out of Mount St.
Helens but the very first sighting of it was not until 1994 14 years later in Pierce County
Washington April 1994 Brian Canfield said he was driving his truck it breaks down he
sees a blue winged creature flying overhead there was another sighting in Mount Chasta
California in 2009 several hikers see a winged creature that matching the description of
bat Squatch down in Cali it's dumb super dumb you would say this is what's so fascinating
you would think the idea of a flying Sasquatch on paper it sounds amazing but it could be
a whole new layer to the Bigfoot mythos a flying one with wings I that I heard that I
was like that's awesome it's not it's super boring let's put on our conspiracy caps here
I believe that and I we've talked about this before and I'm not the only one who believes
this either because we had other people kind of put their own spin on it I believe that
there are hidden codes out there we've talked about these codes being used to pass on insider
trader information we did an episode on that but even before that revelation which I find
very fascinating I and this may fall into that I think that sometimes these stories
are put out there as codes coded messages for other people and unless you know what
the end message is or how to break the code or who it's belongs to it makes no sense out
of all of the stories we've ever covered on the show this is probably the most bland and
it shouldn't be a flying Bigfoot should be awesome I did a ton of research on this thing
you can follow it up on your the show notes it's not good she didn't find it in the Guardian
the the story of or the newspaper organ live did it but there's a lot of stuff on this
and it all sucks it's all really really bad so why if it's made up it should be so fantastical
it can't help but peak your imagination if it's really could be mundane but none of
the details out of why do they keep connecting it to the Mount St. Helens mythos it's almost
like there's something else behind it there's a new show coming out on Fox Nation which
I is either some cable network I think it's a cable network that streams online called
monsters across America and one of the episodes they're doing is the bat squash of Mount St.
Helens that episode's coming out pretty soon like this article is printed just back in
August of 2021 why now I mean sure that's just a television show that needs filler material
I get it but there's way there's just so many better cryptids there even there's even better
bigfoot stories to tell than this one that there's been very there's been no photographs
there's been no video footage there's been sporadic sightings over the last 30 some odd
years I believe there's something else going on to this story I believe it's coming out
now because the story's been around for a while but I believe it's being publicized
now because it's and again conspiracy cat fully on but this is a conspiracy cat theory
that I believe that a lot of times we cease to not predictive programming that's not
what I'm talking about I'm talking about I have a message that I need to send you so
I'm gonna put it in a way that no one else will be able to decipher it that's what I'm
saying I do find an interesting connection to this though and this is something Sabine
also brought up maybe Sabine is in on this mountain madness as this episode's currently
gonna be hitting the air on that Fox Nation show right now there's a expedition on Mount
Adams in Washington it's another volcano there's a group of people around Mount Adams who sincerely
believe that this mountain has a hatch in it a portal a physical portal that you can
find open up and go into and find this alien base there's been alien sightings around Mount
Adams for decades they believe it's there's a base in the mountain and this is the lowest
snow level like the lowest snowpack on Mount Adams in decades so these UFOs are scurrying
all over the mountain all day long and they have been for months if they're going to find
the hatch they believe they're gonna find it now because any other time it would be completely
covered up by snow this is their best chance to find the hatch you know what it's weird
you can find a ton of information on bat squash right now I can find none about this hatch
I've heard about the UFO legends around Mount Adams I know there's groups out there that
believe in that but I wasn't able to find a single article and there is a lot of activity
on the mountain right now I wasn't able to find this any I wasn't able to find a single
article Facebook group anything about this search am I saying the two stories are connected
am I saying the saga of bat squash being in the media all of a sudden is a message about
what's really going on at Mount Adams and they're keeping that one under wraps I don't
know what I'm saying honestly I just find it very very convenient that one topic about
volcanoes is super popular I wouldn't say popular it's super dumb it's boring I can't
imagine a show dedicating 30 minutes to it and then we have this other thing going on
in a volcano in the same state that could have world changing ramifications that there's
no information on misdirection look over there not here because we saw what happened with
a raid area 51 right all those people were talking about it not everyone showed up but
there was a big thing imagine that same thing on land does not control by the government
imagine if there was a big push find the hatch find the hatch find the hatch you'd have all
the forest fin weirdos you'd have all the alien you'd have all the area 51 people out there
you have all these big parties rescue crews that have to be going up there and it would
actually impede the search for the real hatch if there is one but is there a connection between
the bat squash story coming out now I don't know I feel like there is I feel like there
is and sometimes as a conspiracy theorist I mean you can't never win an argument like
that you can never sway anyone's opinion but I feel like there is because otherwise why
is such a dumb story getting play why is the bat squash story becoming popular and I get
it not everyone has to be in the same things that I'm into but if you're there's just so
much other better bigfoot stuff that's what you want to talk about and even just better
cryptids in general bat squash I get wanting to cover something that's obscure I'm glad
that they're covering stuff that's obscure but at a certain point you got to look into
and go well it's obscure because it's lame right I don't know and you may feel like I'm
being a gatekeeper you may wish I still continue to talk about torture but yeah I'm just very
puzzled by it and I have no pithy way to wrap this episode up I didn't plan on doing this
this is one of those topics that I did all the research and it took all the notes and
I thought I don't know if I'm ever going to cover this because the topic itself I don't
find super intriguing but the topic behind the topic might be more important than a big
blue monster flying out of a volcano you almost have to go out of your way to make this story
boring right like it should just intrinsically be awesome but it's just not that good which
I find in an odd way even more fascinating than the middle of the road cryptid story
that I would have told and it would have taken me five to ten minutes and then we would have
forgotten about it because we would have moved on to the next episode maybe I would have
referenced it once or twice going forward but is this story I'm assuming that the people
really saw something back in 1994 but I man I it's kind of hard for me to wrap my head
around like what am I saying that the story is real wouldn't that be trippy if the story
is not real and they made it up because this is super easy we've discovered this before
on this show the story never happened and they made it up recently and they backtracked
it to make it look like it was older that's happened before we've covered that stuff before
with like the lone pine devils which was totally fake I don't know I feel like I'm just kind
of spiraling out and I could probably keep talking over and over again about this but
I it's weird and sometimes when we look at these stories we have to look at the reason
behind the stories a lot of urban legends I say this all the time are cautionary tales
but some of these stories may be planted by the government or by other agencies and they
use them to communicate information between each other and right now the story of the
bat-squatch being aired on fox nation and getting press and organ live and I'm assuming
other newspapers as well as all the websites that I found it on could be a signal bat-squatch
yeah it's lame the government agents know that but pay attention to what's happening
on that other volcano in Washington that may be a story that's far less lame that may be
a story that changes the world dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email
address you can also it's up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio tick talk is at dead rabbit radio
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen
to it every day I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys
you
you you
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]