Is there really a Mayan deity that encourages her followers to hang themselves?
And is this goddess still worshipped to this day?
And then we travel to Venezuela to take a look at a bizarre blob that's oozing up out
of the streets of that country.
Is this a natural occurrence?
Is it a political ploy?
Or is it the key to understanding UFO investigations today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing and I hope you guys
have some awesome plans for the weekend.
Let's go ahead and get this episode started.
We got a ton of stuff to cover so walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our legacy
Patreon supporters.
Everyone give it up for TVs Cody.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in TVs Cody.
Walk on and carry that television set and sit it right over there.
TVs Cody.
You're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
I honestly do.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That helps out so much.
Talk about it online.
Talk about it with your friends.
Talk about it to Total Strangers.
The next thing on the bus, anything helps the show grow.
TVs Cody, let's go ahead and toss you the rabbit robo.
We're gonna ro ro ro all the way out of Dead Rabbit Command and head down to the Yucatan.
Splishity splash.
Work those delts bro.
Get them muscles growing.
We're gonna need them for this story because we're headed back in time to the time of the
conquistadors.
Listen man, history's been full of bad time periods and bad places to be.
I think ranking up there, probably in my top five, would be in South America, in Central
America at the time of the conquistadors.
You know it's so interesting when, and I'm not the first person to say this, this isn't
groundbreaking by any means, but if you really want to look at what will happen to humanity,
if aliens show up, look at what the conquistadors did to the native populations.
The Mayans, the Aztecs, these are huge civilizations, they had their stuff on lock.
And they got just swallowed up by a technologically superior opponent and their reinforcements
were months away when something went bad for the conquistadors.
They're like, "Okay guys, we just have to hold this position for about nine months and
hope that these ships can get here in time to fortify us."
That's exactly what it would be like with alien invasion.
Even if we were able to stop them at certain points, there's more ships out there coming.
It really is interesting to look at the conquistadors and the New World and then us versus aliens.
And we're the New World, it did not end well for us.
But we're in the Yucatan, we're in the mid-1500s.
At this point the conquistadors are cutting a swath across the region.
In 1549 there was a Spanish inquisitor named Diego de Landa.
He's a friar, he comes out to the Yucatan and he goes, "Guys, you know what, I got
something awesome I want to tell you.
I'm gonna tell you a story about Jesus Christ."
And people are like, "Ahh, we got our own gods, we're cool."
And then he's like, "No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,