What would you do if someone magically appeared in front of you and gave you earth shattering news?
And then we meet a man who believes it's his life mission
To conquer the planet
From an early age he set out with one goal
To be a one-man Illuminati today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a ton of stuff to cover
So we're gonna slide right into this first off. Let's give a shout out to our newest patreon supporter Devon
Devon thank you so much for supporting the show. He's doing a little mock rain in the corner
He's doing that dance since the year 1997 apparently but Devon's having a good old time doing that dance
Devon you're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you can't support the patreon
I totally understand just spread the word about the show that also really really helps out a lot
But Devon when you're done doing the mock rain and he's still doing it
He still has a couple more verses to go, but he's finally done
I'm gonna toss you the keys to the Jason Jalabi drive us out to Brazil
Driving down the long lonely highway that stretches all the way from America to Brazil is there one?
Specifically we're going to Marisol. That's in Sao Paulo
Brazil
Also hit that little time travel button because we're going back to the year 1983. It's March 30th
1983 and it's late at night and as we're driving down the road we come across the man
He's not named in this so let's call him Gary Gary is a night watchman at his job and he's just doing his thing
He's watching stuff. He's perfect for it. He has eyeballs. He's born to do this job
He's watching everything and then right in front of him a
Humanoid appears
This creature with for lack of a better word. It's not necessarily an alien or a cryptid
But this humanoid appears right in front of him has dark skin and red crinkly hair
like that's kind of an odd combination begin with but
Also the fact that he magically appeared in front of you
And this stranger is standing right in front of Gary and says
We have a kid
Her name is Azalea
you
Figure disappears
into a puff of smoke
You don't see that often. You don't see that very often outside of a looney Tune cartoon person appears
Disappears in a puff of smoke says we have a child together named Azalea. That's it. That's the whole story
Now what's funny is that that story is
More perplexing than so much other stuff we talk about on this show because if it had been a great alien if it had been a
Ghost I've mentioned this before on the podcast. You have mythology. You can plug that into context
You're like, oh here's a ghost I can do research and maybe the place used to be haunted or it's still haunted
There's a ghost here
But maybe someone tragically died here if it was an alien that would appear you go
Oh human hybrid experiments like I must have been abducted at some point
Just a dude showing up
Saying hey, we have a kid together disappearing. That's way more perplexing
There's no way to put that into the catalog of paranormal events
The less context the more bizarre like where do you go from there? How would you ever research that?
How would you deal with that?
Like if an alien showed up and was like, oh, I abducted you like a long time ago. We had a baby together
I'd want to see the baby
Maybe hold it how weird it looked I'm like gross. Yeah, that's a gross little baby. They're like, but it's yours
Don't you have an attachment to it? I'm like no super super gross, baby
You could probably like explore it more but just some dude with crinkly red hair showing up
You like what and the puff of smoke? I don't know why keep getting like fixated on the fact that there's just like someone saying
We have a kid he had disappeared in a puff of smoke. That's super weird in and of itself
No wonder why if a ghost can have a kid with a person we've covered stuff like that before with crazy women saying that ghosts have been
Pregnated them, but they were nuts
Outside of people being nuts. Could you have a ghost baby?
could you have a if you can bang an alien and have a
Alien baby and apparently you can bang this dude
You can bang this dude if you want a kid named Azalea. Could you bang a ghost?
Did you have a not talking about suck you by either like an actual ghost like some woman who died in the 1800s who looks kind of
You know kind of hot and that old pioneer clothing and then like can you banger?
That is the immortal question that is truly what every paranormal investigator really wants to know
I don't care about orbs
EVP meters nothing like that and I bang it can I have sex with a ghost and
preferably like if it's preferably a living baby
Which would be hilarious to watch a ghost walk around she's like I'm getting pregnant
He's like a full-on little baby person that's totally solid inside of a ghost keeps falling out
She's like, uh, this is gonna be a long nine months. He has to hold it in or
Barring a real-life baby from a ghost and maybe the baby has like ghostly eyes
Like the eyes are like a ghost blue
Barring a human baby born out of a ghost
Casper
I want to if I'm gonna bang a ghost lady if she gives birth to Casper
That'd be dope because Casper was pretty cool like I mean for what he was he was a bad cartoon
But out of all that era of just like really cheesy cartoons you could kick it with Casper
That is my that is my side to tracking from that
Otherwise bizarre story. What would you do if someone just appeared in front of you and said they had a kid?
Obviously in real life, you'd be like no we don't but if they magically could appear and disappear in a puff of smoke
You'd kind of wonder if maybe at some point you had banged dude and you had a daughter and then what again?
Super perplexing the less information the scarier really maybe someday he'll meet Azalea
Devon let's put you in that carboner copter. We are going to fly on out to Florida
Now Devon I chose Devon to be the pilot on this episode
Because he has the military chops that are going to be needed to keep us safe during this episode
So everyone gear up put on your BDUs get your guns cocked
Make sure no teachers are putting bullets in backwards. That's yesterday's episode if you didn't hear that one all of our bullets are in the
Right way we are flying out to Florida Devon's given us the a okay because he is bringing us now over the business a
Frank Amodio
It's a very unassuming business just sitting there
You wouldn't even think anything of it as you're flying 15,000 feet over it
You wouldn't think anything of it if you were walking into the front door, but this business is owned by a man who will someday
Conquer the planet before we get started here. I got to give a shout out to two people first off the person who recommended this story to me
Der Grob man on YouTube
He recommended it to me about midnight the other night and I was up till about two to thirty reading this article
Very very fascinating story. Thank you so much for sending it over and I want to give a shout out to the author of the article
Matthew B Cox he wrote an article called its insanity the bizarre story of a bipolar
Megalomaniacs insane plan for total world domination. That's not clickbait
That's what we're gonna be talking about and Matthew did an amazing job and did a ton of interviews with this guy
Wanted to give a tip of that to him most of the information I got is from his article
I had other sources as well, but as far as all of the interviews and things like that Matthew did an amazing job
Frank Amodio knew from childhood
That he was destined to rule mankind
Divinely destined. It's not just like he woke up one day and goes hey, I want to do that
He's pointing at a globe someday. I'm gonna own that as a toddler
These are stories that he told at least as a toddler. He walked away from his daycare
I don't need you daycare you suck little toddler dudes walking out as little jammy jams. He walks into traffic
You're like Jason this guy's supposed to rule the planet. He doesn't even know what traffic is
Well, he is a toddler you would think he would die
Because generally when toddlers walk into traffic, it's not good. It's not a happy ending
Eventually a good Samaritan found him and ran over him a couple times like oh
But don't he just ran over the footsie part of his pajamas didn't hit him take some drops him off at his parents house at age
6 he was walking along the train tracks walking tight rope style on the train track and he's walking and then all of a sudden
He hears a voice in his head saying get off the tracks
So he got off the tracks and a train drove by almost killed him
If you hadn't heard that voice in his head
Or if you hadn't heard the sound of an 800 ton mechanical beast from behind him, I don't know if he was listening to Walkman
I don't think the voice in your head is really what you need to listen to you need to listen to that
Three years later so when he was nine he said that his aunt was like hey
Frank you want to come hang out I forgot your name and looked over at my notes. Hey my favorite nephew
Frank
Why don't you come over my place and let's just like hang out do a bunch of stuff, you know like walk on train tracks
We know you like that
I got a lot of traffic by my house and Frank's like now I'm good because he actually hears a voice in his head saying don't go to your
aunt's house tonight and
Then the next morning his aunt was murdered and her body was found in a dumpster
She'd been murdered in a fiance's best friend killed her
So basically he was having these near misses and the fact that he was surviving these things
meant that God was willing him towards a greater destiny and
Also, he should probably get his hearing checked because he didn't hear a train coming and as he gets older
He has a pretty varied life
He was like going college double major doing all this stuff at one point the CIA was trying to recruit him
But then his dad felt ill so a lot of this story makes you think that this guy is making this stuff up because we cover
Blowhards all the time on this show, but early in life. He's telling me stories
I got a skim over a bunch of the stuff because it's just like he was a lawyer and he was a guy
It's very very fascinating story and you can read the article for more in-depth stuff
But I want to kind of get to the meat of the conspiracy realm of it in college
He comes up with a plan called capital Genesis
Which is described basically as benevolent
capitalist
fascism the world would be run by
Corporations and he would run the corporations he basically wanted to push out
Governments and politicians and create a corporate structure that would rule the planet. He said quote by 2012
I expect I'll have offices within one hour of every human alive
Everywhere and the thing was is he was a good businessman
He knew what he was doing, but he was also this is where we start to get an allegedly type of stuff
But he was also really good at
Hiding numbers from his time as an accountant. So he set up this is how his businesses worked he would
Find businesses that were having financial trouble because he was a bankruptcy attorney by trade before he started this thing
He would find companies that own a bunch of money to the IRS and then go to the IRS and say hey
We'll set up a payment plan. We'll pay make these payments every month or every year however the plan was set up or
I can gut it right now
I can declare bankruptcy right now, and you'll never get the money and IRS is like yeah, yeah, yeah
I mean we'd rather have some money later than no money now
So they're working and while he's doing all this stuff
He realizes that he can skim
IRS money from the payroll tax of all these different corporations
So he'd buy a company they'd pay payroll tax
But he would take tax dollars from the payroll tax because the IRS is thinking they're gonna get paid in the future anyways
It was this really weird financial scheme he had going on
So not only was he getting money from the business as it was continuing to turn a profit because he's revitalizing it
He was also getting extra money from all of these companies skimming a little bit out of their payroll
Taxes because the thing is a dictator needs money
So he wasn't just investing in businesses to help people out or to make short-term goals
He was going to use this money to fund his plan of world domination
This all kinds of starts to pick up around 2005. So first he's buying little firms here and there
There's a little shop in Florida that needs some help. Here's some place in Saskatchewan that needs bigger investment
He's building up this portfolio of money-making businesses. Then he starts to invest in tactical operations
He was basically investing in security companies that were then being
Contracted out by the US government to go do things in other countries that the US government didn't want to be tied to
Snatching grab operations. You send some people over there. He sends six dudes twelve dudes
Whatever it is, they'll grab a drug lord off the street grab a witness that the government wants
Snatch up a terrorist take him back. So he wasn't just running a bunch of kinkos on the side
He was actually starting to build a security
Operation he buys a couple fighter jets. So right there right there. You should start getting alarm bells
Sure, people do have private security concerns, but he starts buying fighter jets
He starts to invest in a factory in Russia. He's going global. He invests in a factory in Russia
He knows that he needs to be all over the planet if he wants to take over the planet
He's going he's very successful
He gets this reputation of taking businesses that otherwise would fail and revitalizing them
Sure, he's skimming a little off of the back end, but nobody really knows that and even the people who work with him
Some people kind of knew what he was doing
Everybody knew that he had bigger ambitions and I should touch on this as well. I touched on it in the headline
He is bipolar. He's manic depressive
So the people at his job would see him like in this like raw raw super energetic
This is the way the company's going. Let's all get together and you'd really get everyone all psyched up
But then he would fall into a deep depression early in his career. It seemed to be worse
He would just shut down for weeks at a time, but now he's on a roll
He's just constantly pushing forward and people who work for the companies. They're all making a ton of money
They know he keeps talking about like taking over the world
They're like, dude, it's kind of weird. You keep wearing that co-work commander outfit to work
But we're all making money. What could go wrong?
The democratic republic of konga was having this big election and because of his reputation of kind of
being able to save companies being really good with numbers
A one of the political parties reached out to him and said hey listen, there's like 32 people running for president of the
democratic republic of konga. We would like you to come out
And talk to us and see give us some ideas on how we can if we win how we can revitalize the country
And then we'll use that as our political platform and it's funny
Let me take a break here real quick. This story should show more than anything the power of the law of attraction
There's tons of successful businessmen all over the world
That would never be contacted by the democratic republic of konga
But because he was so driven on this idea of having this political power
It's it's 100 law of attraction. I'll throw I know that sounds mystical to some of you guys
But he's so focused on that. He's putting out into the universe. This is the type of connections he wants and he gets them
Democratic republic of konga one of the political parties reaches out to him. He goes. Yeah, sure
He goes over there and he sets up this plan with him and he goes. Okay. Here's what here's what you guys should do
Take all the mineral wealth in the democratic republic of konga because there's a ton of it
It's worth like billions if not a trillion dollars worth of minerals over there
We're going to sell the mineral rights to a middle eastern investors. They'll invest in the country. They'll build up the infrastructure
It'll be great. It'll be great for everybody. Everyone gets money. Everything gets stabilized over here
But because he's talking about bringing in foreign investments because he's a foreigner himself
He has a security team on the ground to work with this political party
They get arrested because there are a bunch of foreigners
They're talking about bringing in outside interests and people are super suspicious of them and they're all thrown in jail
at this point franc's really upset because this is almost like a
Black eye on this idea that he's going to rule the world someday like his people are actually being detained
He ends up calling the state department the united states state department
He's like you guys got to get my people out of there
They were being used as a propaganda tool every show after they were being marched out put guns to their head
And then ha ha we're not going to kill you today and take them back into the jail
So that's a war crime. You can't actually do mock executions. You oddly enough can do real executions
but the state department is trying to get this all settled and frank tells the state department i have
100 men ready to go. I have hellfire missiles
If they try to do anything to my contractors i'm going to level the city
And his contractors are eventually let go they leave the country
So after that this is his first big public step into
International politics. It's actually a news story and people are going how did this guy in florida
assemble a bunch of shock troopers and hellfire missiles and everything like that
How did this go on but again? It's not raising red flags nato says, you know what we kind of we kind of like your style
How would you with all your business acumen and your security connections like to actually host a nato meeting that we're going to have in latvia
Now of course he's like oh
Why you had me at latvia? I was totally down. They're like that was the last word in the sentence. He goes it doesn't matter
I'm totally down with that. He also meets with president bush president george busch jr at the time
He meets with them
They have a meeting about this whole thing that happened in the democratic republic of congo
Apparently also at that meeting george busch goes walks up to franken goes. Hey, I heard I read the after action report about congo
And I heard what you said about leveling the city. You're my kind of guy. He's all elbowing him in the ribs
We both love blowing up cities, don't we so frank is on his way man
President thinks he's pretty dope dude. He's getting invited to nato. He has this small security force
Everything's going great
But the people he was backing in the democratic republic of congo election
They lost the guy the president who had his people arrested won
But frank never passing up an opportunity to take over the planet frank tells the president of congo
Yeah, you won and I backed this other guy
But let me tell you my plan and he lays out that idea about selling the rights to the middle east
And they're like that actually is a good idea. We need a lot of money invested and the president goes
You know what I really have a problem with is there is a ethnic group in the area called the buji mai
He goes they're pretty cool dudes, but no one really likes them
They're kind of like this impoverished part of our country. They're basically the equivalent of an american hillbilly
He goes no one likes them. They're kind of out there all by themselves
I would really like to see them lift it up as well
So we can have a more unified country because there's like millions of them
And so frank's sitting there and he goes hey, tell you what I got a plan
I will guarantee each of them military training
I have the people who can do it. I have the resources to do it
I will train all the men of the buji mai region
There's two million of there's two million of them
So basically what you are doing is for free because i'm going to train them
You're going to have a two million man army to help stabilize your country and then later you can help stabilize other parts of africa as well
presidents like that sounds amazing and frank
Frank knows what he's doing. He's building a two million man army for him
This is the start of capital genesis. This story is 100 true and it happened just a few years ago
And it would have kept going on. He would have had this little building in florida and done all of these things made all these maneuvers
Start an army
Had it not been for one conversation
In latvia at the nato summit that he helped organize
Someone goes hey, so what happened? What exactly happened in the congo?
Like I read on the newspaper like your people got kidnapped
And they were there for a couple days and apparently you made some moves and the state department made some moves and they all got let go
What actually happened and he begins talking to all of these nato representatives about capital genesis about his plan
To take over the world now people will say that the pesh modal writes songs about it. It happens
But this guy has hellfire missiles
This guy has a small amount of troops that he already threatened to level the city
But while he's at this meeting he says he's going through the plan quote once i've created a military
a million
UGMI soldiers i'll use them to stabilize central africa
Then someone asked what's your objective?
frank says well obviously once i've built up my peacekeeping force i plan on taking all of africa
And then he goes on to say he's going to continue to build his military
He goes a five million man military capable of policing the planet
We won't need nato anymore
Probably not the best thing to say to nato meeting probably not the best thing to say at all
He laid out his plan. He thought the plan was so genius anyone who heard it would have to go along with it capital genesis
A worldwide corporation ran by him and he had already been taking his first steps
Now he ends up leaving the nato summit later
It's not like he's like gotta go once he realized that he revealed his plans the nato summit goes as normal
But by the time he's headed back home to florida on his private jet
There are already phone calls
To the united states government because people are starting to put two and two together one
He has what seems like unlimited wealth two. He already has a private security. He already has quite a few private security forces
But one was ready to go with hellfire missiles three. He owns fighter jets
These are all red flags that should have popped up earlier
But the biggest one for that company. I said that he invested in in russia. He was a factory
That up until a few years before he invested in it built intercontinental ballistic missiles
By the time his plane landed in florida his companies are already being hit with subpoenas
The government is sending out people
Figure out something that this guy's doing illegal because something is wrong and they tried
Over and over and over again and they could find nothing
Even though he was doing this thing where he was kind of digging into the payroll taxes that money was going to be paid back
Eventually
He was saying we owe you 10 million dollars in taxes. I'll declare bankruptcy or you can just pay you later irs
They go. Yeah, they owed for past taxes. He was taking out current taxes
It was this weird scheme. It sounds pretty illegal. It probably was illegal
But the government couldn't prove that he was doing anything illegal. He hadn't done anything illegal as far as they could tell
July 2008 they still can't find anything that's going on with this guy
But they do get his lawyer
They're somehow able this is really interesting this article. I read they lean on his lawyer
I don't know what they found on this lawyer
I don't know if the lawyer is a good guy and developed a conscience and you know
Didn't want to take over the planet or if they found something on him
I'm not for sure but the but the government leaned really really hard on his lawyer
His lawyer goes listen. You got to take a plea deal for this
Take a plea deal for pulling money doing this tax scheme
Do a couple years in prison not a big deal
Frank won't do it
The lawyer goes okay. Well, you know that whole manic depressive bipolar thing you have going on
I'm going to have you ruled incompetent by a judge
And then the decision isn't yours
And you would think that it would be very very hard to do no
No, not in this dude's case because the government already wanted to clamp down on him
The lawyer has frank this guy who owns all these companies
Declared incompetent and sent to the mclean psychiatric hospital at that point. He is diagnosed with bipolar disorder
Which he does have earlier in life. They didn't really know what that was back in the 60s 70s 80s
There wasn't really a thing. You were just depressed and that even wasn't a medical condition
He was medicated very heavily a september 22nd 2008. So just a couple months later
His lawyer has frank in court and says hey my client is now ready to plead guilty. He's competent
We know he was in that psychiatric hospital for a while
He's now ready to plead guilty to these charges your honor and the judge looks over at frank and he's literally
Druling as he's sitting there. He's so pumped full of anti psychotic medicine. He's drooling in court
The judge is like, okay, I'll take it. I'll take it. Yeah, he seems competent in totally
He owns 70 companies and it taken a total of 64 million dollars
In the end through all sorts of other shenanigans that were going on in the end. He did get
Sentenced because he plead guilty. He was competent even though he's all
Quite guilty. He got 22 years in prison. He's still alive. He's still in prison
For quite a few years. He was drugged out of his mind
Not by choice the prison authorities were keeping him on drugs and then when he finally gets off the drugs
It had been a couple years. He's a lawyer by trade
He starts to realize stuff. He goes first off
I was a ward of the state when I was declared incompetent
I was a ward of the state and by not having my own
It doesn't matter whether or not i'm competent or someone else says i'm competent if i'm still a ward of the state
I can't take a plea deal to when I was declared incompetent. There was someone else who was appointed as my
Guardian it wasn't a lawyer. They should have been present as well
When I took the plea deal
Even the judge said had I known he was a ward of the state
I can't take a plea deal if someone's a ward of the state. You should have realized the guy was drooling
That should have been your first thing
But he goes maybe there was just a really juicy steak and I couldn't see so the judge was like maybe that's why he was drooling
The government actually did take a look at all of his findings frank puts this thing together and goes to the government
Look at all these problems with the trial and my lawyer didn't have my best interest in mine
A lawyer has to have your best interest in mine. My lawyer was actively working to get me thrown in jail
So this stinks. I need to be let out and the government looks at it and they go you're right
You're right. However, you only have one year after you are sentenced
To argue that your lawyer didn't have your best interest in mine. It's like five years later
He's like, yeah, but I was struck down the government was pumping me full of drugs and they're like, no, that's the deadline, dude
so
Frank still sits in prison now actually runs a law firm in prison
He's constantly getting inmate sentences reduced some of them released
He has other inmates working as paralegals
Oddly enough, he stole about 60 million from the government through that IRS scheme
He saved the government 83 million dollars
In housing criminals by getting them let off to wrap this up. Let's go back to matthew cox's article here
I'm gonna read you this passage from it and it really should give you an idea of where
Frank's mind is at right now
Matthew asks quote, how long did you think it was going to take for you to conquer the world and become emperor?
Frank says you keep speaking in past tense
I'm going to do this
I will be emperor
When Matthew says, you know, you're kind of getting getting older Frank completely dismisses that there's still time
Moses started when he was 80 when I walk out of those gates
My legions and I will march on washington burn the miserable constitution and the president will kneel at my feet
My flag will fly above every city in this country
and then
the world
It's interesting to look at a megalomaniac who failed
Which to be fair, I guess a lot of them do
But to have someone who actually dedicates their life to trying to take over the planet every edgy teenager imagines it, but he actually
Took steps to do it actually may have
Succeeded given a long enough time the idea of him marching out of jail with his legions and the president kneeling before him
That's obviously a delusion of grandeur now
But if his plan had been able to continue and he had amassed a five million man army in africa
I don't know if the president would be kissing his feet, but he'd definitely be in a position of
immense power
And this is a type of person I talk about when I always talk about the Illuminati when I say I don't think there's one group
Controlling the planet
I think there's dozens if not hundreds of smaller groups each maneuvering their way
Each one trying to conquer the planet
But their alliances and their infighting and all this stuff going on and that represents the chaos of the world
This is what i'm talking about this man became a key player
He was just some college student who was a lawyer for a while
He kind of bumbled his way through life
And ended up coming very close
To being a dominant player in world politics. This is the Illuminati
It's people like this and whether a couple of them team up to form a group
Or you just have a lot of lone wolves out there. These are the people that can really affect
world politics
It doesn't take a group to control a television station. It just takes a guy like this to own a television station
And the creepiest thing is that this is chaos
This is full chaos. It's almost more comforting to think that one group
Rules the entire planet because that way you can focus all your energy on one group and everything that goes wrong
You can ascribe it to that one group
But to know that there are people like this in our lifetime
Who are able to maneuver this and the only thing that tripped him up was him opening his mouth in front of the wrong people
That's terrifying because that's pure chaos had he gotten an icbm
And he was in a manic episode
And he's threatening to destroy cities
Raw chaos
Knowing someone is in control even if they are evil can be more comforting than
thinking that random people can just pop up
By a missile factory and start taking over the world
That's why more people want to believe that 9/11 was an inside job versus
Some dude 3 000 miles away gets 19 people to change the scope of american history
Because chaos is terrifying
And control is comforting
That's why people like frank scared the government into doing whatever it would take to get him behind bars
Because people like frank are true loose cannons
And he's not alone
There's probably thousands of other people out there just like him
Who not only dream about taking over the world. We all do that
Reshaping the world in our image, but knowing how to do it
The government was able to stop frank will they be able to stop the next one?
And the next one and the next one?
Or will there be a day when you wake up a new flag is flying over your city?
You see the president on bended knees
Kissing the foot of a man you never even knew existed
But is now the king of the planet
We may think that sounds far-fetched, but to frank
It's just a matter of time
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]