Was Ariana Grande haunted by a demon? Did she actually have concrete proof of the existence of ghosts?
And then we take a look at one of the supposed seven gateways of hell.
Does the devil really come out twice a year at Stoll Cemetery? Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. I just woke up.
I know it could probably argued that it's not really considered a nap if you go to bed at 7pm.
But man, I was so tired when I got off work today. I was at dinner and then I just kind of started...
You ever see like a baby? Like just not off and like fall over? That was pretty much me.
And I thought, I still gotta record my podcast. I mean, I know what I'm gonna talk about, but I still need to sit down.
The whole process takes about two hours, about an hour and a half plus uploading it to YouTube.
And I was like, I can't. I can't do it. So, and I was like, oh, just wait till tomorrow. I'll do it tomorrow.
And then I guess, you know, people get upset when you say something's gonna come out and it doesn't.
Rightfully so. I know there are gonna be times where I can't actually get an episode out on a certain day just out of sickness or technological issues.
But I was like, okay, I'm gonna go to bed. I'm gonna go to bed at 7pm. I'm gonna take a nap.
And then I'm gonna wake up. When I wake up, I set my alarm clock for midnight and I was like, okay.
But I ended up only sleeping for probably about two hours. It's 9 o'clock now.
And I feel more awake. I knew that I could probably have recorded the podcast as sleepy as I was, but I wouldn't have been able to edit it.
And honestly, it probably wouldn't have sounded that great if I did it while I was that sleepy.
One thing I have noticed, and you may, if you listen back to the intro I just did, I don't know if it's because I'm tired or what,
but I dropped words and left off the end of words, almost every sentence, in that past intro.
Like now I'm having to concentrate to make sure that I get those words in there, because I really did just wake up maybe like 10, 20 minutes ago.
I am quite sleepy. So that's a little puzzle for you. You can go back and go, man, he really did drop a lot of words in those sentences,
but he just kept on going. So let's go ahead and get started with the episode here.
So the first thing I wanted to talk about was Ariana Grande. Now, Ariana Grande, pop superstar.
I don't really think she needs more introduction than that. She's 25 years old. She looks like she's 16.
I actually used to watch that show she was on, Victorious. It's funny, because she was probably the most entertaining/most annoying character on that show.
But yeah, out of all of them, she wasn't the one I thought would be, world famous, but it's cool that she is. I enjoy her music.
And you know, her music's pretty good. I do have probably four, the first four or five albums.
I'm not for sure. I haven't bought anything recently, but yeah, it's enjoyable. I enjoy a good rap music and I enjoy top 40 pop music.
It's a weird combination, but so Ariana Grande, but it's not like Kanye West where I will be like, oh, I really like Kanye West,
even though he's like a total weirdo. I make excuses for him because I like him so much.
Ariana Grande is a pop star who I buy albums from. There are some artists that I will defend to the death.
So when Kanye West is floating around on a glass stage or dressing up as like a giant block person or doing that incredibly insane Saturday Night Live performance,
I'll be like, no, you guys just don't understand the genius of Kanye West.
Ariana Grande is like, oh, she is a good pop star. She's good at what she does.
I'm always afraid she's going to blow her vocal cords out, though.
I remember, anyways, it's enough talking, it's enough of me reminiscing about Ariana Grande. Let's get onto the story.
So Ariana Grande, she said that she had a encounter with ghosts/demons, really demons.
Now, everyone kind of has a story about ghosts and demons. Well, most people do, but very rarely are they so big in the public eye
that they're interviewed by Complex Magazine and it's just like a weird aside in this article.
The interviewer is like, oh, you have nice hair. Oh, you know, what's good for your next project.
And then the conversation starts to steer towards the dark, the macabre.
And so what happened was this is the story that Ariana Grande told to Complex Magazine in 2013.
So she went to Kansas City. She was on tour, I'm assuming, because I don't think that's an area that Ariana Grande would normally hang out in.
But anyways, first she said she's really into ghost stuff, paranormal stuff, which I will say, guys, the boob hill, I'm telling you,
if you express an interest in the paranormal, girls will flock to you, even Ariana Grande will flock to you.
So Ariana Grande is in Kansas City. And first she says they go visit a haunted castle.
Now I looked that up and there's no castles in Kansas, but there is something called the Sours Castle, which is a haunted building.
And I think that's what she was referring to. And I looked at the hauntings there and it was just like a ball of light or like the shadow of a dude walks.
I was like, I'm not going to spend time talking about it. But anyways, so she went there. She probably thought the same thing.
And then her and her friends were like, let's go to Stoll Cemetery. So Stoll Cemetery is considered one of the seven gateways to hell.
It's one of the seven places on earth that the devil can enter into our reality. And we'll get into more in that in a second.
But let me finish the Ariana Grande portion of this story. So Ariana Grande is talking to Complex Magazine and she says that the Pope won't fly over Stoll Cemetery.
So in the, I think it was the 70s or the 80s when Pope John Paul was flying, not like Superman, but his jets.
Not his jet will not fly over the cemetery. He had the pilot divert his plane so it wouldn't fly over Stoll Cemetery because it's unholy land.
We'll get more into that as well. But anyways, so the Pope's plane won't fly over it.
Her and her friends went there at night and the car, the smell of the car was full of sulfur.
And Ariana Grande started to feel sick. There's just this negative energy filled the car up. And then there was a fly in the car.
Now a fly is the sign of a demon. We'll get into that. We'll address all of these things.
But let me tell you the rest of this story. There's a fly in the car. Now she rolls down the window and she yells out to Stoll Cemetery.
We apologize. We didn't mean to disrupt your peace. And she takes a picture, which I take it as a human.
So let's say like some kids are like bugging you and you're sitting there and then someone goes, we're sorry.
We didn't mean to disrupt your peace. And you're thinking, oh, those are good kids.
And then they pull out a camera and take a picture of you and drive off.
And this picture apparently showed three distinct faces, which Ariana Grande described as textbook demons.
So you imagine like horns, maybe a long face, big grin, things like that.
Now of course the interviewer for Complex Magazine asks what any normal person would ask right away.
Where's the picture? And not in an accusatory tone.
She's like, wow, that's an amazing story. I want to see that picture. She deleted it because it was possessed, basically.
It was a dark picture. She said she tried to send the picture to her manager.
And when she put it as an attachment in the email or sent it through SMS or however she did, it said this file is too large.
It's 666 megabytes. Oh, dude.
And then she said she started to see this shadowy figure. So this is actually from the interview.
This is what Ariana Grande said. "I was going to sleep about two weeks ago."
Now 2013, not now. "I had just gone off the phone and as soon as I closed my eyes I heard this really loud rumble right by my head."
When I opened my eyes it stopped immediately.
But when I closed my eyes, it started again with whispers.
Every time I closed my eyes I started seeing these really disturbing images with like red shapes.
Then I opened my eyes and got back on the phone and I was like, I'm really scared and I don't want to go to bed tonight.
And then I scooched over to the left side of my bed because that's where the best service is in the room.
And there was this massive black matter. I don't know what it was.
It was like a cloud of something black right next to me. I started crying. I was on the phone like, what do I do? What do I do?
And they said, not the ghost. Not the ghost. The person on the phone said, tell it to F off.
I thought, I'm not going to do that. It's going to upset it.
So I'm just going to chill and not feed into it and because all it wants is my fear, it feeds on fear.
I watched it move to the front of my bed and then I fell asleep on the phone.
I woke up and it was gone. The next night my friend Tyler was staying with me.
She said she was trying to sleep and her body felt paralyzed.
And she described the exact same thing I saw.
And then the interviewer goes, alrighty then and moves on to the next topic, which I guess the interviewer really was there to do an article for Complex Magazine about the lives and times of his glamorous singer.
But she seemed like she was just like, very dismissive of her.
And that's the thing when people tell paranormal stories, things like that.
I try to be when it's face to face. I know when I was reading that it was kind of smart of me, but I'm going to get into elements of that, elements of her whole story.
Generally when people tell me a story face to face, no matter how incredulous it is, I'll be like, oh yeah, that's really interesting.
And then, of course, there's a point where you have to break it off.
But a lot of times when people have these experiences, unless they're lying right to your face, which happens time to time, to them it's almost like a religious experience.
And they're also really reluctant to tell people.
So when you tell a story to someone and you go, alrighty then, then they're really going to stop sharing those stories with anyone.
And these are just personal stories that people go through.
So let's look at this quickly, because there's a couple of elements that I want to touch on here.
And I'll start off by doing this.
So in, because I'll forget otherwise, I had a plan and then I realized something while I was reading her quote.
So let me touch on what this is.
There may be a biological answer to this, but the thing where she says that she closed her eyes
and she would hear something and then she opened them and it went away.
She closed her eyes and she would hear a noise.
She opened it and it went away.
I didn't repeat myself. That actually happened a few times.
So I've experienced that.
And I don't know if I never thought, when I read this story, when I was prepping the story, that didn't stick out to me.
It wasn't until I was kind of taking my time reading it.
That happened to me.
It happened to me one time where I was trying to sleep and there was something.
I'll tell the story. This episode is probably just going to end up running long, but I was sleeping at my grandma's house in my room bordering the backyard,
which is where I said there's been some, I had paranormal experiences with shadow people and things like that.
I remember one night because I didn't really have a bed.
I had like a futon mattress on the floor.
And one night I was sure, and so it was a futon mattress on the floor and then cement underneath.
It was surprisingly comfy. I can kind of sleep anywhere.
And I had my little cat, Remy. He was hanging out in there. He was asleep.
But as I'm laying on my little futon on the cement.
And I remember one night I went to go to sleep and I shut the light off and I closed my eyes.
And I felt all over my back, on my neck and my head, I felt fingertips pushing through the mattress.
It felt like probably 20, 30 hands.
All just kind of trying to lift me with fingertips.
I felt them all over from my back to my neck.
Immediately opened my eyes, turned on the light.
I was like, that's obviously impossible. Like nothing could do that.
But it totally creeped me out and I'm sitting there, the lights on.
I closed my eyes and I start to feel it again.
All these, and it was only when I closed my eyes when I felt all of these fingers,
it felt like someone, felt like a bunch of people under me were kind of poking me with their whole hand.
It was very, very disconcerting.
And so I opened my eyes again and that happened a few times.
And then eventually I was like, this has to be, this is either really happening and this is all they're going to do,
or it's all in my head.
And so just like Ariana Grande, I just made the decision to fall asleep.
So that is an interesting part of her story because I've experienced it myself.
And I've said that before, there's a lot of stuff that I read that I'll kind of dismiss out of hand
because I haven't experienced it. That's just part of kind of being a skeptic and not really knowing where,
where the division between someone telling the entertaining story and somebody actually telling the truth.
But I've experienced that where you only, it only happens when you close your eyes,
but there could actually be some sort of psychological component to that.
That being said, let's go back and talk about the other issues with her story.
So the idea of a photo being 666 megabytes, that's possible,
but the thing is, that part didn't necessarily ring true because generally you can send files,
correct me if I'm wrong, in 2013 even, a file that's 666 megabytes isn't incredibly large.
Now it could have been that the file was 666 gigabytes and that wouldn't be impossible to send.
It could be that she, I'll say this, I don't think she made the story up.
I think there may be parts of it that aren't, there absolutely are parts of it that aren't factually correct,
but I don't think she's making it up and you'll see what I mean.
So let's take it apart though. She has the file, 666 megabytes, the number 666 is the mark of the beast.
There's even debate about that, whether or not that's the actual mark of the beast,
but it's generally assumed with satanic imagery that file should still be allowed to be sent, dead.
And it's possible that it was 666 gigabytes as she misread it.
It's possible that that part of the story is not entirely true, but again, I think the other elements of her story are true,
so I don't think she's making that up.
Is there a chance that she took a photo and it had proof of demonic activity on it and it was 666 megabytes/gigabytes?
It's possible, I think that's probably the weakest part of her story, honestly.
I think that's the part of her story that I'm questioning a little bit,
but for whatever reason she had a photo and she deleted it.
Now, the fly in the car, that's a sign of the devil, Bales' old bub was the Lord of Flies.
That could be a coincidence that she's driving her car and there's a single fly in her car,
and to jump to the conclusion, I can understand if she just saw the fly in her car and jumped to that conclusion, it may be ridiculous,
but when she's connecting it with the smell of sulfur and the ghosts, the negative activity where she was at,
I mean, she would actually make a pretty decent paranormal investigator because she didn't say there was just a fly in the car,
and that means demons. There was other elements that added to it, but I'm assuming there actually was a fly in the car.
I'm assuming, again, I don't think she's lying, but the biggest issue with this story,
it's wrapped in a bunch of mythology that can easily be dismissed, that Ariana Grande wasn't being trying to be a liar about it,
it's actually just not factually true, and that's the story, the legend of Stoll Cemetery.
So let's talk about that briefly, this episode is definitely going to run long.
So Stoll Cemetery is a spooky, well, I shouldn't say spooky, it's a cemetery in the middle of Kansas,
and it doesn't get explored a lot, there's never been a paranormal investigator show shot out in Stoll Cemetery,
despite its legendary reputation as being one of the seven gateways to hell, and there's a few reasons why one, it's out in the middle of nowhere.
But so this town of Stoll was founded in 1857, it's only a few buildings, it's not even really a city, it's an unincorporated town.
So to people who don't live in America, there's basically like, we have cities and we have suburbs,
and then every so often there's little breakaway towns, sometimes they're on the edge of suburbs, sometimes in the middle of nowhere,
but they're not considered an actual city, it's just buildings, a place people live.
You have to incorporate to become a city.
So Stoll was a little town, in 1912 it only had 31 people, the max amount of people that it has had is about 50 people.
There may be a few more people there now, but it's just a very, very small town.
Before Karsit was a two hour trip to the nearest town.
Now Stoll, the city of Stoll had two major tragedies.
One was they were doing a controlled burn on a field and a little boy got lost in the field and he got circled by fire and burnt it up.
The second big tragedy they had in that town was one person went missing and they later found him hanging from a tree.
Now those wouldn't even be on the radar for most cities, townships in America.
But when you only have 30 to 50 people, one death is a big deal.
And the little boy dying in the burning fields, horrible.
And the guy hanging from the tree, those are horrible incidences, but they're not these major tragedies in most cities that have 10,000 people, 20,000 people so on and so forth.
Now the first time Stoll Cemetery is exactly what it sounds like. It's just the cemetery.
Apparently there was a professor at the University of Kansas who would tell the students at the college that Stoll Cemetery was a gateway to hell.
It was one of the seven gateways. He would tell this story to college kids.
It sounds a lot like me, just kind of just riffing on, you know, riffing to people.
And in 1974 the University of Kansas was the newspaper for the University of Kansas.
They ran a story about Stoll Cemetery as one of the gateways to hell.
That's where the legend started. No one, other than this professor, there was really nobody else talking about this.
And the newspaper ran this article and it totally took off.
The article posits, the article says that the gateway opens at midnight on the spring equinox and on Halloween and that is when the devil can pop out of it.
There is a church there, the evangelical Emanuel church that is now possessed by the devil.
The church has been torn down now, but it had no roof at a time and the legend went that even on rainy nights with no roof the inside of the church was bone dry.
It was the power of the devil keeping the rain out.
Seems like an odd power for the devil. Why would he care if the church got wet? Does he not like water?
Don't tell me it's because hell's on fire, but anyway, so he would keep water from getting into the church.
There was legends that there were rich witch trials in Kansas. There never were. There was no record of them, at least.
So this legend just grew and grew and grew. In 1980 people just started ascending upon this little town of 50 people.
They were rowdy teens and college students, they were like, "Yeah, we're going to be here. We're going to see the devil show up on the equinox.
We're going to watch the devil come out on Halloween."
It ended up peaking in 1988. 500 people showed up on Halloween and nothing happened, of course. They trashed the graveyard.
Now cops are stationed there, generally on those two days, but they usually have a guard as well.
In 1999 a news crew showed up to be like, "Hey, we're going to investigate this story."
And they got ran off by the townspeople. They're like, "We don't want you here. You guys are just trash in the place and everything like that.
We got all these looky-loos coming."
And that's the second reason why no ghost investigator show has ever come out here is because townspeople don't want them.
They don't want any publicity. They're not in.
They could easily turn into a tourist town and have gift shops where they sell little gateway toys and little demon figurines.
And people would go there and they'd look around the cemetery for a while and then they'd blow $100 in their gift shop.
But they refuse to do that. The people in town don't want any attention whatsoever.
So no one can investigate it. No ghost shows can show up nothing.
Now, Supernatural, the Stoll Cemetery is a big part of their mythology.
One, the two Winchester boys were actually born in Kansas.
And Kripke, Eric Kripke, the creator of the show, Supernatural, said he did that.
He placed them there because of Stoll Cemetery.
And then the season finale for season five, this great huge battle, takes place in Stoll Cemetery
because they're going to face down the devil and they have to do it at one of the gateways to hell.
And I will say this briefly. Again, episodes are running long, but first five seasons of Supernatural are great.
If you're into the Supernatural, if you're into like action shows, mystery shows, and X-Files type,
check out the first five seasons of Supernatural. They were great.
Now, the seasons after that, they've been hit or miss, but the first five seasons of Supernatural are really, really good television
if you're into this type of stuff. Definitely the first five seasons.
So it was interesting. I was reading an article.
A reporter did go out to Stoll Cemeteries. It was a very, very well-written article.
I'll put it in the show notes, of course, but he said, he goes, "You know, I watched the Supernatural and I read all this stuff about it.
And you think it's this cemetery in the middle of nowhere. He goes, "The town itself is in the middle of nowhere."
Well, the cemetery is like right off the freeway, and there's a bunch of houses facing it.
So he goes, "I pulled up, and on one side of me was just cars flying by.
On the other side of me was a bunch of townspeople sitting on their porch staring at me."
He goes, "It was not what I expected." He goes, "I expected this spooky cemetery."
He goes, "It's just regular cemetery. It's just very noisy. There's people all...
Really, there's witnesses all around June, things like that."
I'm assuming Ariana's grande's car was probably going down that freeway.
Maybe they took a short detour, but it's totally accessible if you can get to the town.
And the story that the Pope's plane refused to fly over Stoll Cemetery completely made up.
The reference to that said it was in a Time magazine article.
The Pope never said that. The pilot never said that. There's no confirmation that it ever happened.
Completely made up story. The Pope has no problem flying the Pope plane over Stoll Cemetery.
But I will say this. It is really weird that the townspeople don't want any attention.
Because again, Roswell, their entire tourist industry, millions of dollars a year
based on holding up this idea that aliens crashed there.
And you can look at all other sorts of Winchester Mystery House.
You can look at all these other touristy trap places in America and really around the world
that are like the most haunted city in the world. The most haunted house in the world.
You know, this is a haunted tree. Come visit the haunted tree and go to our gift shop.
So it's one of two things. Either the people in Stoll really do not want
a bunch of people coming around poking around their graveyard.
Or they're possibly covering something up.
Is it really a gateway to hell? And is it so ingrained in that area that the people who live there,
rather than making a quick buck from people like Ariana Grande and every paranormal ghost show in the world,
rather than bringing them there and making millions of dollars, what if they know what's really there?
And the town is almost infected by some sort of dark spirit, some sort of dark energy
almost controlling the town. Keep them away. Keep them away so they don't know what really goes on here.
The Pope will fly his plane over it. But on the ground is there something darker covering up
what's really going on in the town of Stoll. I can almost just imagine this town that looks normal at night.
Just 50 people. Even that seems bizarre that it's still so small, but it's normal during the day.
It's closed off to outsiders. How do they have 50 people yet enough cops to guard the cemetery?
The more you think about it, the creepier it sounds. It almost seems plausible that you have this town
that is set up for one reason and one reason only. To guard the gateway to hell.
And not to guard it in the sense that Sam and Dean Winchester would go to shut it down,
but to work for some sort of supernatural darkness that's there.
Guardians. It's the ones that keep people away all year around.
So those two nights when the gateway does open, the dark ones can enter our world unseen.
They could make a lot of money. I could be putting sinister implications on a town that would just rather be left alone.
A small town with an old, quiet, slow way of life.
But sometimes the cover-up is what ends up making things more suspicious.
Is there anything at Stoll Cemetery? We may never know, but it's likely that the people in the town of Stoll definitely have the answer.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend, guys.
(upbeat music)