Did a talking mongoose haunt a family in the 1930s?
And today I talk about personal experiences I had at the historically haunted Stanley Hotel today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
Both my best friends forgot my birthday.
One, I could understand both.
So if you detect that my voice is a little monotone than normal or you
hear the sound of my soul being ripped from my body, that's why.
I actually didn't plan on recording an episode today, not just because of that, because I had got called into work tomorrow
and I had a long day today, but
yeah, what are you gonna do?
Let's go ahead and go on to our first story.
So our first story is the story of Jeff the Talking Mongoose.
Now his name is Jeff, but it's spelled G-E-F.
He's a little...
Well, he's a talking mongoose. I think that kind of is obvious, but
it's a little more than that. It was almost a... He looks like a mongoose, but nobody really ever saw him.
He acts like a talking animal would if you think animals can talk, but
he also has qualities of like a poultry geist. It was a curious case back then.
Well, I guess it's a curious case now, but you know... Man, this is going to be a hard episode to record.
Okay, let me get centered here. So anyways,
Jeff the Talking Mongoose. So this story took place back in the 1930s. It was in the Isle of Man, which is somewhere in Europe.
Maybe it's off of England? I don't know.
Let's just see if we can get through on this episode.
So Isle of Man is somewhere on the planet Earth. I believe it's in England.
And so anyways, there's this family living out there.
They're called
the
Irvings.
And it's a mother and a father and a little 12 year old girl.
And they start to hear little voices. No, no, no, no. Let me back up here. So the dad's name
is James. This is going to be a rough one, guys. Just just get through with this.
We can get through this together. So the dad's name is James and they start hearing like these weird noises in their walls
of this house in the 1930s. So it's not the most well put together house.
And he keeps hearing these like noises and for whatever reason he decides like I'm going to start talking to these noises and figure out what they are.
And he realizes that the noises change.
So he begins like growling at the at one point there's like a growling come from the wall.
He growls back and then it seems like the creature responds to him. So he's like, oh, that's interesting.
So he's talking to the wall. He's talking to the wall for a while.
You know, over the course of weeks and stuff like that.
And like he would,
if he growled the creature on the other side of the wall would make a similar growl. So then he's like started making other animal noises.
And eventually he could name an animal and it would like if he goes chicken, it would go back back back back.
And he goes every so often it sounded like it was a gurgling.
Like it was trying to learn English. And and here's your this is where I say and you I'm sure you're saying as well.
How do you how do you make gurgling? How do you equate that with having to learn English? Here's the thing. This story is so
inconsistent.
Because yeah, if you heard first off if you heard anything coming from your walls, you're taking a sledgehammer to it and strangling anything.
On the other side, especially if it's making a bunch of animal noises. Eventually it does start talking though and introduces itself as Jeff.
And I don't know it's spelled a g-e-f. I don't know if that's normal
for Isle of Man or if the the mongoose is like spell it with a g and leave off an f.
But anyways, so James Irving is like, oh, I got this hyper intelligent
mongoose. Even he said he was a mongoose from New Delhi.
And he's like Jeff's like, hey, I'm a mongoose
from New Delhi. And so James begins talking to it.
And it gets to the point. There's a bunch of weird stuff that goes on in the story. So anyways,
the mother doesn't like Jeff and the Jeff.
Or the mother doesn't like Jeff and Jeff doesn't like the mother so they don't interact much. But the young girl, she's 13. Her name is Vori.
That's a bizarre name. So
the the mongoose
talks to Vori, talks to James and talks to Vori and Vori actually like
Jeff will show himself to Vori.
James only just he catches like fleeting glimpses of it.
And he's basically like a total dick. Like he's and that's where he has the qualities of a poltergeist where he'd like throw stuff and be mean
and he'd say like jacked up stuff to these people one time he called James Irving like a big fat potato head or something like that. And yeah, so
at one point he Jeff is like
really really like getting on
Vori's nerves like in a creepy way in like a stalker way and and Vori's like i'm tired of Jeff. I'm tired of Jeff running around
this house, you know, and i'm i'm seeing them and stuff and he's just being a dick to me.
So the parents are like okay, well, let's see if we can figure out another room you can stay in.
And Jeff doesn't like that.
Okay, he didn't call him. Let me back up here.
Because he didn't call him a big fat potato head. What he called him. So James was reading the newspaper very slowly.
And Jeff wanted him to read it quickly for whatever reason. He said read it out. You f-
Fat headed gnome.
So i mean i well maybe fat, fat potato, fat potato head was funny. I don't know. But anyways
Fat headed gnome is what he called James once. Anyways, Vori got sick and tired of him like
dicking around with her. So the parents get together and they're like let's have a meeting
and figure out what room to put you in that we can, you know, so you don't have to interact with Jeff much because you couldn't find him.
And then like as they're having this meeting Jeff says i'll follow her wherever you put her.
Which is creepy. Here's a little thing. So
James at one point they're like
We'll put you
Vori you can sleep in your bedroom and we will barricade you
In you like you can barricade yourself into your room. So when you sleep you don't have to like hear like
Creepy mongoose noises while you're trying to sleep and here's a quote
Soon we saw the top of the door bulging in as though some terrific force were thrusting against it. That's that's some um
50 shades of gray shit right there
Soon we saw the top of the door bulging in as though some terrific force were thrusting against it
But the door held
Then Jeff's queer
Uh, yeah, this is probably good. I'm doing this episode then Jeff's queer
Then and I know the word means weird, but then Jeff's queer high voice said i'm coming in
a few seconds later a heavy pot of
A few seconds later a heavy pot of ointment kept in the room crashed against the bedstead
It should be bedstand, but whatever bedstead that might be a real thing in the isle of man
But so he basically like when they were like stay out of our daughter's room
He's like thrusting against the door and breaks his way in the door bulges and he has a queer high voice. So anyways
He busted now, of course
Vory ends up like kind of getting over her fear of
Jeff and they kind of start living with it, but
What happens is word gets out that there's this little
Little mongoose guy running around this house talking mongoose and so of course paranormal investigators start showing up at the house and
You know the neighboring town knew of it people in the area knew of Jeff the talking mongoose
and
And then these psychic investigators show up
See what's up, and this should be your first clue something's going sideways with this story
Nothing happens. They don't hear them
They don't see them
Nothing happens now
Family would be like hey jeff say something
say something
nothing
Now other psychic investigators would come out and they would hear jeff being like get him out of here
He doesn't believe in spirits. I don't like him that knucklehead
And they'd be like oh my god psychic investors like oh my god. I totally heard that
At one point actually this was interesting so at one point like so there's this theory that poltergeist activity
Is caused not by the spirit like poltergeist activity that between that and it goes is poltergeist is when stuff moves around your house
like doors being open and stuff sliding around
And there's a strong thrusting against your bedroom door that's generally classified as a poltergeist and there is a
Scientist who came up with the theory
That poltergeist activity is actually not
Ghosts it is caused by mental anguish. It's basically more like psychokinesis than anything else like than that
Than like a spooky spirit. It's more like
Your mental your your basically your mental is leaving
Like your mental anguish can't be contained in your body or in your brain. So it has to find another outlet. His name was
Nam dude, that's a dope name. Sounds like the lord of the rings villain
nandor
Fodor maybe not a villain. He could actually be like anyone that could be the most normal guy in
Lord of the Rings where does that take place middle earth?
Nandor Fodor could like be the guy who delivers your mail, but in any other
Universe he'd be the bad guy. So anyways, he came out
And he had a couple interesting theories, but the main one was first he was like, uh, it's kind of kind of poltergeisty kind of not
He ended up thinking that it was not generally poltergeist activity is caused by young kids going through adolescence
And they're go have all this energy and it's like being expelled psychically
His thing was I think it's the father. I think he had like all these great dreams and desires as a kid
and now he's like locked in he got a woman pregnant. He's
Just the husband and has a kid and all this stuff and he's just letting all the psychic energy out and so on and so forth
Now a couple psychic investigators, like I said, didn't hear anything and some of them did some of them brought reporters and witnesses as witnesses nothing
They couldn't hear anything. Now words started to spread
That it was a hoax
That it wasn't true
At one point one of the psychic investigators was walking and he heard the voice
He's like, oh my god, he heard the voice now. He's walking in the the father
James is next to him and vori standing behind him and here's the voice being like he doesn't believe in the spirits
and a psychic investigators like
Uh, that voice came from right behind me where the little girl is who's following us and the father's like no, no, no, no
It wasn't it wasn't it was it was the the little mongoose it ran into the walls
And so that kind of really soured people on jeff because this fabled psychic investigator was like
Yeah, I heard it. It was the little girl
Eventually the family moved the Irving's moved and jeff didn't follow them
They had no other reported
dealings with jeff the james passed away and the the mom and the vori had to move away
They actually had to sell the farm at a discount because the word in town that was that it was haunted
No one wanted to buy this house at this haunted house
Which I wouldn't have a problem with it, especially if he was kind of like a dope little
Mongoose running around the new owner ended up buying the property
The new owner ended up buying the property and maybe like a couple months a year or whatever later ended up shooting this giant
mongoose
This giant creature that was running around because there were mongooses in the area or mongies
Some guy imported them. I could just just sit that in the beginning
Some guy imported them to help
Coal the rabbit population
Anyways, the new owner of the house
Shot a mongoose and he's like I killed jeff and vori now an adult was like that's not what he looked like and now the house is
Burned down. There's been no jeff sightings
Even in her old age vori
Was like no it was totally true and I didn't like him and I wish he just left us alone
So again, it's kind of weird. I can understand her saying no it is true
And it was a whimsical fantasy of me hanging out with this talking mongoose or
No, it was all fake and it sucked because it ended up ruining my life
But she's stating that no it is real and it ruined my life like she basically
She became no one as the fraud. I guess that would be a reason to
Keep up keep it up if you didn't want to be considered more of a fraud. I don't know
Do you think I remember my very first episode on this podcast all those months ago was about talking critters little talking animals
And obviously not like jeff. They were about how
animals communicate with each other, but
I think for an animal to be oh and it could speak hebrouw and knew all these languages
It was just such a it's such a weird if it's fake
It seems like they made it overly complicated. They could have just said there's a creature in my walls
That throw stuff or that even that's complicated. There's a creature in my wall that talks or makes noises or whatever
Or it would if you're gonna fake it just say there's a ghost in your house
But it wasn't just a talking animal. It was a talking mongoose
Who came from new deli?
and could throw things
and could hear whispers like they were normal conversations and
spoke several different languages it seems
If it was a hoax, it seems like it was an elaborate hoax
It's possible that they were the victims of the hoax
But other people have said you know it went on for so long
Either the entire family was in on it from the beginning
Because they go the way that the house it's kind of cramped up
That one person wouldn't be able to hoax the other people
They did also say the way because you know the creeks on the wall
I was saying the built the house wasn't built really well
You could be on one floor talking to the wall and you would hear the sound somewhere else
But the investigators who came out said everyone was in the same room
But again actually now that I say that those are the times nobody heard it
It's probably a hoax
But no, there's no but to that. It very most likely is a hoax. However
It would be awesome if it wasn't. It would be awesome if there was a little
Like rap scallion mongoose who was running around your house being like listen to me fat head of gnome
And like bulging your door open
Maybe not the second part
But yeah, jeff the talking mongoose
Hoover the talking seal I found out about because I was researching jeff. This was the story and I should say this too
jeff the talking mongoose was recommended to me by through email from a listener named antonio
So thank you for that
He I had heard about jeff a while back and kind of passed on the story because I was like, uh, and then I ended up
But I said, you know, he sent this to me. I'll do some more research on it and
There's a ton of stuff on jeff
And they found like hair samples and there's like photos and stuff like that
But again, they sent they like we found hair from jeff and they send it out to a lab and they go yeah, it's from
a dog
Or a cat or rat or whatever
Same thing a little paw prints and there were mongooses in the area as well
There's drawings of them if you find a drawing very convincing. It's not really evidence, but
Jeff the talking mongoose. I wish you existed, but I think you are completely fake
Let's move on to the next story here. So
the next story
is
I'm going to talk about
Some personal experiences I had
at the Stanley hotel. It's a historically haunted hotel
The story is that the Stephen King stayed there on the off season
So his family were the only ones there and he had a nightmare about his son being chased down the
hallway by a hose or something like that
Then he's like i'm gonna write a book about that. I'm not a huge Stephen King fan
I think his short stories are amazing, but his novels are just pretty wandery
Go on and on and on but
So anyways, there's you know, a lot of ghost hunter shows have gone there and it's just no one locally and
nationally and internationally as this haunted location so
At the time my mother was doing
She worked for the national guard
Helping veterans come when they're they're coming from Iraq or Afghanistan or really anywhere
But generally it was coming from the hot zones
So my mom was she worked for the national guard. That was her job
So veterans would come back and she would help she ran these programs to help get them back into
The groove of things so it was a lot of like family retreats and things like that to just kind of
automate them to civilian life
They're still they're still soldiers, but you know what I mean like now they're back to like having to pay bills and go to the movies and things like that
And they do these big seminars. So one year they were having the seminar at the Stanley hotel
And my mom I was in the area my mom said hey, do you want to go up to the Stanley hotel?
We're going to be there for the weekend. We're going to be running like these workshops, but you can just run around the hotel
I was like hell. Yeah, dude. You know, it's pretty dope
So we go to the Stanley hotel
And the first night I just decided to we were there for like
Two days three nights or whatever the first night. I was like, you know what? I'm here. It's cold. There's snow everywhere
I hate the snow
And I was like, I'm just gonna like chill. I go tomorrow night
I'll probably like walk around and look for ghosts and stuff like that
But tonight we're just gonna chill and so I ended up watching for the very first time eastbound and down and I was laughing so hard
That shows hilarious never heard of it before and I watched like six episodes
They're doing like some marathon and showtime
The next day I get up. I'm just kind of again walking around eating croissants, you know stuff
You do normally hotels. I went for a walk around the hotel. It's just very normal place
One thing I've noticed is that it's beautiful hotel was built like in 1907
It's beautiful
Like old school antique
Really rich person hotel
Just hardwood everywhere
It's just it looks like you're walking around a giant mansion
and
In the middle of this like turn of the century built
hotel
There are these math. I mean massive like the size of a baby's head
water mains like fire
What are those things called
Not necessarily like what are those fire sprinkler things was this? I mean like you be walking through this
like
Million dollar hotel and right above your head. There were these huge metal pipes running all it totally looked
like half of it was
Trump tower and then you look up slightly and you're like in the steerage section of titanic
And you're like what it was weird because it was totally throwing off this vibe
I'm thinking oh, you know, they probably just have to have like this world-class sprinkler system for
You know because it's a fancy hotel. They don't it's maybe it's for insurance reasons
I'd never been in a fancy hotel before I'd been in like
I don't know
I always thought holiday in was nice. So
The next day I'm just kind of walking around exploring stuff walking but not like super exploring stuff like I said I was eating croissants
And that night I said, you know what so now it's the second night
I was like I'm gonna like just walk around and the place was
packed
Because it was winners for people were up skiing
They had all the national guard people there not all of them obviously, but you know a bunch of national guard people there and their families
Oh, oh, oh, so so this is when it started to get weird. So the whole thing is
Ghost based around ghost tours and stuff like that
Which is really not what I'd want to hear if I just came back from Iraq
Being here about these tortured soul. They're like this person died a horrible death
And now he's doomed to walk the planet and you're like
I just watched a Hummer get blown up in front of me like three weeks ago
I don't want to hear about this stuff and there were complaints about that afterwards people were like
Don't ever have another seminar here all they ever talk about at the hotel
Like all the tours are based around like people dying
But he was so I go on the ghost tour
During the day and they're like the tour guides this very attractive young woman and she's like
Oh, this is the ballroom where sometimes you'll see like a ghost at 3 a.m
Dancing around that I'm like, uh, and they're like this is this hallway and this is the door. This is room 237
This is where Stephen King stayed or 217 or whatever
This is where Stephen King stayed and this is from the movie and everyone's like, oh
Then we go to this one room
And she's like this room is haunted because inside this walk-in closet
There's a ghost of a randy old man
And if women walk in there, he'll feel you up
He'll like grab your you know, he'll like tickle you or grab your butt or whatever
And I'm like, uh, and she goes any volunteers that go in
And this 13 year old girl goes all go in and the tour guides demeanor totally changes
Before you know, she's dressed up in like this old school like colonial costume or 1900s costume, whatever
And she's like been super bright and vibrant and she's talking about like this creepy pervert ghost in this closet
Who grabs women and the little girl goes all go in and the tour guides demeanor completely changes
She goes you have to be over 18 to enter the closet
So I remember thinking okay
What like if this is totally fake
Why would it matter how old the person was because whoever goes in there?
It's the power of suggestion. They're gonna go in there and they're gonna be come out and be like he touched my butt
But if if there really is a perverted old man living in that closet
You don't want to send a minor into that room
I remember thinking they totally changed the color of the whole tour because before it was like
You want to hear some campfire ghost stories and then after that it was like
Stay away from the men to stay away from the old man with the candy. I was like, what?
And I was like that's that's a weird thing you think I mean, maybe you don't want a 13 year old girl going in there
And then coming out being like mommy mommy he touched me like even the power suggestion works
But it's kind of I was like well, that's a weird reaction and that was just the beginning
So that night I'm walking around the hotel by myself and it's probably around 10 o'clock at night
And I wasn't like a big nerd and have my camera or my infrared scope or anything like that
I might have had my I don't think I had a smartphone back then but you know, I wasn't like I'm gonna find me some ghost
I'm gonna prove
These exist. I just kind of wanted to walk around late at night in this creepy hotel because it is admittedly quite creepy
And I get I'm walking down the hallways and I see
Here talk about taking the boob hill guys. I see these four coeds
Sitting kind of hanging outside their hotel room kind of chatting it up and I walk by and there's some guys
They're like, hey, baby. What's up? Not to me to the girls
So that would be a totally different story
So I kind of walk around the hotel. I come back maybe 30 40 minutes later and they're still out there
And I walk up to him. I'm like, hey, what's up? And they're like, oh nothing
And they go, what are you doing? I was like, oh, you know, I'm just kind of exploring the hotel and stuff like that
Of course, we started talking about ghosts because that's really why people come there
So I just sit down there and I'm we're kind of just sitting on the floor outside their hotel room
Two of the girls are kind of coming in and out and then the other two girls are staying out there the whole time
We're just talking and stuff like that and one of the girl goes, you know, it's weird
Before you showed up we kept hearing this noise in this door down
The way like we can hear the alarm clock going off really loudly
I'm like, well, that's not that weird and and she goes. Yeah, but what's weird is that?
Why isn't anyone
Acknowledging it like you think if the person in the room was asleep
They shut off the alarm
But at the very least the people in the neighboring rooms should be complaining because it's really really loud
and I was like
That's interesting. Yeah, let's go check that out and they're like, yeah, really? I was like, yeah, yeah, yeah
Let's go. You know, I used to hunt ghosts and something. Yeah
So we get up and we go down the hallway
And I you can clearly hear this loud ass eat
Eat the most annoying noise in the world is an alarm clock. You can't shut off
Eat eat eat and it's very clear when you're standing outside the door
And again, I'm thinking well, it could just be that the alarm clock's going off
And I'm talking to the girls and I was like, it could just be the alarm clock's going off and
Nobody knows that it's on and that the the walls are fairly thick
at this point one of the girls
kind of leans to the door
and I think she went to test the handle or something like that and
She it doesn't open
She let's go the handle and we're talking there for a bit more and then the handle turns on its own
Like someone's trying to get out
So at that point we realized that either one of two things have happened
There was either somebody in there and they thought someone was turning the knob to get in
Or there wasn't someone in there and something was turning the knob to get out
So we kind of like did a Scooby-Doo run
Back down to where their room was and I was like, oh my god, that's totally terrifying
But again, I'm thinking, you know, completely
understandable
Then we got in our brain to break into a janitor's closet. It was so bizarre
That okay, that's standard Jason stuff
And I remember there's this janitor closet. Oh the light was on in the janitor closet. That's why and again now
We're like at midnight and I go that's weird the the lights on the janitor's. I don't know why I thought it was weird
I think I was just saying stuff to impress chicks
But I was like, you know, the janitor's lights on I wonder if there's something spooky in there
And they go, oh, yeah, let's check it out. So we go now we're back on their floor
I actually the whole thing the doorknob down the way also took place on their floor and the alarms clock did stop
Going off after a certain point, but again alarm clocks electricity stuff turns on and off doorknobs
Maybe when she turned the doorknob and let go and then we were talking maybe she tightened it and then undid itself
There's rational explanations for a lot of this not all of it
I remember I was thinking. Oh, you know, we should break into this janitor's closet
I used to be a real hooligan back in the day. I didn't have a problem with like breaking into stuff
So and I remember I want to impress these girls and I thought you know what I should do
I should pull out like my credit card and like try to jimmy the door thing
And it's not going to work. It never works because the way that the lock is it's
The smooth part is on the other side on the your main part on the outside part. It's like the rectangle and on the inside
It's the little
Half moon shape thing
And I thought but you know, I'm gonna try it'll be kind of cool
Like to look make it look like I'm a burglar or something
That wasn't far from the truth at the time
But and I pulled out my credit card and I remember I stuck it in knowing full well it wouldn't work
And it worked
And I so I'm like in front of these girls and as a care I got this
Pulling out my credit card knowing that I was just going to jiggle it around for a bit and then be like
I must be one of the special lugs
I pulled my credit card out
I slide it against the lock and it goes click click and I was like holy shit now. Maybe that's not paranormal
Maybe that's just me being a pimp
But again, I or a badly designed door, but I thought that was really weird. It shouldn't happen
The the janitor's closet was not haunted by the way
But as the night progress you're like Jason you're just
This random stuff. This is the creepy thing. So I'm sitting there with the girls and now we're probably around
I don't know midnight one o'clock and I say, you know the scariest stuff supposedly happens at 3 a.m
The witch's hour and they're like, oh really? Oh and I asked them. Why are you ladies here?
Why are you it's spring break? That's okay. Yeah, I remember now was happening during spring break
But there was snow everywhere. I guess it was in colorado. So there's always snow everywhere, but
I go so why are you guys here? Like, why aren't you guys like on a beach and spring break? Oh, I should add if they were all
really really hot
I go, why are you guys here and not like at a beach somewhere and they go?
Oh, we just wanted to go and see a bunch of ghosts and I'm thinking I said
That's how horror movies start like going four hot girls going together
To like a haunted like a purposely haunted location. You know how many horror movies start like that and they're like, oh
They didn't make ghost noises, but I mean, you know because they were hot and I'm telling them are hot, but anyways
So we're sitting there and I said let's stay up till
I don't know how many people are still listening to this episode, but
We're sitting there
It's and I said let's stay up until 3 a.m. Now at this point two of the girls were like, you know what?
We're tired. We're gonna go to bed but the other two girls were and at this point
We're just chatting about all sorts of stuff their room was right on the corner
So it was right next to us the staircase one of many staircases in the building
And we're sitting there and we're talking and the girl who's sitting closest to the stairs goes
Did you hear that?
I see her kind of look over the awning and she goes
Did you hear that me and the other girl are like, what did you hear and she goes?
someone she was just walking up those stairs, but
Like they stopped halfway and there's no one down there and I'm like what?
The other girl would kind of look over that ledge and there's nobody down there
It's like three or four flights of stairs and there's more stairs going up
So maybe about an hour later
We're all sitting there. We're talking
And we all hear
Someone walking up the stairs and you could hear like the
Going up and the stairs don't seem to make that much noise when people normally walk on them
But you can hear like the creak of each stair getting closer and closer
And we're like what what was that?
And then I think about an hour
It happened again, maybe a half hour later. We hear the
But now it's the flight
Like so there's a flight of stairs a landing and then another flight of stairs and a landing a flight of stairs and a landing
It's on the landing that we should be able if it's on the landing directly below us
So it's like let's say 10 steps up
Landing then 10 steps up that second 10 steps up is where we're at
We hear a go
Like slowly though, I'm not going to prolong it again and it goes up the landing we hear a
Very clearly
Like we're dead silent. We heard the walking earlier
From floor to the floor underneath us and now we're hearing it at our landing basically
Like below us
And we're looking and there's nothing there. We clearly hear someone breathing
And I remember thinking it had gone an hour long intervals
So I think it was midnight the first time we heard it at the bottom of the stairs and then it was one
And now it was two and we heard it on that landing and I thought it's happening. I told him I go it's happening every hour
So whatever is doing this it's taking its time, but I said that means at 3 a.m
It will be where we're at
And I was like do you guys want to stay up till 3 a.m. And they're like hell yeah, dude
We're almost there and we're sitting we're talking
and then um having a good old time and sure enough
I
Walking up the stairs
And then we don't hear anything
It's not breathing in front of us. There's no jump scare. No big ghost
And then we're like, okay, we're going to bed like whatever had whatever was walking had gotten to our floor
Was where we would have been
We didn't hear it walking past us
We didn't look in the mirror and it say help me or anything creepy. It was just this weird
Exhaired audio experience that we had
And so we're like, okay, that was weird again. You don't know what's gonna happen
We didn't know if we were all gonna get like taken to some hell dimension or something like that. Obviously it didn't happen
Unless the hell dimension is where your friends forget it's your birthday
however
I said au revoir to the beautiful young women and went back to my room the next day though
I was walking around the
Hotel getting more croissants and there was a starbucks in there too. Oh, no, no, it wasn't a starbucks
It was a normal coffee shop. So it sucked and
I was talking to the guy
We had the counter just like a you know a dude working a job
I said, hey, what is it with all of these big pipes? I go you got this such a nice hotel
The wire these giant water like water pipes. They totally ruins the vibe
He looks at me and he goes
Happy birthday jay. I was joking. He looks at me and he says
You know how many fires get started in this place? He goes nobody knows why he goes there's fires everywhere in this place
And so we have to have a state-of-the-art
fire suppression system to stop it
Everyone so the Stanley hotel sits above a town
And I go, you know is do you think it's ghosts causing these fires and he looks at me and he says everyone in the town
Has either been injured or know someone who's been injured at this hotel
The people who live in town wouldn't care if this entire place burned down someday
And then we my coffee
I think that's an interesting button on that story because we hear like oh the spooky legends of this place
But if you lived in the shadow
Of a building that if it is truly haunted and it's the main source of your economy
You would have people go. Hey, I'm gonna go get a job at
Stanley. Yeah, I finally got my job and people would be like don't work there, honey
Don't work there. You know what happened to your uncle. You know what happened to bruce. You know what happened to tina
But that's really the only job in town
It almost is like this shining-esque prison for the people there
They have these mysterious fires and these
Hauntings and these accidents and these injuries that don't see that's one thing you can sell people on come stay at our hotel
It's spooky. You can't sell people on come stay at our hotel
The people who work here get injured very very often you wouldn't have that
You wouldn't put that in your brochure. So if people were like working on something like working on a ladder
And the ladder gets knocked out from underneath them and they fall down and break their arm
They're gonna quit because there'll be like there's I was the only one in that hallway
Or some if a maid's cleaning a room and she turns around and a dresser's on fire
She's going to be like i'm out of here. You're not going to put that stuff in your brochure
You're going to talk about the spooky ghosts that float around in the ballroom
Or the room that steven king wrote his
Stories in but if the guy who worked there if he you know wasn't pulling my leg
And I don't necessarily think he he he was because I was it was such an odd quack
I asked him about the water mains and he just was like oh, this is why
Rather than just being a barista and being like I don't know
Other than the tour guides and the people being part of the hotel everyone else to them
It was just a job. It wasn't this spooky adventure. They were on
It was just them showing up to work. So when they're just like
This place is cursed. It's not fun haunted
People get injured here and the people in town wish this place would just be destroyed. That's different than
You know wearing a colonial costume telling people to go into the closet full of the creepy pervert man
I wouldn't go back there
I got that sense of
Negative energy from that place
I've went there once
I would not spend another night at the stanley hotel. That's my personal read on it
I do think that I think I think it's you're very likely to get injured there
And very likely for it. You're that world class fire suppression system to kick in
I don't think it's a fun haunted place like say the winchester mystery house
I think it's something much more sinister than that if you get the opportunity to go you you might want to take it but
You know
You might want to sleep with your eyes open and not go into your closet
I did rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/didrabberadio
@jasonlcarpenter is going to be the twitter account
Did rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
But i'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]
[MUSIC]