I had a few odd things happen to me this weekend, nothing too dramatic, but some of them worth
discussing on this show.
A quick update to the "Storm Area 51" meme that is coming and gone.
And then we take a look at the story of Martin Guerrero, a man in France who got accused of
stealing grain and disappeared.
And then he came back.
Or did he?
A day on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
I had a great weekend.
I went to a toga party.
Toga.
Dressed as a care bear, I watched a bunch of YouTube videos on how to make a toga.
Couldn't get it right.
I just wrapped a silk sheet or satin sheet.
Sheet.
Not a sheik.
There's like this Middle Eastern oil baron wrapped around my waist.
I wrapped a satin sheet around my waist.
So I just like at the toga.
I was wearing a care bear onesie.
I go to this party.
Baller status guys.
Baller status.
Here's a little tip.
Here's a little tip for your Halloween costumes.
Wear materials girls like to touch.
She'll be getting touched all the time.
Girl, look at me.
I'm a big old care bear.
Now everyone might not be able to pull off the care bear.
I think you guys can.
So anyways, I had my suit of a million, million touches and I hung out with some really good
friends and rigged a toga contest.
So my friend won and she was really happy.
She said she'd never won a popularity contest before.
So cute.
Anyways, why am I talking about this?
Am I humble bragging a little bit and I'm giving you advice on your Halloween costumes?
You betcha.
This also has to do with dead rabbit radio.
It has to do with spooky paranormal stuff.
It has to do with dead rabbit radio stuff.
First off, I'm sitting at this, it's at the Elks Lodge.
So spooky, masons, conspiracy.
It's at the Elks Lodge and I'm talking to this chick and she's just completely hammered.
So at a certain point I'm kind of getting bored of talking to her because she can't keep
ascended scowing.
So I turn and I'm watching the television and a commercial comes on for Terminator Dark
Fate and I go, this is going somewhere.
This isn't me just talking about what happens at the bar.
I'm looking at the television for Terminator Dark Fate and I go, what?
That movie already came out.
That movie came out like two months ago and it came and went and it got like 68% on Rotten
Tomatoes and no one really cared about it and it made like half its budget in the opening
weekend.
It wasn't a huge flop but it wasn't a huge success and then it said coming November
first and I was like, oh, Mandela effect.
I have moved into a reality where Terminator Dark Fate has not come out yet.
So I originally was in a reality where Terminator Dark Fate, the new Terminator movie came out
a couple months ago and then I got ran over by a bulldozer or steamroller which would
be more apt.
I could probably outrun a bulldozer.
Steamroller sneak up on you and then I'm here in this reality.
Now obviously that's what a mad man would think and that's what a lot of people in conspiracy
theory circles think.
Mandela effect is you moving from one reality to the other where certain things.
I'll tell you why I thought that Terminator Dark Fate came out.
This is turning into a plug for that movie because I keep saying the whole name.
I can tell you why I thought Terminator Dark Fate coming theaters November 1st came out
two months ago was because I could care less about the new Terminator Dark Fate movie coming
out November 1st.
I could care less.
I've seen them all.
I'm really tired of the Terminator franchise.
Genesis burned me out.
I would watch a reboot.
I would watch a remake.
I would watch a Terminator set strictly in the 1980s but I'm tired of Terminators to
one movie I would probably be fine watching a prequel of.
I don't like prequels in general but I could watch a 1970s version of the Terminator that
would be really interesting.
I don't care about the robots punching each other in their current iteration.
I'm done.
This is the thing.
People who Mandela affects stuff.
Mandela effect is because the reason why that terminology is there is because there were
people who swear up and down that Nelson Mandela died in the 80s in prison and then when Mandela
actually died like in the late 90s early 2000s they were like what no they swear up and down
he died in prison in the 1980s and that's why it's called the Mandela effect.
This idea that your memories aren't wrong you're from a universe where your facts are
true and here is my argument for that.
The people who believe Nelson Mandela died in prison in the 1980s I will bet were not
huge fans of Nelson Mandela's work.
Not saying they were actively trying to stop him they're like knocking him over as he's
like walking through jail they're pushing him and they're like we're gonna make a
broomer.
I don't think they were following his career closely because then they would have been
like oh he's out of prison now.
I think that these are people who didn't really care about Nelson Mandela they knew he was
famous and they kind of knew why and then they stopped hearing about him for a while
or they just stopped caring and so I don't care about Terminator Dark Fate coming out.
It might be a good movie I think it'll be a middling movie I think it'll make middling
amount of money and it'll have middling reviews on Rotten Tomatoes and it will disappear into
the consciousness and then I will forget that I even recorded this segment.
I think it'll be that gray of a thing.
I wanted to highlight it though because that's how Mandela Effect stuff starts.
Because you just don't care in the beginning enough to pay attention.
So when someone points something out to you you go what?
I didn't know that.
I thought it was this and it turns out you really didn't care until someone brought
it to your attention in the first place.
Now also I wanted to say this I go to the Toga party and I'm hanging out there and I'm talking
with different girls at this point and all these girls are my friends I'm not like super
pimp I'm kind of pimp but I'm not like super pimp right?
I'm talking to this other girl and she's pretty drunk too but not as bad as the first
one.
The first one was anyways talking to this girl, she's a friend of mine and all of a sudden
I don't know how many people have been in an Elk's Lodge.
I've been warned by people over the years dude don't go to Elk Lodges don't go to Mason
buildings and stuff like that.
Like even for fun even go there to drink or to play pool or whatever don't do it.
I was like why not and they were like just don't and then it was just like mysteriously
vanished in front of me.
Turn into a flock of birds and fly away.
I was like oh I always wondered what Susan was up to.
She was just a flock of birds.
So I've been told that for a long time anyways I go to I've been to this Elk's Lodge quite
a few times.
We're sitting there watching I'm probably breaking some sort of Elk law saying this
I'm gonna get killed.
I'm sitting there, Jenny's sitting next to me.
We're at the bar and she's going on about something.
I don't remember exactly what it was.
Probably something about her because she talks about herself all the time and I'm starting
to hear a low murmur through the crowd.
There's maybe about like 40 people in the area we're at.
I start to hear this low murmur through the crowd right and Jenny's still like yeah so
anyways if you look at my hair and then like this bracelet I made and I'm just here like
this and it's growing this murmur is growing and I can't figure out what what they're
saying but I start to pick up that there is there is some sort of chance going on and
I'm at this point going Jenny's trying to get her shirt and she's like yeah and so anyways
like if you look at the hem of this dress I'm like I think we're about to get eaten
dude like you need to be quiet and as she's finally starting to calm down we hear this
the golden hour of recollection the homecoming of those who wander the mystic roll call of
those who will come no more living or dead and elk is never forgotten never forsaken
morning and noon may pass him by the light of day sink heedlessly in the west but air
the shadow of midnight shall fall the chimes of memory will be peeling forth the friendly
message to our absent members and everyone takes a drink and I'm like what is going on
so apparently at 11pm on the dot this this chant starts which it would have been I would
have been fine with and I am fine with this is your tradition but I would have not have
been as petrified if I knew it was coming like if I go there again I'll be like but what
was super weird dude is like you could hear it like it was a chant now chant again like
if you're at a if you're out of sports arena and they're like go team and it's like 10,000
people going go team it's nothing spooky about that right but if you're in a dark if you're
in a dark building you know a really you know five people the five girls you came with who
really want to be able to like fight their way out if these guys all of a sudden grab
forks and knives and try to eating us you're in a dark didn't she I shouldn't say didn't
she you're in a very very nice establishment but it is dark there's been a lot of drinking
everyone's wearing togas and you hear a bunch of chanting and you can tell everyone is quiet
and somber except for the girl sitting next to you who's talking very very loudly about
her personal appearance and I'm thinking I had no idea what's gonna happen next 30 seconds
if they all turn to me and point this is not going to be a good night but they didn't and
I did go home and figure out why they did that I didn't go home immediately I was like
see you later ladies I got a mystery to solve the next morning I looked it up they do it
at 11pm it's this weird thing because back in the day there was a curfew at 11 every
fire had to be put out at 11pm so that way you couldn't stay up all night and plot against
the king ah King George it's not like people can't talk in the dark but I guess in olden
times if the fire was out you freeze so anyways that's where the term the 11th hour comes from
because they'd be like you know they haven't told the 11th hour to get back the ball whatever
sports thing go team and so anyways it's from that and so back when Mason lodges are being
started they go we should do something at 11 just like kind of some king thing because
we're kind of like underground still I don't know anyways it was weird and creepy I don't
remember what the other stories I was going to talk about let's see here we're like Jason
you just wanted to talk about toga party I did I did I didn't want to talk about toga
party something else weird happen oh dude so this this was the area 51 thing so I was on
4chan today you know people go you don't really go to you don't really cover 4chan stuff anymore
I go yeah it's because a lot of it isn't it's there's not a lot of good stuff on there
anymore it kind of goes in waves you really have to dig for this stuff so anyways I am
I still look I still look for interesting stuff I found this now this is going to take a little
bit of a leap of faith but it's pretty brief so and I did not cover the area 51 storm area
51 story I felt that it was pretty well covered in the mainstream medium there wasn't a lot
I could add to it I kept looking for different angles to it and I couldn't find anything
like everything I could come across was pretty mainstream I couldn't find anything relevant
I like to talk about obscure stuff but here we go this is something that I have seen nowhere
else so on 4chan there's currently a Prussian news article it's a couple of paragraphs written
in Prussian on this thread on 4chan that has maybe like 12 responses it's not linked to
an article in a Prussian magazine but it seems that it should be so let me read you
I'm not going to read you the whole thing and I'm definitely not going to read in Prussian
there is an English translation and the three fourths of it is all information we already
know storm area 51 was a meme that was started and people were going to show up at area 51
to do a Naruto run and then it just became like a big joke and they were going to have
like alien wood stock but that got shut down because there was no infrastructure around
that area all basic stuff right and then it goes into someone wanted to use the term alien
stock and then someone else wanted to use that and that was like a legal battle but anyways
here we go with the interesting thing on the day of the event about 150 people were reported
to have shown up at the entrance to area 51 with two succeeding in entering the site and
estimated 1500 attended the related festival so in the area you had about 1500 people you
had 150 people at the storm area 51 designated quote unquote location and two succeeded in
entering the site okay seven arrestor were made for trespassing including one for alcohol
related reasons and one for indecent exposure that was probably someone urinating that you
can get a you can get a sex crime rap if you urinate in public and the wrong cop comes
around the corner or just a citizen sees you yeah you yeah you don't want to do that anyways
three remain at large whereabouts unknown dubbed the Lincoln County war criminals Billy
the Kid Charlie Bodry and Doc Skirlock so the implication is that there's three people
out there and we don't know the real names they're going by the names of these western
outlaws either they've chosen these names for themselves or someone else has chosen
these names for them and this is being reported on a Prussian website or someone wrote a Prussian
write up of this specifically for 4chan because there's no links for anything here they simply
exist as its own thing and then you have the these two little paragraphs and then after
that you just have pictures of T tunnels like a tunnel pictures of tunnel beams where it's
like a stick and then two sticks holding that stick up and there's a picture of rocks and
there's like a rock and two rocks holding that up and then there's photos of the three
real life western outlaws I don't know what this is the whole start of this is this is
what this thread is called G whiz deep and that has to be a code for something or has
to be some funny joke I don't get it G whiz deep seven arrested two are inside new many
photos and documents are uploaded today 30 days the Prussians made it in anniversary
one month now storm area 51 they can't stop all of us and then there's some photos and
some I have I don't really know what to make of this thread it's really really bizarre
part of me thinks it's a code for something someone's trying to communicate information
to somebody else and they're writing it in this way and we've talked about that before
the show a lot of times intelligence agencies or drug smuggling agencies or criminal organizations
or whatever or even people just running an ARG will write stuff that seems like nonsense
to normal people but if you have the key code you go oh I'm supposed to be in Libsyn tomorrow
according to this nonsense the T beams is telling me where to go what street to go all
of that's possible but very very far fetched it's also possible that someone's totally
making it up and they happen to be fluent in Prussian or it's a group of guys and they're
like let's start this fake rumor that there's still two people running around in area 51
and there's three other people that have never been found so are they captured or they still
running around the base who knows could be that it could be true and one of the things
I've come across a lot on this show is we will do articles we'll read articles and investigate
these stories and then it just ends and stuff that happened like five six years ago I'll
be like oh I wonder if that guy was ever found guilty and I'll dig and dig and dig and there
was nothing because once the event is over it's like no people stop doing follow-up articles
it's really really bizarre it's part of that clickbaity thing like when storm area 51 was
a meme people were putting in all their headlines what a storm area 51 mean for the big bang
theory like you put it in your headlines again I mean and then once it's over people stop
covering it and I think that's where we're at now so it's most likely that some guys
are making this up and it's a funny joke but it'll be interesting to see if there is something
going on at that base or you have people that have been detained and not released been detained
and we don't even know their real names that's even makes the story even more complicated
because they are running around a US secured US military base so what was I would love
to say we'll keep you updated but who knows I don't even know what this is it could just
be a bizarro code that some guys have figured out or made up I don't think I have time for
the Martin Guerrero story let's go ahead and do let's go ahead and do this one you know
this is one I've had on the docket for months and it's I just really knew never knew where
to fit it so we'll fit it here and it actually kind of fits with the Martin Guerrero story
let's go ahead and hop in the carbon helicopter get your togas on boys we're headed out east
or west we're headed out west from Oregon get on get on togas getting caught on the
rotor blades I'm like we're leaving you behind dude you're like ah getting chopped up sorry
everyone else get on get on all the other listeners but you are now on the carbon helicopter
you're like Jason this sucks now you're just like floating above as a ghost you have ghost
powers we're flying to China the year is 1937 so not a good time to be living in China
because the Japan Empire the Japan dudes are just stomping all over China they absolutely
hate China and China hates Japan for good reason I don't know why the Japanese hated
China to begin with but they did with a furious fiery passion and so they was not basically
it was not a good time to be Chinese in China Japan it was invading now the year is 1937
there's this story takes place in Nanking which if you are a historian or just a have
a passing knowledge of World War two Nanking was an even worse place to be as Japan was
coming in the rape of Nanking was horrible I remember when I was planning this topic
because I've had it for a while I started researching the rape of Nanking and I was
like oh maybe I could do a nope nope super gross I mean some of the most barbaric stuff
you could think of a human doing to another human happened in Nanking absolutely awful
and I read an article once and I haven't been able to find this and again I've read this
article back like in 97 or something like that I read this article and it said on the
50th or it must have been the 60th anniversary of the rape of Nanking a bunch of Japan it
the rape of Nanking I guess this is a rape of Nanking episode the rape of Nanking is
what it says where they went in they just brutally raped a bunch of women they're also
just shooting women children civilians men women I guess I already said that they're
just shooting people in the street bashing their heads in with the butts of rifles stabbing
them with bayonets raping them is a whore I mean that is me that's a whitewash of how
bad it was but anyways in 1997 the bunch of Japanese businessmen said hey you know it
would be so funny to do they go to Nanking which is in China so just so we're clear
Japanese businessmen 60th anniversary of Nanking or 50th anniversary is one of those two it
was the anniversary of the rape of Nanking a bunch of Japanese businessmen rent out an
entire floor of the most expensive hotel in Nanking and then hire every prostitute in
Nanking and they have a massive orgy on the anniversary of the rape of Nanking in the
city of Nanking now I don't know how true that I read that story like 15 20 years ago
and I was trying to find it again and I don't I wasn't able to find it so that story may
be fake news but I did read that anyways long story short Japanese people do not like the
Chinese and at this point it's vice versa 1937 let's do the story there are 3000 Chinese
soldiers who are ordered to guard an area around Nanking because Japanese are just stomping
everything and they're like you guys need to get over there you guys need to set up right
here you're going to guard this place okay you division you go over here you go over
here and so on and so forth and so December 9th rolls around right and you have all of
these divisions all of these troops scattered around the area surrounding Nanking the Japanese
have not gotten there yet but what happens is December 9th rolls around people are talking
to the Milwaukee talkies back then they had radios people like over hey alpha team will
call him alpha team I don't know what they were alpha team alpha team are you there yeah
yeah we're here and they're like okay and they would people would talk they'd do the rounds
but by December 9th they'd pick up division would pick up the line and go alpha team alpha
team report alpha team alpha team report so people are very very nervous that this whole
group they're not getting any answer from these guys you're thinking of is to have have they
been assaulted is the attack started what's going on send some scouts out you two you
guys look fast you guys run out there or take a Jeep and this isn't the ancient Greece guys
get in a Jeep they're like oh that's much better they get in a Jeep the scouts go to where
this 3000 troops were situated there's nobody there it's completely empty scouts are looking
around and they're like this isn't good they radio back hey yeah we're here but they aren't
you guys might want to come out and take a look at this so they send out CSI combats
scene investigation bunch of guys walking around with suits sunglasses they're like hey
shouldn't you be in like an actual uniform and prepare to fight the Japanese they're
like shut up and investigation they're reaching down they're like rubbing dirt between their
fingers and they're like ah yes I don't know I've never watched CSI I just know the memes
I don't know exactly what they do on this show but anyways he's rubbing dirt rubbing dirt
between his fingers the other people are like actually doing investigation this is what they
find all the weapons are still there so you know it's funny all the weapons are there
I wonder where their vehicles were that might be a little clue but anyways that solves the
mystery all their weapons were there but every land vehicle had mysteriously disappeared
anyways all their weapons were there other troops like you know because you have this
ring of defense around the city other groups of soldiers said well we didn't see any any
fighting over there we didn't hear any fighting and we didn't see a bunch of people leave
and then of course things get a little more complicated when the Japanese imperial army
just crashes over Nanking like a tidal wave so at that point they really aren't worried
about what happened to these 3000 dudes like full on World War two has hit China the city
of Nanking it's block to block fighting and eventually the government of China just like
I give up not as a government but the city they just kind of pulled out of the city and
the Japanese just went to town just smashing in people's heads it was a horrible thing
now I could be a little off on the detail not the smashing heads they did that but I
like I said I researched this quite a few months ago and I'm pretty sure that's how it went
out that eventually they were doing block to block fighting and the Chinese government
just said we got to pull out I remember there was a couple of Westerners there that were
trying to like it was it's actually a fascinating story but there was a people there trying to
negotiate like make this a safe zone like can we get all of the civilians here for a safe
zone and the Japanese are like yeah and the Chinese are like yeah and then they all went
the safe zone and the Japanese just went in there and just it was just smashed people's
heads open it was brutal but that is a different podcast to totally you can listen to hardcore
history or something like that you want to hear about people getting bayoneted in the
uterus because that's what happened and then let's get back so the war is over now Japan
gets stomped out of China a couple bombs dropped on them they get just pushed back to little
tiny island in the middle of the ocean and so China goes hey you know yeah yeah you did
a bunch of messed up stuff but whatever happened to those 3000 troops and the Japanese go what
you have to be a little more specific than that we killed a lot of people over there
and they're like yeah but there was a 3000 troops outside of Nanking and they just disappeared
like what happened to them the Japanese go through all their logs and they go we don't
know we actually never engaged in a fight at that particular time in that particular area
so we had nothing to do with it I've always thought it was weird how militaries keep track
of stuff like we've done a couple shows about boats and they have ships logs and I guess
I get that but what do you write in the log there was more water around me today there
was a fight over a loaf of bread like what do you put in the stuff and then why do you
keep it like after the war why does Japan have a book saying oh here's here's our book
of atrocities it's a scrapbook like just burn all that stuff why do they keep logs and I
don't know I have no idea I'm sure somebody in the military could be like oh it's because
we like writing and it's an outlet for our creativity I don't know but anyways Japan
goes through their logs and they're like they're like atrocities A through F and they're flipping
through it and they're like yeah no you're not in here so there's some theories about
what this was what this was some people say that it was a time slip you have a group of
people 3000 troops that basically Mandela affected out that would actually be a convenient
time to Mandela effect you go to a timeline where Japan is not about to invade your country
they're like oh this is beautiful there's been theories about a time slip there's been
theories about mass alien abduction I think they have a hard enough time getting one person
3000 people would be kind of hard to abduct I thought it was interesting because a long
time ago we did an episode about the black bamboo forest and the stone's gate in this
mystical weird it's real life forest it's super spooky in the guards not the guards the guides
will only take you so far in the forest there's a massive stone gate and their story after
story of China sending in explorers and survey teams and stuff like that and they'll cross
stones gate and then they won't come back or they'll feel like they're being whisked away
to another dimension something that this place is only 20 bike vehicle is only 21 hours away
from the black bamboo forest and there was a story of troops during the Mao revolution
that were loyal to the capitalist government or whatever they had over there they went
beyond the stone gate and that was the name of that episode I recommend checking it out
but they went beyond the stone gate and they never got found again so it's possible these
3000 troops also did that but but what's even more interesting is actually it's not it's
less interesting but what's even less interesting is that some people say this story is not
true at all that it's a local legend now when I look at my articles for this story of where
I got this from because I had heard this pop up a couple times some of them are mystical
websites message to eagle.com is a website I've gone to a lot they do a lot of unexplained
stuff but then we have war history online which is more of a mainstream website where
they talk about surprise war history online so it's kind of a legend that's been going
around for a while and I've got this article from multiple sites but some people say that
this is the first clue that it's fake is that some people say the story takes place in 1939
so that makes it way after the battle in Anking and so that makes it even a little more suspicious
but there's a possibility that it's just a retroactive legend that none of it happened
there were no 3000 troops in that area and no one ever asked the Japanese if they had
any records on it and it's just completely made up it's fake but if you are going to
disappear right before a massive battle is the time that you could see doing that it's
an interesting story to think about because what we have let's assume that it's true for
a moment what we have is a mass disappearance and we'll get those on the high seas for me
to triangle type stuff but 3000 soldiers simply leaving their posts never to be seen again
it's not like these people popped up after the war or anything like that and shortly
before the rape of Nan King so this supposedly happened on December 9th and later in December
was when the siege started it's an interesting time to go missing imagine that you are a
young Chinese man you're conscripted into the military and one night when you're just
ready to do your job you're terrified of what's coming you don't know if you're prepared
for the combat but one night there is a flash of light and you're abducted you and every
soldier that you've bonded with over the past few months of training you have been abducted
by aliens or teleported to another dimension another timeline where you are the alien December
9th 1937 in China would be the only time that you would prefer to be in the hands of alien
captors because what was happening back on earth to your own people was more horrible
than any alien intelligence could ever conceive what we do to each other as a species would
even leave them speechless dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address
you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead rabbit radio
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't
have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys
bye
you
you you
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]