A farmer out checking on his cattle has a close encounter of the "burned" kind.
And then we travel to Illinois to take a look at the story of a bizarre ghost
that pulls people out of their beds and forces them into the closet.
And then things get a little kinky today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys are
having a lot of fun, whatever you're doing. You're all robbing a bank right now. You're like,
"I'm having the best fun ever." Shut up, hostages. First off, let's welcome into Dead Rabbit Command
coming in on a blue light cycle from Tron. [Humming]
It's Blue Synth, everyone. Give a round of applause. Don't bump into his light wall.
Otherwise, you'll de-rez, but Blue Synth, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or if you don't fight for the users, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show. Really, really helps out a lot.
Blue Synth, I'm going to go ahead and touch the keys of the Jason Jalopy. It's not as cool as a
light cycle, but we'll leave a stream behind us, a stream which is junk falling out of the trunk.
Don't bump into that either. You'll get tetanus. I'm going to give you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're headed out to Quixota, Brazil.
Jason Jalopy is driving down the road. I got most of my information from the story from an
article written by Marcus Loth for ufoinsight.com. It's a really good website. I recommend checking
it out. A lot of great articles on there. It's April 3rd, 1976. We're in Quixota, Brazil. It's
two in the morning. Jason Jalopy is driving real quiet. It actually broke down a while ago. We're
pushing it. All the stuff that was falling out of the back was essential to make the car run.
And we see a man. His name is Luis Barroso Fernandez. He's just a simple farmer checking on his
cattle. Brings his wagon out little donkey. Walking frame. I wish I could get that donkey
checked out. That's not a donkey noise. Hee-haw. Hee-haw. Luis and his donkey are taking this wagon.
They're out checking on these cattle. And then all of a sudden, the distance Luis
sees these bright lights in the sky. It looks like an airplane flying really low to the ground.
He thinks that's weird. It's two in the morning. I wonder what it's doing this far out here. And
the way it's flying so low to the ground almost looks like it's about to land. Now, remember,
this is his farm. He's just want to play destroying all of his crops. And him and his donkey are
standing there. And this plane is getting lower and lower and lower and closer and closer to them.
And then all of a sudden, it shines an incredibly powerful blinding beam of light at both him and
his donkey. The donkey puts one hoof up to cover his eyes. They're both paralyzed. They're both
paralyzed by this beam. And the craft continues into the night sky, leaves the area. And Luis is
just laying there on the ground. Now, there was a cowboy in the area just passing through. He sees
what happens. He comes across Luis. He's paralyzed. He's laying on the ground. Luis is completely
discombobulated. No word on the mental state of the donkey is probably just acting like a donkey.
They take him to the hospital. They take Luis to the hospital. He actually had burns on the left
side of his body. So it was like he was turning as the beam hit him. And he was in incredible pain.
The doctors can't really figure out what's going on. They see that his skin is burned. They see
that he's in pain. But when they ask him about it, he's like, "Uh, there's a UFO. There's a plane.
Plane was coming down the side of the beam." The doctors don't know how to make that. Like,
did he have an epileptic fit? No doctor, especially in 1976, is going to go and must be UFOs.
So the astronomy lab, you're just going to think this guy had some sort of epileptic fit,
had some sort of seizure and saw the bright light. That doesn't account for his burned skin,
but they don't know what to make of it. They just know that his skin has been damaged and he's
in a lot of pain. A few days after that, his hair goes completely gray. And he starts to suffer from
memory problems as well. This affliction never leaves him. This happened in 1976, and it sticks
with him until he dies in April of 1993. His memory gets worse and worse and worse to the
point that he has the mentality of a child. By the time he passes away, he can only utter three words.
"Mom, give and fear." Now, he was elderly when this happened, so you could go, "Well, maybe it was
dementia, maybe it was some sort of Alzheimer's thing." But what made this weird? I mean, nothing
in the UFO, him and a donkey getting paralyzed, and him only saying three words, is that his skin
healed. But not just the burned parts. According to reports, as he got older and as his mentality
dropped to that of a child, his skin was repairing itself. All of the burns went away,
but so did his wrinkles. By the time he died, he was an elderly man, but he had the skin of a
healthy man in the prime of his life. So whatever this beam was, it seemed to regress him. It's not
like the mental deterioration was similar to Alzheimer's. It was reducing him to the mindset
of a child, and his skin was also being made to look younger and healthier and more supple as well.
He was already old when this happened. It would have been interesting to the aliens,
let's do a test. It'd be interesting to see what would happen if they did this to like a guy in
his 20s. Would he eventually, it must seem he would shrink into the size of a baby, but would
he have lived long enough for his skin to be baby-like? You know how they have those arms that
look like rolls, like dinner rolls at Thanksgiving? Would a 20-year-old man eventually start going,
"No, me, no, no, that's some dude's fetish. That's some diaper fetish." But you know what I mean?
Would they start to look like a baby? Not in size. Would they be like a six-foot-tall baby-skinned
person, which would be incredibly terrifying. They have like ready cheeks, big ready cheeks.
They have their hair in a little bow. They're wearing a onesie. That's a guy's fantasy too.
Dammit, why does everything have to be a kink? We'll talk about that actually in our last story.
But again, it's almost like this beam was regressing him mentally and physically
too far mentally. Like if he had had the mind of a 20-year-old and the skin of a 20-year-old,
his muscles are still super old. But who knows, maybe his organs and his muscles were repairing
as well. But was this alien beam actually the fountain of youth? Interesting. We've seen people
get shot with beams before by alien crafts and melt or have horrible burns, but I can't recall
one where it had this sort of effect on someone for such a long period of time. The guy who melted,
I mean, he died. This affliction lasted for almost 20 years for this man.
So bizarre story. If in another circumstance where it didn't regress him that young,
he would actually would have been a miracle. He would have been able to handle his farm and he's
imagined getting hit by this alien beam and actually being younger and more fit and have
your mind even more sharp. But instead he was turned into a man with the skin of a 30-year-old
and the brain of a baby. And that is nobody's fetish. I hope not.
Blue Synth, go ahead and call in that dead rabbit, Durgible. We're going to leave behind this farm
and we are headed out to England. I didn't mention the story in the intro. I didn't know if I was
going to cover it. It's actually really, really brief. Long time listeners of the show know that
I'm very, very picky with my musical taste. I despise jazz music. I know I know I know I risk
losing listeners every time I mention that. I despise jazz music. I don't like a lot of music.
I don't like stringed instruments. I can't eat while I'm listening to heavy metal. I have these
really weird hang-ups about music. I listened to 1990s to early 2000s, Gangsta Rap, and I listened
to pop music. I can listen to pop music from really the 80s to current hits today. Basically
those radio stations that your mom listens to all the time, that those radio stations are also for
me. Hits from yesterday and today. I can listen to the newest Doja Cat. I can listen to Tiffany.
I can listen to all this pop music that drives people nuts, drives people absolutely up the wall.
I can listen to it all day long. Adele, Britney Spears, Jonas Brothers, Big Time Rush, One Direction,
all that stuff. All the hits, all the great ones. So most people think my musical taste is trash,
and that's fine. I'm totally aware of that. That's the music I enjoy. I know most people don't. I
don't tell people, "Oh no, if you don't like Britney Spears, but you got to listen to this album and
then three songs off this album, you just don't like Britney Spears." That's totally fine. I totally
get it. I've listened to maybe one Rolling Stones song my entire life, and it was the one...
Most people wouldn't even consider it a Rolling Stones song, and technically it's a Mick Jagger
song. It's the one with him and David Bowie and they're dancing in the street. I remember as a
kid when they were doing it, I'm like, "This is trash. This is the Rolling Stones. This is like this...
I thought these guys were competitors to the Beatles. I'm like, "Rolling Stones, trash, dude!
What is this?" I've only heard dancing in the streets with Mick Jagger and David Bowie dancing
uncomfortably close to each other. I'm eight years old. I'm like, "What is this? What is this video?
Are they a couple? Why are their nipples touching while they're dancing?" I knew I couldn't really
make heads or tails of it. So I'm not a Rolling Stones fan. I'm not a Mick Jagger fan. I've never
really sat down and listened to a Mick Jagger or a Rolling Stones song until the other day.
And it is brilliant! Now, this isn't a music review podcast. This obviously has something to do
with paranormal conspiracy and true crime. This still, I guess, isn't Rolling Stone. This is still
Mick Jagger. This is really interesting because I saw the news articles pop up about it and then
immediately they dropped the story, which goes to say something. So there is a bit of a conspiracy
angle here. I saw these articles pop up and it was almost like no one had listened to the song.
Everyone wanted to be the first person to report that Mick Jagger had recorded a brand new song,
featuring Dave Grohl, who is dope. As much as I may talk about my crappy musical taste,
I recognize Genius when I see it and that's Dave Grohl. Like everything he touches is amazing.
So Dave Grohl and Mick Jagger made this song called "Easy Sleazy" and I saw these articles pop up and
it was, one of the articles had some of the lyrics and I was like, "What?" So I listened to it and I
expected it to be trash. I expected it to be even Dave Grohl dancing so close, their nipples
are touching, and me being like, "It's like me and eight years old all over again. What in the world
is going on?" It's a perfect song about conspiracy theories and the lockdown and the effect of the
quarantine, the COVID-19 quarantine on society and on a single person. It's brilliant. The song
is amazing. It shows the mental degradation of Mick Jagger throughout the COVID and it's
very, very anti-lockdown, which is why I think they were reporting it being like, "Mick Jagger has a
new song and they were hitting publish and when he listened to the song it is absolutely anti-lockdown."
The first verse is basically like, "I did whatever the government said and I shouldn't have."
Basically played me for a fool. I was like, "Whoa." I was listening to the song and it has a lyric
video. It'll be in the show notes and I was like, "Whoa. Okay. This is not the narrative."
And then the second verse is him just kind of going, trying to like find some sort of normalcy
in the lockdown. Like he's kind of wandering around his house and he's kind of losing his mind.
And by the third verse we get to this and I'm going to have to say it. I can't sing it for copyright
stuff, but this is how the third verse of this song starts. "Shooting the vaccine. Bill Gates is in my
bloodstream. It's mind control. The earth is flat and cold. It's never warming up. The Arctic's
turns a slush. The second coming's late. There's aliens in the deep state."
And you can easily read that as him mocking those conspiracy theories, but the fact that he's even,
and I think it can go both ways. I think on the one hand he is mocking it because there's just so
many different conspiracy theories there and we've noticed that. Some people would just believe in
every conspiracy theory put in front of them, but on the other hand the fact that he's even
giving these conspiracy theories, like saying them in a song by Mick Jagger, a rock and roll icon,
and the song itself is good. Like the instrumentation or whatever you guys used to describe music.
The fact that he's putting them in this song and he's amplifying them when people are constantly
trying to... This video may have trouble being on YouTube and Spotify because I even read those
lyrics because him saying it... I'm not saying it's big and like he's red-pilled or anything like that,
but you know what I mean? Like we have this rock and roll icon making jokes about the Bill Gates
microchip in the bloodstream, aliens in the deep state. It's very, very interesting and I think
it shows that degradation of Mick Jagger. And I think we're going to see. I remember before I said
we're coming to the Golden Age of conspiracy theory and then I called it off on that episode of
The Nashville Bombing. I'll put it in the show notes saying that now we make conspiracy theories
out of everything. I mean now I'm starting to think that we may... I think we have a whole group
of people now who have spent more time due to this lockdown, spent more time in front of their
computers than they had before. They're working from home. They were trapped in their homes. I think
we're going to have people who are discovering conspiracy theories for the first time. And
that could be like this character in Mick Jagger's song or Mick Jagger himself. He's been locked in
so much he's buying in to all these conspiracy theories. By the end of the song the character in
the song believes these things. Mick Jagger may be taking the piss out of him. But the character
in the song actually believes these things because of the mindset that he's endured, the lockdowns,
and if kind of locked in. So I think that this song is kind of a herald to that. We may actually
start to see people who are never interested in conspiracy theory become interested in conspiracy
theory. A fresh fertile ground. The question is who will win the battle? Will it be people like us
who enjoy conspiracy theories, who believe some of them, but are analytical enough to discard
ones that just don't make sense? It's that or real raw news and dark outpost. But I do enjoy
conspiracy theories. I know you guys do and apparently Mick Jagger knows enough about them to
write this lyric. So sorry Mick Jagger. Sorry if you are listening to this podcast. I apologize for
saying your music sucks. I have now heard one song that I like of yours and one song that I didn't.
So technically you're 50/50. It's not as good as Britney Spears. But it's doing okay. Blue Synth.
I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys of the Carbentercopter. We're leaving behind Mick Jagger's
recording studio. He's still in the lockdown. He's like no please let me out. I'm going insane.
See you later Mick. Write some other songs. We're never gonna let him out. We're leaving behind
this recording studio and we're headed out to Jacksonville, Illinois.
We recently covered, I think it was Tuesday's episode, a haunted university in Ohio. And while
I was researching that I found a couple other haunted universities. Most of them, I always
thought on this show when I started doing this podcast two, three years ago. It's almost three
years at this point. I always thought we'd be covering way more ghost stories. But when you
read ghost stories, they're so repetitive and it would constantly be stories. Woman with no legs
floating down the hall, orbs, rocking chairs, stuff like that. It would so repetitive. I thought we
would cover more ghost stories. I love covering ghost stories. I love reading ghost stories.
So it turns out that a lot of colleges have ghost sightings. But most of them are in that vein.
Most of them are, we hear that there's like a ghost floating down the hallway. At least
the Ohio University had an entire ghost basketball team. Like that's something I can sink my teeth
into. Illinois College was founded in 1829. So of course, there's going to be a ton of ghost
sightings. And a school that old, there's going to be a ton of ghost sightings. And the question is
how many of them are legit? How many of them are just rumors? Because that's what's going to happen.
Students coming and going, stories being passed on, altered, being made more elaborate, all of
these things are going to happen over the years. We have a classic ghost story about a woman in
love with a man. He gave her a ring. She wanted to test if it was a real diamond. So she etched
her name into a window. That story is real. That's not a ghost story, right? That's just a woman wanting
to see if a diamond is real. But she does that. And then through what this is where the story gets
more elaborate. Some people say that they were kept apart by her father. And the man was trying to
hide in this building. So he hid in the attic and nailed himself in and then starved to death.
He nailed the hammer on the outside of the door and be like, oh, there we go. Now I don't have
any way to get these nails out. And I'll start to death. Did the dad just wait on the other side of
the door for three or four weeks that he lay a siege to this attic? We don't know. There's just a
door in this attic at Illinois College that is nail sticking out of the wrong side. So a story
has evolved that a man nailed himself shut. Doesn't make any sense, but that's why they're in college
to learn. Obviously, this is the first day of college they haven't learned about nails or physics
or ghosts or really anything at this point. Another version of the story is he went off to
fight the civil war, died when this young woman found out. She threw herself out of a window from
the attic, falls to her death and dies. Why does the attic keep popping up in the story? Well,
apparently two things. One, there was a window with this girl's name etched into it. So you had
that level of proof. It's been replaced. So did that even exist? All the ghost stories that I
read about this said that at least that existed. The other stuff they go, well, you know, there's
different versions of it, but apparently for a time there was a woman's signature in this window.
But the ghost story part starts with there is a rocking chair in the attic
that is always facing out the window. That's where she sat in her rocking chair waiting for her
beloved to come back from the civil war. He's really locked in the other room with the nails
broken out. It's like, help me, help me. And she sit in there rocking back in the world's loudest
rocking chair. It's so loud she can't hear his cries for help. If you go into the attic and you
turn the rocking chair and then close the door, when you open it back up, the rocking chair will
be facing the window again. That has to be a rumor for a couple different reasons. One, if it
happened all the time, there's several ways you could test that is basically what I'm saying. One,
you would have someone in the room as you shut the door. Two, nowadays you could put a camera up
there. Three, if it's really her ghost, why would you have to shut the door? Like, why is the ghost
shy? Like, if it's a paranormal activity that happens every single time, why would you have to
shut, why would you have to close off visibility to the chair to make it move? This is what I'm,
this stuff I'm talking about, like I'm not trying to poop on these ghost stories. I find them
fascinating. But this is where we have to analyze things. When someone tells you a ghost story
like that, you go, when I first read that, I go, oh, that's kind of creepy. And then I started thinking,
why, why, why, why, why, why? And I started sounding like a little crybaby. Illinois College has a
medical school there. The legend goes that they weren't allowed to, back in the old times, I'm
sure it's different now. I don't even know if it was real back then, but the legend goes, they weren't
allowed to use human bodies in medical schools. I don't know what they were using. They'd have to
use human bodies. They didn't have plastic. They didn't have dummies. They weren't allowed to use
human bodies. So some of the more ingenious medical students became grave robbers or paid grave
robbers to bring them fresh corpses that they used in the attic of the medical school. And late at
night, they'd all get together and be like, dude, you want to come over to the attic tonight and
learn stuff? Oh yeah, it's gonna be super awesome. We're gonna cut open some people. You bring the
bruise, I'll bring the corpses. Let's go. Eventually the smell, people were walking around the medical
school. They were smelling rotting flesh. It's not a smell you want to smell anywhere, right? There's
no business where that is a good smell. Even like a mortuary, there shouldn't be rotting flesh. The
authorities are called. They raid the attic. There's a bunch of corpses up there. Does that story
make any sense? No, medical college, medical college most likely had access to corpses too. If you
had access to corpses, even if it was illegal, you think you'd preserve them, right? You want to
just let them rot. You want to be like spring break and you're all like at a party, you're like at
Fort Lauderdale and someone's like, hey dude, what'd you do with all those corpses we illegally dug
up? Huh? And it's like the hot Illinois sun they're all cooking during spring break. If you're digging
them up, you're preserving them. The story doesn't make any sense at all. But this is where we start
doing the backtracking. Apparently there used to be dorms in this building that the administration
said we can't have dorms there anymore. No students can stay there. So what happened most
likely, and we covered this on the episode on Tuesday, is there are dorms there that aren't
able to be used and people made up a story as to why. But Jason, are you just going to poo poo
ghost stories this whole episode? You say that you always want to cover them and I do. You say
that you have a hard time finding them and I do. So why are you pooping all over these ones? Well,
I'm not pooping all over. Technically I'm rotting flesh all over them, but I want to show the
analytical side. Let's get to the meat of this matter. Let's get to the rotting cadaver flesh of
this matter. On campus, this isn't, they don't give a date to the story. There's a young woman,
she's on her way to a party with her friends. They're going to go, they finally got rid of the
smell, the rotting flesh smell that has wafted over campus for weeks. It's a spring cleaning party.
Everyone can now breathe easy. She's walking with her friends and she goes, "You guys go ahead. I
gotta go back to the dorm and get something." And they're like, "Oh, okay." So they keep going and
she runs back to her dorm. She sounds like she's doing more than running. She runs back to her
dorm. She's gooning. She runs back into her dorm. Sorry if you don't listen to Monday's episode.
She runs back in her dorm and there's a spiral staircase that takes her up to the top.
She's running up the stairs. She sees the legs of someone standing up there and she kind of
hesitates. Everyone should be at the spring cleaning party. Everyone should be celebrating that it no
longer smells like human stew. And she kind of slows down and she keeps slowly walking up the
stairs and she begins to see someone dressed in all gray. Their entire body is gray. She goes up a
little bit further and now she can see its face and it has none. Now it could be blurry. Could be
like a blurry face but I'm imagining, imagine with me, grody. Like it has like a caved in. Like
it literally has no face. Like that dude from Saving Private Ryan. Not Tom Hanks. Don't imagine
Tom Hanks. Remember in Saving Private Ryan you're like Jason I've tried blocking the scene out.
Remember in Saving Private Ryan where the guy's on the radio and he's like going, "Hey, we need
more bombs." And then he flips over. You guys, somebody's never seen this movie. This makes no
sense. He flips over and he has a hole in his face. It looks like a bowl. That's him. Well imagine that
guy but but he'll all timey in gray off it. Anyways, he has no face. It doesn't say but I want to
picture this dude with like a caved in face. Not that I want to. It's just scarier. That was the
longest way to say. He has a scary caved in face. She runs down the stairs obviously. She tells her
friends. You won't believe what happened. Her friends and a bunch of other people go to the dorm.
They can't find any sign of this guy. A legend that goes around school. He's called the Gray Man.
Later on in time there's a building, a dorm called Crampedon Hall, where a guy goes to go to a party.
This is later. We don't know actually how close this was to the first sighting but he's supposed
to go to this party. He tells his friend, "Hey, I gotta go. I gotta go back to my dorm." Yeah,
like, okay, see you later. Later on though when the party's over and they go back and they go to
check on this dude, they find his dorm rooms empty. They start looking around for him. They open the
closet. He's hanging in the closet. He's dead and his hands are tied behind his back.
And they say there was no way he could have tied his own hands behind his back. I know what you
guys are thinking. Wait a second. A few years after that, this dude was supposed to hang out with his
buddies. Never showed up. This was also in Crampedon Hall actually. Supposed to show up. Never, never
did. Let's go see what Barry's up to. He's supposed to hang out with us but he's not here. This is a
lame party. We're all super lame without Barry. There's nothing going on. So they go to his dorm.
They actually find his dorm empty. They look around. They can't figure out where he could be.
And then one of them opens the closet and there is Barry. I'm making up the name Barry. His name
is actually Barry. I'm not trying to put you on blast. He's hanging upside down, naked, with his
hands behind his back. Help me, help me. Good you guys. You guys gotta help me. Get me down from here.
So they do. They're not still hanging up there to this day. New freshmen are coming in. He's like,
"Hey, I'm Barry. Welcome to Illinois University. I'm 60 years old. I've been hanging here all this
time." They let him down. They ask him, "What happened? What's going on?" He said, "A ghost did it."
He said, "A ghost did it." He said that he'd fallen asleep with the lights on. He was laying in bed,
fell asleep with the lights on. He hears a noise in his sleep. He wakes up and there's a gray man
with no face standing over his bed. Some sicko. Some sicko goes to the look. Was it all caved in
and gross? Like, "Saving Private Ryan?" He's like, "What? Let's save him Private Ryan." I don't know
what that is, but he just had no face. He didn't go in a detail either. They stared at each other
for a while and then he saw the gray man turn and walk into the closet. The friends are like,
"Wait a second. I don't care. How did you get in the closet?" He's like, "I don't know. The next thing
I know, I was naked hanging upside down with my hand tied behind my back. But I don't know. I'm
assuming it was the gray man who did it." Apparently that same night, other students said that they
woke up and the gray man was standing over their bed as well. I think these guys, both of them,
were doing an act known as autoerotic affixiation. It does happen. We actually covered that at a
college and it was in Athens, Georgia. It was another college one. I'll put it in the show notes, but
men will do it seemingly more often than women. They'll tie themselves up and they'll cut off the
blood flow to their brain and they'll masturbate. It's a very dangerous sex game. So the first
guy may have done it. It is possible to tie your hands behind your back in ways that people would
not think it was possible. The first guy may have done it. The second guy may have done it and got
turned upside down and was hanging there for a long time. And then when he heard his friends barge
into his dorm room looking for him, he's probably like, "Uh-oh. I gotta come over and excuse.
I have to fly. I'm naked hanging upside down in a closet." The only excuse he could think of was
ghost, which is not a great excuse. Luckily, he could have died. It's possible that he was
trying to commit autoerotic asphyxiation. He was saved just in the neck of time.
Everything turned out okay. He had a really lousy excuse. But here's what's been on
our conspiracy caps here. What if conspiracy cap firmly on, hold it down to your head for this one,
what if ghosts can affect you sexually? We've all heard stories about succubi and incubi. They're
demons who feed off your sexual desires and your sexual energy and basically the succubi. When you
have sex with the succubi, it's creating demons and hell, that's one of the versions of it. Lilith.
You call upon Lilith. You masturbate. It's all these sex-spilled stuff. We've covered it before on
the show here and there. I don't think we've ever done a deep dive into it. It's pretty common stuff.
But what if it's way more widespread than that? Here's my thing. Here's what I'm thinking. What if
this dude wasn't trying to commit autoerotic asphyxiation? What if the ghost was making him do
that? We always run into these stories where people, the people who die accidentally of this,
we go, "But what if that wasn't their thing? What if the ghost tricked them into trick them into
coming?" It's like the ghost is like, "Take off all your clothes. Oh, you're so fit. You're so
muscular." You're like, "Thank you, great ghost. How can you see without a face?" He's like, "I have
other ways of seeing." Then why don't you tie your hands behind your back? What if there's a spiritual
world that leads us on to do stuff we otherwise wouldn't do? What if a ghost could alter that
behavior? What if you never wanted to commit autoerotic asphyxiation? What if you never had a fetish for
armpits? What if you never ever thought about being a feeder, like feeding someone so much and watching
them get super fat? But a ghost wanted you to do that stuff. The spiritual world was influencing
you in some way. I'm not talking about demons. I'm talking about ghosts, because when we talk about
ghosts, a lot of times the lore says they have unfinished business. What if their unfinished
business is being pervert? What if you're a totally normal person and your wife brings home some
trinket she got from the thrift store? And you're like, "Great. Another statue of Brainy Smurf.
Perfect. It's totally gonna go with the rest of the Smurf collection." But that statue was owned by
a pervert. He was owned by a peeping tom. When we talk about ghosts and possessed dolls and stuff
like that, we always think about external stuff like you hear footsteps or there's a woman whispering
in your ear. But what if this ghost actually inspires perverted desires inside of you?
Where all of a sudden, for whatever reason, you start having dreams about looking in through
people's windows. That's weird. I've never had a dream like that before. But you brush it off,
right? Dreams are weird. But then you start to think about it more. You find yourself looking for
stories online, new stories about peeping tom's getting caught. You find yourself starting to
watch porn videos, upskirt videos, dressing room videos, hidden camera videos. You start to get this
need to be voyeuristic, as that little Brainy Smurf statue. This episode sponsored by Peo,
that little Brainy Smurf statue was sitting on the shelf. This ghost is influencing these thoughts
and desires that you never would have had before. Until you finally are driving through random
neighborhoods one night, trying to look through windows as you drive by, fleeting glimpses.
It's not enough. Eventually you find yourself sneaking up outside of a young woman's house
and peering in through her window when she's all alone. These thoughts, these desires were never
yours. But if you get caught, you're going to pay the price for them. Not this ghost, not this
spiritual entity that is latching onto you. And again, it's not a demon. It's not malicious. It
just wants to continue its fetish, even in death. That's conspiracy cap fully on. I have no proof
of any of that. I just find it another possible piece of this onion we call the paranormal.
Remember, this grey ghost appeared in several bedrooms that night, but only Barry ended up
tied up in the closet. Was he more susceptible to the ghost? Was he the one that fell victim to
its sick desires? Who knows. It's just creepy to think that when we look out and see people,
when they do stuff we go, "How, why would you even do that? Why would you even think about
taking such a chance?" What sort of visceral thrill is really there for just a brief moment of sexual
pleasure you're willing to risk it all? Maybe they don't have a choice. Maybe, even they don't
understand why they're making that decision. Even they can't comprehend what's going on.
There's just something next to them, something unseen, but it's there. The spirit goads them
forward. It needs the pleasures of the flesh, because it is no longer flesh. It is an immortal
spirit that will never be satisfied, no matter how perverted its victims become.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabberadio. Twitter is @deadrabberadio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true friend podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
[MUSIC]