When a young man is out on a hike, he has no idea he's about to come face to face with
a haunting event from his past.
And then we meet a single mother who's trying her best to raise her two kids.
Life is already difficult for one parent trying to do that job, but it is almost impossible
when the house you are living in is possessed by a demon.
Day on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend.
Let's go ahead and get the ball rolling here.
Let's go ahead and introduce in one of our newest Patreon supporters walking into Dead
Rabbit Command.
Give it up for DJ Blue.
Woo!
Wickedy wickedy whack!
Scratching him turntables, DJ.
His real name might be DJ.
I don't know if he's actually a disc jockey, but DJ Blue, you're going to be our captain,
our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
It really is.
Just help spread the word about this show.
That really, really, really helps out a lot.
It sucks.
Just a quick...
I am having a good day.
I really am having a good day, but I want to see something real quick because I know
other people deal with this.
I'm also like in the middle of an anxiety attack.
I'm like, "Hey, when you have an anxiety attack, your fight or flight mechanism is rewired,
right?"
And I woke up from this nap and I've not felt 100%.
I'm just...
I think, you know, there's a lot of stuff going on in my life right now.
The temperature's really hot.
I had a coffee this morning.
I really don't drink a lot of caffeine anymore, so now any caffeine can set me off.
But you know what?
Here I am, man.
I'm having an anxiety attack.
My body feels like it could shut down at any moment.
I'm like panicking and I'm still doing what I need to do.
And I wanted to share that with you because you can't let your own fears get in the way.
I mean, I have to do this, right?
I enjoy doing this podcast, but I got to get these episodes out and I got to record them
when I record them.
And here I am.
I'm sitting in here.
I'm a little panicky.
I feel aches and pains that actually don't exist or it's like a muscle soreness in my
lower right side, which makes me think I'm having a heart attack.
It's just you got to push through all the obstacles, especially the fake ones, especially
the obstacles we put in front of ourselves.
So let that be a little PSA for you guys this weekend.
Do what you need to do.
Do what you want to do.
Don't ever let fear get in the way because most of the time there's nothing to be afraid
of.
DJ Blue, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're driving all the way out to Willet, New York.
I found this story online.
It was posted by someone going under the alias Left-handed Archer.
We're going to go ahead and call this guy Aaron.
I don't think that's your real name.
Hopefully it's not.
If it is, it's just a guess.
Again, I'm just giving you a name that's a little bit easier than Left-handed Archer.
Aaron is hiking through Redbrook State Forest in Willet, New York.
He provided a Google map when he was talking about this story like a satellite view and
just lush trees.
It's not straight up in the middle of nowhere, but it's also not across the street from a
Wendy's.
It is a hike.
That's where Aaron is walking through right now.
As he's walking through the forest enjoying nature, seeing the beauty of the world all
around him, he stumbles across the cabin in the woods.
It's partially collapsed.
It's sitting there.
The elements have destroyed most of this cabin over the decades since it's been built.
But even though it's weathered, even though it's been falling apart, he immediately recognizes
it.
Memories begin to flood back into his head.
He's been here before.
Aaron tells this story.
He goes back in 1997.
I was between the ages of three and four years old.
I was in that little age group.
And I was kidnapped.
I was kidnapped at gunpoint by a man and a woman.
And they took me to this cabin.
They took me to this cabin and I was sexually molested.
And then they let me go.
And when I got home, I told my parents what happened.
They didn't even know I was missing.
They had no idea that I was gone.
Especially no idea I was kidnapped.
And they didn't believe me.
They thought I made the story up.
So nobody contacted the police.
I was three, right?
I don't know how to contact the police.
I don't know how this stuff happens.
I go home and tell my parents what happened.
They totally don't believe me.
They don't even believe that I'm missing.
There's never been any police investigation done on this place.
So life goes on.
But as I'm hiking through the woods just recently, I came across that cabin again and I realized
I should look into this.
Because let's say he was three years old in 1997.
You're like, great.
Here's a Jason Does Math segment.
This is how I do math.
He'd be six in the year 2000 and it's the year 2020.
He'd be 28 years old now.
So now he does know how to call the police.
Now he knows how things work.
And he's actually, he was posting this on the subreddit RBI, which is Reddit Bureau of
Investigations.
They try to solve mysteries and stuff like that.
I have this one noted and I have an archive of it.
They usually take stuff like this down.
This subreddit is kind of lame.
Anything that involves anything, basically anything that involves anything other than
I have an NES cartridge, but the label's peeled off.
What is it?
Other than that, and that stupid California raisins, ARG that's going on, they delete
anything most of the time that's police related.
But it is an interesting subreddit to take a look at.
He says, this happened to me and he provided the Google Earth coordinate.
So I went ahead and pulled those up and sure enough, you see this little collapsed structure
in the woods.
This is an interesting story, obviously, on a couple of different levels.
Let's start taking it apart.
First off, absolutely tragic incident, right?
On multiple levels.
He was kidnapped.
He was sexually molested.
And then his parents didn't believe him.
That's all three of those things in and of themselves.
Well, your parents not believing you if like, you're like, no, I didn't break the vase.
That's okay.
But your parents not believing you about something serious in and of itself is awful, being kidnapped
is in and of itself at awful.
They took him to the Waffle House and dropped him back off.
That's horrible.
And then obviously the third, the sexual assault is the worst, but having all three of them
happening.
Interesting story.
It's a true crime story.
And there's so many ways we can look at this.
I'm trying to figure out looking at this map, like was he, because there's some information
missing too, right?
I'm sure some of you guys are like, huh?
Where was he kidnapped from?
Was he kidnapped from his house?
Was he walking down the road?
Even the road seemed a little out of the way.
I didn't see a neighborhood in there.
So was he kidnapped from his house?
Was he kidnapped from the road?
He doesn't say that he remembered the people.
He actually looking back, he goes, those people were incredibly dangerous.
They kidnapped me at gunpoint and took me out to this cabin.
And then he said there was a light bulb on in the cabin.
So there was utilities out there.
Was I the only one?
Did they do this to multiple children?
Did the other children just disappear?
Or were they also not noticed that they were missing?
But it's just creepy on that level.
Like he had this thing happen to him, which would be a major news story if the police were
involved, if the parents believe him.
He goes, listen, I didn't have the best family life.
I was looking through his posting history.
That wasn't the first time that happened either.
He does mention that a female family member had also sexually abused him.
And he was trying to see if he could figure out who owned the cabin.
But by now, the deeds had been transferred.
People are actually looking into this, you know, like land ownership and deeds were transferred
in and out.
So just because someone owned it now, and it doesn't seem to be inhabited, it seems like
it's empty.
I mean, obviously there's not a lot of people living in an house with a collapsed roof.
And here you have this 28 year old man.
You know, he's trying to, I think at this point, find out more about the case to see,
you know, has this, these people need to be stopped.
Obviously, if there are people driving around and they're kidnapping children at gunpoint,
it's not the first time.
And it wasn't the last, you know, like did these people do other things to other people?
Are they still out there?
One of the reasons why I like doing this show is to depress you, not to just tell creepy
stories on Fridays.
Especially true crime.
And the reason why I go out of my way to find true crime that people haven't heard of is
because stuff like this, these are the events that happen daily all across America, all
across the world.
But the Ted Bundy's and the Jeffrey Dahmers and the Laurie Valos, you know, these big
true crime cases, those are the outliers.
And that's why they're covered because they're so weird.
But this type of stuff happens all the time.
And a lot of times people don't talk about it because the family doesn't believe the
victim or because the victim doesn't say anything.
You know, at that point, it's normalized to them that it might not have been the first
time that something happens to a kid who's seven, eight, and they get grabbed by some
strangers and taken to the sawmill and stuff happens to them and then they get dropped back
off.
That's not the first time I've had family members touching me.
I'm not even going to re...it's just part of being a kid.
And then they go on with their life.
It's disturbing.
I'm not even talking about it out loud.
I realize actually how disturbing it is.
But these are the true crimes that happen all the time.
Creepy, creepy story and a mystery too.
Like he doesn't know who these people are.
What happened to them?
Are they still out there?
Are they still doing this?
All he knows is that the shack is still there.
The fact that he was able to find the shack and I don't think he was out there looking
for it.
I think he was just hiking through the area and saw the shack.
Absolutely creepy, disturbing mystery.
Are these people still out there?
Did they do it multiple times?
I would say yes.
They probably did this multiple times.
How many other young children did they abduct and take to this cabin or any other cabin?
Creepy, terrifying, true crime story.
I probably would not have told it on a Friday had I thought it through how creepy it actually
was.
But DJ Blue, let's go ahead and give you the keys to the carpenter copter.
We are leaving behind Will It New York?
Not a moment too soon.
We are headed all the way out to suburban America.
The ride is very long and very silent.
DJ Blue, I was going to have him do yesterday's episode.
I go, "Nah, yesterday's episode was too gross."
And then he's like, "Oh, thanks, Jason.
That story is absolutely terrifying.
Keep flying us in this carpenter copter, DJ Blue.
We are headed out to this small house in suburban America."
We don't know where this takes place, honestly.
We don't know where this takes place.
I say suburban America, but the house that this family is living in is like 200 years
old.
It's actually not a set of tract housing somewhere in Anaheim, California.
It may be like a nice big house on the East Coast.
200-year-old house.
We're back in the year 2013.
That's where this saga begins.
And we're going to meet this woman.
We're going to go ahead and call her Monica.
She did not give her name.
Monica's a single mother and she is moving into this house with her two children and
her shih tzu.
Little puppy.
We will call Barkley.
Now she knows she's buying an old house and she said when she was looking at the house
and when she was visiting the house, she could tell the house was haunted.
She could tell the house had this sort of energy to it.
And she actually told her kids, "Listen, listen, I know this is your first night in this spooky
icky house and it's haunted, but just don't give it any energy.
Don't think about it.
Don't think about that lingering death glare staring at you from underneath the bed.
When you're taking a shower, don't think about hands pressing up against the shower curtains.
Don't think about any of that stuff.
Just ignore it.
Don't give it any energy."
Kids are like, "Okay, Ma."
And that's what she kind of did, right?
She's just like, "Okay, it's haunted.
I got a bigger fish to fry.
I'm not going to think about it."
And then obviously, because we're talking about this on a paranormal podcast, things
escalate.
At one point, you know, she's, it's just her in the house.
Her kids are staying with their grandparents and they're like only like a mile or two away.
So she can work on the house.
At this point, she was tearing off the old paneling to the house and kind of fixing it
up.
And she said, "She's tearing off the paneling and it's hard work.
Very physical.
She's exhausted.
She's up calling in at night and her and Barkley go to bed.
So she's laying in the bed and the little shitsue is sleeping at her feet."
And Monica says at around 3.15, she remembers the time at around 3.15, she hears Barkley
yell.
She actually said, that actually sounded like a happy yelp.
She said it sounded like somebody had kicked Barkley.
Like it wasn't a happy one.
It was a, "Oh, Barkley is in pain."
It wakes Monica up.
She wakes up and she's trying to figure out what's going on while her little dog's yelping.
And she said, "I sat up in bed and then my entire body froze in place."
She said, "As I sat up, it was like I got locked into that sitting up position."
And she goes, "The angle that my body was at, you wouldn't need to have a full on ab
workout.
Suzanne Summers came to your house every day and worked out your abs type of physical fitness."
She goes, "When I came up into that position and I locked, she said it was extremely uncomfortable
and she couldn't figure out how she stayed like that for so long.
She sat up and then she froze."
And she goes, "The freezing wasn't just my body.
I also couldn't scream.
Like I was in immediate shock that this was happening to me and I couldn't scream and
I was locked into this very uncomfortable sitting up position almost like a mid crunch.
And then she felt something reach in and grab onto her heart.
She said my chest was just wracked with wave after wave of pain as something is just squeezing
my heart and my tummy.
My abs.
I was in this awkward position.
My entire midsection was cramping up and hurting so bad in her chest was just getting crushed
and she's in this position and she gets a thought in her head.
You have two choices Monica.
Choose to live or choose to die."
And she said because she's in so much pain, this is interesting, this is interesting,
because she's in so much pain, she chose to die.
And right when she made that decision, her body completely relaxes.
She falls backwards onto the bed.
This entire sensation is done.
She reaches over, she turns on the light, she grabs her car keys, she grabs her dog and
that's when she realized that both her and Barkley had both wet the bed.
Now when I'm reading that I'm thinking, I'm reading this in order the first time I read
this.
I go, "Oh man, it sounds like she was having a seizure or a heart attack."
But as the story progresses, as the story progresses, that's not the story.
That's not the end of the story.
As the story progresses, at first you go, "Because I am skeptical of everything, but I believe
in ghosts and all this stuff."
We've talked about that on the show before.
But when I'm reading it, it sounds like she might have had a mild heart attack or a stroke.
Maybe they'll reveal that later in the story.
They don't.
It was a ghost.
But then the idea of her choosing to die, we've covered a ton of stories.
So many stories, I don't even think I can put them in the show notes, of people being
faced with these decisions, these impossible odds, and they choose to live.
And then something happens, they have a near-death experience.
They meet an alien or a ghost or something like that, guardian angel.
Monica chose to die, even though she had two children, she loved very much.
The pain was just too unbearable.
And she chose to die.
And the phenomenon ended.
That event ended.
Or did it?
Was her decision that night an aggravating factor for what happens going forward?
I couldn't say that was the decision that I would make, right?
I'm a big baby when it comes to pain.
And then she peed the bed, which isn't demonic, but it's kind of funny.
It's kind of funny.
She goes on to say, she goes, "Listen, life is not easy.
It's not easy for anyone.
It's not easy for a single parent or two children.
But this house has made it so much worse."
And she goes, "I'm a homebody.
I love staying at home.
That's where I relax.
That's where I recharge.
But not here.
My entire life, I've been a homebody.
I'd rather sit at home watching television or reading a good book than going out.
My entire life, I was like that.
But not in this home.
Not in my home.
And so she finds it odd that when she leaves, let's say she goes away for a weekend.
She's on this little vacation.
She feels amazing.
She feels so good about life.
She feels physically healthy.
She feels mentally healthy.
But when she comes home, she describes it as an unending cycle of depression.
Something is wrong with this house.
And she believes that this house has a ghost in it.
And she starts looking for spiritual answers, which is a great place to start and usually
a great place to finish if it's just something small.
She goes, "I pray.
I prayed in every room.
I was praying for deliverance from this thing."
She said that she saged the place.
She said she brought in a priest to bless the place.
Nothing helped.
The place still was oppressive.
She could feel this presence in her house, in the house of her and her family.
It's like putting a thumb on her.
I'd say more than that.
Just washing her down with a boot into the mud.
She says that when she's alone in the house, which I don't know why you would be, but
again, she kind of talks about that.
She goes, "I can't afford to move."
The story starts in 2013.
I'm telling it in 2022.
She's still there.
She's still trapped.
She goes, "When I'm home alone, because I can't force my children to be there all the time."
She goes, "I will hear someone call my name."
And she says the way that it says it is desperate.
It's not, "Yo, Monica.
Hey, what's up?"
It's, "Monica.
Monica."
Monica.
(music)