There is a man in the world right now who has the power to save us all
All he needs to do is see some rhino balls first
And then we take a look at a bizarre story that's a crossroad between outer space and
Inner souls is it possible that aliens?
cause ghost sightings today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too
I've actually developed Insomnia over the past two weeks
I'm recording this episode way late at night and recording this episode about one in the morning
I have a bottle of Nyquil that I'm going to take a shot from the second I'm done
Actually, I'm taking it halfway through the podcast because that way you know I'm ready to sleep and ready to like curl up like a little
Baby to sleep right when it's over. We'll see if I start to slur my words
You know that I've hit the Nyquil. We actually got a lot of stuff to talk about today. First off
Let's take a look at this artwork we have for Fan Art Friday. This was drawn by Church Going Mules
I love this. This is awesome. Thank you very very much for sending me this artwork and letting me use it as well
Then we have a very special patreon supporter today because it's a Christmas present
So in comes we're clapping already in comes this giant package
So I'll wrapped up and stuff like a normal Christmas present and out of the Christmas present hops Anthony
Detorfino we're clapping he's still in the box. He's like I'm not popping out until you pronounce my name correctly
Anthony go and pop out of that box jumping out. This is a Christmas present from your brother Nicholas
Now we'll give Nicholas a chance because that's pretty awesome to do this Christmas present
We'll give him a chance to fly the carbonicopter in a later episode, but this is all Anthony's episode
He's gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you get to buy the patreon totally understand just helps for the word about the show
That really really helps out a lot dress yourself up as a giant present and then stand outside and go boo
Listen to dead rabbitio. That is a I read that I read that on how to win friends and influence people
It's a good marketing technique Anthony. Let's go ahead and put you inside of the dead rabbit dirgeable
We're gonna take a little flight. We are headed out to a secret military base some of you know as Mon talk
Dirgeable is flying over the United States. We're headed out to Long Island a lot of people have requested
I talk about Mon talk over the years. I'm gonna go through a list real quick
We have Tim Porrell, Stefan, Grey of PTA, John Karras, Calvin Walmer, Jeff D. Padra
They've been wanting me to cover this stuff
Really since the beginning of the show and I got to give a special tip of the hat to Alex F on YouTube
Because again like maybe a year and a half ago
He said you got to do an episode on the Mon talk guys. They actually apparently I wasn't able to find any proof
But Alex F said that they were trying to sue the makers of stranger things because stranger things was based on their real life
So I was intrigued and I started looking into it and I go at
I don't know if I talk about a homeless man throwing his poop around McDonald's and he just kind of fell to the wayside
It was a lot of stuff where it's just basically some guys wrote a book and
It's a bunch of nonsense a bunch of nonsense in this book, but what's interesting
So thank you Alex for doing that. Sorry you got preempted by a hobo throwing poop story
But recently episode 543 I did here on Dead Rabbit Radio madness murder and UFO disclosure
It was about a guy named John Ford
Who really believed that UFOs are flying around Long Island and he ended up threatening to
Irradiate a couple of Republic local Republicans and he's still in prison to this day
That story happened back in like 2001 or something like that that story I got from an article written by a journalist named Michael Colton
He's also a writer on the penguins of Madagascar, so that's pretty
That's no for that's no for than anything he'd wrote in the newspaper. I love that show Michael Colton
I quoted him in this episode because I was talking about how it used to be
How the media portrayed people who had UFO or paranormal events and he had this great passage
About this guy named Preston Nichols who was
Contemporary of John Ford hung out with the dude and Preston Nichols is described as portly and absent-minded
They're talking about how cluttered and small his house is he doesn't live in a cluttered big house
He lives in a cluttered small house my favorite line in the article quote in his living room while his fat dog snores
Nichols cues up a video. I just love I was like dude you're even insulting this guy's dog
The dog's not researching UFOs. I actually reached out to Michael Colton and I said hey, I'm doing this podcast
I don't know why I reach out to him because usually I don't I said hey
I'm doing this whole podcast basically on this one article. He wrote I had a follow-up question
I think I had a follow-up question
We started talking about Preston Nichols
He goes yeah, I wonder what Preston Nichols is up to nowadays and I go
I don't know but I will look into it and I did and
He is the guy who's a big part of the Montauk project
So that was kind of an interesting way to snake back around so hobo throwing poop stories. They're on hold for today
They're on hold for today because we got this nice little windy road to go down
So Anthony after that nice little preamble you are gonna drive us up to Montauk Air Force Base on Long Island
And I you see those guards standing there
You see those military guards with like their barrier and stuff those two little things that come down run it and things like what I'm
Like just run run right through it
Smashes through the gate the guards are opening fire on us. It's okay. I trust Anthony to dodge the bullets in the car
We eventually are hiding he didn't do a good job the car got shot to pieces
So now we're hiding in a dumpster waiting for the red alert to go down
The reason why we're here is because according to Preston Nichols, this is where all of the like psychic testing goes
You ever hear of a super soldier? Well, they exist
If you haven't they totally exist. I don't know why it falls like that. They totally exist
They're trained at Montauk Air Force Base. So we're find our way into the actual base
We see a bunch of people sitting in like chairs and there's these things on their head
I know super descriptive right theater of the mind. They're like
Unlike pink electricity shooting out and stuff like that scientists are taking notes
They're like this for my daughter sweet 16. It's adorable
Pink sparkles everywhere what they do here is they basically have three big things
Three big tourist attractions to Montauk Air Force Base one
Psychic testing and they do that by kidnapping children and hobos
Taking them to the facility and running all these tests on them. That's a weird combination
People hate to be in the cell. You're like, oh man, what did I have to be with all the hobos?
You see all the kids in the other cell they're having a dance party. You're like, oh man
All I get to do is eat beans. But anyways, you have the hobo people you have the hobos
I haven't drank in the night cool yet
You have the hobos and you have these kids all in cells and their psychic powers are being unleashed
Can you think of a worse person to give psychic powers to than a homeless man?
That's the worst person. They're already so downtrodden
Don't train hobos to have psychic powers, but they do I guess they know more than I do
They also they probably know that the hobos aren't gonna go crazy
Because that's only one thing to do the other thing they do is they can view time
I mean you can view time too. You're you're viewing time right now as you exist
But they can look forward and backward in time
They built like this time tunnel that they can just look through I totally wish we could like save those guys and on normandy
They're all and they're just watching it like this is this is directors got to save Brian Ryan. This is awesome
They realize they can view time back and forth, but that's
History book basically right? I mean you get to see in the future
But who cares if you can view the past big whoop so then the other thing they're known for is they've actually built
interdimensional time travel
Portals so Anthony's leading the way pushing him in front of the group. He's like oh man come on
I want to make it till Christmas or like keep going keep going. He takes us into this massive facility and we see this device
And it is actually a time machine an interdimensional time machine
So a lot of times you might not have known this guys
I know you guys are pretty up on your history because you guys are always correcting me when I make mistakes
But did you know that originally Hitler won the war the World War two Hitler wanted?
But here's what happened the Montauk people built a time machine and they began delivering
Supplies into the past which allowed the allies to win. Did you know that?
Well because according to these guys it happened also
They went back Montauk personnel went back and met Jesus Christ
They didn't they didn't save him. They they they they famously did not save him and let me say this
They're making all this stuff. I mean they they are presenting this as what's known as soft facts
There's a book called the Montauk project
Experiments in time and in the book apparently I haven't read the book, but I was reading reviews on it
I'm sure people go how can you talk trash about a book you haven't read well
Do it anyways you can't talk trash about my podcast until you've listened to every episode as that all 576 of them
You have soft facts so it's based and even like when I was doing some research on this
They say they never really come out and say that the story is true
But they never come out and say that the story is false again
I'm taking other sources for that information
So it's really easy to cloud a bunch of minds with that and speaking of someone who does believe in that story Anthony
Let's hop in the Jason Jalopy. We cut Anthony. Let's hop in the wait. What what vehicle did we take first?
Oh my god, I'm losing my mind
Did we take the dead rabbit dirgeable and then he just was driving a car have I do the episode
I'm sorry. I've not taken the night wheel yet. I'm just really really tired Anthony
We are going to give you the keys to the carpenter copter right now
We're doing it early or you have any keys to the carpenter copter
You are going to fly us out out of this military base. The red alert has been resounded again
We are going to the home of one Andy
Perot
Carbenter copter is flying away from this base. We're actually going to come back to this space
But first off we're gonna meet a young man named Andy Perot
Now I got most of this information from an interview that Andy did with Eve Lorgan writing for unknown magazine
Now Andy did not have a simple life. He was very early
Considered to be a prime candidate for the super secret totally real real real
Soldier program we see Andy. He's just like outside. He's like riding his bicycle and stuff like that
There's a stark fan coming up alongside of him and he sees like their logo. It's just like it's just a guy pointing at Andy
That's the logo and they designed it and they're they have a time machine
So they knew exactly how to design the logo to point at him as he's riding down the street
They grab him they grab Andy and they begin this psychological psychic torture
And part of the thing is this is really common in MK ultra theory which MK ultra is real but as MK ultra
Conspiracy theory grew you start to get this stuff kind of be cemented in what you do is you take someone and you deliver so much
Logical and physical trauma it causes the brain to split into multiple personalities and then the handler the government handler
I'm revealing too much. I'm revealing too much
The government handler will then choose one of those alternate personalities to encode
Information into and then they put your brain back together because that works
I mean why not and then you go about life
You don't know you are a super soldier or a sex kitten
Basically, you're one of the two you're either super soldier. Those are usually men sex kittens are usually women none of this stuff is true
I'm just stating how the conspiracy theory set up. That's why you'll see
Britney Spears and Taylor Swift and Lady Gaga and Katy Perry every so often they'll dress up as a cat
They don't every so often they'll wear
Here's but they don't always wet dress them and cats but a lot of times if you see them in any leopard print
Oh, that's the sex kitten programming. You see that all the time
But anyways, that's just in a nutshell. That's years of research that I've done on this stuff MK ultra mind control
This was happening to Andy. He said that they were doing all sorts of psychological kung fu on his brain
They're also sticking needles in his genitals
That's a little that's a little overboard government, right? You can split my mind
Just keep the keep the needles away from my crotch. He said, you know, one of the other things they did
You know, casually. He's like, hey, yeah, he's talking to you as much a needle sticking out of his crotch
You're like, whoa Andy, can you take care of that? He's like, oh, yeah, he puts on a bathrobe
another thing they did was they would put him in a
drum of water like a big old box of water and seal it shut and he would drown and
Then he would create a psychic bubble around him and then come back to life
You know, you know like you learned like you learned when you were in high school
They would drown him and then he would come back to life and they did it quite a few times
You might want to try healing
Healing those needles out of his genitals first before he does the drowning thing
But anyways, they also had this this is where his training really begins that everyone goes through that. It's like basic
Then the military goes, you know, this guy'd make a perfect super soldier
So what we're gonna do with him is we are going to have him
Jump
Training all those needles goes to give him the power to jump and he said what they do was they put a blindfold on him
They go climb up this tiny step ladder and then jump off the step ladder
So he'd climb up the step ladder and go we I don't know if he said we I would say we
But he goes I kept doing this and then eventually I jumped off this ladder
And then I turned around and it took my blindfold off because apparently I can do that at this point
Apparently I can do this. I've gained enough trust though. It was a super tall ladder
But he thought he was just jumping a foot down a step ladder
So they're doing this training forever and he said he gave him the ability
All this training all this manpower all of these pins and genitals
Gave him the ability to jump out of a plane and land without a parachute
Which is cool, but it's not a superpower, but he can do it
He can jump out of a plane forget wind resistance
Forget how they trained that we're like here you're gonna climb up on this ladder
You're like what I can't hear you the jet engine super ladder like you're on a tiny ladder
The winds super blown in his face is like well, there's a lot of bugs up here getting caught in my teeth jumping off a ladder
That is his superpower. He also you know, that's pretty lame, but he also says he can curl
545 pounds. That's impressive. I don't know if they're tiny ladders
Because every day they gave me a little step stool and I just moved it up and down and then eventually I realized I was holding
545 pounds maybe maybe they trained him doing that maybe it's steroids
We don't know he does say that in this particular program at Montauk that people are trained time
He says usually the women are trained to be sex kittens, but the men could be trained as couriers
assassins
Super soldiers or psychic killers
I
Read that and I go I
Would be so disappointed if someone stuck needles in my groin and I just became a courier
They're like you you go ahead go deliver this stuff. You see a bunch of other people like floating around using psychic powers
Assassinating shadows. They're so silent and you're like on your post mates by
Needles and you're crotch are like all this hurts everyone's laughing at you
The psychic's projecting his laughter right into your brain
He is one of the guys who actually stopped Hitler's
Conquest of Earth you I don't know why I'm making fun of Andy
We actually owe this man a debt of gratitude because back in time Andy was dressed up as a soldier
Delivering future technology to the allies now you wonder why we didn't see any like drones during World War two or any
Advanced weapons platform what they had to do is very very ingenious. I wish I had made this up
I wish I had made this detail up. They had to take modern technology
But build it as if it was built to the 1940s using material from the 1940s and then taking that stuff back in time
So you're not disrupting the timeline. You're totally altering the outcome of a war sure, but you're not
Disrupting the timeline. They're not walking around iPhones. There's a bridge too far to do that
So he after all of his training is a courier. He's not even the psychic assassin. He can jump out of planes and go ta-da
Here's your package mr. Roosevelt. How do I get back in the plane? I don't know but so he's a courier
He got all those needles for nothing. He also met aliens
He's been on alien ships and he says the aliens plan is to take our women and children use them for experimentation
Hybrids they want to create alien hybrids on earth this super soldier Andy actually has an experience
He was in an alien facility and he says this he's walking through the facility couple grays on each side
He's like hey, I heard you guys have a UFO. You think I could jump out of it and they're like we wish you would we totally wish you would
He's walking through this facility
And he says that he sees women and children behind chicken wire sobbing begging him for help
He doesn't do anything. He doesn't not do anything to save these people at all
He's just like what you must be talking to the other super soldier in this room not me
What type of hero is crafting his story and I was like hey biographer
Don't miss out the time when I left all those women and children captive in an alien facility
The biographer is like what so how does he know all this stuff? He had all these memories suppressed
He didn't know he was able to fall long distances in a single bound. He wasn't aware of this stuff until
1996 he's in Atlanta, Georgia. We've been in Georgia a lot this week. He's in Atlanta, Georgia
We walk into this cool bowling alley. It's 1996
The game is called the game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year
It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year. It's a game of the year.
And standing next to us is Andy Perrow and his roommate and they're bowling as well and Andy Perrow starts the bowl and he kind of freezes and super dangerous the ball almost falls on his feet and he just freezes and he goes
Oh my god
roommates like what there's a billboard that says
Look at this up. See it's actually real. It's a billboard that says bowl with rhino balls
And he's like have no he's having a flashback. He's gonna need a second to scratch
Oh, I wish I didn't have that part of the flashback. He's remembering given supplies to to
Whoever that guy was over there. What was that old man who helped to win World War two?
You have the big nose. What was his name?
What's Winston Churchill Winston Churchill? He's given supplies to Winston Churchill tip of the hat
He's going through all the stuff. He's showing off ladders. He's wondering why he always had that ladder fetish at home Depot
He remembers when he sees bowl with rhino balls
He has a flashback that when he was doing this military training his nickname was rhino
Who wouldn't want a nickname like rhino? His name was rhino in the military and he turns to his roommate. He goes
I'm rhino
They called me rhino and
The roommate according to Andy goes what no no one ever called you rhino. Why would you say rhino?
Why would you say rhino and Andy realized that this wasn't his roommate?
What was his room? He does pay after rent, but he was also a handler for this organization
Like they had kept an eye on him over the years. I'm gonna tell you right now
We're not gonna have time for the ghosts the do aliens cause ghost sightings
We're gonna have to say that to next week because I just looked over at my notes and I realized something
It gave me a little flashback
He says in a story he said it early on but I kind of spaced on it
He kept saying we talked about this on a recent episode
That's why I want to give it a little bit of time to breathe
We talked about this conspiracy theory that the Nazis this guy was leaving yellow notes all over New York
Basically saying the same theory that the Nazi
command and control
operation when they when World War two ended they didn't just you know go
I'm gonna go back to start making pretzels and stuff like that
You did have project paperclip where we were bringing over Nazi scientists to work on a rocket program
but this theory is that the Nazis actually
infiltrated every part of
US government and really world government the Nazis now run the world is this conspiracy theory and I was just looking over at
My notes here and it said I'd written it down explicitly this time that his Nazi
Handlers were still keeping track on him through his roommates
So in his story Nazis have conquered the planet, but they're doing it in a very hail Hydra kind of way
Why would the Nazis go back in time to help the Allies win World War two?
It's a really interesting. I I'm
I read an article on this I took notes on this
I read a couple other articles on it and I haven't looked at it until I'm reading it to you
So a very casual viewer to this narrative, but if you're crafting this over the years
I don't get how you can miss such an integral part of the mythology now
I'm sure there may be an answer that oh well the Nazis really wanted to lose World War two so they could do this but if they had
The technology to just time travel they could have just done everything right in the first place
So it doesn't make sense if you're crafting your own
Story if you're making it up, which I do believe he's making it up. How could you make such a fatal flaw?
Again, there may be some book that he's selling. I find it odd that it wasn't in this main interview
He may it will actually is selling a book. We'll get to that in a second
We'll get into that in a second
But he says that his Nazi handlers helped him win World War two for the Allies weird and
Equally weird equally weird they erased his memory gave him a roommate who knew his memory knew his name was Rhino
And now this roommate's job was to make sure that
Nobody called him Rhino again. You can't watch Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles can't watch Animal Planet
There's only two places. I know rhinos are at so he has to start, you know kind of like
Maneuvering around his roommate is very very tense next couple months until the lease was up
His roommates just standing silently over him while he's sleeping
Roo mate has his finger to his ear going no boss no movement. He's still just sleeping
He doesn't suspect a thing Rhino is down and Andy's laying there. He's like oh man. This is gonna suck
He does say that over time he starts remembering more and more of his past
So he starts to put this narrative together about what happened
But his roommate was actively working against the worst roommate in the world, right?
He would write notes to remind himself because he kept forgetting this stuff
He kept forgetting his his made of stuff. He's like oh, where was I at? He starts to forget his head cannon
So he starts writing notes. He's like oh dude remember the ladders remember the ladders
That's not puzzling at all and he'd hide the note and then he would get brainwashed again
His roommate apparently was dr.
Mindbender could brainwash him and then he'd wake up and be like oh what a beautiful day
He'd be walking around he sees a rhino walking on the street doesn't even think about it
He's a ladder
Which is less exciting than a rhino walking down the street, but he still doesn't acknowledge it
But then he finds a slip of paper in his sock drawer and it says remember the ladders
It starts freaking again every time he reads a note he gets the needles in his crotch again
He's like no need to see he leaves a note. This is stop reading notes. He looks at it. He's like
Anyways, he gets out from his lease. He gets out from underneath the thumb of his roommate and in 1998
He goes public with his story and that's how he's being interviewed by this woman
He was introduced by Preston Nichols
At this big convention weird con in 98 come on down with your craziest conspiracies guys
It's organized by the CIA. You know have so much fun
Preston Nichols brings Andy Perrow on because Andy's basically telling the same story. He was being trained at Montauk
You have this guy Andy Perrow coming publicly and saying yeah, all this stuff happened all this stuff happened the whole time
Preston Nichols is just counting money in the corner. He's like keep it coming kid
He's a sucker boy in every minute people are just throwing cash in him
Andy Perrow tells this story and a book has been written about him. He hasn't written it himself
Because he kept losing it. He kept getting brainwashed after through the sentence. He's like, uh, this book is called Illuminati
Aliens and the Nazis
the true and untold story of Illuminati mind control survivor Andy Perrow
This book though in some sort of cosmic joke
I don't know if this is a pseudonym
Or if this is an author's actual name if it is get a pseudonym because when I saw it I chuckled
I'm not gonna say a laugh out loud. It's building up. I had a slight chuckle and then I read the reviews and quite a few
Reviewers were like, what's up with this guy's name? His name is kin
hardly read
That has to be a joke
Because obviously you think can't hardly read
kin hardly read kin hardly read
As two books are written two books one a totally true story of a man whose roommate was a nazi
Who went back in time and delivered future technology disguises old timey junk to Winston Churchill
Got a bunch of needles in his crotch, but haven't we all this book this true book was written by kin hardly read and kin hardly's other book
Is a three minute book. I didn't know books had time
So you have to finish it before then your ipad's heating up. It is a three minute guide
called free bitcoin earning
Earn unlimited bitcoin for free
I do not recommend reading that. I just think by purchasing that book your computer becomes infested with dark web viruses
Unlimited bitcoin for free if you are interested if you have three minutes to spare you can check out kin hardly reads book
Um whatever advice he gives it's like step number one rip off the russian mafia
If you happen to live in Moscow kicking a random dude's door most likely has some sort of bitcoin mining operation illegally
Whatever the advice is in the book. I recommend not not doing it because there is no free unlimited bitcoin
However, I guess if you're already tied into the Illuminati nazi mind control paradigm
Maybe they've figured out a way to get bitcoin for free
Originally, this was just supposed to be like a 15 minute story, but I really got carried away
I love how this mythology is not only growing in the real world
But it's growing on the show like we've had this arc
It was neat to see this little evolution of a story over the course for a year and a half
So I really appreciate everyone who recommended Montectomy
Obviously michael colton for writing that article
Also led me down this path as well find all that stuff very fascinating
I think this is a great story to end friday on even though I had planned to do another story
I think this is a great story to end friday on because let's go back to how it started
John Ford believed all this stuff as well in the story that michael colton wrote
John Ford is the main subject matter and Preston Nichols is just some shlubby dude
He's kind of walking to the background going hey boss, would you hear about all that time travel?
And then john ford lets his delusions get the best of him
And ends up committing a crime
Attempted murder and he's in prison for the rest of his life. He's like has no competency hearings
It's really fascinating episode. I recommend checking it out or you can read michael colton's article
But he believed it so much that he
Went too far
And ended up ruining his life
And then you have Preston Nichols and I think this is the more savvy way to do it is he was the
secondary character in that article but watching that happen to john ford
I think a lightbulb popped up a sci-fi lightbulb popped up in Preston Nichols head
I can have the best of both worlds
I can have this belief system and have these ideas of time travel and things like that and at the same time
Make a lot of money
And not being not being prison. That's just the third thing. That's the third thing
And I think he saw what happened to his friend and he goes he larked too hard. He believed the bs
He believed the bs too much
So the point that he thought the government was out to get him
Preston Nichols is writing books and going and they might be true
And he's telling these crazy stories of time travel one of the stories he mentioned
I forgot to say this is that I should I mean this should have been the headline for the episode
One of the stories Preston Nichols says is during one of these time travel interdimensional experiments
A monster hopped out of the vortex and began eating scientists until he was finally shot to death by us troops
That's how crazy this episode's been that I forgot that
And I think that's where the whole strange of things
Allegations come from if those are true again, alex f i'm not saying alex f is a liar, but I just couldn't back it up
I don't want Preston Nichols to sense some interdimensional creature after me being like I never said that there is no lesson
I don't believe Preston Nichols
Believes the story of Montauk. I think he probably picked and choose. There's probably he probably does believe in aliens
The theory of time travel. He does say that he saw a videocassette of himself
Time traveling so I definitely know he believes in time travel
But as he's weaved this story together, I think there's a lot of fiction thrown in there
It makes it more spicy and he's inspiring these other people Andy Perot may know what he's saying is false
Or he may know what he's saying is true
And obviously my opinion on it has just been put forth in the past 30 minutes or however long this episode is going to be
But you can do the story wrong you can play out your role too much as the paranoid
investigator and end up acting out
being thrown in prison or
You could be the person who steps back and goes listen. I know there's some truth here
But I'm gonna make up a bunch of fake stuff people love to hear fake stuff disguises real stuff
I'm make a bunch of money. I'm gonna get a big social profile
I may even have people follow in my footsteps someday and that's Preston Nichols route. There are two routes
But they both lead to the same destination
silencing an investigator
John Ford is no longer looking into the stuff that he believed in whether or not it was true. He believed it was true
Preston Nichols
Is now known as the Montauk project guy. So if he does start to make other revelations going forward
Most people especially skeptical community go well, he did write that book that had a bunch of soft facts in it
Why should we believe this at the end of the day two investigators got taken off the game board?
one through criminal charges and the other one through
financial gain
Preston Nichols may have status and money and fame
But is he still just another prisoner of a system?
That is constantly trying to keep the truth
From reaching the masses
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you listened to it today. I'm about to drink some night quill. Have a great weekend guys
[Music]