It's a race against time!
Can the FBI stop a madman before he strikes again?
And then we travel to Tennessee and go way back in time to when the Cherokee Nation ruled the land.
Everything was going quite well until a creature came down the mountain today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Hey guys, big news.
You know, the Patreon supporters, you guys have been awesome. You guys have been supporting me
for a long time and I really haven't had any awards or rewards, I guess would be the right
term for that. That changes Tuesday. That changes next Tuesday. I got stickers for you guys. Now,
I took an entire month of my Patreon donations and turned it into stickers. I need your guys's
addresses. I need Patreon supporters. I need your addresses. Now, I'm not going to reveal what these
stickers look like. These stickers though are really, really cool. They're really, really cool. I want
people to just get them in the mail. A little handwritten note by me. There you go. Thank you for
your support. Now, right before I put in the order and put the announcement on Patreon about the
stickers, I did have a Patreon supporter. Leave the show. Leave the Patreon. You know who you are.
I'm not going to put you on blast. You still get a sticker. You totally still get a sticker.
I sent you a message. You know how to get ahold of me. Email me. Give you your address. You
missed it by a day. I'm not, you've been supporting the show for a long time, so I'm not going to
keep the sticker from you. I'm not hyping these stickers up, dude. These stickers are dope and
they're an exclusive. You're not going to sell these in the store. These are an exclusive sticker.
So, if you're interested in joining the Patreon, now's a good time. Actually, if I get a bunch of
people joining, I'll have more to send out and I'll probably have to buy more. But I just wanted to
give a show of gratitude for the people who have been supporting the show and kind of transitioning
into that. I want to thank today's supporter of the show, Smashers25. Smashers25. Smashers actually
does some of the artwork for the show. Does the Dead Rabbit expose logo. So,
Smashers, we're going to make sure that we take care of you. She's been doing stuff on the back
end of the show as well, so it's very, very helpful. And Smashers, right now we're going to give you
the keys to the carpenter copter. We're going to drop them in your hand. Smashers, a.k.a. Ashley,
it's actually, you see, you can call you Ashley, Resty, what's up. As the keys are falling into
her hand, her name changes. Ding! Let's hop in that carpenter copter. We are headed out to
Richland, Virginia. So, we got Ashley flying the carpenter copter. Flying over. It's June 3rd, 2020.
So, incredibly recent story. This just happened. You guys know how calendars work a couple days ago.
We're flying. We see the Clinch Valley Medical Center. The helicopter is landing on the roof of
the hospital. We're walking through the hospital and there's this dude who just walked in as well.
His name is Cole Carini. He's 23 years old and he's like, "Ahh! I'm having a terrible day, guys!"
And the doctor's like, "Well, that's kind of a weird way to introduce yourself." And then
Cole holds up his arms. One hand is completely gone and the other hand's missing a bunch of fingers
and he has shrapnel all up in his neck. And he's like, "Ahh! I can guarantee my day is worse than
anyone else is at this hospital right now." And the doctor's like, "I'm not taking that, but..."
Now, a couple hours later, "Bring, bring, bring, bring!" Federal Bureau of Investigation,
Virginia office dude, and they're like, "Hello, Virginia office. Send out your best agent. Send him
to the Clinch Valley Medical Center." And the guy goes, "Okay, that's what we do. Click." And then
goes, "You're our best agent." And he points to Special Agent Neil Schmeich. Schmic? Neil Schmic.
I don't really want to make fun of this guy or get his name wrong. He is a special agent of the FBI.
This guy, when you look at his pedigree, he's fought drug cartels in Laredo, Texas. Then he went to
Orange County and specialized in investigating crimes against children, homegrown terrorist,
extremist groups. He also has this little quote in his affidavit that he fills out later on,
"I have been deployed overseas for the FBI to investigate international terrorism in both
the Philippines and Jordan." This guy has a pretty good record, right? Now, to be fair,
I don't know if he solved any of that stuff. He may have just went over there and been like,
"Yeah, I'm sure there's terrorists somewhere. He's drinking amitite. They're like, 'Neil!
You're supposed to investigate this stuff. You're not supposed to go over and just tell us that.
Oh, yeah, I'm sure there's drugs in Laredo, Texas. Neil, we know that." I'm going to assume
he solved these cases because he seems to be pretty savvy. He goes out to the Clinch Valley
Medical Center and he walks in and Cole Carini is sitting there. He's like, "Oh, my hands
totally suck, bro. They're all messed up." Special Agent Neil sits down and he's like,
"So what happened? What happened here?" Cole goes, "Makes a little flashback noise and everything
gets blurry." It's a couple hours ago. Now, Cole is mowing his lawn. This is a very quiet lawnmower.
And then the lawnmower flipped over. Whoa! And now it's laying on the ground, but it's face up.
And he's like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!" And he falls into the lawnmower.
Technically, his words to Special Agent Neil and to other law enforcement was that
when the lawnmower flipped over, the blades are spinning so fast it, quote, "acted like a bomb."
Unquote. Now, the reason why the FBI agent is here is because Cole Carini had been arrested before
for building bombs. But he's like, "No, no, no, I was lawnmowering. I was mowing a lawn is the way
you humans say it." The lawnmower flipped over like I'm running goat simulator or something and
hit an invisible wall and went, "Woo!" And then I fell into it. It was spinning so quickly it mimicked
the effects of an explosive blast. That's why I have shrapnel in my neck and I'm missing a hand
and fingers off another hand. So, law enforcement and Special Agent Neil go out to Cole's house.
And I was reading like the affidavit, the arrest warrant, whatever the term is, the legal document
about this. And it's, it's, it's, I love reading these sometimes because you can tell the person
writing it had a lot of fun writing it. There's basically a narrative thread to this investigation.
First thing, they get out of the, first thing, Special Agent Neil gets out of the car and he
notices something. The grass is six inches long. Little leather sole shoes walking by as he's
looking at it. Ladybugs scampering hiding from law enforcement. They're up to no good, you know,
those little ladybugs. Their houses are always on fire. They're a bunch of arsonists. Notices that
the lawn, first off, I would notice there's not a blood-soaked lawnmower. That'd be the number one
thing, right? But anyways, the lawn is not mowed. So he's like, hmm, suspicious. Very, very suspicious.
At this point, he really knows what happened. He's just trying. He has to do his job.
He notices there's blood leading up to the car door and there's blood on the car door. Now,
what I would assume, again, Basil, the great mouse detective, could figure this one out,
was that this dude blew his hands off. I'm sorry, chopped his hands off in a lawnmower that acted
like a bomb. And then he was trying to paw at his car door to get inside. And then I guess he
probably realized, well, I only have two fingers across two hands. Even if I got inside, I'm not
going to be able to drive. I'm assuming he called 911 or a neighbor took him to the hospital, but
it doesn't sound like his neighbors were too fond of him. But anyway, so there's blood on his car
as he's trying to get in. Then they follow the blood and they're like, hmm, looking around. They
see it like dripping up the stairs, like drops up the stairs. He's basically, especially Agent Neil,
went from being like in an episode of 24 to now investigating an Edgar Allen Poe story. He's like,
hmm, very suspicious. Where's the gorilla now? He's looking at blood and stuff. He's like going
up the stairs. So he gets to Cole's bedroom and here we get this great quote. Talk about Edgar
Allen Poe. This might be a little more HP Lovecraft, honestly. Quote, at the bedroom door on the floor
was a flesh colored substance that, based on my experience, looked like a piece of human skin.
He didn't put the laugh in there, but he really should have because he could have just said,
I walked up to dude's room. There's obviously a human flesh hanging off of his doorknob.
But flesh colored substance, based on my experience, looks like human flesh. I'm sure he's seen a lot
of grizzly things. I'm sure he's like, could smell it before he even got in there. He walks into the
bedroom. There's bomb parts everywhere, like the PVC pipe. Dude's not a plumber. This isn't
circumstantial PVC pipe, bunch of nails. You're like, Hey, I have those. Your neighbors aren't
complaining about explosions happening in your shed all day long. When the feds are actually
investigating, like talking to neighbors, they're like, Yeah, we kept hearing like popping in his
shed out in the backyard because they went there as well. And then they got a warrant for there.
And they found even more bomb making stuff. But we just thought he was shooting a gun in the shed.
And I'm like, where, what neighborhoods is this guy living? That you can just, I mean, I listen,
dude, I live in a pretty rural area up here. You have farm community, people are shooting off guns.
You can go up in the woods shooting off guns. It's kind of rural community. I don't know where
this dude lived. But first off, I would be very suspicious of anyone who was shooting in a shed.
Because what target could you possibly not hit? That's only like two yards away from you. But
anyways, their hand is pop, pop, pop. They think, Oh, that's just, that's just harmless coal who's
been arrested several times for explosions. Let's just be shooting a gun. That's far less
suspicious. Shooting a gun indoors is far less suspicious than a someone who's been arrested
for building bombs and there's explosions coming from his house. It'll like cartoon smoke clouds
shooting out the windows. So when they're in his room, though, they find a crumpled, they're back
in his room now narrative wise, they find a crumpled up letter. And it was like, he was walking
through the mall. This is one of those things where I wish I had the whole letter because we
only have these fragments. I guess some of it's like covered in blood, which actually makes it
kind of cooler. But anyways, the letter goes like this. This is what it said. Like you can read
quotes from it. I'm going to paraphrase it a bit, but he was walking through the mall. Nobody knew
how dangerous he was when they when they looked at his frail body. They didn't know the man,
the monster that he really was inside. Yes, he was a three days grace song turned mortal
and nobody could stop him now. Now they will pay. That's pretty much the gist of the letter. He
makes a mention to Elliot Rogers and he says something that I'm sure sent chills down the
FBI agent's spine. It probably sent chills throughout all of law enforcement. Definitely
infuriated me. In this letter, he describes what his target is. In the letter, he's walking. He's
talking about how awesome he is and he's walking through the mall with a bomb in his jacket. And
he's headed towards his target. His target is quote, "hot cheerleaders." Shame on you, Cole.
Shame on you. Do you know there's only 5,300 universities and colleges within the United
States and we can average there's about 25 cheerleaders per college. That means at any given
time. Yes, I did the math. There is only 132,500 active cheerleaders and you want to blow them up.
How dare you? How dare you, sir? Neil reads that, throws the note on the ground. They're like,
"That's evidence." And Neil turns around, tear streaming from his face. He wanted to kill cheerleaders.
There was just everyone in the house is silent. The cat stops meowing. That's inhuman, Cole.
And Cole is now facing real federal charges for building a bomb, for having a bomb blow up. I
think there was two different charges and his hand's gone. Like he's missing one hand, the other
hand he has a couple fingers. Honestly, like he's definitely going to do some time. The evidence
is his missing hands. He still won't admit to it. He still says, "No, no, no, your honor. The lawnmower
flipped over." You know how lawnmowers do? They just turn over and they act, quote, like a bomb.
Anyway, still probably do like, I don't know, I'm going to assume 10 years. But the fact that he's
missing a hand and a bunch of fingers means his sentence is going to last a lot longer than that.
Cole, I wish you the best. I hope that your head gets right and maybe you get some robot hands
or something like that. In the end, he didn't hurt anyone but himself. Like I'm glad, I wish that
didn't even happen, right? I hope that he just was building a bomb and he looks in the mirror and
goes, "Well, this is a stupid hobby and I'm not going to hurt people." And then just kind of pushes
his side and goes up and plays Nintendo Switch. Moral of the story is don't attack cheerleaders,
don't build bombs, and if you are going to try doing either of those two things, make sure you
don't do it within Special Agent Neil Shemecky's jurisdiction because he will come after you.
How do they put cuffs on? How do they put cuffs on this guy? He's like, "Aha! I've snuck out again."
They're like, "Cole!" And then a little Looney Tunes logo goes, "Dun dun dun dun dun dun."
And then that's the end of that segment. I had no other way to end that. Maybe I'll come up with a
hand pun later. Anyways, not going to worry about it. Ashley's just in there tapping her fingers on
the control panel of the carbon helicopter. Can we leave now? There's a bunch of helicopters
trying to drop off lifelike people. Can we just leave because you're sitting there thinking of
stupid hand puns? And I go, "Yes, we can leave." So Ashley is fire up that carbon helicopter again.
We are headed out to Tennessee. Now this was a story I completely stumbled across. I don't even
know what I was looking up. I have no idea what I was looking up when I came across this. We're
flying out to eastern Tennessee, technically it's eastern Tennessee, western North Carolina. Obviously
like as the United States was formed, the government was drawing state lines. But we're going farther
back before the United States even existed. We're going back to a time where we don't really even
have a time period it's taking place. This is just during the time when the Native Americans
ruled the country and this particular portion of the country was ruled by the Cherokee Nation.
Nowadays it's the Great Smoky Mountains National Park. At the Great Smoky Mountain National Park,
there's a Chilliwee Mountain. So Ashley, let's bring the helicopter nice and low.
It's now old timey America. We get out, we're walking around. Now we are sitting, we're hiding
in the bushes, because that's what we have to do because apparently we're just a bunch of weirdos.
We're sitting in the bushes. We see a tribe of Native Americans running around and the little
kids are like, "Mama, mama, mama." Apparently they're Italian as well. "Mama mia, tell me about the
story. Tell me about the story." And the mom's like, "Now you little young ones, I'll tell you the story
one more time and I'll tell it very loudly in case anyone in the bushes is listening."
So the mom starts telling the story long, long time ago. Now we're even further back in time,
right? And this is the story. I don't know why I had that narrative device, but here's the story.
The Cherokee warriors started to hear whispers throughout their nation that there was a creature
hunting them. Now this was a group of hunters, of warriors, but now something out there was
taking them out one by one. But it wasn't just that this thing was killing warriors. It was killing
women. It was killing children. And you couldn't stop it. It was like a plague. That's the way
they described it. It was like a plague. But they knew it was a person. They named it,
I'm gonna butcher this, but they named it "Nun-Yuni," which means "stone dress,"
which would translate to "skin of stone." Because the warriors who did interact with this thing
realized something very quickly. You couldn't kill it. Any sort of arrow, club, spear, whatever you
had just shattered when it impacted this creature. But that wasn't its only trick up at sleep. It
would appear as an old woman. And of course, you need to value your elders in that culture.
So you see an old woman walking through the middle of the forest. It's weird, right? You're two days
outside of the village, but you see an old woman walking through. That will make you hesitate.
That will make you not try to take that kill shot right away. She would always walk
with her right hand kind of hidden in a shawl. But sometimes when the warriors would interact with
this thing, they'd see what was really there. It was a normal hand, a closed fist, and the forefinger
was a blade as black and sharp as obsidian. She would lunge at you. Hunter would have run away.
Go back to tell people you gotta watch out there's something in the woods. Her name wasn't just
stone dress. She also went by another name, utlanta, which meant spearfinger. And really,
both names combined show how powerful and feared this creature was. Old woman, impenetrable, can't be
defeated, and had a weapon that's hidden and would just go right into you. Now, the reason why they
describe this as a plague was that, okay, you're like, there's an old woman walking around in the
woods. Who cares? Don't go under the woods and if you see an old woman walk the other way.
You might be walking away from an actual old woman who needs your help, but chances are not.
Well, she was a shapeshifter. Not only was she a shapeshifter, she could assume the shape of somebody
you loved. They said she would appear as your grandmother or your favorite aunt. That's fine,
Jason. I hate aunts. I only like uncles. And I'm not particularly fond of my grandmother anyways.
If I saw her in the woods, I'd just walk away. Those were her favorite forms, but she could be
anybody. This was a master shapeshifter. To the point that the pe- this went on for so long that
the people of the Cherokee Nation in this area were so paranoid of running into spearfinger,
that if you left the tribe by yourself for any amount of time and you came back, they thought
you were her. Hey, I'm gonna go pick some strawberries. Okay, hey, bring Billy with you.
Yeah, sure, Billy. Come on. And Billy's sitting there playing Nintendo Switch. What? I didn't
even know that was invented yet. Okay. Then you walk off, you get strawberries. You come back.
Everyone in the tribe is their arms crossed. Billy's like, "I told him not to go out. I was
gonna join him." I said, "You know what? I was just picking up strawberries and they would thank
you or spearfinger." Now you would go, "Why don't you just hold your hands up and be like,
'I'm not her. Look it. I don't have a spearfinger.'" Her number one thing. Yeah, but still, being
under suspicion of a monster for even a couple minutes is rough. And I'm sure there are people
who also said, "Well, maybe she hit her hand as well." That seemed to be a limit of her power.
She couldn't actually shape shift her hand. People were super paranoid of this thing. So,
Yurga Jason, why was this thing so threatening? I mean, the fact that it's impossible to kill
and it has a built-in weapon. What she would do is she would stick you with her finger,
stick it into you, and then you wouldn't even know what happened. You would feel no pain whatsoever.
But a couple days later, you'd die. You'd get yellow, super gross, blah. And what would happen
was after they would die, the medicine man would diagnose. I'm sure at some point they were doing
an autopsy of sorts when people are just falling over dead. The liver would be gone.
And people were putting two and two together. Wait a second. This guy was out by himself
hunting. A couple days later, his liver's gone and there were sightings of spearfinger with blood
on her mouth. So, the implication was that somehow she would be able to stab you, pull your liver
out without you feeling any pain whatsoever, eating it, and then you die a couple days later once
your body realizes you don't have a way of filtering out toxins. And to make things even worse,
sometimes she would poke you out in the woods, you're far away from your tribe. She'll stab you,
eat your liver, you die before you get home. She would then assume the shape of that warrior
going to the village and feed to her heart's content. Now that type of hunting technique was
done mostly before people knew to look out for spearfinger. Because again, they're like, "Hey,
Johnny, how was the hunt?" And he's like, "Oh, it's pretty good." And they're like, "Hey, you can put
your spear back." And he's like, "I already did." And I'm like, "What's that on your finger?"
"I was eating some hot fudge. That's why it's black. Why is it sharp? Stick. Eatin' liver,
runnin' away." As time grew, they started to learn ways to defeat this, or not defeat it,
but at least avoid it. But in the beginning, it would come to a village. If it could get into
your village, it would eat as many as livers as it could. Now, the one thing we look at cryptids a
lot, that I like to look at cryptids a lot, are their weaknesses. Because we always have these
weird weaknesses for these things. Spearfinger had two weaknesses. One, the reason why it always
kept its right hand closed, even though it had that spearfinger that not just would stab people,
but could pull their liver out without them knowing, that's also where her heart was.
It was the one part of her body that could be pierced by a blade, is her hand, her wrist area,
on the right hand. Anything else is just going to bounce off of her, so she always kind of
guarded that. People just assumed she was doing it to hide her weapon, but it was actually her
weak spot. Her second weakness was she had an equal. This is fascinating too, because I haven't
really come across this encrypted lore. She had an equal. Stone Man. Stone Man was his name,
the not super original name for that guy. At least Stone Dress is kind of cool. Stone Man.
Now, he was actually more powerful. He had a magic wand that he could use to control boulders,
build bridges and stuff like that. But neither of them were strong enough to kill each other,
and they both ate human livers. So they definitely had to watch out where they're like. They had
particular hunting grounds. I'm sure over time some of the deaths of spearfinger were blamed on
Stone Man. It doesn't matter when your liver's missing. You don't care who took it, but you have
basically two ultra powerful cryptids, almost demigods at this point, fighting over control of
who gets to eat the most livers. But he also wasn't penetrable to weapons. And they just kind of stayed
away from each other. He had a magic wand to control rocks. I left this detail out. The fact she
looks human, but she has skin as strong as stone. She can also pick up boulders. She can squeeze
them together morph them. At one point she made this giant stone bridge to try to get to heaven,
and the gods electrocuted it, and she flies off of it. She probably just bored one Tuesday. I don't
know what building a bridge to heaven has to do with hunting humans and eating their livers, but
apparently that structure is still in the area. It's called like stone tree or something like that.
But anyways, so it's not like she's just walking around eating livers. She has the ability to
throw boulders at you. She could pretty much wipe out any tribe anytime that she wanted to.
Her main way of hunting was following to where population centers were. And every autumn in
this area, the Cherokees would set brush fires all up and down, and it would make all the chestnuts
fall off the trees, and then they would just eat roasted chestnuts, which I always thought was kind
of a meme. Apparently it's a way you can survive in the wild. And she would see these fires from
far off, and she would just continue her walk. Her "it follows" walk. Walk slowly, slowly, slowly,
as long as it takes. There's no other transportation really back then. And eventually she's in the
smoke, you're in the smoke, you're picking up chestnuts, and then three days later you go home and
your liver's missing. Like you wouldn't even see her coming in that circumstance. Or she goes home
and she's you, and then you show up later and they think you're her. And she was just a master of
deception. Now, eventually, a bunch of different tribes of the Cherokee Nation got together and
they go, "We have to take care of this thing. This thing is just decimating us." So they got this
medicine man and he goes, "Okay, here's what we're gonna do. We know a little bit about her. One,
we know she's a shapeshifter. Two, we know to stay away from her. She's impenetrable. The only thing
we can do is hope to catch her and get lucky." Which is a bad strategy when the general's like,
"Well, we're just gonna put a bunch of troops in this area. I don't know. Maybe the other guys
were all like fall of a cliff or something like that. I don't know. Maybe we'll get lucky."
But anyways, that's her plan. So what they do is they build a big old pit and they set a fire.
And spearfingers off the distance. Ah, yes, I see the smoke and she starts walking towards the smoke.
Now, it's pretty smoky, right? She can't really see where she's going. No one can really see where
they're going. And some guy sees an old lady walking through the smoke. Now, he goes, "Oh,
that's my grandma. I'm not going to attack her. Hey, guys, look out. Don't shoot. Yeah,
there's a grandma walking by and the medicine man goes, "What the- No, that's really her. That's not
a joke. That's actually in the legend. I'm not making- I'm not ripping on a joke. This guy,
even though they know this is a shapeshifter who assumes the form of grandma, and they've
set this trap to end this menace that has plagued their nation for a decade at this point, or if
not longer. Hey, look at grandma. Hey, we're over here. Watch out. There's a big trap. Don't worry
about it. The medicine man's like, "Shut up, you numbskull. That's- That's who we're hunting." And
the guy's like, "Oh." So they start shooting arrows at her and of course they're bouncing off
of her, but in the smoke and all of the chaos, she falls into the pit. It's full of spikes.
Oh wait a second. These don't hurt me. She's just pushing the spikes over.
Now she's yelling at them. Now she would sing a song about how much she loved to eat livers.
That was like her hot- That was the only reason she existed. Like, I like eating food,
but I don't sing songs about "Mmm, mm, mm, gonna eat a hamburger." But she's taunting them basically
at this point. Stone Man also had his own song about livers. It's just some weird- It wasn't a
lot of music back then. No VH1. She's in this hole. She's shaking her fist. Not the one with the
spear on it, because she's hiding that one. She's shaking her fist in the air. Singing about how
much she loves eating human livers, the Cherokee are up there and they're like, "Uh, this isn't
gonna end well." Because she's immortal. She's in a pit. I mean, like, what are we gonna do? We can't
make concrete. What's concrete? He's like, "I don't know. I don't even know why he said that. I don't
know why. I don't know how we're gonna keep her in there." Now at that time, a little birdie,
comes flying down from heaven, sent by the divine beings. It's a little titmouse.
And it lands on a warrior spear and begins to say "Tip, tip, tip, tip, tip," which in Cherokee,
that's not the actual translation, but it was making this noise that in Cherokee sounds like
"heart, heart, heart." I think it was like "oon" or something like that. "Oom, oom, oom." That makes
more sense. And the medicine man goes, "The weakness must be the heart." So they're like,
"Concentrate all fire on her chest." So they're like, throwing spears down, shooting arrows,
and the spearfinger's like, "Ha, ha, ha, nothing will defeat me," and she's hiding her hand. Now
they take it as the titmouse, which is a bird, not a mouse, or a boob, was lying to them. So they
get mad and one of the warriors takes the titmouse and cuts its tongue out, and it flies back to
heaven. So that's the reason, if you ever wondered, if you're ever a bird watcher and you wondered,
why does a titmouse have such a small tongue? It's because it was cut off for lying.
Which when I read that part, I go, "That's kind of messed up because we know the weakness is the
heart." They just don't know where the heart's at. So they're continuing to sit there and they're
like, "Man, I probably should have just eaten that titmouse. I'm so hungry. How long are we
gonna have to sit out here for?" "Well, you can eat its tongue. I'm, I was okay, but I'm still kind
of hungry." Starts singing a song about titmouse tongue. Another bird comes flying down from heaven.
[Sings a tune]
And this one flies into the hole and lands on spearfinger's right hand.
So the medicine man goes, "Oh, so sorry, titmouse. I think we only got half the message. Hey guys,
come here." And they huddle together and they go, "I bet you that that bird on that right hand, at this
point I imagine spearfinger's trying to shake it off and it's like perched on her finger."
Like, "Get off, get off, get off. I bet you the heart that the titmouse is warning us about
is in the hand. So concentrate all fire on the right wrist." And warriors go, "That's a good idea.
That's a good idea. I'm just getting real hungry for some more delicious titmouse." So they get their
arrows ready and they just launch a volley in and it actually goes into her wrist and severs her
heart from her body. She falls dead almost immediately. Just "Wooah!" No more livers for
spearfinger. And the warriors are like, "Yes, dude, totally awesome." Jumping up, they invented the
high five at that moment. They invented the freeze frame. They jump up high five, freeze frame.
Later on, they're at the village and they're like having this huge party. Someone's patenting the
high five. He's like, "I'm going to make millions." They're having this huge party. Now they took
spearfinger's hand, they chopped it off, and they mounted it outside of the village as a trophy
and it's a warning because they all know Stone Man is still out there. But for now,
they've defeated an otherwise impossible foe. And Stone Man walks by that village and he sees that
hand perched up. It's like making the number one sign. We're number one tribe in Tennessee and
North Carolina is what's written on it. And Stone Man just looks at that hand and it's dark and the
fire's crackling in the distance. All the people are having this huge party. This hand is just perched.
And Stone Man looks at that hand and he smiles because, see, they figured out her weakness. No
one could figure out Stone Man's weakness. Stone Man now had no adversaries in the area. He could
eat as many livers as he wants. Or so he thinks. And as Stone Man walks away into the darkness,
humming a jaunty tune about eating human livers, will he be defeated? Or will his reign of terror
last till today? We'll continue this story on tomorrow's Dead Rabbit Radio. Dead Rabbit Radio
at gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal, conspiracy,
and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.