Hey guys, I'm going to give you a real quick sneak peek of episode 666 that comes out tonight
on Dead Ravra Radio and I'm telling you, this is not a lark.
I don't know what was going on during the recording process.
I was recording it in the haunted closet as I normally do.
And first I thought it was me shuffling around in my chair.
I had recorded a lot of stuff that day.
Maybe it was uneasy but throughout the editing process and it gets worse through the episode
there's wrestling in the closet.
And this particular segment you're about to hear, you'll hear first off a set of three
knocks and then a weird sound.
And then I continue on because I'm not hearing anything in the closet while I'm talking.
And then you'll hear me continue talking and then you'll hear a set of three knocks again.
I don't know what this is.
It could easily be me shuffling around in the super hot closet because I did have a long
day of recording.
It could be someone else doing stuff nearby that it's picking it up.
I've been editing out 90% of the knocks but it's getting to the point where they're happening
while I'm talking.
So I wanted to share it with you.
Possible demonic intrusion into episode 666 or the ghost of the closet warning us or
totally rational explanation that doesn't involve any of those but I wanted to share
with you as a preview for tonight's episode of 666 of Dead Rabbit Radio.
And sorry for the sound quality.
I'm recording this on my gaming headset while I'm editing.
And people are at the end of the day I think people who do try to summon demons it's because
of two things.
One they're seeking power is three things.
One of them is seeking personal power.
One of them is trying to prove that they exist some sort of validation.
And the other one is they're desperate.
They're desperate.
And that's the saddest one.
Like someone just trying to figure out like I wonder if demons exist and they do these
rituals and nothing happens then that just confirms what they think.
But there are people who are desperate who they're backs to the wall they don't have
enough money things like that.
[BLANK_AUDIO]