If you saw a loved one being kidnapped by aliens, what would you do?
And then in my never ending quest to get this podcast taken off of YouTube, we take a look
at the conspiracy.
Is COVID-19 actually an alien virus from another world?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys have some fun plans coming up this weekend.
We got a ton of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, take a look at this beautiful fan art submission from Goose Motion on our Patreon
Discord.
This is some graffiti.
This is some graffiti that he didn't work.
And it's awesome he said he painted it and other people started listening to the podcast.
He probably thought he was some sort of weirdo.
St. George's worth something.
He's writing these weird glyphs on the wall.
That's amazing Goose Motion.
Thank you so much and for everyone at your workplace.
Bow down to the new symbol.
I don't know where he works, but this should become their corporate logo.
Really, really appreciate it.
Really appreciate taking over your workspace.
And let's give a shout out to today's Patreon supporter coming into Dead Rabbit Command,
walking on all fours, making little oinky noises.
It's Piggy.
I wasn't insulting the guy.
Piggy is his name.
Piggy, thank you so much for supporting the show.
You're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the Patreon.
I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Graffiti, paint your workplace in the logo.
Help spread the word about the show.
Really, really, really helps out a lot.
Really appreciate it.
Now Piggy said, "I don't want to be in any disgusting episodes."
Which is good.
If you don't want to be in a disgusting episode, it's good to note that.
So he's not on Monday's episode.
Monday's episode is gonna be super gross.
But for today's episode, Piggy, I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead
Rabbit Durgible.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're flying all the way out to Trenton, New Jersey.
Piggy's like, "I said nothing disgusting, man.
Nothing disgusting."
As we see the sewage heap known as the state of New Jersey in the distance.
The only thing I really know about New Jersey is Jersey Shore and the Sopranos.
It's like super polluted, right?
I don't know if that's still true.
I don't know if it was ever true.
That was a big stereotype in the '80s when I was growing up.
That New Jersey is where New York dumped all their trash.
So whether or not that's true, whether or not that holds any variant in truth, I heard
it so many times in sitcoms and stand-up routines.
I assume the state is just a giant pile of black plastic bags.
But we're headed out there.
It's July.
I lost every listener in New Jersey.
It's July 19th, 1948.
We're in Trenton, New Jersey.
It's 3.30 a.m.
Very, very early in the morning.
This little boy wakes up in his bed.
We're gonna call him Sam.
Sam wakes up.
Sam wakes up in the middle of the night.
We don't know how old he is.
Maybe he's like 10, 11 years old.
He wakes up in the middle of the night and something must alert him to kind of start
skulking through the house because he ends up viewing, he ends up coming out and seeing
five little men walking through his house.
Now that was odd.
He's like, "What?
There shouldn't be any little men here.
I'm the little man."
But not only are they walking through the house, these five little dudes are carrying
his mom down the stairs.
That's a shocker.
That's a total shocker.
So he goes to interfere.
He has this natural, "I gotta save my mommy."
And so he goes to do that and all the bravery goes away when one of the little guys looks
at him and says, "If you interfere, you will die."
So Sam just starts to slowly back up as his mom is being carried down the stairs by these
five little people.
And he shuts the bedroom door.
I'm assuming they don't give that detail, but I don't think he would leave it open.
And he sees a bright light outside his bedroom window and he runs to the window and he throws
back the drapes and looks.
And now he sees his mom walking with the five men into a blinding white light.
All six of them walking to the light.
And then Sam says he doesn't remember falling asleep.
He has no recollection of falling asleep.
It's like, "Oh, well, that was exciting.
See you later, mom.
I'm gonna take a nap."
Sam has no recollection of falling asleep, though.
The next thing he remembers is, "Honey, honey, wake up."
And his mom's like pushing his shoulder.
You know how parents wake up, kids?
"Wake up, wake up, honey."
And Sam's like, "Uh, he's coming too."
And it's his mom sitting there.
"Oh, Sam, I'm so glad you're awake."
And he notices his mom has this really sad look on her face.
She looks at Sam and goes, "I have some bad news.
I have some bad news.
This morning I woke up and you know that dog you love so much.
Rusty, rusty, your loyal pup.
Oh, been there through thick and thin.
Always been your best friend till the end."
Well, Sam, the end came last night.
The mom says that when she woke up, she was walking around the house and she saw that
Rusty had killed himself accidentally.
Accidentally.
I don't know if there's like a bottle of pills next to him.
She says, "I don't know what happened last night, Sam, but it looks like Rusty tried
jumping out of the window and his collar got caught and he hung himself right outside
the house."
Right there.
I left a body there for you to see.
He must have seen an intruder and got so scared or so brave or both, he jumped out the window
and he died.
He's hanging or hung or hanged, whatever it is.
And the mom pulls up a dictionary to figure out what the right word is.
Anyway, your dog is dead.
That story came from a set of UFO reports called Mysterious Reality.
I got it from Albert Rosales, humanoid report, a great resource for this type of thing.
Fascinating story.
You could write off the first part as a dream, right?
He was dreaming that he saw his mom.
But the way that this event, if it's true, is set up is that the boy, Sam, did what the
aliens said, or elves or gnomes or whatever they were, but tiny little people did what
they said and went back where the dog didn't.
That's what I got from when I read this story.
I imagine they continue walking down the stairs and the dogs are...
And the aliens go, "If you interfere, you will die."
And the dog jumped like...
I think that as she was walking in the light, the dog's like, "I'll rescue your mom."
And he jumped out the window.
And there's actually a couple different ways you can read this.
One, I'm gonna go into a lot of ways a dog can die right now.
So you might want to skip ahead 30 minutes.
The dog jumps out the window and its collar gets caught and it hangs to death.
That's possible.
It's horrible, but it does happen.
Or that the dog jumped out and the aliens hung him.
They caught him in air and then they hung him.
There's no part of the story that actually says that, but that would be chilling too.
I mean, it would be horrible if the dog accidentally killed itself.
But also if the dog interfered and the dog hung itself, it's also possible that this
was a message to the boy as well.
To show their power, they said, "If you interfere, we'll kill you."
And he doesn't interfere, but the aliens go, "You know what, better send a message to
this kid."
One thing that's interesting, and I know if you're a victim of alien abductions, you're
not gonna want to hear this, but one thing is interesting with alien abductions versus
other paranormal activity.
People who see ghosts, you know, you have like mediums and you have like psychics and stuff
like that.
I'm not talking about that.
I've seen ghosts.
And there are often long periods of time, like we're talking decades where I don't see another
ghost.
You may not see ghosts.
It seems to be location-specific.
And you may see a ghost in your childhood and never ever see another ghost.
People who have alien encounters, they tend to have multiple alien encounters over the
years.
Whether or not they remember them is another thing, but it's when people talk about getting
alien abducted by aliens, like they're walking through an alley and they get abducted by
aliens, that is not always the end for that.
It's like you're marked.
So it's possible that they would, this might not have been the first time these aliens came
to the house.
It probably wasn't the last.
This was the one time that Sam woke up to see it.
And since he saw it and since he was going to remember that, maybe the aliens wanted
to send the clear message.
We're being serious.
If you do see us again, do not interfere.
We killed your dog last time.
Next time we'll kill you.
And they give him a little box with a dog collar with a little Sam name on it.
Terrifying story, and there is a real difference between ghost hunters and even UFO hunters.
They look up at the lights and be like, oh, look what's up in the sky.
And alien abductees.
There's a alien abductees I think falls more in the realm of people who are like possessed
by demons.
It's far more serious than me breaking into a haunted house, me being a ghost hunter,
seeing ghosts interacting with ghosts.
Once you start getting abducted by aliens, it's a little more serious.
Once they're breaking into your house.
So yeah, interesting story.
We do see aliens kill people from time to time, not even including cattle medallions.
Personally I believe cattle medallions are probably humans.
I believe they happen.
But I think it's the work of humans.
For whatever reason, I still don't know.
But we do see aliens kill people from time to time.
We do still see them kill animals from time to time.
And they may be responsible for some of the cattle medallions, sure.
But yeah, just a creepy story.
Even that, that's the same thing if you're living in a mafia controlled area or you're
living in New Jersey.
And you see something the mob doesn't want you to see so they kill a loved one.
They kill little Rusty.
Creepy creepy story.
The moral of the story is if you ever see your mom in danger, just let her be.
Just close your eyes and pretend she's not there.
Nah, just joking.
You should have jumped out of the window too, bro.
You should have tried to rescue your mom.
Then I guess you probably would have died, so don't do that.
So basically the moral of the story is do not take advice from a man who hosts a paranormal
podcast from within a haunted closet.
Piggy, let's go ahead and touch the keys to the carbonicopter.
We're leaving behind Trenton, New Jersey.
We're gonna fly all the way out to...
Again, again, I don't know why I'm tempting fate.
Wuhan, China.
As we're flying out there on my break, I saw some of the best movies I've seen in a long
time.
There was like a 48 hour period where I saw like 5 or 6 great movies in all these different
genres and I wanted to share them with you.
Nah, I'm not gonna do them all at once, but you guys know I do my Dead Rabbit Recommends
and I can't wait to tell you about this first Dead Rabbit Recommends.
I came across this movie, I'm gonna tell you this right now.
The title, Super Generic, the movie poster, Super Generic.
I saw the movie poster a couple years ago when it came out and I go, "What is this?
Like Saw meets Tales from the Crypt meets some sort of horror anthology?"
But I just happened to watch it the other day, dude.
It is so dope.
It's called Poker Night.
And it's directed by Greg Francis and I looked him up.
Greg Francis does a lot of true crime shows on Discovery Channel and investigation channels
and stuff like that, you know, true TV, whatever.
He does all of these true crime shows but nestled into his filmography is this, I don't
even know how to classify it, horror movie, crime thriller movie called Poker Night?
To me it is the best crime thriller since 7.
Because that's a hard genre to really just stand out above.
And it's basically two plots interwoven perfectly.
One of the plots is a bunch of police officers are having Poker Night and they're trading
their best, most memorable stories with this new rookie on the force.
And then the other part of the story is that rookie is being held captive by a serial killer
in a basement.
And it's so, knowing he does a lot of true crime stuff actually makes me wonder how
many of those police stories are true.
But it is so masterfully done.
It does have the limitations of the budget, you see that.
But it has a killer cast, no pun intended.
You have Ron Perlman in it, you have the dude, the chicken man from Breaking Bad, he was in
the new Far Cry game as well.
He's in it so good.
It's so good.
And it's one of those movies that I don't really even want to give you anymore of the
plot because it's twist after twist after twist and they earn each of the twists.
Like you're watching it and you're like, "Wait, what?
Oh, okay, okay, we're going in this direction."
And then you're watching it for another 20 minutes and something else happens and you're
like, "Wait, what?
Oh dude, no way, I'm getting goosebumps just talking about it."
It's so dope to the point when the movie ended and I was just staring at the ending credits
with my mouth open going, "Uh, like what in the world?
Such a masterful gym."
Completely slept on.
Check out Poker Night.
I think it's available on Netflix.
Where is it available actually?
You can find it on streaming.
It's a really, just a really, really well put together.
Crime, thriller, horror movie.
It's just really, it's great.
Dead Rabbit recommends Poker Night.
Piggy, the reason why we're headed out to Wuhan, China is I recently got, this is actually
right before the break.
I got an email from a listener named ChromaSoFour.
ChromaSoFour sent me this.
Fascinating.
Fascinating story.
This is the type of stuff that I love being sent and covering with this stuff is these
weird fringe beliefs that this one has a lot of real world implications, right?
Because we're going to be talking about the coronavirus, COVID-19 and all that stuff.
October 11th, 2019 in Northeast China.
Over the city of Songyang, a bright fireball appears.
People look at it, you can see it.
They go, "Oh, that must be a meteor coming down from the heavens and everyone's just
kind of waving at it or just ignoring it going about their business."
But is it just another meteor?
Or did it change the way the world worked?
Back in 1979, there was a scientist named Inchandra Wickramasing.
And another scientist, he was working with this other scientist named Fred Hoyle.
And they wrote a book, it was published back in 1979, called Diseases from Space.
And the theory that is outlined in this book is that a lot of common diseases that humanity
suffers like influenza, the common cold, whooping cough came from outer space.
This was their premise of this book.
And they studied this for 20 years.
And what, for context here, Fred Hoyle was the guy who coined the term the Big Bang.
So these aren't just like people who were doing some research on the internet, which
didn't exist back then, and then calling themselves scientists.
These were respected people in their related fields.
They started looking at it and they go, "We think when we look at cosmic dust, there's
a chance that within the cosmic dust, there might be the right components for life."
And some of their, this is what's so interesting about science, right?
That is possible.
They've actually been able to confirm that yes, some of the cosmic dust that's floating
through space does contain the building blocks for life.
It's like carbon and nitrogen.
So scientists go, "Yeah, they were actually able to confirm that."
But then they go to the leap of panspermia, which is the idea that life begins on planets
because of this.
Or like life on Earth, I think we've talked about it on the show before as well, that
life on Earth was basically meteorites crashing into the super water of primordial planet Earth.
And it had like a bunch of microbes in it and they popped out and they're like, "Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
And
you would have planets that are nothing but, some planets are just dead, but some planets
that have the right temperature and the right water and the right soil and everything like
that, when these meteorites strike, when the planet passes through these clouds of cosmic
dust, all of these building blocks of life are coming down to a lifeless planet and over
billions of years are evolving.
Scientists, the mainstream scientific community does not believe in panspermia.
It's considered kind of, it's not considered like a lunatic theory, but it's not generally
accepted.
So they came out with this book in 1979 and people read it and the scientific community
kind of was like, "Yeah, we don't think that's what happened."
But they continue to push this idea.
And over the years, just because the mainstream scientific community doesn't believe it, doesn't
mean that all scientists don't believe it.
Over the years, they've actually gotten other people to go, "Well, it's possible.
This is where life comes from.
It's from outer space."
And if that is true, it's possible that diseases we get plagued from also come from outer space.
In 2013, off the coast of Chile, scientists discovered the Pandora virus.
Don't name your viruses after bad people in or bad events in mythology, the Pandora virus.
It's found off the coast of Chile and oddly enough, in a pond in Australia.
It's the second biggest virus on earth.
And so this was when a foil had passed away at this point, but this is when Chandra goes,
"I think this is proof again that some of these..."
Because nothing on earth has evolved to be this big that we can tell.
It's the second biggest virus on earth.
And just for comparison, the influenza A virus has seven genes to build it up.
HIV has nine genes as part of its building blocks.
The Pandora virus has 2,500 genes.
It can also move on its own.
It's the only virus that is self-propelled.
And the reason why the scientific community is not freaking out about it is because it's
mostly found in aquatic environments.
It infects amoebas, but we don't think it's any harmful to humans.
You'd have to be swimming off the coast of Chile or being in this Australian pond, this
unnamed pond.
So they're not really concerned about it affecting humans.
However, a couple years ago, there was this woman who was having some eye issues, and
in her contact lens was an amoeba.
And in that amoeba was the Pandora virus.
So this possible alien virus was rubbing up against this girl's eye.
But you go, Jason, so it's the second largest virus on earth.
So that means there must have been...
Even if it did come from outer space, something else must have evolved if it's the second
virus.
The largest virus on earth was discovered in 2014.
It was frozen...
I think we all read about this in the news.
It's from Siberia.
It had been frozen a hundred feet down in the permafrost for 34,000 years.
So they also look at that one and go, "People who believe in the theory of Panspermia, that
one was not a natural evolution too."
That's just too huge, right?
The Pandora virus is the second largest.
This other one found in Siberia was even bigger, but...
And then you have this massive leap down in scale to like nine genes and seven genes and
things like that.
We talked about...
We covered this a little bit on episode 649.
We went to Chile because we were looking at the black carpet conspiracy.
It's this theory that off the coast of Chile there was this giant undulating black mass
that just kind of moved around.
And the story was that swimmers were getting caught in it and I think it attacked a submarine
or something like that.
I don't remember the details of the episode, but when I was reading this I thought, "This
sounds awfully familiar."
So it's interesting that the sighting of this massive black algae, this like possibly sentient
algae, I think it turned out to be creepypasta or something.
I don't remember, but it was just interesting that we have that location is also the real
life location of this Pandora virus.
So I mean, I guess the creepypasta could be based on it, but I just wanted to make that
connection as well.
And that's a fun episode.
Go back and listen to that one and tell me whether or not it's creepypasta.
I don't remember, but it was a fun episode to talk about.
So you have all this stuff going on.
Like I said, other scientists are on board with this as well.
Dr. Jean-Michael Clavier of the Eix-Marcellia, whatever it is, some university in France.
Some university in France, dude.
Dr. Jean-Michael said that he believes that this Pandora virus has no ancestral cellular
connection to anything on earth, or at least anything existing anymore.
He goes, "Listen, if it had an ancestor on earth it's not around."
Like this Pandora virus is so different than anything else we have.
It has no relatives.
So he's not specifically saying panspermia, but he's kind of like nudging the scientists
next to him.
He's like, "I think this came from outer space."
I'm putting words in his mouth, but.
So now we're looking at a new conspiracy theory.
COVID came from outer space.
So Chandra and some other scientists got together and recently published a paper asking the
question, "Is coronavirus from space?"
They also connected there's a thing called Candida fungal disease that's going around.
It's hit in Canada pretty bad.
They also believe that's from space.
I guess the spoiler alert is they kind of believe everything's from space.
But for the topic at hand, we're going to look at the COVID thing and they said, "Listen,
Spanish flu came from space, killed millions of people."
The fungal disease they're talking about, they said, "Listen, the fungal disease has
existed before 2009, but at 2009 it got way worse, way bad, super more infectious."
What they believe is that the planet Earth passed through a cloud of radioactive cosmic
dust and the fungus mutated and became even more viral, even more vicious.
It's coming after you.
It's looking for your eyeballs and stuff like that.
And COVID-19 completely came from space like the Spanish flu.
It wasn't a simple mutation.
It was actually a meteorite coming down.
So fast forward, we got the Pandora virus which may have come from space.
They were talking about influenza and the common cold coming from space.
Basically, this is why we can't really defeat these things because it's an alien menace.
It's just not meant to be on this planet.
You're going to get the common cold every year.
What are you going to do?
So when Chandra and these other scientists recently put out this paper saying COVID-19
came from space and they actually specify the meteor that was spotted over China.
On October 11, 2019, they said that that might have been a virus bomb.
That could have been a bunch of viruses in that, or specifically the COVID-19 virus.
And it explodes like meteorites tend to do.
And then it rains down little particles on people.
They're getting hit with pebbles.
And one guy's, "Look at that!"
And he has his mouth open and a little virus lands on his tongue.
It didn't actually lay out that scenario.
But the idea was that this meteorite contained COVID-19.
It's a fascinating conspiracy theory.
The problem that they started to run into is apparently when they were writing the paper,
they said, "Since it's from space and there's nothing we can do about it, we don't have
to worry about getting any sort of vaccine or doing anything like that."
And the scientists were like, "Okay, listen, we might believe that panspermia exists.
And I'm sure it does on some level."
But to say that every disease comes from space, but if your answer is everything came from
space and there's nothing we can really do about it, that's not super helpful.
So when they were saying, "Oh, we don't even need a vaccine," that's when scientists were
like, "Okay, this is where the theory can actually start to become dangerous."
Right?
It's also interesting to look at their theory.
There was a meteorite spotted over Songyang on October 11, 2019.
And the virus appeared in November of 2019 in that same region of China, northeast China.
However, I think whether or not you believe it came from bat soup or it came out of a
laboratory or a can in my ever-ending quest to get this podcast completely obliterated,
built by some government or whatever.
Bill Gates is over there with his 5G tower personally building the disease.
However you believe it happened, I think everyone agrees that it started in Wuhan, Wuhan, China,
which is in northeast China.
This is where you start to get a little bit of the fudge going on because, yes, Wuhan
is in northeast China, but it's 1242 miles away from Songyang.
So that's a bit of a stretch, right?
And they go, "Oh no, we got an answer for that."
You see meteorites when they break up, pieces go everywhere, and maybe the extra juicy piece
with all the viruses went towards Wuhan.
I guess, right?
It's possible.
But you would have think you would have seen an outbreak over a larger area in the beginning.
It wouldn't have been isolated in Wuhan.
So there's no proof of any of this really outside of these theories.
And I know that's how science works.
They have to build up to the proof.
I think what left a bad taste in people's mouth was one, the virus landing on their tongue
when the comet exploded, and then two, the same, we don't even bother working on a vaccine.
And this paper was published a long time ago.
It was published back in July of 2020.
So this is when people were still locking themselves in their houses and things like that.
So when they came out, we're saying, "Oh, we don't need any vaccines."
Then people were upset by that.
But what's interesting, there's a really cool take on this from Rahan Gabriel-Joseph on
this website called Cosmology.com.
That kind of takes it to another level.
This is where we're going to wrap up this episode.
This is a really cool way to look at it.
So let's say that this is true.
Let's put on our conspiracy caps and say this is true.
That these diseases that seem to plague mankind for years and years and years are alien.
He goes, "Maybe this is why comets are seen as signs of doom."
Maybe this is why when people looked up in the sky and they saw a comet, they thought
the world was going to end.
These previous times and previous civilizations, when a comet showed up, the earth pastored
the tail of the comet and got a face full of microbes, or when a meteorite flashed into
the sky, it brought death.
It brought disease.
We did an episode a long time ago about, did aliens bring about the black plague?
You think about how much the world or especially like European history changed because of the
black plague?
It wouldn't even have to happen every single comet or every single meteorite, bright big
meteorite in the sky.
It wouldn't have to happen every time.
But if it happened enough, your civilization as it's dying would write in its record books
we ended when the great light appeared in the sky.
The great and the poor both fell ill.
There was no safety in the streets or in the temples.
We were cursed by the gods.
We have been written out of the books of humanity.
How many times would that have to happen through human history before people just started seeing
comets and go, "Oh!"
And that is super common throughout history.
Comets were seen not as a good omen, but as an omen of destruction.
I keep using the words comet and meteorite interchangeably here, just a bright light
in the sky.
Something happening in the sky or even in the day if it's bright enough that it shouldn't
be there.
It's not part of the normal order.
And as we're floating through space and we see the celestial objects today we go, "Oh
that's just the way the universe works.
Look at those old superstitious goons back then."
And maybe they had it right.
Maybe when they saw these things there was a chance.
It didn't happen every time.
There's meteor showers all the time.
It didn't happen all the time.
But it happened enough throughout world history that they became very cautious when they saw
the brightest falling star or the comet that hung in the sky for weeks.
Because these were heralds of doom.
If they landed in the right area, it could wipe out a civilization.
So do I believe that COVID-19 came from outer space?
I think the answer is far more terrestrial than that.
COVID-19 aside, probably not.
But when we look through the scope of human history and the diseases that have plagued
us through human history, mysterious diseases that have popped up, I think we know the origins
of COVID-19, but previous discoveries, previous diseases that are unexplainable, pandora viruses
that are sitting off the coast of Chile that they're just too big to exist on this planet
to evolve the naturally.
It makes sense of why other cultures would look up at the sky and be scared when they
saw that because they all heard the stories of the previous culture.
They had moved into this area.
The buildings had been abandoned and streets had been littered with bodies.
So they built a new culture on top of it and they'd been there for 50, 100, 200 years and
then once again this comet's coming and they remember the old records.
They remember the old stories.
The light in the sky brought death.
The gods were angry with them.
Creepy.
Makes us feel so fragile and small that for all of our medical technology, all of our
wonderment, all of our hopes and dreams can be dashed because a rock that had been tumbling
through space billions of years finally nears Earth's orbit.
Everyone always talks about the planet killer meteorite that comes zooming from the opposite
side of the sun.
We don't see it in time.
We have a day to prepare and it smashes into the planet.
Being life as we know it.
But maybe it's not that dramatic.
Maybe it's far less of a noble last stand kind of death.
Maybe it's just that same meteorite coming into Earth's orbit.
We don't even notice it.
Maybe a couple of rock nerds do.
It burns up in the atmosphere.
Explodes over the Earth high in the atmosphere and we go about our days and this disease
rains down on us.
We catch the sniffles.
We get a little bit of a sore throat.
And then you hear about an epidemic in downtown Detroit.
People are vomiting up blood in the middle of the day.
It was a Wednesday afternoon.
People were getting off work and someone on the bus started vomiting up blood in the middle
of the bus.
They send any Ebola experts.
It's not that.
The disease continues to spread.
It's mysterious.
So organs are being liquefied.
You lose your vision.
You're both paralyzed and your body is wracked with uncontrollable seizures.
Hospital beds as far as the eye can see of humans suffering, suffering, suffering until
they finally die.
This disease ravages Midwest United States.
In three months it's spread across the entire North American continent.
Borders are shut down.
They don't even know what's causing this.
But the borders are closed far too late.
And the disease ravages the entire world.
A disease from an alien world mutated by cosmic dust during its journeys pierces the sky of
planet Earth and rains down hell.
We always wanted to make first contact with an alien life form.
Little did we know it would be last contact with an alien virus.
It wasn't first contact.
It was the last contact.
Man whatever have.
It's not the first contact.
It's the first contact.
(upbeat music)