If you stumbled across a human sacrifice in progress, would you try to stop it or would
you join in?
You know what Jason, that's not a question.
There's only one answer to it or is there?
We're going to take a look at a little thought experiment and then we travel into cyberspace.
Are you ready to fight for humanity's future?
Are you ready to take on the Chrome Lords?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had an awesome weekend.
It's almost Christmas dude.
That's insane and I will be doing a Christmas livestream.
Like Jason, you should just do a livestream that's not during a world holiday that we
can actually participate in.
I am looking at doing more regular livestreams, not during holidays where you're incredibly
busy.
I am trying to etch out a little bit of time but we'll get into that.
We'll see.
I would really like to do more livestreams but until then let's go ahead and get started
with this episode walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our Thanksgiving
livestream contributors who sent a very, very, very generous donation.
So give it up for ChimeChile.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Alright, come on in to Dead Rabbit Command.
ChimeChile.
ChimeChile, longtime contributor, longtime very generous contributor to Dead Rabbit Radio.
You're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, it's totally fine.
It honestly is.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
It really, really does.
If you get any value from the show, just spread the word.
How much you enjoy Dead Rabbit Radio.
ChimeChile.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the...
Jason Jalopy.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to the middle of the woods.
And this is a really interesting thought experiment.
I came across this the other day.
I was on the X board and someone posted something about being a willing human sacrifice and
there was kind of this conversation going on about what that would entail.
To be clear, this person wasn't saying they wanted to sacrifice themselves.
It wasn't some weird masochistic thing.
There's kind of a conversation about it and you would see people post things like, "Well,
a willing human sacrifice generates more power than if you broke into someone's house and
dragged out a teenage girl kicking and screaming and sacrificed her."
You would get more power for whatever ritual you're trying to do if the participant was
willing.
That's the kind of citation needed, right?
I'm not for sure if that's the case.
It would seem...
I would think if it was dark magic, right?
If it was dark magic, it would be the inverse.
Because it would want more of the suffering.
That's the whole thing about it, like the adrenochrome.
The adrenochrome theory is that it's the suffering that creates the adrenochrome that
makes it so powerful.
If someone's like, "Oh, dude, I would totally like for you to pull out my adrenal gland.
I'll be super scared.
I swear.
Do it."
It wouldn't work as well as if you did it against someone's will.
But who knows, right?
Who knows?
It's not something that I'm ever going to find out about unless I'm being sacrificed myself.
And I was like, "Oh, yeah, this magic is going to be pretty cool because I'm terrified."
But all these different people were talking about being a human sacrifice.
And again, they weren't lining up to do that.
But just kind of the concept of it.
What I thought was interesting is that as I was reading it, I kind of came up with this
idea.
One of the people said that people are still sacrificed, people are still sacrificed in
religious rituals to ensure that the sun rises.
I mean, literally that's what they said.
They said, "Without it, the sun won't rise."
So the reason why the sun rises each day isn't because the earth is revolving around the
sun.
It's because this sacrificial act, there is a group of people out there sacrificing a
human.
Is it every day or do they do like a bunch on one day?
Do they let it pile up?
They have their in and their out box.
And they're like, "It's probably time to sacrifice all those people.
We've been pushing it a little too close."
We're not for sure.
But this person said, "It's, quote, entirely necessary.
Without it, the sun won't rise."
Then they went on to say the word "soldier" literally means sacrifice to the sun god.
So implying that war itself is some sort of mass ritual.
Now let's do a couple of fact checks on that because I was like, "I don't know.
I don't know."
It turns out that soldier does not mean that.
Soldier actually means mercenary.
It comes from an old French word that is like "suder."
And that was someone who was hired to fight and then it meant to mean for pay and now
just soldier is generic term for anyone fighting in war.
So that's not true.
But the idea that war is a mass ritual held by the elite, that's not a new theory.
That's actually quite old.
I've heard that for a long time.
That these wars that we fight, whether or not land is gained or lost, it's actually
this huge black magic ritual that's churning out the bodies of all these young men, plus
all of the civilians in the war zone and it is part of some sort of super diabolical ritual.
More blood for the blood god type of thing.
So we have that.
I thought, because I'm reading this, I go, "What if this was true?"
Not the war thing, not the war thing, but what if Chime Chili's driving us out into
the middle of the woods?
We're wearing our cloaks, we're sneaking through all of the security.
The security's just looking for people not in cloaks.
They're really bad security.
And we get to the ritual that's actually being held.
And there's probably about two dozen worshippers here, two dozen people in similar garb as
ours and they're holding this ritual.
There's a young woman tied down to a stone in the middle of the woods and they're getting
ready to sacrifice her.
Our first instinct is going to be to start beating people up.
Not the girl on the stone, you're like, "Me first, punch, punch, punch."
Okay, now you can sacrifice her.
Our initial instinct, if you came across anything like that, would be to start beating up the
Satan worshippers, right?
Just beating up this coven of people.
And they would be super, admittedly, they'd be super easy to beat up, right?
Like whenever you see photos of these people who are supposed to be the elite, who are
supposed to be these like hardcore worshippers of the demonic, they're never physically
fed.
They're never Arnold Schwarzenegger, they're never buff.
I don't think I've ever come across.
Any conspiracy story involving a boxer or an MMA guy or whatever who also worships
Beelzebub.
I think it's always the weak people, right?
It's always the weak people.
It's always some billionaire or some artist or something like that.
So we could clean house.
We could totally take all of these guys.
And I think that would be our initial reaction, right?
We'd save the girl.
But what if we did this with an episode last season, we did a little thought experiment
about aliens, kind of doing the same thing here.
What if we show up at this ceremony and we are told by these people, they take their
hoods off and they go, "Listen, we know you're about to beat us up.
We've been beat up several times in the past just by being bullied in school.
Please don't beat us up.
We have to sacrifice this girl.
We have to sacrifice her not because we're trying to get riches or more power or anything
like that.
We did those ones yesterday.
You missed those ones.
We have to sacrifice this girl.
We have to do it once a year.
We have to sacrifice a young woman or a young man.
We have to sacrifice a young person.
And if we don't, the sun won't rise for the next year.
This is something that high priests and priestesses have been doing since the dawn of time.
If we don't sacrifice somebody, only one person, the sun won't rise for a year.
Now obviously that sounds fake.
We're still winding up our punches.
But for the sake of argument, this is what we did with the Alien episode, I said, "If
aliens came down and could prove beyond a matter of a fact there was no trick, no hidden
agenda, no monkey paw-like twist, if the aliens could convince you that they were fighting
only against the evil humans, would you side with the aliens against evil humans?"
And it was whatever humans you thought of as evil.
Whatever group or government or whatever, that was the one they were after.
You just thought experiment.
So this is the same way.
Whatever it takes, because obviously you're not going to believe them, right?
You're not going to believe them.
You're just going to think they're a bunch of perverts who want to sacrifice young people
in the woods.
But whatever it takes, they actually are able to convince you, and it's not a trick, it's
not a twist ending, they are able to prove to you beyond the shadow of a doubt that if
they do not sacrifice this young person tonight, the sun will not shine for a year.
I mean, it would pretty much be the end.
It would be the end of humanity.
I mean, maybe we could go a year without no sunlight, I don't think so.
Would you let them kill that girl?
And it's a tricky one, right?
Because first off, when I thought about that, I go, I don't know, like, because I want to
trust them.
I want to trust them at all.
They are in the middle of murdering somebody, right?
The aliens, at least they came down and they're like, hey, we want to talk to you, buddy.
They're in the middle of murdering somebody.
They're in the middle of getting ready to kill this girl.
So obviously they have a high hill to climb to gain my trust.
But whatever they could use, I don't think they could show me some sort of religious text
or anything like that.
But if they did convince me 100%, whatever they used to do it, if they did convince me
in the end, with no tricks or twists or anything like that, I didn't get fooled at the ending.
At the end of this conversation, I knew 100% that if this young woman was not sacrificed
tonight, the sun would not shine for a year.
What would I do?
That's a hypothetical thought experiment.
I just thought it was really cool.
There's no correct answer to it.
I think, obviously, it's made up, right?
Obviously I doubt this is happening.
But again, like, when I was reading this stuff, this guy who said that soldier means sacrifice
to some guy, that's not true.
But when I was reading it, I go, what if there's at least people who do believe that and they
are sacrificing somebody every single day or on a regular schedule and they're doing
it and as they're doing it, they're praying to the sun god.
And they actually believe that the reason why the sun is still rising is because there
are this long line of priests and priestesses stretching back out through history.
So people could be doing it because they think it's real.
Then extrapolate it out, that what if it was real?
And it would depend on the person tied to the rock, right?
If it was just some random teenager that kidnapped off the street, this dude hitchhiking and they
threw him in a van tied him to a rock, you'd be like, can't you just get some, aren't there
better people to tie to the rock?
Aren't there actually bad people out there in the world?
Serial killer, tie serial killer to the rock.
What if we just only did human sacrifices on bad people?
Those are the people, those are generally the people doing the human sacrifices.
I think that's why.
I think if they kidnapped a serial killer, they're like, hey, Barry, how have you been?
Haven't seen you in a long time.
Sorry, I thought you were just some teenager walking on the street and they let them go.
And then anyways, an interesting thought experiment nonetheless, also kind of grim.
Chime chili, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the world famous carpenter
copter or leaving behind this spooky forest.
Take us all the way out to a blockbuster video.
Chime's like, so we're going to Bend, Oregon, the location of the last blockbuster on earth.
I go, look again, my friend.
Look again.
And we all look out of the carpenter copter and there's blockbuster video stores as far
as the eye can see.
Because it's the year 1995.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's time to meet the Chrome Lords.
There is a AI program called mid journey AI.
And like all of these AI programs, you know, I've obviously played around with them a
bit on the Patreon discord.
We have an entire board set up for just people playing with the AI programs.
You type in a string of words and it spits out some images.
I'm a novice with this stuff.
Obviously, whenever a new one comes out, I type in dead wrap radio, try to get some logos.
But recently on mid journey, I think this was one person, but it may have been several.
But I do kind of think it's one.
I think it at least started with one person.
Other people have jumped on.
There's a new movie for lack of a better term that's been popping up called the Chrome Lords.
And what it is, is it's a movie that supposedly came out in the mid to late 90s.
That is a rip off of Terminator and Robocop, but had this really deep lore, had this really,
really cool world building behind it.
The plot was a little clunky as far straight to video movies go, but the movie never existed.
The movies never existed, but someone wrote up that description and then produced over
a hundred screenshots from the movie, the Chrome Lords.
And it looks almost exactly like the VHS screen grabs or the photographs you would see on
the back of a video cassette box when you're walking around blockbuster.
While putting them in the show notes, they kind of have to be seen to be believed, but
it's absolutely fascinating.
Now when you're working with AI, some of it doesn't look a hundred percent.
Some of them looks maybe a little more like a painting or like, you know, like concept
art.
But as you continue to look at the photos, they're not photos.
As you continue to look at the images, it would be a better term, your brain begins to
become convinced that this is real in some way or another.
Your mind is creating a story.
It does seem like there's some sort of conflict between humanity and these cyborg warriors.
And because some of the robots start to look more skeletal and some of the humans begin
to look more robotic, my brain was creating this idea that there was this movie.
And I knew it was fake, but there was this complicated relationship between the robots,
the cyborgs and the humans.
And the humans were becoming more, the cyborgs were becoming more robotic.
The humans were becoming more like cyborgs.
By the time you get to the image of the robot crucified and all these other robots like impugn
humans looking up at this crucified robot with this very, very 1990s straight to video color
palette in this photo, your brain has completed this movie.
The Chrome Lords is something taking over humanity and washing away the remnants of what was once
living flesh.
But anyone can look at these images right now and create their own story.
And I don't, I mean, like even that, I didn't, I was looking at the photographs.
I mean, there's a photograph also of a robot playing poker, right?
Or working at a roulette table or something like that.
So I don't know where that fits into my mythology, but I didn't purposely set out to think any
of that stuff.
It just kind of pops in your head.
And this is super fascinating.
I love this.
But you also would get a segment of people going, where do I find this movie?
I can't find any information about it on Wikipedia or IMDb, like what?
And then other people would post, hey, numbskull, it's fake.
Like this is fake.
AI art is a really cool toy and it's already starting to go sideways.
It's already starting to create some serious issues, well, or not so serious issues.
Fiverr type artists, you know, people who can bust out logos for you for like $5, $10
like they're going to go extinct because of these AI art programs.
I was messing around recently with this one that you take a photo, I'll put this one in
the show notes, I'm gonna have a lot of fun with it.
You put a photo in there and within a minute it is turned into an anime photo.
Something that would have taken someone hours to draw is provided to you for free.
I'm sure the Chinese government scraped my computer for all my information, but I didn't
have to pay technically for it.
For free I get an anime version of myself and when the AI starts doing fursonas, when
you can send them a picture or send them a description within a minute, you get what
looks like a professionally drawn picture of you as a furry.
I'm gonna do that for you.
I'm gonna send you a bunch of furry pictures of yourself.
When that happens, that will also completely collapse the economy because there's a huge
economy on the internet for people to draw fursonas.
So we'll have that.
There will be a gulf between people who are super eclectic artists who are doing stuff
so far out of the norm that they're known and then you're gonna have the greats that
are still around.
But the journey it takes to go from being a beginning artist to becoming one of the
greats or just to become commercially viable will be removed because the AI art is going
to do all of these things.
To create this many images of the Chrome Lords would have taken hundreds of hours.
You would have to dress sets because some of these looks so realistic.
You would have to hire actors and build sets and costumes and all that stuff.
It's fantastic for the consumer but this could be something that replaces storyboard artists
as well.
And eventually it could be something that replaces a whole slew of professions within
the film industry.
And all of that stuff, the way that science, the way that technology interacts with humans,
interacts with society, it's fascinating to me.
But that's not the main reason why I'm talking about this.
It will get malicious where people will create things to mislead you.
And there's nothing new with that theory too.
There's always been the concern with deepfakes that eventually there's gonna be a deepfake,
a 100% convincing image of a world politician saying, "You know what?
Who cares what the Poles think?
Who cares what the poor think?
Us rich people, we can eat babies all day long and nobody can stop us."
And it will be 100% it will sound like them, it will look like them, it will act like them.
And of course I think you would have half the people not believe it.
Because they're like, "I agree with that world leader.
I don't agree with the baby eating thing.
I think that's fake."
And you don't have half the people who do agree with it.
But that's always been the concern and we haven't seen that happen yet.
We haven't actually seen that happen yet.
But as this technology gets better, it will become more malicious.
It will become a way not just to fake what a politician says.
But I think you could actually break somebody's will.
I think you could break somebody's psyche with this type of thing.
I think that you could create images that are so convincing that they could convince
you the Chrome Lords did exist at one point.
And here's the thing, if somebody showed me these images and goes, "You know there's
a movie called The Chrome Lords and there's a late 90s movie as a rip off of all this
other stuff and I'm looking through these."
And I didn't know that they were AI generated.
I had no clue.
Let's say the technology is 30, 40% better than it is.
And I didn't know and I'm talking to someone and they're telling me this movie existed that
they saw and stuff like that.
My reaction would be, "Wow, that sounds really cool."
Yeah, they never got put on DVD and it's not on streaming or anything.
I'm like, "Oh, that sucks, man.
It's too bad."
Because at the end of the day, I haven't seen every movie ever made and that does happen.
There are movies you don't have access to anymore.
Oddly enough, Last I Check Dogma is one of those.
I read an article probably last year and they said Dogma, unless you buy a used copy on
eBay, it's not streaming anywhere.
The rights are all tied up by the Weinstein Corporation and that dude has bigger problems.
He has to worry about...
They go, "Unless you buy a used DVD of Dogma, you can't watch it."
Like that movie's pretty much close to being erased.
You have to buy a copy from someone else who has a copy.
They're not making anymore.
So in a movie like Dogma, big movie release with big movie stars can disappear.
There may come a time where nobody has a copy of Dogma.
Chrome Lords?
Yeah, sure.
That sounded really cool.
That sounds like it's cool.
I have a huge book, the complete book of zombie movies.
Every zombie movie ever made up to 2005, 2006 maybe.
And I can't find most of them.
They were never released a video or they were released a video but never turned into DVDs
and then you can't get a copy no more.
So it does happen.
So you can create movie after movie after movie and convince people they were real and
they're not.
But that wouldn't necessarily break your brain.
That wouldn't...
You'd be like, "Oh, it's too bad."
You wouldn't go like, "I'm going crazy.
I can't watch the Chrome Lords."
What I think is interesting, a more interesting idea is the opposite.
And again, I think this is also a little bit of a thought experiment.
Is it possible for someone to convince you a movie that you saw, that you know you saw,
was radically different than what it actually was?
We've always probably seen Titanic at this point.
You're talking to someone and they say, "Yeah, I really like Titanic but I thought it was
kind of cheesy at the ending where her and Jack both got on the raft and then they both
got saved and they went to America and the last scene was them surrounded by their children."
I'd be like, "Wait, that's not how Titanic ended."
And they go, "Yeah, that's totally how Titanic ended."
And we don't have a copy of Titanic sitting around us to watch.
We go to a website and this dude starts showing me screen grabs of multiple images of this
happening of her and Jack on the raft and then the spotlight shining in their face as
the boat comes by and then them hugging as the heart of the ocean is wrapped around her
neck and then we see them back in Chicago.
All the cinematography looks exactly like James Cameron, the staging, everything like
that.
He shows me like 10 or 15 images and says, "Yeah, this is how Titanic ended."
That's not how it ended.
That's not how it ended at all.
I would have to eventually go out and find a copy of Titanic because that would if someone
was showing me images that were 100% accurate to what would be in the film because these
AI programs will scrape every single second of these films and it doesn't have to be
moving.
You don't have to imitate Jack's voice or Rose's voice or anything like that.
It's just these images.
If someone's showing me this website, I would have to then go find Titanic on streaming
or go and I mean, I can't rent a copy, right?
I'd have to find it on streaming.
I'm not going to buy it on eBay.
I was like, "Oh, maybe my memory is destroyed."
But $13.99, I'll just sit here and be confused.
Eventually I watch it and I go, "I knew that was in the ending.
I could easily go track down."
Well, it wasn't that easy, right?
I had to find it on streaming.
I guess that's relatively easy, right?
You're like, "Dude, how lazy are you?"
I watch the ending and I go, "That jerk."
And the next time I see him, I was like, "Dude, that's not the ending of Titanic."
"Oh yeah, I was just joking with you, blah, blah, blah, blah."
He was James Cameron.
He wanted to get one more rental on Titanic.
That would be that process, right?
Someone is trying to convince me of something that I know for a fact didn't happen.
It happened.
They were trying to get me to change the ending.
And that's a very personalized example of it.
So what happens is people are going to keep pumping out all of this data.
And I'd say 99% of it is to be creative or funny, pulling a goof, right?
But as more and more and more and more of these AI images, and eventually we're going to get
AI generated video, like completely indistinguishable from the source video.
And I think audio would be the hardest part, but we'll get that too.
We're going to create all of this stuff that nowadays I can track down a copy of the movie
Titanic and watch it.
And reaffirm my belief that that wasn't the ending, that ending was never produced.
But future generations won't be able to do that.
It'll be harder for them to find a copy of these movies.
It'll be harder for them to track it down.
And really, I think at a certain point, they won't care.
The same way I don't care whether or not Chrome Lords is a real movie, it looks cool.
But if someone told me it was real and I just didn't catch it on video, I'd be like, "Oh,
that sucks.
Too bad I can't watch that.
That's unscathed."
And then I'd go about my day.
And you're going to create all of these illusions.
You're going to create all of these chunks of lost media spread throughout the internet
that people are just going to take as fact because it's easier to take as fact than it
will be to track down the truth.
And again, you're like, "Okay, Jason, people are messing with movie endings.
James Cameron, your personal friends at James Cameron, he's messing with your brain."
That also doesn't...
How does that change the world?
How does that break humanity?
I think that it's the stepping stones.
I won't wrap it up like this.
I don't want this episode to go on for too long.
But I think there are these stepping stones that, one, you convinced me that a movie never
existed.
That'd be fairly easy to do.
Because I don't know, there's a lot of movies out there.
As long as it wasn't something super bizarre, if they were like, "Do you ever see that movie
where Ronald Reagan had sex with a monkey?"
I'd be like, "That doesn't exist."
And if it does, I don't want to see it.
But if it's just the Chrome Lords, I'd be like, "Oh, yeah, man, that sounds like a cool
movie.
That sucks.
I lost media."
That's the first step.
And then you've got to convince me that a movie that I did see has changed in some way.
And I think that, when people are confronted with that, it does psychologically mess with
you.
When someone goes, "Hey, do you know C-3PO used to have one silver leg?"
You're like, "What?
No, that's not true."
Yeah, C-3PO had one silver leg.
He was like a junk robot.
He was just like...
It showed how just kind of worn out he was.
What are you talking about?
He had a full golden body.
And then someone shows you a photograph of C-3PO with a silver leg and you're like, "That
is weird."
That 100% was my experience when I saw that.
It was the same thing when the first time it came across.
The Mandela Effect was the Bernstein Bears in the way it was spelled.
And I go, "That is not true."
That messes with you a bit.
It really does.
It messes with you.
I can go, "I get the quotes.
Life was like a box of chocolates versus life is like a box of chocolates."
That doesn't mess with me, right?
But I know the way that book was spelled.
The C-3PO leg have kind of come to terms with it, but it still messes with me.
What happens though?
This is the ultimate test.
This is the ultimate psychological test.
This is where things like mid-journey AI and the people behind it, not the programmers,
but the people using it.
This is how bad things can get.
99% of the people using these programs are doing it for fun or for the art of it.
But what happens when...
What happens when someone is able to sit you down and ask, "What's your favorite movie?"
And you say, "Transformers 3."
They start laughing.
They're like, "Seriously, that's your favorite movie?
What's your favorite movie, Jason?"
"Transformers 3, Dark of the Moon."
It's not the best movie, but I love it.
What happens when they're able to convince you that your favorite movie, your favorite
movie, the movie you've seen so many times, you know it in and out.
You know it in and out.
What happens when someone's able to convince you that movie never existed?
Or if it existed, it was so radically different than what you remember.
What happens when the technology gets to that point where it's not creating new images,
but actually deconstructing what already exists?
And someone can sit you down and prove to you that your favorite movie never existed.
And you might think that's impossible, but is it?
It's hard.
It would be extremely hard, but it is not impossible.
It is not impossible.
I mean, you could say, "Let's take out torture."
Obviously, if someone started to waterboard me and say, "St. Transformers 3 never existed,
it's going to be a pretty short torture session."
I'm like, "Optimists, forgive me.
It never existed."
Outside of torture, outside of actual, like, your solitary confinement until you admit
minions 3 never existed, I think that it would work.
I think that you could honestly sit somebody down and prove to them that their favorite
thing is not real, or it is so radically different from what they remember.
It's basically a completely different movie.
And that's the real problem that we get into with this stuff.
That is the future of the Chrome Lords, because right now we're creating movies that never
existed, but eventually you will be able to create...
I mean, they could sit you down and they go, "Your favorite movie was Dangerous Liaisons."
Watch this.
They put the movie in and it's a totally different movie.
You're watching it and you're like that, I do not remember that scene.
I remember this scene, but wait, what?
I never saw Dangerous Liaisons.
I was like, "Some guy probably gets stabbed in some girls' boobs or probably bouncing around
in a corset."
But other than those two key scenes, everything else is different.
You could do it.
You could absolutely do it.
And again, people might do it on accident.
I want to go over this passage here before we wrap this up.
I thought this was really interesting.
Someone wrote this out on this thread, on this thread about the Chrome Lords AI.
Someone says, "I wonder if this will.
I wonder if this AI program will eventually be used maliciously to mess with historical
documentation."
For example, he gives this example.
Let's say you don't like the Mona Lisa.
You have the AI produce 100 million copies of the Mona Lisa with very, very minor changes.
And you can have this program running for years, creating all these alternative versions
of the Mona Lisa.
Some noticeably different, some slightly different, but you're actually filling the Internet
full of Mona Lisa's versus the limited number of actual photos taken of the Mona Lisa.
You've now created a million to one gulf between the fake images and the real image, which
there is a concrete number of actual photos taken of the Mona Lisa versus 100 million
false ones.
And he goes, "You could do the same thing on a bigger scale with maps, portraits, films,
etc.
You could flood the Internet with fake images, fake media, until it's absolutely impossible
to find historically accurate information like we can today.
Today I can stream Titanic."
But when Dogma came out, it was everywhere.
You could get a copy of Dogma everywhere.
Who's to say where we'll be in the future?
Now Titanic obviously is a much bigger movie than Dogma, but what happens when a streaming
service accidentally starts airing the wrong version of Titanic?
Now obviously the change of the ending would be so drastic, a lot of people would notice
it right away.
But let's say there was someone who wanted, who didn't like Titanic and started making
all of these minor changes and created thousands upon thousands of versions of Titanic that
only a super fan would notice the difference.
But as time goes on, the chances of people seeing the false version of Titanic would
override the chances of someone seeing the authentic version.
And the people who watched the movie early on, they'd be like, "I must have misremembered
that.
I swear in that scene he was wearing a life jacket, but in this version he's obviously
drowning."
You're just flooding the Internet full of all of this fake information.
And you're doing it on purpose, if you're being malicious about it, you're actually
trying to mislead people.
And this isn't impossible.
A long time ago Fabio Nurbon sent me a story where a guy actually did this.
Fabio Nurbon, a long time ago, sent me the story about the Street Sharks cartoon.
It's a cartoon from the 1990s.
And in 2003, there's this dude named Jordan Miner.
He was in middle school.
He found a website called TVTOME.com.
He started creating fake episodes and created a fake character and said that Henry Winkler
was the voice of this guy named Meat Hook and posted it all over TVTOME.
He became an editor of the Street Sharks TVTOME.
He's doing it as a joke.
And then TVTOME got bought by TV.com, which was owned by CBS Interactive Media.
So it got linked up into Wikipedia.
All this information got pushed onto Amazon.
It got pushed onto IMDb.
It became official information.
These episodes that never existed looked like they were lost media.
Looked like they popped up.
And since the cartoon was impossible to find, you could buy the DVD if you really wanted
to see Roxy the shark who never existed.
But most people just read it and accepted it as true.
Some guy wrote an article later on about Henry Winkler's career and he goes the lowest point
was when he was Meat Hook on Street Sharks.
What was he thinking?
He didn't think about it at all.
That never happened.
He never was on Street Sharks.
And that was just from a television Wiki page that got bought up by a corporate conglomerate.
And that happened.
The Titanic example seems extreme now because we know that that's not how it ended.
But the more the fakes come out, the more the real disappears.
I just find this absolutely fascinating.
I really do.
I think you could.
We see it happen with Mandela Effect.
We see it happen with the Street Sharks thing, right?
Where you can confuse people.
Our memories are Fruit of the Loom had a cornucopia.
But all of the images now say it doesn't.
Mandela Effect does add the paranormal theory onto it that we're shifting time streams.
And Mandela Effect may be real.
I think some of the examples are flawed.
But I've never said it doesn't exist.
I do think there is something behind the Mandela Effect.
What if you could just create Mandela Effect's 100 million of them in a matter of a week?
Really really break someone's brain if you could convince them that something they loved
never existed or was radically different.
I could damage the human psyche because there are so many things that song that you love.
You remember where you were the first time you heard it.
You know all the lyrics to it.
That album that got you through that bad breakup.
But then years later you go, "I want to check out that album.
I don't want to throw another bad breakout.
I'm going to check it out."
And there's more false versions of the album out there than the true.
And you listen to the false version and you go, "This isn't real.
This isn't real.
This isn't real."
But because the only thing you can find are the false versions, you have to realize that
no, your memories are false even though your memories were real.
The evidence is false.
The evidence today is fake.
That could really blow your brain out.
It really could mess with the sense of self that we have.
Because then you'll just question, "What is true?"
All these movies I watch, like it seems like 30, 40% of them are different than I remember.
All these songs I loved, it seems like so many of them are different.
It's not the same lyrics.
But anyone you talk to, if they didn't hear the original media 10 years ago, they will
go, "No, it always had that."
Imagine a world where your memories themselves outside of the Mandela Effect, like real life-changing
memories, moments that were so personal to you are being falsified over and over and
over and over again.
You would basically either have to choose, and I think this would be the most likely
thing, to believe the lie.
You go, "Well, maybe I heard all my favorite songs and all my favorite shows.
Maybe I'm wrong."
And you accept the lie.
Or you just go nuts, you realize that the world is false.
Things that you believe in can change rapidly, and everyone around you goes, "No, this was
how it always was."
And the creepiest thing about this whole thing is even if you do, for peace of mind, even
if you do to fit in, accept the lie.
You go, "I know these songs weren't super popular.
I know a bunch of people didn't listen to them back when I listened to them, and they're
saying they're different today."
Okay.
And I know the shows and the movies that I liked weren't super popular, and not everyone
saw them 10, 20 years ago, but people are saying they're like this today.
I must be wrong.
I must be remembering wrong.
The evidence in front of me is the truth.
This is the truth.
Even if you accepted that, you accepted the new reality, the way this AI is pumping out
images, the very next day, everything is different.
Every moment you have to sit and think, "I must be wrong."
This is the new truth.
And how long could the human brain do that before it finally, simply, broke?
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
TikTok is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great week, guys.
Bye.
[MUSIC]