Will humanity team up with one of its greatest enemies to defeat its current threat?
Is there currently secret coded messages appearing over shortwave radio?
And then we travel to England to take a look at three young boys out for a walk.
They expected a fun day of exploring the countryside.
Instead, they walked directly into the past, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I'm actually recording this at 10.30 in the morning, super early.
I'm normally working out right now.
I finished watching that show Freakish.
It's pretty good.
I recommend it.
They're not making a new season though, so some cliffhangers.
You gotta use some headcanon to figure out what you want the ending to be.
But overall, I enjoyed it.
I'm watching a new show called Zomboats.
It's about, it's a zombie comedy, which I normally abhor.
But you know, any zombie port in a zombie storm.
I'll check it out.
I watched the first two episodes.
It was clever.
I haven't laughed out loud, but it's clever.
Before people trying to escape on a canal boat, which apparently is the slowest boat.
The zombies are constantly like 30 yards behind the boat.
There are two episodes in it and it's the same group of zombies following them.
Pretty clever.
I did play my escape game last night, the Haunted Roller Coaster.
There's a box.
And you know, you guys know about those escape rooms, right?
You know, they made that terrible movie based on them, but there's actually like an escape
room you go and you pay to have you and your friends argue about who's the leader of the
group as you guys try to solve this puzzle.
You can replicate that anger at home through a boxed game.
They have the escape room in a box and it's only to be played once.
It's like 15 bucks you play at one time.
So I'm in self isolation.
I bought myself a copy.
I sat down last night and I played it.
It probably took about an hour and I had to use a couple of the solution cards because
the quizzes, some of the puzzles were really, really difficult, but it was fun.
Like yeah, it was 15 bucks for like a one time thing, which is also food, right?
You don't go, "Mmm, mm, mm, can't wait to eat that again."
"Bleugh."
And then eat your vomit.
Most stuff is a one time thing, but I enjoyed it.
I recommend doing it.
Now I don't know how much fun I would have had doing it with another person.
It's like, "No, don't look at the solution card yet.
Don't do that."
Yeah.
If you want to fray, if you want to start a fight while you guys are all quarantined
by it, but again, you can also just play by yourself.
It was really fun.
I enjoyed it.
So anyways, I recommend that.
Now we are going to give the keys to Eva Marie.
She's our newest Patreon supporter and this weekend is her birthday.
And since yesterday's episode got cut short, we're going to let her fly around.
We're going to let her drive us around.
It is a privilege to be our chauffeur.
So Eva Marie, I hope you got, you know, good back muscles.
Let's hop in the dead rabbit rowboat and you are going to row us across the big pond.
We're leaving behind America.
We're headed to France.
Now guys, I'm going to tell you this right now.
This is pretty good news.
Okay?
My fellow addicts out there, both drug addicts and spaces above houses addicts.
They're all involved because we need the addicts to store all this stuff.
And apparently in France, a bunch of doctors are sitting around and they go, we just got
new reports from China.
We put them in the shredder because China's lying to us about everything coronavirus related.
We're not even going to talk about China.
Done talking about China and their lies regarding this thing.
But in France, they were looking at these Chinese quote unquote results that doctors
are all rolling their eyes.
I hope another study from China throw it away, but they did start to notice something in
France.
And they started to notice something in France as well.
China said they had this, but again China says they had 3,000 deaths.
So they're lying.
France says this.
It's, let's look at the stats here.
25% of the French adult population smokes.
When we're having our patients come in, 8.5% of the patients coming in to the hospital
for coronavirus are smokers.
And the doctor, like that's kind of a weird statistic.
And the head doctor is like, it is weird.
Like we expected it to honestly be higher because this disease can attack the lungs,
but it can also attack the central nervous system.
That's why they say people will start to lose their sense of taste.
That's why they say people lose their sense of smell.
Sometimes has a nervous, I have a theory about that.
I have a theory if it gets in your eyes, it causes neurological things.
If it gets in your throat, it'll cause the lung thing, but it's the same disease.
But I'm not a doctor and I have nothing to back it up, but because it doesn't affect
everyone the same way.
They go, it's weird.
We expected honestly to have that basically be a preexisting condition.
We know smoking is bad for your lungs.
If this thing attacks your lungs, which it primarily does, you're boned, right?
And you're already full of black tar.
So when they started getting these patients coming in and they knew Italy had a high smoking
rate, they knew China had a high smoking rate, but again, you can't trust anything coming
out of that government.
They expected the results there and it's not the case at all.
So they started doing a study.
They started doing a study where they are taking people who currently are infected with the
coronavirus and putting nicotine patches on their skin.
This is their theory.
Despite the fact that smoking can actually weaken your lungs, they believe there is something
in cigarettes and they are pinpointing nicotine itself that can not only help you if you have
the coronavirus, but it may prevent you from getting it in the first place.
So here's the thing, nicotine down regulates your ACE2 receptors.
That is old research.
They've known that for a long time, a couple of years.
I won't say it's like super old, but they've known that for a while.
The coronavirus needs to have your ACE2 regulators flying up.
"Gay, give me some, give me some of you to sweet, sweet coronavirus.
Come on, touch me."
Nicotine actually down regulates those receptors.
Makes it harder for the coronavirus to get into your lungs.
They also believe because nicotine can work on the central nervous system that it can
stop it from getting into your central nervous system as well.
So this study is going on right now.
They're putting nicotine patches on it.
In France, the French researchers are saying, "Listen, this is an addictive drug."
And I read an article and they said, "In the end, 50% of the people who smoke, it kills
them."
And that doesn't necessarily mean lung cancer.
Obviously, it causes cardiovascular issues as well.
And I don't know if that statistic is true, honestly.
That sounds quite bizarre if it really is 50%, but maybe they lump in all these different
things.
That sounds extreme.
The point is, is that here's a study that's going on right now that scientists have, when
this whole thing started, they go, "I've read other studies on this.
This is the first official one, but I've read other papers on this where they're like, 'We
do know nicotine down regulates ACE2.'
This might be a treatment option."
So would you be willing as a society to embrace nicotine?
We've been taught our whole lives how awful and horrible it is.
And it may actually be not only a treatment if you have it, but a preventative measure
if you don't.
And I know what you, I know what long-term listeners of the show are thinking.
Jason, does this mean you're going to start doing nicotine lossages again after not taking
them for eight months, nine months of this time?
Only time will tell, my friends.
Only time will tell.
Wouldn't that be awesome though you go to the doctor and they're like, "Oh, here you
go, nicotine."
And I miss nicotine.
I think that's my drug of choice.
I keep going to those subreddits.
I'm still going to the meth subreddit and the opiate subreddit, the crippling alcoholism
subreddit.
I found there's a subreddit just for heroin.
I mean, they don't want to be lumped in with the pill takers of opiates.
How does this stuff up online?
Like, I get it.
I always thought Reddit was like the prissy principle.
No, they have a subreddit directly dedicated to doing heroin.
And they even go, "This isn't about harm reduction, guys.
This is about how much we love heroin."
There's a subreddit called heroin-hotties.
There's not many of those.
I don't even know how a person on heroin operates a phone, how they can even post.
There's a subreddit I found today for PCP users.
And I scrolled through it a couple times and I already came across two posts and they're
both like, "Help!
I need your help right now!"
Which I imagine is what everyone on PCP says.
Nicotine, it's a wave of the future, guys.
Let's move on to our next story.
Our next story we actually found on Reddit, too.
Eva Marie, let's hop in that Jason Jalopy.
We are driving out to Germany.
So that's pretty good, pretty close, right?
I imagine France isn't too happy about being that close to Germany, you know, considering
world events.
And as we're driving to Germany, and really this is happening all over Europe, but I've
seen this come out of Germany, Netherlands, France as well, that's a rumor of where this
is coming from.
But as we're driving around just Europe in general, taking a look at, do you guys still
have battlefields over there?
Like in America, they're like, "This is Gettysburg.
It's like a park where you can go and you can walk around, eat a sandwich."
I don't know really what you would do there.
I think it would probably be cool to go there, but you know, like, or you could just show me
a picture.
Do they have?
I mean, I guess probably not, because everywhere was a battlefield in Europe.
You're like, "Here's Paris.
It's a national park.
You can't go in there."
Like everything ended up getting bombed out at some point.
But like Normandy, can you bring a metal detector to Normandy?
Just walk around, looking for stuff?
Or can you just hang out on the beach or surfing?
Whoa, hang 10 veterans.
I wonder if it's a national park over there, but again, everywhere would be a national
park.
Normandy's like, "Oh, we don't want to talk about that.
We don't want to talk about the two world wars we lost."
Anyways, we're driving around Germany going, "Losers, losers."
Everyone's like, "We will rise again, losers."
Moaning them.
Anyways, anyways, after we're done getting beat up by a bunch of Germans for mocking them,
we turn on the radio of the car.
Found this on Reddit.
There's a user named shadowpeople4life.
That is a name I can get behind.
That's a name I can get behind.
So thank you, shadowpeople4life.
We're listening to the radio.
Now what's going on?
I'm going to play you a clip.
So this is the part where you can start lowering the volume.
If you have headphones on, I'm going to try to minimize the damage, obviously.
Not going to have it start off super loud, but if you're across the room working on something,
you can start to turn the volume down a second.
What's happening is in the shortwave radio community, people are sitting there with their
headphones on, turning the dial.
Hey, everybody, this is Old Candy Cane driving down the road.
Turning the dial some more.
Hey, hey, Barney, is that you?
Yeah, it is me, Piccolo Pete.
How you doing?
I'm doing good, but I got to keep dialing this dial.
And then what's happening is people are coming across this signal.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Now, I played a little bit of it for you, and it goes on and on.
And I didn't want to basically be the rest of the podcast just noises.
But what you've heard in that clip starts off-- and I have different clips of this, so I may
be not describing it in the right order, but you're going to hear a tone like a siren-type
tone, actual American police sirens, wolves, the howling of wolves, and then people talking.
Now, people are saying that they're speaking English.
It sounds like it, but I can't really decipher what they're saying.
Now, the shortwave radio community has no idea what this is.
There's a couple different theories, but people keep tuning back into this.
First off, you have that it's a glitch.
Some people said that.
You guys who have shortwave radios, I'm sure some of you guys do, I always thought it'd
be cool to get into in 1992.
But nowadays, I'm sure it would still be cool to get into.
It's just nothing that I really have time for.
When I was in high school, I thought it was awesome, but not knocking it.
It probably is pretty fun.
It's on the 3460 kilohertz channel out of the Netherlands or something like that.
But nobody knows for sure.
I guess some people are saying that it's a French pirate radio station and if you have
your setup wrong, it sounds like that.
That sounds a little iffy, but again, I don't know anything about shortwave radio.
I know about real radio.
If I have my radio upside down, it doesn't turn from Shakira to Blink 182.
A sound is a sound, right?
You could even say, let's say you rigged up, so you're listening.
Shakira is playing on an FM radio, but somehow you're able to get it on the AM station.
Shakira is not going to sound like a bunch of wolves howling.
She didn't have that one song called "She Wolf."
But the point is that she's still not going to sound like that.
So some people say, one person came out and said, "This is actually a French pirate radio
station that does techno music, and you're listening to it with this wrong setting."
So that's why it sounds like that.
And that might work for me, but people who are in the shortwave radio community, I don't
think they all went, "Slap their head," and they go, "Oh, he's right."
People are like, "No, no, no.
That's not the case.
I know how to work my shortwave."
Some people say it's a glitch, and that kind of goes with the French thing, too, that something's
not translating, right?
It's weird that you hear those elements.
Some people are already larping, and they're saying they can hear it when they stick their
head out their window.
This is like starting April 20th.
This is super, super recent.
People are already larping it.
And that's the thing that we've got to be aware of in this community.
You're going to get a lot of liars and a lot of jokers.
A lot of people just having fun like the Penguin guy yesterday.
So it's never being a rush to take this stuff too seriously.
Like, obviously these tones are real.
Someone could have made these tones and could be making an ARG, but you already have people
saying, "I stuck my head out the window in an ARG."
So expect to hear that.
Expect to hear those fanciful tales start spreading.
Really want to look at the facts there.
But speaking of not having any facts, the main theory among the shortwave radio community
that I've seen is that this is some sort of code or call to action.
Basically, when you think of wolves, you think of two things.
A lone wolf and a wolf pack.
Right?
And so it could signal a code as far as it's time for the lone wolves to do something.
You got your orders guys.
Go out and do this stuff.
Or it could be a symbol of it's time to form the pack.
It's time to get everything in together.
When you have the police sirens, obviously, that makes you, that raises an alarm.
That's what they literally are.
They are alarms.
Letting people know that they're coming.
So it's funny because that's kind of it.
People are really trying to run in this stuff through analyzers and spectrograms and trying
to figure out if there's any sort of other type of message.
But for right now, the shortwave community is just listening in to see if there's anything
else coming through that stream.
It's funny because of one of the groups of people that are monitoring this are people
who normally monitor number stations where you basically can tune in and it goes like
five, nine, blark, nine, seventy, nine, twelve.
They really like nines for a reason.
But they basically read off numbers.
Sometimes they're not necessarily numbers.
It'll be words, like simple words that don't make any sense.
Sometimes they're in English.
Sometimes they're in Russia.
That's most likely.
Number stations have been around since the Cold War.
I think number stations, honestly, probably have been around since radio.
And I bet you anything is just, and I think this is not anything groundbreaking.
It's code.
So if you're in Istanbul and you're running in operations and you're a CIA agent, you
can tune in and you'll hear that dace code and then we go to your talk to your handler
and reveal.
I mean, that may be an oversimplification of it, but it's most likely code that you
listen from 630.
Your job, your code plays between 6pm and 6.04.
And that number or whatever they give you then, again, the super oversimplification
of it could be more advanced than that.
Then my Neanderthal version, me no number four, let me in secret base.
They're like, oh, okay, Neanderthal CIA agent.
That is a new Nickelodeon show, bro.
Neanderthal, FBI.
I know I just said CIA, but kids don't want to learn about the CIA.
Kids know about the FBI.
You have a caveman who works for the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
James Wan, I know you listen to the show.
Make that happen.
Just split.
You got to split me that money because that Nickelodeon money, that's good money.
Let's go ahead and move on from Neanderthal FBI.
We are going on to his partners in Dinosaur.
You don't even have to make an animated, right?
It would be better if it was a live action.
And then you have this giant dude, giant hairy guy, right?
Okay, I guess it's not really what kids want to see.
They're like, you look like daddy.
Daddy without a shirt on.
No, you just have a giant caveman, right?
I'm off topic.
You have a giant caveman, right?
He's like walking through the bureau and he gets assigned with a dinosaur.
But, and you go, James, so that's kind of trite.
No, no, no, you didn't let me finish.
He hates dinosaurs because they ate his family and stuff like that.
So us dinosaurs are cute because we only see them in like movies or like Barney, right?
Or chickens.
But to him, the dinosaur represents like everything he hates.
Me remember, 9/11.
That's when dinosaur 8, 911 of my tribe.
I do not work with dinosaurs and the dinosaur.
Dinosaurs like a Chester cheetah dude with like the sunglasses, tiny little T-Rex arms.
He's sitting back.
He's like, that was in the past.
Literally that was in the past.
That was 65 million years ago, bro.
So but anyways, anyways, we're leaving behind Neanderthal FBI.
We're leaving behind his new partner, Tommy T.
We are headed out to Britain.
This has actually been a pretty European-heavy episode.
I didn't plan it that way.
We are leaving behind all of our new friends that I just made up.
We are headed out to Britain.
Fire up that Carbentercopter one last time, this episode, Eva Marie.
We are going to a little town named Curse in the province of Suffolk in the quaint little
country known as England, or as I often refer to England as a city.
I've called England a city multiple times on this podcast.
I don't care.
We're going to Curse.
The year is 1957.
The month is October.
Spooky, spooky pumpkins out on porches, which is so many witches flying.
You can't even see the moon sometimes.
Sucks.
But these three, it's not nighttime, so it's not super spooky.
None of that stuff has happened yet.
There's three young men.
They're British Royal Navy cadets.
So we're flying overhead and we see these three young men walking through.
And I'm like, land here, land here, and Eva Marie brings the helicopter down.
And we land in a little pasture.
We sit, we pull out our binoculars.
You brought your binoculars this episode, right?
Because you're not borrowing mine, bro.
Not getting none of your pink eye.
I got my binoculars on looking out.
We see these three kids walking.
Now, they're all 15 years old.
They're all members of the British Royal Navy cadets.
And they're on a pathfinding exercise.
So basically the British Royal Navy cadet group is all sitting around and they're like,
"Dude, are we going to learn guns today?"
And they're like, "Yes, we're going to learn guns, but those three losers don't know how
to shoot."
So hey, you, Tony, Joey, Michael, you come here.
We don't know their real names, but that's very British sounding names, right?
Tony, Michael, and Joe, I don't remember who the second guy was.
Even the guy running the cadets.
He's like, "I'm not going to bother learning your names."
As the other kids are loading up their really cool guns, he gets down on his knees.
He goes, "Hey, kids.
Hey, Michael, Tony, and Joe.
You guys are going to go on a map making quest.
You're going to try to find your way back to base.
We leave you.
You go somewhere.
And if you can find us again, you get a gold star."
They're like, "Yay, we're totally, yeah, can't wait to get a gold star."
They go running off.
He's like, "They should have brought supplies, but they didn't.
Anyways, they take off."
The point is, is that they are on a path finding expedition by themselves.
So I don't know if they're the losers of the group.
Allegedly, my version.
Don't sue me.
So anyways, Michael, Joey, and Tom, I don't remember their names either, are walking through
the countryside.
Which, I mean, could you figure out a worse way to spend an October afternoon just walking
around, walking around the city of England?
I'm sure it's quite beautiful.
Now they're walking through and they see, cursey.
A little town, right?
They hear the church bells ringing.
Jing-dong.
Ding-dong.
And the kids go, "That is perfect.
Like, we have to eventually find our way back to camp and hope that they just don't get
there and there's just a note and an empty camp."
And it's like, "Losers."
That's their fear.
They know this is actually part of their training, but at the same time they're thinking,
"What if the entire navy leaves before we get back?"
So they figure, "Let's go through the town.
Let's go through the town of Cursey.
It looks like a nice thing.
Maybe we'll buy some..."
What do they eat over there?
Maybe we'll buy some biscuits and gravy or sausage and mutton or whatever.
Whatever the hell British people eat.
Boiled lamb.
So they're walking through.
They're like, "Oh, I can't wait to eat some boiled lamb."
They're walking into town.
And then ding dong ding.
Church bells stop ringing.
Now, that's not super abnormal.
Church bells don't go 24 hours a day.
Like they eventually do stop ringing, right?
They're like, "That's weird.
It stopped ringing mid-ding.
Like everyone knows it goes ding dong."
But it just went ding.
That's weird.
Physics.
And Tony goes, "Well, yeah, that is kind of weird.
But let's just keep walking through this town.
Because this town's not weird.
Look."
They're kind of like just looking around.
Just normal buildings right now.
But they notice that the town itself is quiet.
The town itself seems to be empty.
But off in the distance, those, that was the sound of ducks playing in the water.
So it makes the kids go, "It is weird that this town's empty."
That's kind of weird.
Maybe they all left too.
Maybe the entire country of England is pulling one giant practical joke on these kids.
The entire country moved to France.
These three kids are going to be left alone.
But no.
So they go, "That's weird that the town's empty.
But we can still hear baby ducks."
So you can't, generally when there's like a serial killer or a monster running through
the neighborhood, the baby ducks are the first to go, right?
They're totally out of there.
So as long as you can hear baby ducks, you're fine.
As they're walking through town, they do start to notice some bizarre things.
I mean, obviously the town's deserted and they only got a ding.
But the trees have leaves on them.
That's something that I wouldn't pick out.
I mean, I'm an observant guy for other humans and animals.
Like if I'm walking down the street, I'm caught, which I haven't done in so long.
But when I'm out and about, the thing I'm looking for is human adversaries, attractive
women and hostile animals.
In that order, honestly.
So walking down the street, see a cute girl.
Oh, that'll turn my head.
Walking down the street and see someone who I think can cause me damage definitely will
turn my head.
My body language will change.
See a hostile animal.
Body language will change.
If I was walking down the street and I turned a corner and all of a sudden there had leaves
on the tree, I would not even notice that.
Now if I was walking down the street and it was snowing, I turned a corner and there was
no snow.
I would thank God so much.
But I don't, unless I kept being no snow, I don't think I would thank, I would think,
oh, just a snowplow was here.
I'm not super observant for stuff that can't kill me, basically.
I have super heightened spidey sense for things that can kill me and beautiful women.
But trees in the winter, no leaves.
But now that they're walking through town, they notice green leaves.
This might also be why I'm not a Royal Navy cadet.
They're probably because I have that low situational awareness.
I don't notice when leaves should be on trees.
But anyways, they think that's a weird detail.
So they start to go, wait a second, those shouldn't be leaves on those trees, right?
Like it's winter, it's October and the other kids are like, that is a weird detail.
But let's just keep walking through town, because at this point there are a couple blocks
into town.
What are you gonna do?
You're gonna turn around, things might even be spookier.
I would turn around just to play with the baby ducks, but they keep moving farther away
from the baby ducks.
There's no cars at all.
They're all gone.
The church tower, whose ringing bell attracted them to walk through the town in the first
place.
The church tower they can no longer see as they're walking through the city.
Now they start to get nervous, but again, your brain's gonna work in a similar way.
There's such a way that you think, maybe I'm in a part of the city where I can't see the
largest structure in the city.
The church tower you could see from a distance, it was the largest structure.
But you think, maybe I'm walking among these houses, maybe I can't see that.
As they're walking through town, they don't see anyone.
There's no cars, there's no telephone lines, no telephone poles, nothing.
Now some of the houses, some of the shops, they can see through the windows.
They see a butcher's shop.
They're like, "Boy, old lamb!"
And they all run to the window and they look through.
It's empty of humans.
But hanging inside the butcher's shop are large cuts of rotting meat.
Just from where they were looking at, they could see the green putrification of the
carcass on the hook.
So here's a quote from one of the boys.
Now that I've looked farther down my notes, one of the boys is named William.
Did I name one of my fake kids William?
I don't think so.
But anyways, one of the boys, we do have his real name, is William Lang.
There you go for not looking at your notes all the way.
Here's a quote he had about his time in this town.
"It was a ghost village, so to speak.
It was almost as if we had walked back in time.
I experienced an overwhelming feeling of sadness and depression and cursey, but also
a feeling of unfriendliness and unseen watchers which sense shivers up one's back.
I wonder if we knocked at a door to ask a question who might have answered it.
It doesn't bear thinking about."
After all of these events, the unseen eyes looking at them, realizing they can't see
any traces of modern technology, after looking in the butcher's shop and seeing the rotting
meat, the three kids run out of town, and when they leave town, when they get past the city
limits, they turn around, cars are driving through the town, they see telephone poles,
they see trees with no leaves, they see the church steeple.
No word on the baby ducks, but we can assume they are still there.
At some point I'm sure they went back and finally found the Navy cadets and they were
like "Oh good, you got here just in time guys."
But anyways, I don't know if they told this story to the Navy, there's no point in that,
but they did eventually end up telling this story.
Now this puzzled them for decades, and as adults they got back together pinniewyestyle
and said "Let's figure out what this could have been."
Then they got with a psychic researcher, so I mean, basically probably could have saved
their money on that one, but anyways, these three guys who experienced something very
real to them and someone who gets paid to lie to people, team up to form a group, this
is what they discovered through their research.
The psychic researcher was like "Oh yeah, no, I was totally gonna like look into the
past, but you have that history book there, so I'll just save my psychic energy."
You can keep looking in that book.
I'm sure honestly the internet has helped psychics more than anyone, not only from finding
rubes to pay them for stuff, but for being able to say "Oh your name is Jason Carpenter?
Yeah, no, come meet me Friday and then they can Google everything about me."
And they're like "I sense that you spend a lot of time talking."
"Whoa, golly, how'd you know I had a podcast?"
Well, they use the internet, but anyways, back then, back when this story started coming
out when these kids are getting together, the psychic quote researcher, which is a researcher,
had a library card, could go find the stuff out.
Anyways, that was your skeptical minute on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Anyway, this is what they found out, because obviously there's a lot of details, a lot
of history of the town.
There was no butcher shop in Kersi since 1905, which makes sense.
Like when's the last time you actually saw a butcher shop?
There's grocery stores that have butcher places in it, or unless you work in slaughterhouse,
then you see it all the time.
But there was no butcher shop in that place since 1905.
So the idea is these guys must have teleported back in time to at least 1905.
But some people, because this story started to gain traction, these young men came forward,
other people have done research, so they go at the very latest, because the idea is they
walked into the past.
I don't know if that was implicitly said, but that they walked through some sort of portal,
they walked to Kersi, not of 1957, but of some time previous.
The very latest it could have been was 1905.
Some people place it as far back as the year 1350.
The church tower that should have been visible from any point in town, if you go there today,
you can see it from any point in town, was built in 1481.
So now you're pushing it farther back.
If they cannot see the church tower, I mean not hearing it, again they don't ring their
bells all the time, but if you can't see the church tower if I walk in through the town,
we're talking pre-1481.
Now some people obviously are skeptical about this story, they say the kids made it up.
There's one detail in particular that they say, other than the fact it's three board
teenagers walking through England, like people can make up stuff for any reason.
We have to be aware of that when we're talking about this stuff, that people make up stuff
all the time, like I said in the previous segment, and that's just something you kind
of have to deal with.
People say they're making it up.
A town that size in the 1400s would not have its own butcher shop.
It just wouldn't be there.
Now other people go, but we have town records saying there was a butcher shop until 1905,
but they go, ah you know, they must have been bringing it, they might have had a shop where
they were selling meat?
But a town that size wouldn't have a shop where they were cutting like an actual operational
butcher shop.
The town didn't have that.
However other people have put, this is a weird argument, but other people have pushed back
and said the town actually was very wealthy.
We know that, they made a ton of money off wool, and we know they were wealthy because
they have had glass windows for a very long time, and we covered that a long time ago.
The thing was in the episode, in the first 100 episodes, about how glass used to be
a sign of immense wealth, to the point that people who were super wealthy started to believe
their bodies were made of glass, and if they sat down they would break.
It's called the glass delusion.
Yeah, it's not an old episode, but yeah, because glass was associated with wealth, and wealthy
people, only wealthy people got this mental illness where they thought their body had
become glass.
They refused to move out of bed.
Some people believe they became cork, which was also a sign of wealth, because you had
to get it out of the trees and everything, the cork trees.
They were afraid that they would bobble along in the bath.
That would be very easy to prove.
Just put a bunch of water in there.
They won't bobble.
But anyways, so yeah, they go, the town probably did have its own butcher shop.
If they had enough money that everyone had windows, glass windows, they would be able
to have their own operational butcher shop, so nothing's being moved in the town.
Plus the fact that the kids specifically saw the glass windows is more of a point in their
favor, because they're seeing something that town actually had.
If they were walking through, they walked through a quote unquote "time warp" they were
making the story up and they walked through a town that wasn't poverished, that didn't
have windows back then, and they said there were windows, it would be easily disputable.
But they happened to walk through a town that was rich enough to have glass in their windows.
I've always been a fan of portals.
I think they're very creepy too.
It's one of those phenomenon that you just can't predict.
You don't want to get attacked by a bigfoot, don't go into the woods, or the desert, or
really any place where a bigfoot can hang out.
Don't go to the Himalayas.
You don't want to get attacked by a ghost, don't go to a haunted house.
But portals just seem to *vvv* appear.
And you don't know what's going to be on the other side.
And you don't know if you'll be able to get back home.
I think there's something intrinsically scary about thinking you could walk out of your
house, go down the street, turn around, come back, and you're no longer in your neighborhood.
Sure it looks like your house, and your neighbors may look like your neighbors, but you know
you're somewhere different.
Could you find a way back?
Or even more terrifying is you just go for a quaint afternoon stroll and then when you
come back home, you realize you're the only one for city blocks.
You're the only one left in the city.
And for all you know, you're just the only one left.
These are supernatural stories, obviously.
And you could say they can never happen.
And I could say they may happen.
As remote as the possibility could be, I believe that it could happen.
Virtual portals, time portals, dimensional portals, they all sound like science fiction,
and I'm totally aware of that.
But it's one of the very few phenomenon that I both believe in and am terrified of.
I can avoid a cryptid, I can avoid a ghost, I can avoid a demon.
I can even avoid a hostile human.
But you can't avoid nature.
You can't avoid a glitch in the system.
You can only hope that you can survive it long enough to find your way back home.
And you know what?
We're going to end this Friday episode with something a little different.
Something that I've wanted to do for a long time.
We're going to have a special musical guest.
I've talked about this band before, Local Hood River Band.
I'm a big fan of them.
They're called Sun Diver.
And I got permission from the lead singer, Aaron, to actually play one of their songs
on this show.
This song reminds me of a breakup on a summer day back in 2006.
This song reminds me of trying to fall asleep alone in bed.
I love this song.
This is Branch Davidian by Sun Diver.
This is a song that I've been listening to for a long time.
Be safe, be kind, have a great weekend and I will see you Monday.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]