What happens when your soulmate turns out to be a
Bigfoot and then we take a look at a story of two boats crashing on the exact same island
At the same time and depending on which boat you're on you either live or get eaten today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. I want to start this episode off with the correction a
Long time ago to remember what episode it was on I said that I was not a fan of post Malone
That is wrong now that kid slaps dude like I've been listening to the radio a lot post if you're listening to this podcast I
Apologize for saying that I didn't like your music. It's pretty good. It's really good. Okay now that that's out of the way now that
That correction is out of the way. I want to give a shout out to our newest patreon supporter Dennis
key recall
Dennis key recall. Thank you so much for supporting the show
It really really means a lot and if you can't support the patreon that's fine, too
Just help get the word out about the show
We also have a merch store and you can jump on the Minecraft server
That doesn't help me in any way shape or form, but it's fun to play with you guys, but Dennis. Let's go ahead
We're gonna start off in the Dead Rabbit Durgible. We haven't taken that for a while
We're gonna take a nice slow trip from the United States to Russia, which is actually where Dennis is from
I actually didn't plan this so that's perfect. He's like he has to fly all the way out to America now. He's all he's all tired
He's slowly flying the Durgible. I'll fall asleep by the control wake up wake up. Don't fall asleep. We're about to hit something
What was like 10,000 feet in the air? Yeah. Yeah, I just didn't want you to sleep with the wheel
So eventually after 10 cups of coffee and us constantly pestering him we finally fly out to Russia
It's the mid-1800s
And we're flying over Mongolia is really the area where he's like I thought we were flying Russia's idea
We're flying over Russia's what I meant to say. He's like oh man. I was gonna check my mail
Flying over it's the mid-1800s now. There's a Russian author named Ivan
Turganov now he reportedly told this story
I'm about to tell you to a guy named guy. That's actually his name guy D
Guy D. Mopazin so he's the one who tells the story to us
Basically, it's a game of old-fashioned tell before telephones are invented. This was a game of telephone
I also saw a note that this guy guy is thinking this guy D
Mopazin't he was considered the master of the short story and on Wikipedia
They said his first story was considered his greatest work that would suck dude
The first thing you ever did was the best thing ever and he wrote like 200 stories
Everyone's like yeah, it's not as good as your first story
Anyways, so that's why he had to tell us when he's like no no no no. I'll tell you a really cool story
We're going back in time. There's this guy named Ivan who's also an author
But when he's not writing he's hunting so he's out in the woods. He has it's in the mid-1800s
So he has like a musket and stuff. He's like I better make this shot otherwise
It'll take me two days to load a new one. He's blowing stuff up
And then he's like oh
Man that sure was hard work killing all those animals
I think I'm gonna take a swim so he sits there and he takes off his little wooly cap his wooly jacket
His wooly pants. He's totally naked and he's like nothing like a brisk Mongolian morning to really wake you up
He jumps into the river
And he's swimming there now we're standing on the shore and Dennis looks over and he goes
Did you really bring a bring me out here to watch a naked guy swim and I'm like wait for it
Splashing around he's swimming he's swimming he's swimming in the river and he feels something on his shoulder
You kind of shake it off. You know, maybe it's a spider. Maybe it's a spider, right?
And then he thinks wait no why would a spider be in the middle of the river and he slowly
Turns around and he sees a big ol hairy hand on his shoulder
And he's like I should turn around a little more fast
But I'm gonna slowly turn around for dramatic sake and then he starts to see a hairy wrist and he's like oh this isn't good
He's still slowly turning around. He sees a hairy arm. He's like I'm gonna turn around a little bit more the rest of it
Better not be hairy he turns and
There's a big foot behind him, but not just any big foot
It's a woman big foot has a big ol smile on its face and a look in her eye
She's ready for some loving
Now I don't know about you first off
I'm not a swimmer, but that really has nothing to do with this if I was walking through the woods or just sitting at home
And I fell tall and on my shoulder. I'm turning around much quicker than Ivan did but if I saw like a big foot lady
And she looked like she wanted to have sex with me. I'd be a little flattered
I'd be a little curious
But I would be I'd leave right right. I mean actually not that she think about okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you'd leave you'd leave right because
Like it's an animal
That's actually not well. No, is that the only thing stopping me from banging big foot if it was like a big foot and she had already
Attended college and I knew she was like a rational person. She's all wearing glasses and long hair and it's all done up
She didn't have glasses. I'm like what you don't have glasses. I'm not having sex with you big foot lady
If you saw a female big foot and you knew that it wasn't an animal. It was just like this
It's just a human a hairy human. I guess am I saying what I have sex with a hairy human female?
Yes, I would I don't even know why I have to qualify that
But if it was a monstrous beast if it had the brain of a monster, I'd beat feet right and you don't know
Plus he's in a river so he doesn't have much time. He couldn't be like hmm
Can I do an IQ test on this thing? He panics right? He's not as progressive as I am
He starts swimming away from this thing. It's almost like blind fear and he's splashing in the water
And then he hears it swimming behind him splash splash splash splash splash over the raging river
It might have just been a bro. I don't know what anyways has their dodging rocks boulders are coming down him hot law the shooting
I'm making it so more dramatic. He's swimming the creature swimming after him
He jumps up now
He's totally naked right and he's thinking there are my clothes. There's my gun, but right behind me is this giant hairy woman
He takes another look. He's like maybe no no no
Bloze that thought up should I grab the clothes should I grab the gun, but then he thinks it's a musket
It's gonna take me two weeks to load it. He takes off running in the woods and he hears a squealing
Jump out of the water not the sound effect. That's big foot jumps out of the water and make that noise
Female big foot is now chasing him through the woods
Apparently it's the crypt keeper
He's running he's running and then like oh no, which way do I go? I guess there's only one way to go
It's a forest I can go straight. He sees a young boy in the distance and he's running. He's running
He doesn't know why but he's thinking I
Have a feeling that young boy is going to solve all of my problems and is he
Probably because whatever is behind me will eat the child and then I can definitely get away
he's running he's running and the creatures right behind him and
Then the kid pulls out a whip and straight Indiana Jones style
Which starts whipping lady bigfoot?
She stops in her tracks, right? I think a whip will stop anyone
She's holding her arm she turns and she runs in the other direction and the kids like non-plus about the whole thing
He basically rolls a cigarette afterwards
Smokes it and Ivan's completely out of breath now
He's embarrassed because he's just having clothes on and he was being chased by a female bigfoot
So Ivan walks up to the little kid little kids standing there with his whip bigfoot ladies running off still squealing
Ivan's like yo, what was that like you were just standing there waiting for her and
Little kid looks at looks up at Ivan roll rolls a little cigarette puts it in his mouth
He's not making kissy faces. He's smoking the cigarette. He goes
Yeah, we're not scared of her around here. It's just normal
Ivan's like, what do you mean normal little kids like tell you what why don't you go to the village?
They'll take care of you get you some clothes. They'll figure stuff out you go
You know you're getting kind of weird just standing in the forest naked just go go so he go Ivan goes to the village
He walks in and he goes guys guys
You won't believe what just happened to me and everyone's everyone's sitting around smoking cigarettes
Let me guess let me guess
Apparently something involved you taking your clothes off so I'm not for sure what that is but
We imagine that you probably met the bigfoot lady taking drag everyone takes his jacket to cigarette at the exact same time
Yeah, why is nobody shocked that you're more shocked than I'm naked than the fact that there's a bigfoot lady walking around
And he's like and there was a little kid out there too with the whip. They're like, oh, yeah, Jerry
Jerry's one of her Jerry's that he's supposed to be doing his choice. Uh, yeah, whatever his name was he wasn't scared at all
He just started whipping this big old monster lady and they're like, yeah
Welcome to Mongolia dude. They said that the woman was actually a local crazy woman living in the woods
That she wasn't a monster. She was just some tall hairy
squealing woman who they have to deal with from time to time aka run her out of town with whips
And Ivan's like
He's a little dicey on that he does eventually go get his clothes
He's not naked when he's telling this story to guy years later
He's like and that's the reason why I'm naked in front of you right now and everyone's like what it's a weird story
He did eventually go get his clothes and his gun. He thought about it
He goes that doesn't really make sense that doesn't really make sense
But over time he started to go well, maybe it was just a crazy lady
But when guy retells the story later on he goes
Yeah, I even started to kind of believe that explanation, but this is the last line of guy story
Yet it was known in the 19th century that people do not get covered with thick hair all over their bodies
Even if they lived alone in the woods
So guy believes that it was some sort of
Obviously the word Bigfoot wasn't around in the 1800s in France or England or anything like that
But you would have had mountain man or yaoi or any other word
But the term Bigfoot is fairly new sasquatch things like that from people who'd been traveling around the world hearing these stories
But I've been in the end believes the story. I think but guy doesn't I think it's interesting because you would want to
Yeah, as opposed to this as I want to believe is just a picture of a hairy woman like read in the newspaper
You would want to believe that it was just some hairy chick chasing you down as opposed to an actual Bigfoot
Because what would that say about you? Yes, I did say that I would have mixed feelings about going on a date with a Bigfoot, but
Like if an ugly human woman is attracted to you at least she's human if you're attracting
biological creatures that are known for their size strength and smell
What does that say about you? Ivan's like at night. He's like no it was a human. It was a human. It was just a human
It's just a human girl. It's just a hairy human girl. He's rocking as he's rocking back and forth in his bed
And guy pops up in the window. No, it was Bigfoot. Bigfoot likes you
I don't know. I think I'd be flattered if a female Bigfoot had a crush on me
I don't know what I would do if she was a rational consenting adult Bigfoot
I might at least take her out to the movies, but
Wouldn't you I mean like you're curious obviously, right? You're like hey everyone just now goes no, it's it's Bigfoot
It's Bigfoot
Is Dennis's like can we hop in the carboner copter we can good sir we can let's go ahead and hop in that carboner copter
I'm waving goodbye to my new girlfriend. She's on
Blowing cuz is that me I'm like see she's cool. We're taking off. We're leaving behind Mongolia Dennis fly that carboner copter
We are headed out to the Auckland Islands
We're going back to your 1864. This is actually pretty much just a few years after this
Bigfoot and love story
We're going to the Auckland Islands. There's a boat called the Grafton
It's a whaling vessel and we're looking down at it and it's just getting beat up by the water
Water's punching it the water forms a hand and it's ripping it up. They're like what's going on?
We thought we knew physics, but apparently not water is doing a body slam on it
It's getting bad and it's midnight and captain Musgrave is on the deck. He's watching these waves come over
The black sea in front of him and he sees an
Island way too close to where the boat should be and he's like well
Either we move the island moves and we can't move with these waves the islands not gonna move because it's part of the globe
The boat crashes into the island. He starts giving out orders as the boats taken on water grab the food the tools the gun
The ammo materials let's start getting whatever we can off this boat now before it sinks
they make it to the island and
There's a ton of animals there and luckily they have all the materials they need they got their guns
They can hunt seals they're shooting birds. They're eating fish. They secure a clean source of water
They build a really quick shelter at all the debris of the boat and then they start to build a permanent one
They're like you know what this is this is a great shelter and all but we might be here for a while
Let's build ourselves as something else stand up to the elements
So under the command of captain Musgrave they build like a house of stone and timber at a chimney and a desk
Basically, but I just imagine he's sitting on a bunch of coconuts
Everyone has everyone had their own little bed. They're sitting there and he's writing letters dear Margaret
It's the 14th day we've been trapped on this island and I already live in a better house than I have at any time in my life
It's amazing here. I wish you could join us. It's a tropical paradise
The captain you know to pastime starts reading classes everyone's sitting around
They all have made salvaged a bunch of glasses. They're like I feel smart now
I feel super smart now the one guy fashions a chess set. They're making dominoes
They start making beer and then eventually they go listen. This is this is pretty awesome
This is almost like a working vacation
But we should try to like figure some way off this island everyone's like, oh, and he's like I know I know I know it's pretty dope
We do have this beer, right?
If you guys all do know how to read now, but we eventually should probably get back to civilization everyone's like
Yeah, I guess they made a raft that could carry three of them
So that crash happened on January 3rd 1864
on July 24th 1865 is
When they launched the raft so they were there for about a year and a half almost
The raft goes out they end up seeing a rescue ship. They flag it down
the rescue ship comes in and
Everyone's like just kind of chillin rescue ships like do you want to be rescued and they all look at each other like yeah, I guess
Because I have to all right, you know, we were running out of food
We're not all these seals were breeding seals. They started wearing seal skin clothing and they go yes
Yeah, let's go so they get on the boat and the boat starts going away
And on the other side of the island that they're trapped on they see a plume of smoke
I'm looking at each other and they knew the island was deserted they go
We should probably send another ship over to check that out because there might be more survivors, right?
This is one of those interesting stories where everything comes down to basically a handful of decisions. It's 1864
It's May 11th, so we're going back in time
This is five months after the Grafton had crashed on
The other side of the island. There's a boat under the control of captain George Del Garneau
It's 2 a.m. Waves are crashing over the boat. Ah, it's super dark. You can't see anything
Why this happened in the middle of the day or not happening at all waves are crashing over the boat?
It's 2 a.m. In the morning and the captain goes you did to do something and you I don't know just walk around in circles
I don't know what to do and then you had the first mate being like no no no don't walk around in circles
You idiot walk around in an octagon and every the crew is completely panicked. They're getting contradictory orders. It's super dark
Everyone's wet
Which they kind of expected that on the boat, but they didn't expect it to crash in the panic
Four people drown as the boats going down and there is a guy in the sick bay laying in bed
What's going on guys just woke up from a deep nap. Why is the water up to my nose?
They don't even rescue him
six people drown and one man
Didn't even have a chance. He was in sick bay
They get to shore and their boat is still sinking and they go okay
Here's the plan when the sun comes up when we can see what's going on. We'll go back
We'll get the food we'll get the supplies
We'll get the guns and the ammo and all that stuff
We'll be able to shoot seals and shoot birds and build a temporary house and all that stuff
Maybe you get one of those chess sets you've always been talking about yippee, but in the morning we'll go out there
They were able to get a couple pounds of biscuits and some salted pork and had just enough wood to build a little
lean-to shelter
But by the time morning came the boat had completely submerged the boat was sinking when they left it
So by the time the morning came they were like oh, it was kind of a restful night
I had dreams of people drowning, but I wasn't one of them. So I'm okay. Let's go salvage the
It's just boats gone like I don't know what they were expecting
But anyway, so they do have some food and they have a couple pieces of wood
They built a little lean-to they had two packs of matches. They're like, okay these matches are wet
So let's dry them out
Let's set them out in the sun because we'll probably need them later
So let's start this spend a long time starting this fire. They're rubbing the guy, you know doing the stick rub thing
Trying to you hear my hands rubbing together. I'm gonna start a fire just doing the sound effect. They start a little fire
Oh, this is awesome
So the matches that they'll use later to make it easier in the future sitting out in the sun and they go whoa
I got a better idea those matches. Sure. We can leave them out in the sun and they'll drive very slowly or we can put the matches
Next to the fire which is hot right fires on we'll put the matches next to the fire and the matches will dry
Matches catch on fire the matches catch on fire. So they're like
Well, okay, there goes that now. We just have to not leave this fire this little fire
We built will be totally fine May 11th 1864 four days after the boat sinks
They're already out of food and they really don't have a way to hunt
They don't have any of the guns that captain Musgrave was able to get I
Think you can kind of see
Where this is going they see a cliff they see a 2,000 foot cliff then they go
We should probably climb up the cliff and start looking for food because maybe there's would they see these delicious seals
Floating around but they can't get them and they go maybe there's like pigs on the island or something like that
So let's climb up the cliff and we'll go look at now
There's one guy is like I'm too sick to move. I'm just gonna lay here. He's faking it. He's like I got bit by his seal
I got the seal disease. I can't move slowly turning into a seal. I can't move. So anyways
He's not a fake. He's actually very very ill
But this everyone goes to climb up the cliff. They've run out of food. Let's climb up this cliff now
One guy says I'll stick around on the beach. I'll stay with this sick dude
You climb up there and when you find food just bring the food back and everyone's like oh, that's a great idea
Is there I shit from side to side?
They climb up the cliff
They do find pigs up there and they immediately just spear it and they're like oh wait
Oh my god, I cook it sir. Rubbing the sticks together rubbing the sticks together eventually start a fire now the dude on the beach
Apparently he lives in a looney Tune cartoon because from a 2000 foot cliff he smells
Cooking pork I can just imagine like little wavy lines and it makes that makes a finger and it's like
Do it like goes under his nose it's tickling his nose the guy sitting next to this dude on the beach and
He smells the food cooking up there and he hasn't eaten in a while and he's like hey buddy
I'm gonna go climb up this cliff and I'm gonna go eat some of this food
I'll be right back, bro. I'll be right back and the dude on the beach obviously knows knows the jig is up
No, man. Don't leave me. Don't leave me his buddy though
I couldn't climb up a 2000 foot cliff to to save my life
But apparently just the smell of bacon this guy is able to scramble up and
No one ever went back to help the guy on the beach. He dies on the beach
They're eating the pig. They're eating roots. They're basically eating really whatever they can get their hands on and while this is going on
The body count starts to rise
They eventually made it to another whole different part of the island. They never went back for that guy
You started to have disagreements in the group people are dying of exposure seven people go. You know what?
We're going to break off on our own. We're gonna go and we're gonna try to find food on our own
You have they're at each other's throats and everyone knows what's coming, right?
Everyone has the same vision. They're looking they're talking to their buddies and they're imagining chickens standing there
They're imagine broiled chicken standing there again like a loony toon cartoon. They know they
They're able to eat roots. They're able to catch a pig every once in a while
But every seamen knows
cannibalism is not far from now so seven people go you know what?
We're gonna leave this group. We're gonna strike out on our own and Captain Del Garna goes whatever like
The less people we have to feed the better those seven people walk out into the jungle. They're never seen again
Their remains are never found. No settlement is ever found. They're gone from the face of the earth
They get to another beach
They've walked all the way from one side of the island to another they get to another beach
They find some delicious seals. They're actually able to at this point at this point
I'm sure they are very hearty men who are great with a spear because they've now been fighting their way across the island
Spear and pigs you got a lot of practice now. You just have to what is what is a seal but a slippery pig a more slippery pig?
People are still dying off though
Three months later people are still dying off. They can't get enough food. They're dying off one by one by one by one
They end up making a canoe out of seal skin so definitely they've ranked up their experience level as far as seal killing goes
They put a lot of points into their hunting skill. They have a seal skin canoe. They go to another neighboring island
It's full of rabbits and they're like
Why couldn't we crash on this island? They're eating rabbits. They're having an okay time
May 20th 1865 more than one year since they crashed a
Boat happens to come in on repairs
She's a bunch of dudes standing there
You won't believe the year we had a bunch of people died and
We left a couple on the boat and we left from the beach to die
But we're alive and the rescue crew again, they were just there to make repairs in their boat
they're like, oh, that's awesome and
From what it sounds like nobody resorted to cannibalism everyone's eyes kind of shiver inside a site again
One of them did actually I did these two guys were fighting one of the guys false cracks his head open and dies and
The buddies like well, I guess I won that argument and they starts eating his buddy
So they did resort to can one guy resorted to cannibalism according to their story
And as that boat was leaving on May 20th 1865 they were leaving
They got back home and that was a huge story because obviously cannibalism at sea always gets headlines
It's just the most barbaric practice and it's the story of survival and it really was juxtaposed because what happened was by the time
They get back so they're leaving on May 20th 1865 and then in July of
1865 the Grafton shows up and they're all like super they have like three piece suits made out of seal skins
They've gained a muscle. They're super fit. They're like, oh, yeah, do that island's totally dope dude
I mean if you prepare for it if your boat sink and you just grab what you want and
Del Garne was like, oh man, I should have thought of that
You have these two ship crashes at the same time roughly the same time two completely different captains
And what boat you on depended on whether or not it was a vacation paradise or a hellscape
Where at least one person ate one other person
But remember it was in July when the Grafton was being rescued and they saw the smoke coming from the other part of the island
So that means that that group of seven people were definitely still alive when both rescue ships showed up
Signaling for help or was it a fire destroying their camp?
Was there a war over who would be eaten first?
Nobody knows nobody has ever found their remains on that island. I find that story really interesting
Because it is a story of survival, but I find the story very interesting
I think it's something that we can relate to our own lives. I tell people and this is a Bible verse
I didn't make this up, but I always tell people this steel sharpens steel
Who you hang out with who you have company with is a very important thing to how you are in that steel sharpen steel
Two great people will make each other greater. I don't hang out with scrubs. I do not hang out with scrubs
I hang out with people as good as me or better
And I tell my friends that steel sharpens steel
Steel sharpens steel you hang out with the people that you want to be like you you hang out with the people who aren't better than you and
You continue to try to be great every single day steel sharp and steel
Depending on you had these two different captains
But they weren't different captains just on that particular day
Those crews would have been completely different and if the crew members on Del Garno ship had been on
Musgrave ship
I believe that over the course of that journey. They would be better crewmen. They would not panic
The set their circumstances were the same, but because you had different crews
It wasn't just the captain because you had different crews
They had one disagreement with Musgrave
They had one disagreement when they were playing chess for a while people started getting in fights over chest
So Musgrave just threw the chest set away and goes if you guys can't be nice
Everyone's like yeah, that's probably a pretty good idea steel sharp and steel
You want to hang out with the people who are going to make you a better person?
Because while this may seem like an extreme example, you never know who you're going to be in a
Crazy situation with and it might not even be this insane
But you never know when life is going to throw you a curveball
And when you turn to those people around you for assistance the people you've gathered throughout your life to help you
Are they going to take you on a fun adventure that everybody learns from or are you guys going to start cannibalizing each other?
In a metaphorical sense
Steel sharp and steel who you hang out with not only determines if you survive, but if you thrive and
if in the end
You are a better person
We're in a snazzy seal skin suit
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)