Apple sensors Alex Jones and child molestine reptilians have taken over
Antarctica today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I'm your
host Jason Carpenter I'm having a great day I hope you're having a great day. Got
a lot of good stories for you today. Today's actually the first day of my
vacation so that's pretty awesome. Took a long nap. Don't really have much planned.
Napping, working on the podcast, hanging out with my family, stuff like that would be pretty cool.
You know this is a weird thing I don't know how many of my audience does drugs.
I assume it's probably like a 50/50 split maybe a little bit more and when I
say drugs I mean like basic drugs like marijuana. I'm not talking like how much
of my audience is heroin which I'm sure is an insignificant amount but what I
think is interesting have you ever done drugs in your dreams? Every show often
I'll have a dream where I smoke weed. I don't smoke weed anymore because I get
drug tested all the time but I I've had dreams where I've done drugs in my
dreams and the dream like your dream state becomes incredible. It becomes
basically what you think drugs do to you when you're a kid like when you're a kid
you think drugs make Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck dance around in front of
you and it's not the case. Spoiler alert for anyone who hasn't smoked marijuana
it's not that cool. It does make television incredibly amazing but it
doesn't make you hallucinate. Well I did hallucinate a couple times but anyway
that's beside the point. The point is is that in dreams or I've done drugs it's
totally tripped me out. It's been the most intense experience. So my question I
wonder why I've actually heard other people say that too when they do drugs
in their dreams it's like the most intense possible experience and I'm
wondering if because the brain is trying to simulate the effect of the drug it
just goes overboard or actually I just thought of this maybe when you do drugs
you do have this totally intense impact on your brain but you can only perceive
so much information while that's going on. So you may actually your brain to your
brain it could be like some sort of cataclysmic slash orgasmic event but
because your ego couldn't handle that it kind of just makes you want to eat
Taco Bell and watch The Sweet Life on Deck. So I don't know but yeah whenever
I've done drugs in my dreams it's the most intense drug experience ever. So let's
talk about the big news of the day. Again I'm recording this on Monday but you'll
be hearing it on Friday because we're doing the pre-recording so I don't have
much of a gap while I'm on vacation. But the big news of the day Monday is that
Alex Jones was taken off of iTunes. His podcast four of his five podcasts were
taken off of iTunes. He was I believe taken completely off of Spotify. Facebook
has shut down some of his pages. YouTube I think as of now may still have one or
two of it like they were taking down individual videos. iTunes announced that
they were taking down his podcast at three in the morning local time which is
unusual. I think they knew that these other sites were going to take him down
and iTunes wanted to be first they wanted to set the benchmark. Here's my
thing about Alex Jones. So when I first I used to be a 9/11 truth or I used to be
more believing in these conspiracy theories and that's when people go do
your research do your research. I was reading about Osama bin Laden when he
gave an interview I think it was with Time Magazine or Newsweek back in 2000. I
was researching 9/11 on 9/12 like I was into that truth or movement and into
those conspiracy theories conspiracy theories and spent years and
years and years looking into it and I always say generally you fall down the
rabbit hole and eventually you end up back on the surface and you go out of
everything's fake that's all nonsense. If you keep an open mind you fall through
the rabbit hole you come back and you're like yeah it wasn't a waste of time I
enjoyed the journey but most of the conspiracies out there are complete and
utter garbage entertaining garbage but garbage nonetheless so I used to go to
Info Wars and Prison Planet back in 2001-2002. It was amazing it was this huge
treasure trove of conspiracy thought. I've always seen Alex Jones as an
entertainer first and a quote-unquote journalist second and for lack of a
better term. I think Alex Jones had a character I think he might have originally
believed some of the stuff he says but I don't think he actually believes most of
it. I think you would have to be a lunatic to believe every every single
thing that he's talked about over the years. It would drive you mad so I
believe it's an act during his divorce with his wife his defense lawyer said
as much he doesn't act like this around his kids this is a performance that he
puts on and he lost that case by the way his wife is getting a ton of money
through alimony because he cheated on her apparently I don't know allegedly I
guess I should say. Now if you are a journalist and you are stating facts and
you can show your work basically is a term I like to use a lot with the
conspiracy theory community you can say what you want you can say reptilians are
taken over the planet but show your work show me documents show me proof and
I'll believe you I'll be on your side but if you can't show your work then
you're no different than someone telling me that China is making fake cabbage
you're using undisclosed surface sources you're using people that are easily
disputed and so on and so forth. Alex Jones can't show his work if Alex Jones
could actually show his work and say Sandy Hook was fake which is one of the
big lawsuits he's facing now by two families of Sandy Hook victims if he
could prove that if a journalist or a researcher can prove that you have that
as your defense but when you're just acting when you're just making it up
and then people say what you're saying is hateful you have no defense well you
have one which is the First Amendment but that one covers you from the
government and two it only covers you in the United States and what iTunes and
Google and Spotify and YouTube and all these groups can say is one we're a
private company so we can choose what's on our platform and we feel you are
being hateful Mr. Jones or yes you are protected by the First Amendment in the
United States but because we are a global company we have to follow basically
the strictest laws the way America works is that generally the strictest law is
what you fall under if California has very strict gun control laws but the
this nation has more lax gun control laws generally fall under the purview of
the strictest law and I think that's what's happening to Alex Jones. Alex
Jones what they are saying is that he makes hateful content towards
gays, transgendered people, and Muslims in particular so they took his shows off.
Do I think that causes a problem for the conspiracy community in large? Do I
think that the fact that these outlets are banning Alex Jones do I think it
makes an impact on the conspiracy theory community at large? I do. I think it may
make a positive impact. I think Alex Jones has been such a magnet of attention
that if he's no longer the most visible voice in the conspiracy community I
think it may be taken a little more seriously. I think generally when you
start talking about conspiracies or something like that and someone can
immediately just go "Water's turning the frogs gay!" it dismisses it all. Now to be
fair most conspiracy theories deserve to get dismissed but I think you know what
I'm saying he is so bombastic and so such a caricature of a conspiracy
theorist I think that it may help. I think it'll make room for other people to
kind of move up in that conspiracy theory realm. Do I think that as society at
large it is beneficial to have Alex Jones removed? No, I don't. I don't. Now to be
fair on that the comments that he makes that some would consider hateful and to
be honest I don't watch the show. I went to the website a lot but that was
before he did his show. I've only seen the clips most people have seen so when
they say that he's hateful towards gays or transgendered or Muslim people I
don't know. So they're making that claim and I don't know. I haven't seen any
clips or anything like that but I think for society at large for some of the
biggest content providers to shut someone down because they say they're
producing hate speech when in general he's not known for producing hate
speech in general he's known for saying crazy things about Sandy Hook and 9/11
and say Tannock pedophile, Stake on the World and stuff like that. He's not
Richard Spencer where that's all he's saying. He generally makes these wacky
conspiracy theories and I think what the problem is is that we have him deep
platforms from some of the major major platforms. I've heard the term this is
basically digital book burning because he will be gone. It costs a lot to host
the podcast or especially video on your own site. The upload download the bandwidth
is insane so you get deep platform from these major major platforms. There's
nothing else for him to really distribute his content and you know keep his
company going. And I think what we're going to see is we're going to see a
Roseanne James Gunn situation where the left takes out Roseanne for her tweet
about a black woman look like a monkey which I can't believe that she still
wrote that. And then the right takes out James Gunn for tweeting jokes about
pedophilia and it just becomes this tit for tat this back-and-forth thing. I
think that's what we're going to see. What the next big push will be to get
young Turks de-platformed or something like that. And I don't think that type
of tribal warfare is good for society. I don't think that it's good for the
culture. So yeah it'll be interesting. I have and I have a feeling that this isn't
going to last very long. I have a feeling that this is going to be revoked.
So that they are going to allow him back on the platforms. Because I just don't.
I don't see it sticking. I think he could if he can prove that I never made those
hateful comments or those that video that I supposedly made a hateful comment
had been up for two years on iTunes. So it'll be interesting to see how this
plays out. But again I think for the community for the conspiracy theory
community it's nice to have one of the biggest most laughable characters in it
removed is beneficial because then more more thought-provoking or more well
thought-out conspiracy theorists can move to the top. But I think as society at
large I don't think it's a good thing. So we'll see how this plays out. Okay last
story of the day we're going out there. And when I say out there we're going from
outer space to ice in your face. I don't know I couldn't come up with anything for
that. So apparently this again this seems to be a political episode but it just
happened to be that way. So what's going on according to this truth seeker this
man above men this fear bean. Fear bean? That's his website. So there's this guy
named Corey Good. So quick info on Corey Good. Corey Good has been kidnapped
multiple times by the United States Air Force. I mean just like they've come in
and they've taken him and they're like how are you revealing all of our secrets
and Corey Good's like I can't tell you and the Air Force is like tell us who's
the leak and Corey Good's like I won't tell you the Air Force lets him go.
Because what you know that's what military is known for. They're known for
taking people prisoner and then letting them go when they don't get what they
want. This happened multiple times. Poor Corey Good being abducted. Where are you
getting your secrets? Who is leaking our info to you and Corey Good's like I will
not tell you. And then one day Corey Good is taken in by a secret U.S. Air Force
agent who works for special space command named Sigmund and the agent goes
who's giving you this information and Corey Good goes aliens are talking on my
brain and the agent goes yes you are right aliens are talking to your brain
here's even more secret documents for you to leak. Together we can destroy the
pedophiles who are taking over the planet. So now Corey Good is no longer
being kidnapped by the U.S. Air Force. He's working for them along with his
telepathic alien baby in his brain and what he has to report this time is that
special teams of soldiers from around the world is like a straight-up GI Joe are
capturing high-level world powerful pedophiles. Get down on the ground pedophile.
No I own eight banks in Europe stay down. Watch I'm gonna get flagged for hate
speech because of that accent. The pedophile anti-pedophile special forces
teams have been raiding groups across the United States and they're shocked
shocked at how deeply these people are in the U.S. government. This team has been
in effect by the way in the middle since the middle of the election but since
Donald Trump's become president it's become totally ramped up and at this
point a special forces some of them have actually been fired unfortunately from
this made-up job. They're having to collect made-up unemployment. They've
been fired from this made-up job for killing low-level pedophiles. That has
to be the worst description ever. That not only are you a pedophile you're a
low-level pedophile. That's like you only have sex with baby ducks. Like you
don't even qualify to be as gross as a regular pedophile you're just a low-level
pedophile. Other pedophiles look down on you. Anyway so these special forces
squads a couple of these guys have been fired from this made-up job because
they've been killing these low-level pedophiles because they're just so angry.
Now before we get into the weird part let me just do an aside. Yes there are we
do have a pedophile problem. It's everywhere and it's super gross. Before I
go any further I think I need to make this clear. I'm not making fun of
pedophilia and yes there are powerful people out there who are pedophiles.
What I have a problem with is the idea that a pedophilic network is running
the planet. I think that idea is laughable. I think that there are private
groups of people who want to have their vision of the world put onto everyone
else. I think that is such a basic description of the illuminati or
conspiracies. I think that's fair. I think that if I had a billion dollars I
would want people I would want to leave my impact on the world and I would want
the world to see the world as I see it because I think I know what I'm doing
is right. So when you have George Soros or you have the what is it the Koch
brothers the Koch brothers they're both the same thing. They're opposing forces
but they're both the same thing. They both have massive amounts of money and
they use that money to reshape the world and how they see it. I do not think that
they're both pedophiles that know a million other pedophiles that are
running the planet and if the Koch brothers knew that George Soros was a
pedophile or vice versa that'd be the first attack line every single day.
One of them goes, you know, my opponent believes that climate change is not
man-made and the other people would be like he's a pedophile. That would be the
only conversation ever. So either they're both pedophiles and in that case it
doesn't matter because everyone's a pedophile or one is and one isn't and
that would be the only line of attack ever. This person believes that taxes on
corporations should be 10% that person's a pedophile. That would be every single
conversation and all of these stories would be buried 100% of the time
because if everyone in the power structure even let's say 10% or 2% of
the world's power structure was powerful enough to not only hide their own
crimes but initiate other people into their group. We would never hear about
any of these stories. Corey Goode would be a smudge at the bottom of the
Empire State Building. So that's my problem with these stories about these
worldwide groups of super powerful people that are doing this Illuminati
Satanic pedophilia group. There are powerful people who are pedophiles
absolutely. There are networks of pedophiles absolutely. Those are facts. We
catch them. We bust them not as often as we should but we do. But this idea like
Corey Goode's putting forth that local police are in on it. Local reporters are
in on it. Low level politicians are in on it.
Entertainment industry is in on it. Politicians like if the local cop is in
on it then he's the weakest link. Why is he part of your global? Why is he
banging kids with George Soros in Vienna? It doesn't make sense. Think about this
stuff for one second please. It gets me... you know the reason why these stories
get me so upset is this is a problem and it makes it into this wacky
conspiracy and like I said it only gets weird. And when I say it's a problem I
mean pedophilia is a problem. The story gets even weirder so not only are there
special forces squads going around kicking down the doors of the local
ombudsman for the newspaper being like get on the ground get on the ground show
me your hands. There's another there's another level to it. Sometimes these
kids that are taken by the Podunk Sheriff of Nebraska they're taken to
Antarctica and given to draconian reptiles to beat up and get even more
molested. So apparently in Antarctica there are... oh and I'm not supposed to
talk about this either. According to Corey Goode this is not supposed to be
information that is revealed in any way shape or form even though he reveals it
on his totally public website and he's still alive and charging $110 if you
want to watch a webinar with him. Anyways in Antarctica there are these huge
research and development bases to build these giant spaceships the draconians
which the reptilians live in. They live... Aunt why Antarctica? Why are lizard
people in the ice? I don't know. Why aren't they in Brazil which is like equally dense?
But anyways they're in Antarctica for some reason lizards in the ice because
those things go so well together and they're building these giant spaceships
and sometimes they bring kids they ship kids all the way from you know Iowa
that's where all those missing kids are going they're putting them on planes and
flying would probably releasing chemtrails as they fly across the globe
to land in Antarctica to be disembarked and then aliens beat them up and make
them slaves I don't know. I like to think at some point the special forces are
going to be here and they're gonna say if you want to kill a serpent cut off its
head and then they like go to Antarctica and assault these huge bases but I mean
it's not going to because it's all made up you know I just it boggles my mind
sometimes like I can get when someone who has a blog and they write something
completely ridiculous and you're like okay you know whatever when someone has
an entire organization dedicated to spreading arguably false ideas it's
just mind-boggling and to end the cap this I think that's that's the same way
I look at Alex Jones I think he's just an entertainer I think this core good
guy is an entertainer I don't think he was ever captured by the US Air Force I
don't think he ever had telepathic visions from an alien I don't think that
there's top-secret kill squads moving through the United States shooting
pedophiles I think that there are if hard-working investigators shutting down
pedophile rings constantly and more pop-up and I think the government this
government is doing a good-faith effort in shutting down human trafficking I do
think those things are true and those are interesting stories don't add
reptilians into it just tell me I think the story itself that we've had massive
human trafficking arrests in the past year and we're making a good-faith effort
and we're changing the laws that if you are involved in this we are going to
hurt you legally and financially we will shut you down I think that's
interesting you don't have to add space aliens into it or hit squads that are
killing low-level pedophiles and other people like Barry what a Junies like I
just couldn't stand looking at that son of a bitch one more time like I don't
know I I think the I think the story of Sandy Hook is interesting in and of
itself it's tragic you don't have to add this conspiracy stuff to it I just
think that this idea that the world is not already completely messed up and
has a bunch of evil in it and I have to add space aliens and telepathy and
starships and stargates and all of that stuff I think it's just a little I I
think it's disingenuous because I honestly think that if Corey Good wrote
a book about America has a pedophile problem here are the stats here are some
witness accounts here are some victim accounts here's a couple of words from
the perpetrators and you know why they did it or how they feel now here's some
you know we'll talk to these investigators that book is not going to
sell as well as book after book after book of aliens are in my brain and
they're eating your children you're not going to be able to pay a hundred and
ten dollars for a webinar with Corey Good talking about real-life events so he
just makes stuff up and I think that's the trap that Alex Jones fell into I
think he probably did honestly believe that 9/11 was an inside job and as time
progressed the theories got even weirder and weirder and eventually it catches up
with you because you're stopped being a journalist and you start becoming an
entertainer and you become a caricature of yourself so yeah I mean I think that
is the same thing with what happened with Alex Jones I think that it's easier
to sell a fantastic story you may believe in it at first or you may not but
what happens is it starts to sell very well if I start doing videos let's say
I do a video series where I talk about how cryptids are invading the national
parks and those videos and those podcasts get download multiple multiple times my
first inclination is going to make more of those and eventually as content starts
to dry up I'm gonna start making it up because that's how I make money I don't
make any money off the show but you get where I'm coming from you start off with
a conspiracy that you genuinely believe in and people respond to it you make
money and you get used to that money and you got to start making more money I
don't think I personally again don't know much about Alex Jones other than what
I've read I don't he doesn't cross me from what I read back in the day
especially he doesn't cross me someone who's genuinely a racist person or a
homophobic person but if during the time when people were talking a lot about the
invasion of Europe and refugees and all of that coming in the West he starts
making more videos because he's getting more views because he's supporting that
viewpoint and eventually he just started saying stuff that maybe he didn't even
believe in but it was getting him views I don't think Corey Good actually believes
reptiles are living in Antarctica I mean if he does I guess more power to him
but that's nutty and my question is if he's revealing this information that's
never supposed to be revealed why was I able to find his website on Google which
is controlled as we all know by the pedophile draconian Illuminati Alliance
dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address facebook.com/dead
rabbit radio is our Facebook. Twitter is @jasonocarpenter that's gonna be our
Twitter so I think we had some really good stories this week I really enjoyed
them I do have to say something real quick before I officially in the show
the Circleville writer man you might think like I was doing some coke during
that but I was actually really excited about that story I had just found out
about that story maybe an hour before I recorded it as I was thinking about it
I was like man I sounded super excited during that so hopefully it came off less
as crank using and more like genuinely enthusiastic because I love a good
mystery I love a good mystery dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but
I'm glad you listened to it today have a great one guys
[Music]