Indonesia takes an interesting approach to fighting the coronavirus, and then we take
a look at a story of a werewolf that stalking the streets of a town in Mexico.
Is there really a creature of the night howling off in the distance?
And if so, is it possible it was created by drug cartels today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
It's hot.
It's hot in here and there's a storm coming.
Last night was a big windstorm in Hooded River.
Really loud.
I left the windows open and I just sat there and was goofing off on the computer reading
and oh man.
The elements, the elements just really kind of fly through the gorge.
Big storm coming though.
Look out my window.
I can kind of feel like I'm in prison.
I can kind of like crane my head just a bit to look off into the distance.
Big storms coming.
So we'll see what tonight brings.
Let's give a shout out to one of our legacy Patreons.
Let's go ahead and give a shout out to Scott Stewart.
Scott, thank you so much for supporting the show all this time.
Really really means a lot.
Really really helps.
Really really appreciate it.
So you're going to be flying us around.
You're going to be our pilot captain.
Whatever vehicle we use, you're going to be in charge of that.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too guys.
I totally understand.
You can help just by spreading the word about the show, giving the show a good review, all
sorts of stuff.
You can use to support the show and I appreciate all the assistance I get from you guys.
I really really do.
So Scott, thank you so much for your support.
We're giving you, you're going to be the captain today on the Dead Rabbit Dreadnought.
It's a brand new vehicle actually.
It's a massive warship.
Dinky little rowboat.
We'll save that for swimming across the lakes.
I guess we don't need to swim, we'd be in a boat.
But anyways, Dead Rabbit Dreadnoughts are massive warship.
It's one of those ones with all the oars and stuff like that.
We have a bunch of Greek fire.
I'm just like cooking marshmallows over it.
The chemicals make it taste so much better.
We're sailing from the United States.
We're headed all the way to Indonesia.
And there we're going to see a little village.
We parked the boat and then we all like hop out.
That's how boats work, right?
You just like bring them right up to the beach.
We hop out, we walk into Kepa Village.
It's on Java Island in Indonesia.
And everyone's kind of hanging out in their houses because it's quarantine time, right?
You know that, right?
You're like, no, I what?
I didn't know that.
You're jogging down the street listening to this podcast.
I didn't have phones.
You're like, oh, I was wondering why my town was super empty.
I'm wondering why it looked like a zombie movie.
Yes, we're in quarantine for the most part, not everywhere, but they're doing quarantine
in Indonesia right now.
How do you keep people inside?
There's a couple of different ways you can like, I think the weirdest thing going on
right now is you can get arrested for violating quarantine.
But if you're currently in jail, they're letting you go so you don't get coronavirus in jail.
That's a weird, I think that's one of the weird things about this whole virus thing.
And I guess in Florida, they let a guy go and a day later, he murders somebody.
There's going to be a lot.
If we look back on this thing, there's going to be a lot of overreactions.
I mean, obviously murdering a guy is an overreaction, but the idea of like letting people out of
jail and then arresting people who go to church is just going to be a weird, that'll be one
of those things that people kind of look back and go, what were we thinking?
But we're panicked right now, right?
Speaking of panic, the government of Indonesia decided this.
Let's keep people inside by scaring them, which actually seems to work for pretty much
everywhere else, right?
You're scared to catch this thing yourself or you're scared to give it to one of your
loved ones.
And that's why we're all kind of obeying the quarantine for now.
They decide to go the route.
Let's dress people up as pokongs.
You're like, what's a pokong?
Let me tell you, whoa, dude, don't don't don't interrupt me, bro.
You want to a pokong?
I'm just joking.
Put my arm around you.
I'm just messing with you.
Give a little nookie.
A pokong is a trapped spirit of the dead.
It's an Indonesian belief systems, Indonesian mythology, however you want to put it.
They have a thing called a pokong.
It's a spirit of the dead, basically a wraith, someone who's been trapped on earth, a ghost,
a tortured ghost.
So anyways, people were dressed up as pokongs and basically it's just they have white sheets
wrapped around them.
Not this super ornate costume.
They're not like, they don't look like Power Ranger monsters or anything like that.
They're just like, dude with a white sheet wrapped around them.
They'd walk down the street and the idea was that you would either one think these were
actual phantasms and you would stay in your house to stay away from the ghost.
That's terrifying, right?
One thing for your government to say, this disease can hurt you and your loved ones,
it's another thing to say, the dead have risen.
They're coming after you.
The other idea is that it's just to remind you that death is outside.
That's also quite terrifying.
The government was saying basically not necessarily trying to trick people into believing there
was paranormal activity going on outside, but just as a reminder, just like a cigarette,
when you buy a packet of cigarettes in other countries, they'll have pictures of like cancerous
mouths and stuff like that to really put the shock in your system, this might happen to
you.
Backfired, if you can believe that because what would happen was people would see the
ghost and they would leave their houses.
They'd be like, "Hey, let's go see the ghost.
Come on, kids.
Hey, grandma, let me get your oxygen tank.
Yeah, hold on to that.
We'll put you in the wheelchair."
It's wheelchairs kicking up a bunch of disgusting dust.
Everyone was hopping out of their house to see the ghost.
It became a sightseeing thing.
Eventually, though, people in town wised up.
I guess like when the first article hit, they're like, "The people in town, this is encouraging
them to go out and they're basically playing Pokemon Go."
But there's just people and ghosts walking around and they're like, "Hey, got you."
And they're like, "Let go of me.
I'm already infected with the disease."
Now, people, maybe they've just gotten, I was reading an article recently and they said,
"Nowadays the people see them and they go, "Yeah, yeah, let's stay indoors."
It could also be that they just got bored because how many times could you see a ghost?
That's a good question.
How many times could you see a ghost before you started getting bored of them?
You could say, "Jason, never."
If every time you walked home, there was a hot ghost chick sitting in your favorite chair
and then she disappeared.
The first time, it's going to terrify you.
Second time, you're going to be curious and you're going to start setting up cameras and
EVP and stuff like that.
By the 1,573rd time, before you put your key in your lock, you're going to be like, "Are
you walking the door?"
And she's just sitting there and then she disappears.
The smell of sulfur, once again, fills your apartment.
It would get boring.
How many times do you have to see a squirrel?
Never mind, I love seeing squirrels all the time.
I could never get bored of seeing a squirrel.
So maybe I never get bored of seeing a ghost.
What's interesting is that, and this is the reason why I wanted to cover this, this totally
grosses me out.
This is apparently working, but in some regions in Indonesia, they wear, they're like mounted
police.
They do this in India too and they wear helmets that have the image of the coronavirus on
them.
They look like characters from the 1990s Nickelodeon cartoon.
For whatever reason, these things are like green and red and they're super cartoony and
they're made out of like plaster of Paris or maybe just paper mache, I don't know.
But it's like, you see a cop on a horse and they're wearing this massive neon green hand
painted homemade model of the coronavirus.
You know what grosses me out about that?
We as a society, I haven't done it and you may not have done it, but I'd say the media
has done it.
They've created the image of the coronavirus.
Have you guys all seen what this looks like?
And you're like Jason, that's science, right?
Are you going to deny the fact that this is, no, no, lay off.
Dude, you're going to be real touching today, bro.
I'm just trying to find out a podcast.
No, I just get you in the headlock again.
I'm just messing with you.
Give you a little tummy rub.
The idea is this, that, I get it, it exists and this is a 3D model, but like if you go
to a website, you go to YouTube, does it, and you watch anything that mentions the coronavirus,
they'll have a little coronavirus infobar and then a picture of the virus.
You go to major news sites, it'll be like coronavirus update, a picture of the virus.
The picture is everywhere of what this virus supposedly looks like.
We've created a meme of it.
It's a computer generated image.
It's not an actual photograph of it.
If you showed us a photograph of it, it would be this really grainy gray, I mean it's not
a photograph, like a microscopic, be a really grainy gray thing.
We've turned it into a symbol.
Symbols have power in the human mind.
And I hate that we've made this a symbol because it gives it more power.
I can, just by being my age, just by being 43 years old and living through things like
this before.
I didn't live through the Spanish flu, but I've lived through things like this before.
I'm gonna make a couple predictions.
Dead Rabbit Radio is gonna predict these things.
One.
At least one.
This probably has already happened.
And this is a minor prediction.
At least one heavy metal group, death metal group or whatever, will name themselves coronavirus
and have their CD, if they still even make CDs or their cover art, to basically be a
stylized coronavirus.
That's not even a prediction.
That's just something that's probably happening right now.
Two.
This is gonna become a fetish.
I'm not talking about corona Chan.
I'm not talking about drawing a hot Asian girl and giving her a little corona adornments
on her dresses.
There are going to be young people now who are in the developmental stage that in their
twenties and thirties are going to want to bang this image.
Again, not as a lark, not ironically, not as something funny to post online.
There is going to be, in a generation of men and women, you're gonna see one to two percent
of them have a sexual attraction to the virus itself.
100% predict that.
We will see that in our lifetime.
In the next 15 to 20 years, there will be people saying, "Well, I deserve equal rights
because I want to bang a disease that killed a million people or whatever the end result
is.
I imagine it's going to be fairly low in the end."
But that is going to be out there.
There are going to be people who actually are sexually attracted to the image of the
virus itself.
I believe as well that this image will play into a future iteration of the Illuminati theory.
This image will somehow be turned into an image of a death cult.
Still or imagine, there may actually be right now a cult of death worshipers or dark magic
practitioners or whatever that are already worshiping this symbol.
Again, I'm not talking about Kronachan.
That's an ironic attempt to meme this thing.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about serious adherence of dark arts either currently worshiping a stylized
version of that.
And I think going forward, some major conspiracy theorists, be it David Ike or Alex Jones,
might, Alex Jones, here's my prediction.
Alex Jones is probably going to retire in the next five years.
I think he's going to realize it's just not worth the trouble or he'll do a course correction
on this thing.
But we'll see someone basically say, "If the coronavirus symbol, if you look at it
clockwise or whatever, it has 13 spikes and it represents the 13 families."
It will, because it's getting, you can't go a day.
If you go online to any news site, YouTube does it too, you will see this image constantly,
constantly, constantly, constantly.
To the point that some people, let's say in the past month, if you're not a religious
person, you may have seen this symbol more often than you've seen across.
You've seen a menorah, then you've seen the crescent moon.
This easily could become a fixture in the subconscious of humanity.
And I don't like that, because symbols are so powerful.
Symbols are so powerful.
So you know, and it's funny now to think about, I don't really have any crosses.
I, myself and the Christian, I don't have any crosses in my house or in my, on my jewelry
or anything like that.
I do have one on my ring, but I don't wear it all the time because I'm trapped inside.
So I've definitely seen the corona symbol more often than I'm seeing any sort of religious
iconography.
And that's my religious iconography.
And again, talking about the star of David, talking about the crescent moon of the Muslim
faith, all of this stuff.
It's, we've created a symbol out of it.
That's funny, this segment became a little more serious than I thought it was going to
be, but we've created a symbol out of a disease.
And I don't think that's good for the psyche.
I don't think that's good for the metaphysical well-being of humanity.
I don't think it's good for just our psyche in general.
I think it turns, do you know what the Spanish flu looks like?
Do you know what Ebola looks like?
I know what Ebola looks like because I've seen images of it with the whole Ebola chain.
When the internet was like, hey, let's make, it's the same thing.
They're trying to turn Ebola into this sexy female thing.
So again, it's like a little worm.
But even that, and microscopic thing, but even that was nowhere near as popularized as the
image of the coronavirus.
And it's damaging.
I believe it's damaging.
You're taking a thing that people are terrified of, rightly so, because right now, I think
now we know more about it than we did just a month ago.
But now we know that it can be defeated very easily with soap and water.
We know the risk factors and what to look out for, how not to catch it.
We know these things now.
We didn't know these things in February.
It was interesting.
I was watching a press conference with Andrew Cuomo, very telling how little he, I don't
think he meant to reveal this.
Sorry, this is becoming more coronavirus-centric than I expected it to be.
Very telling interview with Andrew Cuomo.
He's a governor of New York.
He said, I'm paraphrasing here, but again, I don't think that he understood what he
was saying, the impact of it.
And no one really commented on this.
He goes, when this all started, we didn't know.
We didn't know how you could get this.
He goes, I feel better now.
I feel safer now because I know if I wash my hands and I practice social distancing, I'm
not going to get it.
He goes, but in the beginning, we didn't know.
For all we knew, you could be in your house and it came underneath your door.
For all we knew, everyone was going to get it no matter what.
And that's creepy because we didn't know.
China wasn't giving us accurate information, really.
China really was too overrun to do a lot of testing, not testing, but to do a lot of
studies on it.
They're just trying to stabilize their nation.
So when it came here, and again, I believe it was here in November, December, and I think
it was just passing pneumonia deaths, but as we really put it under a microscope, in
the high levels of the government, they probably thought, we don't know how this is spread.
For all we know, this could be 100% airborne.
It could be within 50 feet of, if one person coughs, 10 people are going to get it.
There's no protect.
And he said, he goes, we didn't know.
That's creepy.
Now we know that you can defeat it very easily.
Now we know that it looks like the death rate is actually going to be extremely low.
People talk about reinfection rates, but most likely that's bad tests.
Most likely it's people who pass a test and then they fail a test and it turns out that
the first test was a false negative.
That's really what it looks like.
Anyways, we shouldn't symbolize it.
We shouldn't symbolize it.
And I apologize actually.
I try to avoid, I'm trying to avoid covering a lot of coronavirus stuff because we're getting
inundated with it, but I thought it was an interesting story.
Apologize that it took so long though.
Let's go ahead, and I hope you found it interesting as well.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
Our next story.
Now our next story, this is going to be a long episode.
Our next story is an interesting one.
I came across it just kind of going through the internet.
There's a website call, it was kind of a paranormal type website.
It's called the Daily Grail.
This was written by a journalist named Red Pill Junkie.
Actually, most of this information I got from three particular sources.
Daily Grail, I got a report from kron4.com and I got a report from nature.com.
And the reason why I want to shout that out is a lot of times my research takes me to
multiple places I just put in the show notes.
But this story is pretty much made up of those three places particularly.
There's a lot of really good journalism involved in all three of those resources.
I really think, thank you guys for that.
Let's ditch the dead rabbit dreadnought, Scott.
Let's hop on board the carbon helicopter, the world famous carbon helicopter.
We're leaving behind Indonesia, taking off.
We're flying over the Pacific Ocean and we're headed to Mexico.
We're specifically going to a place called Ocozolatia Espanizo.
Oh dude, what?
That was actually pretty good.
I know my Hispanic listeners are out there.
They're like, dude, he got it on his first try, I think.
It's also known as coita.
You're like chasing, oh, he mispronounced that word, the little word.
Coita apparently is what it's pronounced.
It's a town of 40,000 people.
That's a pretty big town, honestly.
And I live in a town of 10,000 people.
So 40,000 is big.
They're having a problem over there.
A problem of the lichen kind.
So we land our helicopter in Coita.
And there people are like, oh dude, I'm so glad you came here.
World famous paranormal investigator, Jason Carpenter.
Nice to meet you, thank you so much.
They're shaking your hand too.
Oh, I don't know what your name is.
You're supposed to say your name there.
Oh yeah, nice to meet you.
I heard so much about you.
So anyways, we're walking through the town.
Hey, so what's going on?
And they're like, dude, you won't believe it.
So we've been having problems with a werewolf.
And we're like, oh, interesting.
Do you have any proof?
Yes, yes.
We have Twitter video.
And this is in the show notes.
Here's the Twitter video.
And you hear a wolf howling in the distance.
That's clue number one that a werewolf may be involved.
Do you have any-- that could also just be a regular wolf.
It could be a no werewolf.
What?
Uh?
Looking at you guys in every response.
Okay, sorry, tough crap.
Anyway, so now that we have that joke out of the way, do you have any more evidence?
And they do.
They have like, foot-- giant footprints in the dirt.
They have footprints on roofs.
Okay, so I mean, easily faked stuff, right?
Photographs of these things.
They're just not articles saying-- and they found a footprint.
There's footprints everywhere.
What's interesting is the footprint on the ground, one of the things is like, when archaeologists
and other nerds are doing stuff, they take photos of stuff, they toss them.
They toss quarters on the ground.
They're like, no, not on top of that amoeba squish.
They place quarters very nicely on the ground, so you have a sense of scale.
How big this is.
There's a close-up photo of a giant paw print, or it could just be a medium size or a small
paw print.
I don't know how big it is.
There are photos of what it looks like paw prints on a roof, but they look fake.
And you can look at the photos yourself as well.
Now am I automatically discounting the wolf story?
No.
It's very possible that there is a wolf or a werewolf in this town and one person decides
to paint some paw prints on a roof.
Or it's possible that I don't know how werewolf prints normally look, so they may look like
that.
I don't know.
The residents in town, though, can't sleep.
They're up all night and not in the cool Gilbert Gottfried USA way.
No.
They're afraid a werewolf is going to eat them, to a point where a local priest says,
"Guys, just set a candle and go to sleep."
Which actually is really bad safety advice.
I mean, I'm not trying to be, like, sacrilegious, but aren't you nuts of us to sleep with candles?
To be fair, though, the priest may have also said, "Set a candle, then blow it out and
go to sleep."
I don't know.
But the point is, is that the town hasn't burned down yet.
There's been no deaths attributed to the werewolf.
However, in Red Pill Junkies article, he did say, "This was a kind of a gross point
to put in here.
Two children were recently found dead in a well."
And I guess David Paulides and his Missing 411 theory has something to do with wells
or water.
I've heard, yeah, I've dis- I've really, I used to really be into Missing 411, really
for starting a new traction.
I lose faith in it constantly.
There's actually a really good, there's a website called Chaz of the Dead.
He did a really good write-up on Missing 411.
He reviewed the book itself.
When people talk about the Missing 411 conspiracy theory, and it's this idea that the National
Parks of America have a massive amount of disappearances and the government doesn't
want them to keep track of them and it may or may not be related to Bigfoot or some sort
of paranormal activity.
The theory is actually more interesting than the books the theory are based on.
I really think you guys should read this article.
I'll put it in the show notes by Chaz of the Dead.
He's a paranormal investigator.
He kind of covered this in depth and he kind of reinforced what I had already heard as
well.
The book is, is unsourced.
Just a bunch of short stories that may or may not have ever happened.
So anyways though, but Red Pill Junkie brings up the idea that two kids found in water, so
therefore werewolf.
Like, I didn't really understand that part of it.
But anyways, people in town, there's basically three theories as to what this thing could
be.
One is that people are on edge because the coronavirus is flowing around out there, everyone's
freaking out.
And so basically that magically makes wolf print.
No, that bait, people are already freaking out so they hear a wolf in the distance, make
some thing of werewolf, all these things are happening and then the prints are getting
faked or they're just regular wolf prints.
That's theory one.
Theory two.
Some people believe there's a big national forest.
There's a big nearby protected forest reserve that recently trespassers have been moving
in and out and doing all that stuff.
And it could be a natural elemental coming to wage war against the humans for infringing
on its territory.
I mean possible, right?
I actually think that's kind of the lamest one because otherwise the world would be overrun
by nature elementals.
We're constantly stomping everywhere.
And then there's the most popular theory in town is that it's a gnaw hall.
A gnaw hall that's a shaman who has the ability to shape shift.
And they believe that it's stuck in this wolf form.
Apparently it shape shifts by ripping its flesh off, leaves it in a nice tidy pile, runs
around, does wolf stuff, comes back in, puts its skin on.
But if you salt the skin, can't get it back in its skin.
Now we've covered a lot of like cryptids and stuff like that.
That's probably the most rational weakness.
Like we've covered, there's that horsewoman in Brazil that she tries to kill you because
she sees your shiny teeth.
So you gotta like lay face down so she doesn't see your teeth.
Like what?
And then there's the one where, I think it might have been the same one where you have
to pee on yourself to get away.
You're like why would that have anything to do?
That makes sense.
If you took your skin off and was running around as a wolf and you're like, "Oh, I'm
tired, time to put my skin back on."
And it was covered in salt.
You'd be like, "Uhh, unbearable pain and being a human but being, having salt inside
of me or just sticking around as a werewolf, I'll be a werewolf a little bit longer."
Like that actually is a reasonable weapon against something.
Nobody, imagine having sand in your shoe.
Now imagine instead of having sand in your shoe, you have sand in your skin and it's
everywhere, like inside of you.
But I have another conspiracy theory.
One thing that was interesting when I was reading this was they said not only are there
being kept up by the sounds of the werewolf howlin', but gunfire as well.
Now some people have said they've seen this thing straight on and they've watched it could
jump like nine feet in the air.
It's jumping on top of roofs.
It's jumping over giant walls.
They're shooting at it.
The bullets pass right through it.
But I did find it weird that at the beginning, that's fine, that may account for a couple
of the gunshots, but I thought it was weird in the beginning how they said, "They're hearing
the sounds of the wolf and the sounds of gunshots."
That's what's keeping everyone up at night.
So I'm going to present a theory of my own right now.
What if you have drug cartels organized crime creating superhumans?
Hear me out, hear me out on this.
Let's assume for the first place that these things could biologically exist.
Now the idea of a man turning into a wolf, well actually that's an interesting thing
because we see a lot of drug cartels, specifically in Mexico, South America.
We see a lot of drug cartels that are linked to black magic.
Not all of them.
But there are some that go to black magic practitioners for the ability to be invisible
to law enforcement.
Technically you should just ask for the ability to be invisible, period.
Because then law enforcement, they're like, "Oh where'd those guys go?
I can't see them."
"Oops, time for me to clock out."
Click.
"Right over there, right when I clocked off and I'm no longer a law enforcement officer."
There you are, you see him materially.
But you can find stories, even in other countries too, of warlords and stuff like that reaching
out to black magic practitioners for protection spells.
So why not reach out and say, "Can you build me a werewolf?"
But that's a little far-fetched, however possible, right?
You could go to some high level shaman and say, "Really what I'm getting at is this.
What drug organization, what organized crime unit would not want a werewolf on their side?"
Or any of these beasties we talk about.
Could you imagine you walk, you go to your local drug deal, you're going to re-up, you
walk in there and there's like a couple dudes just sitting there smoking weed on the porch.
Knock on the door, another person opens the door, that person goes, "Ah, he's in apartment."
Says what apartment he's in, then you walk across the apartment complex, you go to that
one, and Bigfoot's standing inside that one.
"Mmm, me see you need more drugs."
Yeah, yeah, Bigfoot, come on man, can you just tell me what apartment he's in now?
He's in this one, Bigfoot's just like a foot long joint.
This is just to maintain.
That would be the best, right?
That would be the best to have a cryptid on your site.
Imagine if you had drug shipments being run by the Loch Ness Monster.
Don't believe he exists, so you wouldn't even bother looking for him.
Drug cartels have all the things they need.
Okay, maybe it's far fetched, let me get back into the realm of things.
Here's the thing, the militaries of the world would love to create superhumans.
Every one wants to create superhumans, but militaries of the world, unless you're going
real deep black box stuff, are accountable for things.
A lot of drug cartels have more money just laying around than a lot of governments on
the world, not all of them, but a lot of them.
So if someone says, "Hey, if you give me $50 million, I can create a child that is bullet
proof."
And then you could hold that child up, bullets would bounce off of you, but eventually the
child will grow up and be a bullet proof drug runner.
All is going to cost to say $20 million for all this genetic testing.
Pablo Escobar had so much money, so much money.
He had to spend $10,000 a month just on rubber bands to band it all.
And he lost like 10% of it.
Over every year he lost 10% of his cash just due to mice eating it.
He said, "Oh, okay."
Because you have tons and tons, we're talking like high level cartel organized crime mafia
stuff, you have tons and tons of cash.
And here's the thing, if someone comes to you and says, "You know, I can start doing
this genetic testing, I can do this stuff."
And you can have like the black magic person, but you can actually have a scientist say,
"We can create a race of half human, half simians, like Stalin tried doing, but that
was back in the 50s now, and he actually did try doing that.
We can do that now.
If you're a drug lord and he fails, you can just kill him and get your money back or at
least get a little bit of vindication for having to waste $10 million.
Best case scenario is, you now have an army of mutants.
You have an army of enforcers.
They have unlimited funds.
They just absolutely do.
They can afford top scientists.
I'm actually surprised that we've never, I am honestly shocked about this.
It makes me think that they don't exist honestly.
That we haven't had a drug organization get a hold of a quote unquote suitcase nuke.
And there's been a lot of debate over whether or not those things actually exist.
Now could you imagine the impact if a drug cartel just nuked another group of drug dealers?
Like out in the middle of this village in South America, a small tactical, very small
tactical nuke goes off, clears 15 miles of foliage.
Everyone's dead.
They would send, now you could say, "Well Jason, they may have those, but they don't
want to use it."
There's been debate over whether or not a suitcase nuke's whether or not they actually
exist or it's just Tom Clancy nonsense.
But you have unlimited funds.
I remember reading that book Monster, the autobiography of an LA street gangster.
It's a really good book.
I'm trying to remember, it was an autobiography this guy wrote in prison.
And he was one of the original Crips.
And he tells his story at one point, one of his friends from the Navy gets an experimental
flare gun or something like that that he stole and he gave it to Monster.
But he used it to shoot someone, light them on fire at like LA's county fair or something
like that.
And then when in the 80, because it takes place in the beginning of the LA, like before
the bloods were around the Crips and there was all these, it's really, really interesting
book.
It was before the bloods were around.
I think the blood showed up at the end of the book.
Anyways, he's this big level drug dealer and he's buying these weapons.
He goes, "First we use to break into people's houses and get revolvers and rifles.
And then we got so much money we started ordering crates of AK-47s."
Like it was no longer, a lot of gun control laws are written because of stuff that happened
in the 70s and 80s where you'd have a gun, your gun would get stolen and it would be
used in a robbery.
Then people just started ordering the weapons straight from Russia or straight from Vietnam
or straight from the Middle East.
This LA street gangster, this guy, I think he was like 24, 25 at the time, this guy shows
up with these crates of AK-47s and he's like, "Yeah, sure, here's the cash."
And the guy goes, "Hey, you know, while I'm here, would you like this grenade launcher?"
The guy looks at me and goes, "What am I going to do in LA with a grenade launcher?"
But nowadays, I'm sure a lot of people would go, "Oh yeah, yeah, totally dude.
How much extra for the grenade launcher?
Do you get that awesome bandolero?
Do I get that awesome strap around my chest like Chewbacca that has grenades in it?"
Yeah, sure, I'll take two of those.
That would be awesome.
The stuff's available.
The technology's available.
The scientists are available.
People who need money, mad scientists, people who need money to fund their work.
They could go, "I'm going to create this half human half wolf."
And America would go, "What?
That's insane."
And they're like, "Oh, he's onto us."
And they have their black book project doing that.
It goes to Russia, they're doing it, and you go to a crime cartel and say, "I can create
a soldier for you right now that has the ability to jump nine feet."
And howl.
They're like, "What?
That's nothing?"
And they're like, "Oh, but it'll also psychologically scare people so your drug patrols can go through
areas and stuff like that."
Oh, yeah, that's pretty spooky.
That would work.
It'd keep people away.
Or, best case scenario, not best case scenario for humanity, but for the cartel, we can create
a monster that when you're in the middle of one of these wars, one of these drug wars
between you and another cartel, and you're shooting it out, all of a sudden out of nowhere,
some lithe, furry creature just kind of sprints out of your ranks and then jumps in the air
and lands on a rival cartel member and begins ripping them to pieces.
And then just the shock of that will give you the upper hand, everything like that.
So I think it's possible.
I think it's possible.
Again, for it to be possible, we have to accept that any of this can actually happen, that
you can just create superhumans and you can do genetic engineering and you can fuse man
and beast and all this stuff.
None of that stuff is proven by science at all.
Right?
Stalin did try making women bang gorillas.
It didn't work.
It might have actually, it's funny because he probably could have went the other way
and had dudes bang monkeys and it'd probably be a lot less like violent, but it probably
still wouldn't work.
It wouldn't be less violent for the monkey.
But you know what I mean?
Like, having a woman getting banged, I don't have to go into details.
The point is, is that it didn't work.
It didn't work.
And as far as we know, it doesn't work.
We've done experiments with men and hamsters though, humans and hamsters.
And it does look like that might work.
So it's not completely out of the realm of possibility.
A shaman creating a spell and having like a magical creature jump up and start, you know,
running drugs for you.
That's far more farfetched.
We don't see any proof of that.
But again, there could, you could have 99 shamans out there that are frauds that are just ripping
off the cartel.
And then you have one real one out there who actually knows what they're doing.
But this story isn't all speculation because of course, I, what happened was I read this
story about the werewolf and then I popped in my mind and go, that would be interesting
if the cartels were actually working on that.
Cartels do actually, this is one, this is where I got the article from nature.com and
the one from K-Ron.
The cartels are actually having a big impact on the world of science.
This is weird.
It kind of makes sense.
It's just kind of sad overall.
The large millimeter telescope, it's in Puebla State in Mexico.
It's been abandoned.
It's a giant telescope that's used to study supernovas, the creation of the cosmos.
They've had to shut it down because cartels are, they diversify stuff.
It's not all drugs.
They're doing tons of fuel theft, fuel smuggling.
There's a massive fuel pipeline that goes by this volcano that's in the middle of nowhere,
which is why they built this observatory in the middle of nowhere.
No light pollution, cartels are showing up, breaking into the pipeline, stealing the fuel.
One of the workers at the telescope got a car jacked near the worksite and the government
shut it down.
It's just not safe.
You're in the middle of nowhere.
We got these cartels running around.
There was a group of scientists studying endangered parrot called like a militant macaw, which
if that's not the name of a wrapper right now, it should be.
Or M&M maybe?
Militant macaw.
But anyways, these scientists were studying militant macaws out in the middle of nowhere.
Cartels are like, "Hey, we need to move stuff through that area."
But there's a bunch of like people watching.
People with monoculars in the bushes looking up at trees.
Even though this is a Scooby-Doo cartoon, we can't doot, doot, doot, like sneak around
behind them.
So they started sending death threats to the scientists.
Get out of here, get out of here, get out of here.
It was ended.
The study was ended so people can't study these parrots anymore.
You had agricultural scientists working with indigenous people in Mexico, showing them
how to make their crops better, treatment of the soil, stuff like that.
Trying to help give them a better life.
One of them, these one was kind of the reverse.
The military showed up and began harassing them, thinking they were cartel members.
And one of the people almost got dragged off to prison.
So they were like, "We're done."
That's scary too, right?
You don't want to get falsely accused and just kind of disappear into the justices.
So that stopped as well.
It's having a real effect on scientific exploration in the country of Mexico.
And that's not even the most tragic part.
Now, like I said, a lot of these drug cartels, it's all about bottom line.
So morals are secondary to them getting their profits.
Tijuana, Mexico, there's two journalists.
There's Manuel Alea and photographer Jo Beth Terriquez.
They did this investigation.
Finding homeless people just dead in the street.
Heroin overdose.
Heroin overdose because there was fentanyl mixed in with the heroin.
And that's pretty popular nowadays.
What happens is they'll take the fentanyl and make the fentanyls cheaper to produce
and it makes the already existing heroin far more powerful.
So they're addicted to your particular brand.
Very dangerous.
I found this out recently because I was going to that subreddit for opiates.
I guess this is a problem.
People are pressing their own pills like Xanax or pain pills, hydrocodone or whatever.
They're pressing these pills and they'll use a little bit of actual Vicodin dust, whatever
the actual stuff is, oxy stuff, and then put fentanyl in it.
And so this stuff, it's imprecise.
You just have a bunch of powder there and you kind of like mix it up.
You put some of the real stuff in and then some of the fentanyl stuff in and you mix
it up and then you're pressing these pills.
You may end up getting a pill of pure fentanyl, which will kill you.
Or you may get a pill that has more of the Vicodin stuff in it.
And it was interesting because I was on that subreddit for the opiates and the one guy
was talking about, "I got these pills and they're pressed."
So homemade.
And I'm going to crush them up and snort them.
And someone goes, "That's how people die."
I guess that's how Lil Peep died.
He was a rapper.
They did with Xanax though.
They'll press Xanax bars with fentanyl in them.
And you may break it up in just the right way that you get a line of just pure fentanyl.
Kill you.
It's absolutely nuts that people are even chancing that.
And they hope that it has a little bit of fentanyl in it because it's stronger.
But anyways, they're finding these dead homeless people in Tijuana overdose heroin and fentanyl.
And they're also laboratories on the Tijuana River, inside like the Nooks and Crannies River,
where they're making fentanyl and they're producing this stuff.
And the going theory that the journalist put forward is that what happens is, if the batch
is too strong, it'll kill you.
And you don't want your customers to die.
But you don't want to make it too weak either, because then they'll just buy from another
dealer.
So what the cartel is doing, again, allegedly, and this is being put forth by this journalist,
is that they're making batches of this and then giving it out to free to the homeless
people to test it.
And they keep track.
This guy got batch number 105.
Here you go, sir.
Enjoy.
This guy got batch 106.
Here you go, sir.
Enjoy.
This guy got that.
And so the next day when they come back through, guy who took 105, "Oh yeah, man, it was so
good, dude.
I haven't been that high in so long.
Oh, it felt so good."
106, dead.
Okay, reformulate.
106, go on to the next guy.
They're basically running lab experiments on homeless drug users in Tijuana.
So they may not be creating beasts of the netherworld.
They may not be creating genetic super soldiers.
But organized crime is having an impact on the world of science.
Whether it's shutting down observatories, running out agricultural specialists, or any
other examples of the cartel interfering with research work.
That is definitely happening.
But they're also running human tests to see if they can turn their deadly product a little
less deadly for maximum profit.
Sometimes the real monster isn't the one you hear in the darkness that's unseen.
Sometimes the real monster is the one holding out a little baggy with a smile on his face
saying here, "This will make the pain go away."
And then waiting to see what really happens.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[Music]