Was the Hollow Earth theory proved this week?
And then we take a look at the mystery of Pauline Picard.
A young French girl who went missing was found and then found again today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. Just a quick update to a story we
did a couple days ago, I think it was last week, where we were talking about conspiracy theories.
Basically YouTube is going to stop recommending conspiracy theory videos and things like that.
It'll have a minor impact on this channel. I do get flagged for talking about stuff even though
I'm disputing certain conspiracy theories. The algorithm doesn't pick up on that. They just
hear that I'm using those words. And in that little segment, I was talking about what is a
conspiracy theory? When I was talking to my friend Mitcham, we started talking about anti-vaxxers.
At what point does that become a conspiracy theory where YouTube is going to start
not recommending those videos? And he said, yeah, at what point does something go from
being a quack medical practice to a conspiracy theory? Well, I just saw an article the other day
where Facebook is actually going to stop recommending or they're looking at the option
of stop recommending groups and pages that talk about the dangers of vaccinations.
Representative Adam Schiff wrote a letter to Facebook and Google saying that we're having
real problems with measles outbreaks and it's on you guys to stop promoting this stuff. So again,
I mean, this is where this is going. I'm personally not an anti-vaxxer. I understand a lot of people
have concerns about the vaccine and they wish that it was broken up into three separate vaccines.
So I get it. I don't have kids. It's kind of an issue that I really haven't looked into that much
because I'm like, I don't have kids. I don't have to worry about it. People believe this. People
believe that. It doesn't affect me. But it's the slippery slope because my example was the
Mueller investigation. If Mueller doesn't find any proof that Trump colluded, does that mean
everything? All the podcasts talking about Russian collusion, all the YouTube videos about
Russian collusion, all of the Facebook pages, are those going to not get recommended anymore?
At what point, stuff like the keto diet, can people say that's quack medicine? It doesn't work.
Like at what point do the companies have to say, listen, we can't censor everything that's not
mainstream? So yeah, it'll be interesting to see how this all plays out because really at a certain
point there's conspiracy theories about everything. I think the thing comes down to the opponents or
proponents of a particular conspiracy theory. How powerful are they? Because they could say,
no, no, no, this isn't, is climate change a conspiracy theory? Is denying climate change a
conspiracy theory? All of these issues will have to be handled in the next, really probably in the
next couple months. The Facebook and Google and all that stuff leading up to the next election are
going to have a lot of pressure on them to shut this stuff down in one way or the other. So we'll
see. We'll keep covering the story. I think it's going to develop very interestingly. But we had
some amazing news this week. And it really gives hope to the weirdos. Hope to the weirdos like me.
And we're going to specifically be talking about hollow earth. Now, so the idea when people use
the term hollow earth is generally that the earth itself is hollow, that there's just an outward
crust. And then inside there's a bunch of like spaceships flying around and octopus people and
eight foot tall mummies dancing and all that stuff. And I think that's kind of the perception. And I
think that's kind of misleading. Now that may have been the idea of what hollow earth was in the 1700s.
But when I've talked about stuff like vast cave systems, and I don't generally use the term hollow
earth because a lot of people think, well, there's not a giant hole in the earth that you can fall
into and meet like mumra flying around ships powered by Vril. I don't believe in any of that.
But I believe that deep, deep under the earth, there are vast caverns and cave big enough for
whole societies to live in. I believe that what we think I don't I never really bought the idea
that the earth was a solid ball. I believe that deep in the earth, you would have huge open stretches.
And I'm talking deep, deep, deep under the earth, hundreds of miles. You'd have these vast cavern
systems. Whether or not those were accessible to us. I don't know. But I never really I was
thought, well, how do we really know what the earth is made of the scientific idea. And it's
funny because I was in preparation for the story I went to the Wikipedia article about hollow earth.
And talking about the scientific debunking and stuff like that, they said, nope, the earth is
completely solid. You have the upper mantle and the lower mantle and the molten core and the crust.
Delicious jelly filled doughnut that we call planet earth, except instead of jelly, it's hot lava.
But so what happened in 1994? There was a massive earthquake, the second strongest earthquake
on record. And it wasn't just like, oh, no stuff shaking around. It was a earth quake. The whole
earth shook during this event. And a bunch of nerds have been pouring over the results for the past,
I don't know, what would that be 15? No, that'd be like 25 years, maybe. So this earthquake happened
when I was in high school graduating year. Happened the year after Kurt Cobain died, maybe it was
his ghost floating around, shaking stuff up like he did with the music industry. But anyways,
so in 1994, the shine earthquake happened, they've been pouring over the results ever since. Now,
last week, Valentine's week, it was a love letter to, like I said, all the weirdos out there. And
I'm including myself in that definition. The report was released. And they're saying,
well, we can measure the seismic waves because this earthquake, it's kind of bounces around the
core and moves from one end of the earth to the other. They said, based on the seismic waves and
the way they moved through this, through the planet, there are mountain ranges and valleys
within the planet earth. This is a quote with stronger topography than the Rocky Mountains or
the Appalachians. And this is at the 600 kilometer boundary. The deepest we've ever dug is seven
miles down 600 kilometers, I think comes out to what, three feet? No, 600 kilometers is hundreds
of miles down. And based on this study, they've had to update what they think the earth looks like.
Now, of course, a bunch of other scientists are going to go, no, no, no, that's wrong and Pluto's
not a planet, by the way. But they're showing a new model of the earth where we have the crust,
we have the upper mantle. Now, there's always been a thing called the transition zone.
But old science was that the upper mantle and the lower mantle touched and there was a slight
transition zone in between the two. And then after the lower mantle, you get into the core and things
like that. But the new vision of what the earth looks like is you have the crust, that's us,
we're the tasty crust. You have the upper mantle, which goes down a couple hundred miles. And then
you have an incredibly vast mountain range that exists between the lower and the upper. And it's
not like the mountains are pushing up again, there's room in there. We can tell from the way that the
seismic waves were bouncing around and all the links are here. Check them out yourself because
they'll have these new pictures of what they think the earth looks like. But it is basically a smaller
version of the earth. We have the earth and you get a little couple go couple hundred miles down
and you got all these other mountains and valleys and stuff like that. The earth has a hollow zone
inside of it. It's not hollow in the middle. You can't, Jules Verne can't take his little
blimp down there and fly around. Well, technically he could, but we don't have a way to get down there.
And there's a theory that there's a ton of water stored up in mineral deposits in the lower
mantle. And they think that if the water wasn't there, it like, it basically keeps the earth,
like it filters up in the earth and signs us like, listen, we think that it's down there based on
these mineral deposits that we know hold a lot of water. And now to be fair, a lot of these articles
were, as I started to dig deeper into it, I was really trying to find some stuff, a lot of the
articles were a little too smart for me using a bunch of five dollar words. But from what I could
gather, there are rocks down there, there's minerals down there that do soak up water. And
there are mineral deposits down there that they believe can release oxygen as well. Now,
if that stuff sounds stupid to you, it's because I misread the articles, but possibly have water
down there. And I don't see why not. You still have hundreds and hundreds of miles ago before you
hit the molten core. You have water down there. Do you have oxygen down there? I tried digging
through all these scientific papers. They're way too smart for me. So I can't say for sure,
oh science thinks there's oxygen down there, but there's a bunch of room. Maybe there is. Or maybe
there's not. Maybe it's a super dark place that has mountain. And let's not get into the, let's
take a step back here. Underneath our feet, past the hot lava tubes, past the mole men, past the
chuds, there are unexplored, never will be explored mountain ranges, valleys, caves, locked in eternal
darkness. We will never, ever get to experience geography that exists on our own planet. And I
always thought it was fascinating because you think, think about all the wonders under the
ocean, not just the fish and stuff like that, but the geography, the amazing, the amazing chasms,
the marinara trench for one. But these amazing geological formations that will never be seen,
but at least we can pick them up with deep sea cameras, kind of seismic x-ray, water things,
you know, topographical maps of the ocean, stuff like that. But now we're discovering that there is
an entire new land base inside our planet that we'll never experience. Is it possible that there is
a series of caves that lead down into there? Just connected here? Is it possible that you could go
deep down enough into a cave and get your cobra drilling machine, cobra commander drilling machine,
and then go through and hit another cave system and so on and so forth and then
eventually get into this other area? I don't know that, but I do trust the old saying that nature
abhors a vacuum. Where there is space, there is life. May not be life that we would recognize,
but life. My personal belief with UFOs and aliens is that they come from our planet,
most likely from inside of our planet, I've stated that multiple times,
and now for the first time just having that kind of half-assed idea. Now for the first time, science
says there is room down there for something to inhabit. Doesn't mean that something's down there,
but nature does abhore a vacuum. Let's go ahead and move on to our next story here. I wonder if
they have like a wonder. It'd be interesting because imagine if you were, imagine if there were
aliens down there and they had built the ships that we see as UFOs and there is tunnels to come
out through the ocean or through you know wherever, most likely the ocean. Imagine them coming out for
the first time and not only seeing a blue sky and humans and cities and things like that, which they'd
all be like, "Yeah, you know, there's water down there and we got people down there and we have
cities down there." But for the first time seeing the stars, it'd be, I don't think there's anything
that we can compare to that. We can think about going into the earth or going under the ocean,
but things simply get black and dark. Imagine coming up for the, what's funny, I say the stars,
I guess I should really focus on the main one, the sun. Imagine seeing the sun for the first
time as a species and being like, "Well, that's all they say. Should have brought a poet. Should
have brought a poet, Hollow Earth aliens." Probably would have had something more to say than, "Well,
anyways, let's go ahead and move on to our next story." Now our next story is quite grim and quite
odd. Very, very bizarre mystery story and it's one of those stories where in the end nobody wins,
which usually makes it the most grim type of stories. We're going back to the year
1922. Let's go ahead and let's see. We're going to take the Jason Jalopy because we're going to
have to keep a low profile because there's a lot of police in this story and a lot of suspects. So
driving across the countryside of France, it's April, it's 1922 and we're going to Brittany,
France, which sounds like a really hot chick, but it's actually a city in the country of France.
Brittany, France. Brittany, France. It does sound like a hot chick though, doesn't it?
Now that was probably a bad way to start. They can't really find a segue to this part.
Probably shouldn't have talked about the hot chick and what's coming. So there is a young girl
named Pauline Picard. So Pauline Picard is a two-year- I actually didn't know Picard was a
real French name until I read this story. I thought it was just something made up for Star
Track. I mean, Spock's not a real name. Pauline Picard, a two-year-old girl, hanging out at the
farmhouse with her family and she wants to go out and play in the field. Now I don't have kids again.
I didn't know two-year-olds could talk very well, but that becomes a main point in this story.
But the young girl, Pauline, goes, "Mama, mama, can I go? Can I go into the fields and play around?"
And the mom's like, "Yes, Pauline, you can do that. Watch out for Klingons." The mom is like, "Yes, yes,
wee-wee. Wee-wee. You can go and you can play." Now I don't actually know if they said "wee-wee"
because they actually spoke a language known as Breton. I don't know if that's like an offshoot
of French, like we have English and then we have whatever they speak in the South, in the Cajun
land. Oh yeah, I gotta stop doing accents anyways. Pauline Picard's running through the field.
And mom's like, "Oh, she's such a wonderful little girl." But then after a couple hours,
the mom's like, "Dinner time, we're eating French food." And the Pauline doesn't show up at all.
So mom starts to get worried, goes out looking for a confinder. The mom alerts the authorities,
they come out there. I don't know where the father was at this point, but eventually he does show up
at some point. They, actually that's interesting, that we'll get to the father in a second, but
they go out. Eventually 150 people are searching the farm. No trace of Pauline. No trace at all of
Pauline. And after three weeks, they're like, "She's not here anymore." Like this, sorry, sorry
French mom, but we think she's gone. But so the search party ended. Like it started off strong
and then people kind of started to peter out. It's kind of like when a concert's over, people show
up, they're ready to go, and then after a while they get bored. But on the fourth week, a month later,
after she disappeared, a police officer arrives at the Picard's door. I'm trying so hard not to
make star-track jokes. The police officer has a photograph of a young girl that says, "Is this
your daughter? We think we found her. Is this your daughter?" And the mama goes, "Oh my god,
that's my daughter." And she gets the husband over there and he's like, "Oh my god, that's a
daughter." And the cop's like, "Okay, calm down for a second." We found her 200 miles away. So there
was another city 200 miles away. Now this is 1922. It's not like you were able to hop a plane back
then and get stuck in the airport overnight. But she ends up 200 miles away. And the reason why
the cops noticed her, because she was just wandering the streets of this town all by herself.
Some accounts she was with an old woman in rags, but other people are like, "No, she just wanted
to be by herself." Either way, it's creepy. So the... how do you just wear rags? Do they just
mean like you had raggedy clothing? Or was she literally like wearing dish rags? So anyways,
they never found out the truth to that. The old woman either disappeared or never existed in the
first place. There was just a one rag laying in the gutter. But the cops do and the parents go
and they go to this town 200 miles away. And they're like, "Oh my god, it's Pauline." But...
And this is where... so we just have a missing child, a missing child found. But this is where the
story gets bizarre. As they start to interact with Pauline, they notice a few key things. One,
she does look just like Pauline. She's emaciated. She's a little starved. Now they're like, "Well,
that's weird. Our daughter was chubby. You're not. You're not her daughter." But it did kind of set
them off. But that wasn't the only thing. She didn't speak Breton. She didn't speak that language.
She couldn't communicate with her parents and her brothers and their sisters. But when they
brought Pauline home, the brothers and the sisters were like, "Pauline! Pauline, you're back!"
Neighbors were like, "Oh my god, I'm so glad you found your daughter." Other people recognized
her as Pauline. But she didn't speak that language. And she interacted with her mother and her father
and her siblings as a child would a stranger. Is it happy? Hey, nice to meet you. My name's Pauline.
Really, I think that's my name by the way. Let's shake hands. You got anything to eat? But it wasn't
in the loving way that she interacted with them before or a child would interact with a parent.
So something was off. Now, the police were saying, "Listen, it's quite likely that your daughter's
going to be acting weird for a while because it's quite likely, unfortunately, that she was abused."
And she might be dealing with some sort of traumatic experience. So she's going to act a little weird
for a while. At one point, a guy, a friend of theirs apparently named, I don't know how to pronounce
this, but I'm going to say call him Eve's Martin. It's that Y-V-E-S, Eve's Martin. Eve's Martin is
hanging out of their house. And he goes, "No, so Eve's Martin, maybe it's Yeves. Yeves Martin
shows up at the Picard home and they're drinking Earl Grey tea, hot." And he goes, "Is it true?
Is it true that Pauline is here? That that girl that is walking around is Pauline?"
The parents go, "Yeah." And he goes, "God is fair. I am guilty." And he runs away.
I'll show you what. Parents are like, "What? A weird, weird, weird thing to say."
Three weeks after she is found, a cyclist is riding around the property of the Picards.
And they had a farm, so it wasn't like doing wheelies in their front yard, but he's bicycling
around their area. And he sees something you don't ever want to see. He sees a child's body,
a little girl's body. No head, no hands, no feet, and a little stack of clothing next to the body.
The body wasn't wearing any clothes. And it totally freaks him out, obviously. He takes off,
he goes, gets the authorities. The cops have to stand there for three days, because it takes
that long for the prosecutors to get out there. I guess they had different divisions. They didn't
have a SVU and a criminal intent. So the cops would enforce the law, but to get the detectives
out there, they had to come from another area. So while they're standing there guarding this
body, guarding the evidence, they notice there's something else there. There is a head, so they're
like, oh, maybe it's the head of the little girl. I don't know why they sound so cheery about that,
but at first they think it's the head of the little girl, but they're go, that head's kind of big.
It was half eaten, half eaten head. So you can't really tell what it is. When the prosecutors get
there and they start running all their investigation stuff, their tests, they realize the head is the
head of an adult male. So we have a little girl whose head, I, this episode, sorry, this is kind
of grim, I should have said early on, but you have a little girl with no head, no hands, no feet,
and then a head, a half eaten head. It was not eaten by the cyclist. It was eaten by a bunch of
foxes in the area. A half eaten head of a man, decapitated man. So now things are really starting
to fall apart. The police immediately begin an investigation over who the bodies belong to,
who the body parts belong to, and who the young girl is living in the Picard's house.
The pile of clothes that are sitting next to the body, the mom of Pauline identifies those
clothes as the clothes that Pauline was wearing the day she went missing neatly folded next to her
body. The police say this area where this body was found was searched over and over and it was
only 800 meters from the house. It wasn't way off in the woods. It was only 800 meters from the house.
So this would have been an area that people were traveling through to and fro searching for the
body. One of the cops was like, if I had dropped my wallet there, I would have found it. Like it was
a place that they were constantly walking by. So they were working on the theory that these body
parts were dumped recently. And this whole thing happened. So she went missing. Pauline was found
in the city two miles away a month later. And three weeks after that, they find this stuff.
They find a head that's been eaten and a body that hasn't. The police start looking at suspects.
The first one obviously is Yev's. So they're like, oh, so a guy came in here and like freaked out when
he found out your daughter was still alive. And they're like, yeah, it was super weird. So they go
track him down. He got committed to a mental institution and was completely incommunicable.
He was just blah, blah, blah. And the cops are like, we're not going to get anything from this guy.
He's just lunatic. He's a nut guy. And obviously, I guess I should say this, huge news story,
global news story at this point. Everyone is reporting it. Huge national news story, huge
international news story. The media was like, the kind of the theory was that he had a traumatic
brain injury shortly before his outburst. So they think that that causes insanity, not the guilt
of this murder. Then there was the theory that the father killed her because the father had a violent
temper. And that's why I was thinking it was interesting because he wasn't there when she
went missing. But now that I think about it, he was probably just at work in the mill shop or
making shoes or something like that. But he was a suspect for a while. They did have this
suspect, this other suspect called Christoph Karamon. Christoph Karamon. The morning that
Pauline, this is weird, the morning that Pauline disappeared, he was a first off, he was an umbrella
salesman. Odd. I mean, either you're selling them during the rain and people are like, now just run
to my buggy, or you're selling them during the summertime and being like, you never know.
But apparently back then there was umbrella salesman. This guy sold them. So he was at the
house eating breathics with the cards. The morning that Pauline disappeared. And he was always like
cuddling her and like telling her, I'm going to find you a good home. And that's creepy. And
somebody apparently overheard him saying that Pauline was going to go away with him and stuff
like that. So creep check 123, like, guys, a total weirdo. But the police said that his alibi checked
out. So he must have been going to an umbrella sales convention or something like that that morning.
But he was acting like a total weirdo. And he was rubbing up on her and stuff like that,
cuddling her. I don't know. It's all gross. Anyways, if it's not your kid, you should keep
your hands off. But anyways, so he got cleared of it as well. So we're still back to the three
main mysteries. Who killed the girl? A girl. They still don't know if it's Pauline. Who killed the girl?
Whose head was next to her? And who's the little girl living in the house? Little two year old
quote unquote Pauline Picard. Unfortunately, none of those questions are ever answered.
But the parents say, we think that the body in the field was Pauline. And this little girl in our
house was not. So they take Pauline Picard, they take her back to the town 200 miles away the
way they found her from, give her to a bunch of nuns. They weren't just walking on the street. It was
like a nunnery convent, convince the word I'm looking for. They say, here, take care of this kid.
We don't know who it is, but it's not ours. They erected a gravestone and put the date of death
for Pauline Picard as the day she went missing. And that was that. No one was ever caught for this.
They never identified the head. They couldn't figure out why the body parts weren't found during
the original searches. So they do believe that they were dumped after the fact. Imagine, just imagine
that. And that there's been a couple other stories in true crime where someone's gone missing and
then someone's found and it's not the correct person. That would be like losing them twice.
She goes missing. You find her, you bring her home, you find out it's not her. And then you take her
back. You're basically losing one child and giving up another one. The question, the biggest question
to me is this. I actually have two big questions because I read the story multiple times and all
the details are pretty much the same, but somebody would have had to dump those body parts.
Most likely, most likely, because it was so close to where they set off the original search.
Whose head is that? I think that is, to me, the big clue. A half-eaten head next to a body that
hasn't been eaten really makes you think that these crimes took place at different points.
Was there a half-eaten head somewhere and it was taken there? Did someone just have a
calvocate of body parts? Was someone still out there brutally murdering children and adults
and anyone who got in their way and just dumping their body parts? Was it a rage-filled incident
from a father or a neighbor and they had to make it look like some sort of creepy
ex-files crime to make it not look so domestic? Who knows? It's a true mystery, but this is what I
think is really sad. I personally, and I have no proof to back this up, I think that the girl in the
town 200 miles away was Pauline Picard. I think that any sort of differences in her personality
or things like that could be attributed to physical or emotional or mental trauma. I find it odd that
you could find somebody who looked like your daughter 200 miles away to the point where everyone in
town is convinced that's your daughter. Where you're convinced that's your daughter, except she's
just a little skinny, and to spend three weeks with this person and then you find another body that
happened to have the same clothes on or off as the matter is and then decide that's not your daughter.
I think if you didn't have a good understanding of how the brain works after trauma, you may think,
"Well, that's weird. She's not speaking the same language and she's not acting the same, so this
probably isn't the same person." If someone did that today, if someone went through a traumatic
event and they used to be happy go lucky and now they're kind of swollen, you wouldn't say, "Well,
that's not the real person anymore. The other person must have just never shown up. That's not
my sister. My sister used to be real happy and now that horrible thing happened to her, she sits
around in cries all the time. That's not my sister." It just seems like a bizarre overreaction.
There was one other theory I wanted to touch on real quick before I wrap this up, but
there was another theory to get this is just an urban legend in town. There was a rich couple who
was due to get an inheritance, but to get the inheritance they had to have a child.
And their daughter died, so they left that body in the farm and took Pauline, but then eventually
Pauline got loose. It's interesting because that story makes absolutely no sense based on the facts
we have. They'd have to come back to the place to drop the body off because it wasn't found initially.
Why would they let Pauline get away if it was all part of the scam? But it's interesting to show how
communities and people want so hard for there to be a reasonable explanation for something that
they just kind of make stuff up. But the saddest part is, is that whether or not that is Pauline
or it wasn't in the town, whether or not Pauline was really killed in the field or Pauline ended
up 200 miles away in that town, she was an orphan, like they just found her wandering the streets.
No one in the town claimed her as a daughter or a sister or a friend or anything like that. She was
a young girl wandering 200 miles away. She was allowed to be taken 200 miles back to the Bacard
home and no one was like, "Hey wait, no, no, no, that's my niece." Like she was completely alone
in that town when she was discovered. The rag woman non-withstanding because we don't know if that's
true. But even the rag woman wasn't like, "Oh no, no, no, she works for me." Like you have this young
two-year-old girl found 200 miles away taken to another place. After three weeks taken back to
that town, dropped off with a bunch of nuns. Two years later she died during the measles outbreak
of 1924. Just a little girl, a little mystery. No one ever claimed her, no one ever loved her.
She just existed and then she didn't. And if it wasn't for this mystery,
the world would have never known she existed.
Was she the missing girl or was she just a lonely child wandering the streets of a city
looking for someone to care?
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @jasonocarvider.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and truth crime podcast. You don't have to listen
to it every day. But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
(upbeat music)