A woman trying to fall asleep.
A couple at Lovers Lane.
A mother and her daughter traveling through France.
What do all three of these scenarios have in common?
They're part of our Trilogy of Terror, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I actually, I don't know if you guys can notice this, but I have a whole new setup.
I bought, I used my Patreon money and I bought some pretty high-end stuff.
So hopefully it sounds better.
If it sounds worse, let me know so I can return it.
But yeah, so this is all new for me.
Investing in the show and I can't do that without my Patreon supporters.
We have a new one.
Let's give a round of applause to Bill Gape's.
Bill Gape's.
Let's give him a round of applause.
He's doing a little bow for us.
He's going to be our pilot, our captain this episode.
You can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That also really, really helps out a lot.
We're almost done with October and I've been thinking, we haven't had any really
scary episodes.
We haven't done any real spooky stuff.
Now the stuff in this episode, I don't know if it's terror might be pushing it.
It's more of a disturbing story, but not disturbing like Monday's episode.
Monday's episode was gross.
Too disturbing.
There's a line.
But the reason why I wanted to do this episode is I actually had a dream last night.
You're like already fast-forwarding.
Yes, no one wants to hear about dreams, but every so often I'll have a very rarely, I
guess I should say.
I'll have a really unsettling nightmare.
I have a really good friend named Jackie.
Talked about her several times on the show.
I haven't spoken to her in probably about a year or now, but you know, because people
have families and stuff like that, but really, really close friend of mine growing up.
Plus, not a dream.
She was a witch.
She was up to no good.
She was casting spells on people.
She was interrupting the daily life of this community I lived in.
It was one of times I didn't live in like 1890s.
I wasn't carrying milk to turn into butter.
This is modern times, but I found out that she was this witch and she was up to no good.
She had all sorts of powers and I grabbed her by the throat.
Don't read too much into this, especially Jackie if you're listening to this podcast.
I grabbed Jackie by the throat and I'm bringing her to the constables or the police because
again, it's not old time.
There's actually officers of the law.
I'm grabbing her by the throat and I'm carrying her through the center of town to where I know
where law enforcement's at.
She's talking trash.
She's kind of like goading me on to do whatever, but I have won the day.
She has this little smirk on her face and I have my hand wrapped around her tiny little
neck.
When I walk into the police station, my hand is around my own neck and she's gone.
I was like, "Where did she go?"
They're like, "Well, that is Jackie for you."
I go, "Yeah, Jackie does have those powers.
You really know..."
I let go of my neck at this point.
I'm not still strangling myself.
You never really know what to expect.
At some point, I did have her by the...
Maybe, maybe I never captured her.
Maybe that was all in my imagination.
I'm talking to these officers of law and they're like, "Yeah, she really has the ability to
warp reality."
I said, "For all I know, this isn't real and I'm crucified in some abandoned warehouse
somewhere with my legs chopped off."
Then instantly the dream ended and I was in this room crucified and I can barely breathe.
I can barely hold up the weight of my body because that's what crucifixion does.
It starts to compress your lungs and there was a mirror set up in front of me and I
could see my face turning a weird bluish purple and I'm gasping for breath.
I remember I start looking down to see if I had my legs but I couldn't take my eyes off
of the image of myself in the mirror that had been set up so I could see my own death.
And then the dream starts again and we're like, "Ha ha ha, laughing with the constables
and stuff because what a wacky idea.
Who would think that someone could alter reality that much?"
And then I woke up and I'm laying in bed and I'm like, "That was a creepy nightmare."
Bill Gates is hiding under the covers.
Come on, that's not the creepiest story we're going to talk about and it was just the dream
or was it?
It's really weird to have a dream where you're watching yourself slowly die but Bill Gates,
come on get out of the bed.
He's like, "These sheets are so clean.
You have to get in the dead rabbit rowboat.
We are leaving behind America and we are headed out to California."
I thought we were going to another country this first story.
We're headed to California.
Some place in California we don't have a specific location.
We don't have a name of this person.
And I know you guys are thinking, "Is this a dream?
Was this made up?"
Well we'll get to it whether or not it was a dream in a second because it does start off
in bed.
A lot of these stories that start off in bed I'm already a little suspicious of.
So it's February 1997.
We're in California and we're going to meet this woman.
We're not going to meet her because she's actually in bed right now.
She's like, "What?
What are all these people showing up?"
We're like, "Shh, we're here for a podcast.
Don't pay attention to us.
Pay attention to the thing that's about to happen, but not all these strangers in your
bedroom."
We're going to call her Margaret.
Margaret is sleeping.
So it could be a dream.
I always got to say that.
Margaret's sleeping and then all of a sudden she wakes up and she hears, "Margaret!
Margaret!"
I don't know if the voices are super creepy.
"Come here, Margaret."
I don't know, but she heard her name.
It could have just been like, "Margaret!
Hey, you!
Margaret!"
She just heard someone calling her name.
They weren't like, "A tisket, a tisket."
They may have been, I don't know, not enough details with this story.
So that's not really creepy.
It is.
It's to wake up in the middle of the night into an empty room and someone's saying your
name.
That's super spooky.
But that's not the creepy part of the story.
She finds herself paralyzed.
She can't move.
Sleep paralysis is very common.
It's a real thing.
She's laying there in bed.
Now eventually she starts struggling more and more.
She's able to roll over onto her side.
And that's when she sees a human walk into the room.
Now he's pretty short guy.
So we'll say four feet tall, fairly short man, almost alien height.
So you think it's a great alien, a hybrid.
This dude has a full head of hair and a little beard.
We don't really see facial hair among aliens.
The story crosses a lot of weird boundaries, but everything else that's going on seems
alien.
He walks into the room, almost floats into the room.
She said the way that he glided, she couldn't see his feet.
She's frozen, but now she's sideways in the bed.
She had struggled enough to do that.
She could see he kind of floated across the ground.
And she's continuing to struggle.
She's obviously distressed that this total stranger's in her bedroom.
She's frozen.
Who was calling her names?
There's a whole bunch of questions.
And the bearded man just kind of looks at her and says, "Hmm, you should be used to
this by now."
And then the next thing she knows, it's daylight.
I think that story's creepy.
Come on, Bill, get out of underneath her covers as well.
He's also super scared.
I think this story is creepy.
All the elements are pretty routine.
Like I'm not saying they're not creepy just because we hear them all the time, but sleep
paralysis, alien abduction, all that stuff is creepy and in of its own.
But the fact that one, that was his exact quote, "You should be used to this by now."
It's so clinical.
The first time you go in for a rectal exam, it's going to be incredibly uncomfortable.
Probably it'll do that for the first 10 times.
But eventually you'll just be like, "Well, it's time for my rectal exam.
What are you doing that you need so many?"
Who knows?
Maybe you like to ride dirt bikes.
Is that a thing?
Does that mess up your butthole?
I assume it would.
You get a bunch of dirt in it.
Eventually you're going to get used to it.
The fact that this is happening so often that this alien doctor I can presume would say,
"Hmm, she's still fighting it.
You should be used to it by now."
And it's that idea of he's probably made comments to her multiple times during these
examinations or abductions or whatever they are.
And she doesn't remember any of them.
There's been so many interactions between herself and this being, not remembering any
of it.
It's weird enough when you're walking down the street and you see someone who clearly
recognizes you and starts talking to you and you don't remember them.
It's always like, "How could I forget a whole human being?"
Now add the possibility of that person abducting you from time to time and putting stuff in
your body.
And then be like, "Hey, Jason, remember me?"
I was like, "Uh, can you jog in my memory?"
"Yeah, I broke in your apartment the other day.
Totally abducted you."
"What?
Why not?
I'm not moving that at all.
Oh man.
Well, I'll see you later."
"What are you talking about?"
It's 10 times more disturbing when you have that on it.
So I thought that story was, again, just creepy.
A creepy short little story for Halloween.
It's not really Halloween, really.
It takes place in February of 1997, but it's still spooky.
And I'm actually a kind of feel bad that I haven't covered enough spooky stuff.
So I wanted to get some spooky stuff for you.
Like, that's kind of spooky, Jason.
Okay.
Bill Gape's Let's Go Ahead and Leave Behind California.
Now we're going to hop into the Jason Jet.
We are flying out to the country that never sleeps, Puerto Rico.
Jason Jet's flying over there.
We're hanging out.
Bill Gape has a bunch of blankets.
He's flying the plane.
He's too scared to fly the plane.
Oh, come on, man.
He's flying out there.
We're going to Ponce in Puerto Rico.
It's January 1999.
It's late evening.
Little crickets.
Apparently they've evolved to be blue jays.
Making those noises.
You're like, Jason, that's the farthest from a cricket noise, I think, is humanly possible.
Frogs then.
I'm setting the scene.
I imagine Ponce Puerto Rico looks like that little lagoon from the Little Mermaid.
Anyways, it's a lover's lane.
See, you have two people.
They're unnamed.
They're called Ariel and Eric.
They're sitting at this lagoon.
They're doing more than just, "Do you want to kiss the girl?"
They're getting hot and heavy.
They've moved far past the musical numbers.
And that's not the guy.
That's not the guy.
I forgot to change perspective.
Now we're outside the car that they're in.
They turn and they look and they see standing outside of their car, Bigfoot.
Now I know what you're thinking.
What?
Bigfoot in Puerto Rico?
I mean, we've covered Mormon Bigfoot in Bigfoot's out of UFOs and Bigfoot's turning
from human into Bigfoot.
I don't know why I'm shocked.
What?
Bigfoot in Puerto Rico?
That's unbelievable.
I don't know why I'm shocked that Bigfoot could show up in Puerto Rico.
Apparently he can.
He did.
And this story, at least.
Could be a localized version of Bigfoot.
Because this Bigfoot has an interesting power.
So let's go back to the narrative.
I just want to do that noise again.
And the couple turns and they look and they see Bigfoot standing outside of the car,
glowing red eyes.
The girl jumps out of the car.
Fight or flight, right?
They figure you're safe in the car if an elk shows up or a bear shows up to your car.
I don't know if they have those in Puerto Rico, but for all I know they do, better to
stay in the car.
Again, something like Bigfoot, your instinct may be to run away from it.
To try to put distance between yourself and this giant creature.
But the boyfriend sees the girl fiddle with the handle and she jumps out of the car and
he's like "Wait, no, Ariel, come back!"
And he's expecting to watch her run off into the dark forest.
But instead, she walks out of the car, walks to a cliff face, that's there.
I should have said that up earlier, it's not a lagoon, there's a cliff there.
She gets out of the car, doesn't run away, she walks to the edge of the cliff and jumps
off.
The Bigfoot leaves and the girl survives.
She doesn't die when she jumps off the cliff.
And of course people are thinking, if you're ever attacked by Bigfoot again, if this ever
happens again, because it's so common, if you're ever attacked by Bigfoot again, stay
in the car.
And she goes, "I didn't have a choice."
And everyone's like, "What are you talking about?"
And she goes, "I was in the car with Eric reading Bible verses, like we do every night."
And then this creature showed up and the creature told me, "No, no, no, the creature forced
me.
It took control of my mind.
It walked me to the edge of the cliff and made me jump.
I didn't want to get out of the car.
The creature made me."
That's another interesting slice of lore we can add to the Bigfoot story.
Maybe that's something only the Puerto Rico and Bigfoot can do, but that is beyond creepy.
I think, again, we've talked about this before, like beating up aliens, you can totally beat
up a grey alien, I've beaten that message into the ground, but you always have to worry
about them using mind controllers, some sort of space-age weapon.
There's not many cryptids that can actually possess a human like that.
There have been interesting stories about people getting ready to shoot cryptids, and
we've talked about this recently on the show, and they're guns.
They imagine their guns are going to miss fire so they don't pull the trigger and the
cryptid gets away.
And the implication is that that creature put that image in their head, much like Jackie,
put the image of me, she didn't really, it was a dream, but put the image of me choking
her, I was choking myself, I never had her in prison.
But that's just illusion, the idea that you could be trying to outrun a Bigfoot or even
look for a Bigfoot, or really even not even knowing Bigfoot is in the area, you're out
on a nature hike all by yourself, and something is in the bushes, completely unseen, and you
start to feel the need to kill yourself.
She survived, so she could tell the story about what happened, but there's variations of this,
I mean there's different ways it could have come out, she could have just jumped off the
cliff and died, and then the boyfriend would have said "well yeah, first thought that would
have been a murder case, right?
You can't go back to town and be like "hey what happened to Ariel?"
And he's like "dude you won't believe it, Bigfoot showed up and then she jumped off
a cliff."
They're like "awesome, can you tell that story again but with your hands behind your back
and your head to the wall, that'd be totally awesome, you're under arrest."
It would be really hard to explain that away, but had she died, it would have just been
so scary that she ran out into the darkness, didn't know there was a cliff there.
Or if there was no witness there, then when she jumped off the cliff there was no one
there to help render aid or get her back to the car or something like that.
And you gotta wonder, just because we're paranormal people, how many times do you hear about these
lone hikers or these mountain climbers or something that fall to their deaths?
Tragic accident, it is tragic, but what if there's another paranormal answer behind that?
What if they are successfully making that trek up the mountain, but then something in
the bushes pushes them closer to the precipice?
See, that's a creepy one, I thought that one was really creepy too.
Bill Gape's, he's already doing it, he's signaling in the carpenter copter it's making a landing,
you are going to fly us out from Puerto Rico, we are headed out to Paris, France.
And while we're headed out to Paris, France, I'm going to turn to you, turn the lights
down a bit, the super dim Bill Gape's like "I can't see where we're going, I just keep
flying."
Eventually you'll see an Eiffel Tower and then stop, land right there.
But I turn to you in the dark and I hold a flashlight up under my face and I say "This
Halloween, prepare yourself for the terrifying suspense thriller Spell."
You'll see him in the movie, "The
Watch the Trailer" a couple times, it looks like a tale from the crypt.
It looks pretty cool and then I was showing other people the trailer too, I show people
trailers because no one has time to watch a whole movie with me.
So we watch trailers.
I turn the lights back on, just in time Bill Gape needs to learn how to fly by instruments,
but he successfully lands us on the tip of the Eiffel Tower, so we got a rappel down,
but you did a great job anyway sir.
We are now at the base of the Eiffel Tower, we are in the late 1880s to be specific, it
is the turn of the century.
This was before Paris was the city of lights, it used to simply be the city of candles.
It was a very dangerous place to be.
We're walking around in our old timey clothes, everything is velvety and we're not in a
chocolate mousse commercial.
You know what I mean, imagine a steampunk but without all the punk, it's just like old
timey ruffles and stuff like that.
Jackets, we just have jackets and jeans on, okay, it doesn't matter.
We're walking around Paris, France, late 1880s, and we see a young woman running down the
street.
She runs into the British Embassy and she's like, "Mangeaus, mangeaus, you won't believe
what just happened, the event that just was laid forth on this fateful night."
The British consulate is like, "Dude, can you speak English?"
And she's like, "Yeah, yeah, actually I'm a British citizen, I don't know why I did
that.
I just read a Jane Austen novel, it just came out, it just came out yesterday, it's amazing."
This woman, we don't have a name for her, but we do have an interesting provenance to
this story.
This story isn't one of those like, "Oh, it could be made up."
This is a really interesting one, they're all interesting.
Otherwise, we wouldn't tell them.
But we're going to call this woman Bella.
Bella and her mother, Susanna, are on a trip around Paris.
It's actually the time of the exposition, so the whole city is full of people.
Everyone's walking around going, "Whoa, look at that.
Ooh, yeah, that's cool, look at that's a globe, I've heard so much about these things."
And then they just walk home, they're just seeing food and stuff from other different
countries.
I did not research what an exposition was.
I mean, I know what it is, just the generic, but I don't know which one they actually went
to.
They just walked around and they're like, "Whoa!"
And after a long day of walking around, Bella and Susanna retire to a local hotel.
Now, because the exposition's in town and everyone knows what it is, and everyone's
there to see it, all the hotels are booked.
So they actually had to, the hotel they got actually, they couldn't get a double room.
They had to get two single rooms.
Which yes, is weird.
If the hotel is booked, you would assume there'd be no rooms.
But so I don't know why there's two single rooms if it's so busy, but that is the case
in this story.
The mom chooses room 342 and Bella helps carry in her mother's bags and they set it down.
And Bella describes the room that her mother chose.
When they're inside the room, they all look the same.
It's a hotel, but when they're inside the room, it's decorated with rose, strewn wallpaper
and plum-colored velvet curtains.
I knew there was velvet in this story.
And the mom goes, "Oh, me, oh my, I have the vapors!"
And she says, "I need to go to bed."
And the daughter's like, "That's weird.
First off, I don't know what the papers are.
I'm not from deep south."
Secondly, yeah, my mom does tend to fall asleep, like most humans do.
But she just seems to collapse onto the bed.
Bella lets her kind of lay there for a bit, but then she tries to wake her mom up.
And her mom is ill at this point.
She's not in a coma, but she's not doing well.
There's a huge difference between the two.
There's a huge difference between having a slight fever and being in a deep coma.
She was somewhere in between that.
So she goes downstairs and she talks to the hotel staff doctor.
I guess they used to have these.
They would have a doctor that would just hang out at the hotel all day.
He's playing pinball.
He's like, "Oh man, I hope someone gets sick.
I'm so bored."
And that's what happened this night.
He's like, "Yes!"
She goes, "My mom, I think my mom's sick."
Somewhere between a fever and a coma.
And the doctor's like, "I heard that diagnosis."
Many, many times he goes upstairs and he's diagnosing her.
And he goes, "Yeah, she's really bad.
What we need to do, I don't have the gear here to take care of her.
It's at my office."
Not at the hotel, even though my job is to be a hotel doctor, I don't have what I need
to take care of her here.
Let's hop in the horse and carriage.
We're going to just go out to my office.
We'll get the stuff.
We'll come back, take care of your mom."
So Bella's like, "Yeah, okay, that totally works."
I mean, obviously she's not from Paris.
She's from England, but it doesn't take long for her to realize that they seem to be going
in circles around town.
She's like, "Yeah, yeah, I know I'm a tourist, but you can only see the Eiffel Tower so many
times before.
Even that's boring."
And then what's going on?
The doctor's like, "No, no, no, this is just the way...
My house is magical.
You have to go around the block three times counterclockwise and then one time clockwise.
It's like playing the Legend of Zelda.
There's a pattern to find my house."
She said, even when the...
And she said he was going really slow in the horse and buggy.
Like it was a tour ride.
And then when they got to the office, he was like, "Where did I put that?
What am I looking for again, huh?"
He sits down, he's watching television, he invents a television, he's watching.
She's like, "What are you doing?
You're supposed to pick up medicine."
He's like, "Oh yeah, but..."
He's kind of looking around, making a cheese sandwich.
She goes, "It took him forever to get there."
And then once he got there, he didn't seem like he was in a hurry to get the medicine.
But he finally finds the medicine.
We go back to the hotel.
She runs in the hotel and asks the concierge, "How's my mom?"
The concierge looks at her and goes, "You came alone, dear.
You checked in by yourself."
Belle is like, "No, no, no, I came with my mom like we checked in."
And the concierge goes, "What room was your mother in?"
She goes, "Room 342, the one with the roses and the velvet curtains."
And the concierge goes, "No, there is no...
I know I've mispronounced his name.
Get worse each time."
Pierre will call him.
Pierre goes, "Your mother did not check in to room 342.
Nobody under the name Suzanne checked in to room 342.
She's not getting to say that name."
And he's like, "Gulp."
He goes, "It doesn't matter.
There's no one.
Your mom has not checked in to room 342.
You came alone."
And she looks at the ledger and it has a different name under room 342.
So she rushes up the stairs, knocking on the door.
"Hey, mom, let me in.
I got that medicine.
They'll bring you back."
Belle is knocking on the door.
Dude opens it up.
The dude is puzzled as she is.
He goes, "No, no, no, I just checked into this room.
There's no one else here."
And she at this point is losing her mind.
And as anyone would, she pleads to be let into the room.
She knows that if her mom is not in there, there will be some trace that her mom was
in there.
So the stranger opens the door and she walks in.
The wallpaper is different.
The curtains are different.
Her mother's luggage that she brought in herself is gone.
Her mother was never seen again.
Now this is a fascinating story on two levels.
One, that story, that narrative.
Because you look at the idea of people just vanishing into thin air, portals, Mandela
Effect, time slips, alternate reality, all of these things.
But then there's even a more fascinating backbone to this story.
Obviously, the question we have, like stories like Manitoured or the nanny who disappeared
in Spain, are these stories real?
There's a Reddit user named A. Carter, 8.
And they posted on the subreddit, "Unresolved Mysteries."
This post, this is what brought this to my attention, so thank you very much, A. Carter,
8.
It might actually be Aaron Carter, which would be kind of interesting that he's now no longer
in a boy band.
He's investigating ghosts.
He wrote this post called "The Vanishing Hotel Room, A True Urban Legend."
Lay down the narrative like I just did and then takes it another step further.
Is this story true?
It turns out a lot of people have been asking that question over the years.
This story was first published in newspapers back in 1898.
So this isn't something that was popping up on the internet and it's been retconned.
Back then, you could pick up the newspaper and read this story about the missing woman.
This story is actually, some of you guys may have known where this story was going.
This story has been turned into television shows, into novels.
Alfred Hitchcock did a movie about it called "The Lady Vanishes," but it takes place on
a train and it involves spies and a knife-wielding magician, which sounds way cooler than this
story, but I read the plot and it's just kind of lame.
There's some woman walking around in bandages, not the mummy, so not as interesting.
And then the knife-wielding magician, I guess, just disappeared.
He just disappeared from the plot from the write-up on Wikipedia.
But anyways, this story has been told over and over and over again in all sorts of mediums.
It definitely captures the imagination.
It's been around since 1898.
And what A. Carter VIII has done is what other people have done over the past hundred years.
In 1929, there was a journalist for The New Yorker named Alexander Wulcott.
He wrote a column on it for The New Yorker and he tracked down the author of the 1898
article.
His name was Carl Herriman.
It's Bigfoot.
It's Bigfoot's cousin.
Carl Herriman of the Detroit Free Press.
And he asked him, "Is that story real?"
Back when I was doing, when I was a journalist, when I was writing, before digital, we were
doing print papers and we had to print everything out and put it on a thing and send it to the
printing press and all that stuff.
You had column lengths that you couldn't mess with.
Like if you had a 4 inch gap in your paper, you had to have an article or an ad in there.
You just couldn't have a blank spot.
Now with online newspapers, it doesn't matter, everything formats to the page.
What Carl says is, he goes, "This is what I remember.
There was a column that we had to fill.
They had a column that they needed something for."
And Carl remembers, I remember we had blank space and I put the story in there.
And so Alexander goes, "Yeah, I get that because that's what journalists do, but is the story
real or not?"
And this was Carl's quote, "Whether I invented the story or whether someone told it to me
as an anecdote and I expanded on it, I cannot for the life of me tell you after all these
years."
And that was the answer for a long time.
People goes, "Okay, whatever it is, it's at least an embellishment.
He may have made it completely up or it could have been a story he just heard and he added
stuff to it."
But people kept investigating it.
It's definitely been something people have been curious about over the years.
And it was found that the Free Press, another newspaper, published a version of this story
ten months before Carl Horryman's post in the Detroit Free Press.
So even though his story is what made it popular, they were able to actually trace back and
find a variation of it.
On November 14th, 1897, this article was entitled, "Dropped out of existence, a strange and
true mystery of the French capital."
This is really cool and weird addition to this story.
So remember the story I just told you.
Everything pretty much starts the same, but this article that came out ten months before
became a viral hit tells a story, but it involves two daughters and a mom.
They're going there for the expo.
The mom gets sick and the two daughters are trying to figure out a way to treat her.
And when they come back, the mom is gone.
Pretty much the same story.
But there's an additional fact in this news article in 1897.
Just later, the expo is ended, the daughters are still looking for their mother.
And a police officer tells them what really happened.
This is so cool.
The police officer says this, "Your mom came into the hotel and our hotel doctor almost
immediately realized she was suffering from black smallpox.
An incredibly fatal, incredibly contagious disease in the middle of the exposition.
So while you were taken off the premises to go find medicine to help her, she died.
We removed her body.
We destroyed her luggage.
We didn't tell anybody, even you, because it would cause a panic."
That would even make sense as far as why the wallpaper and the curtains were different
when they went back.
Because they would have been destroyed because they were contaminated.
Now in that article in the Free Press in 1897, it doesn't have the detail of that stuff being
destroyed.
That may have been something that Carl had added on later.
But remember, Carl's story just ends with the mystery.
The original article published 10 months earlier explains what happened.
And that article wasn't a way to just fill space.
That article appeared in several major US papers on the exact same day.
So a wire had come overseas and major newspapers were publishing it.
It wasn't just a little "we need to fill some space."
It was an actual news story.
I love this story because on the one hand you have the combination of that mystery.
What happened to the mom on that night?
That's very compact.
When in real life the chain of events probably took a little bit longer.
They probably didn't say "oh your mom doesn't exist."
She never showed up.
They probably just go "oh, she got up and left."
We don't know what happened to your mom.
She must have taken her luggage and left.
She disappeared.
The hotel wasn't like "bluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluhluh
It just has all these different combinations of creepy.
The possible mystery of the Mandela effect.
Alternate universe portal stuff.
And then you have real life tragedy and people making decisions that affect other people
without their knowledge.
So that my ghoulish friends would have worked better.
Is our trilogy of terror.
Are you chilled to the bone?
That's actually a symptom of black smallpox by the way.
You might need to go to your doctor.
These stories are not terrifying in the sense of creatures busting down your door to eat
your guts.
Or the serial killer chasing you with a blade to eat your guts.
It's a cannibal serial killer.
They're terrifying in separate ways because they remove power from us.
There's nothing more powerless than being frozen in your bed, from being mind controlled,
or from being manipulated by people who you trusted would take care of you.
Not having the ability to fight back being powerless is actually the scariest thing
of all.
And it happens all the time, every day, to all of us.
We're in a constant state of mental fear because we live in a world that we are powerless
in.
It eats at us every single day.
You think we'd be used to it by now.
But it's still the scariest thing out there.
It's still the scariest thing out there.