did a giant spider star in a porn video,
and a serial killer that's such a loser,
even the news can't take him seriously
today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
(upbeat music)
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode
of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
It's hot.
The heat wave continues.
Just think about how interesting these podcasts
are gonna be when the cold weather comes.
I can't, well no, I really don't like cold weather.
I'm actually glad it's still hot.
I'm good with that.
You know, I've always wondered,
well not always wondered.
I was thinking about it the other day in the shower,
but you know in movies how there's always that,
not all movies, this is getting off to great start.
In movies there's that scene where the bad guy
has this plan to like rob the bank
or steal the money from the factory workers
or be a corrupt politician.
And like the kids or the good guys trick him
into talking into a hot mic.
Where it's like, oh yes kids,
once I get rid of you four,
once I throw you four into the wake thresher,
I'm going to take over this town
and I'm gonna sell it to the Russians.
And the Russians are gonna bury,
it's my voice being broadcast.
And then like everyone in the audience is like,
(gasps)
like everyone heard his secret plan.
That is a trope that's gone on forever.
That's a trope that's gone on forever
from little rascals to doubt.
There is that scene where the Pope was like,
oh, if only they knew that my real plan
was to let priests molest children.
What?
And then they show that everyone in Vatican Square
was listening.
Anyways, my question is,
has that ever been done before in real life?
I wonder if there's ever been like an evil businessman
behind like he's in his, I don't know, dressing room.
I don't know where businessmen get ready for stuff.
But there's like a board meeting and the businessman's like,
oh, I can't wait to fool these rubs
to give me all of their stock.
And then there's like some precocious eight year old
in there with an iPad recording it.
I don't know, that would be fascinating.
I think we would know about it though.
I actually looked up hot mic accidents
and none of them included any of that.
Not even close.
I think the closest you'd have would be like Mitt Romney
being recorded during the 2012 election saying,
50% of Americans don't pay taxes or something like that,
which was lame.
So no, I hope that something like that has happened.
It would be a great way to in someone's career,
but it's turning out to not be a great way
to start a podcast because that story went nowhere.
Let's go ahead and get started with the episode.
So we got two great stories for you today.
I know you guys are waiting for if the spider
was as ever started a porn movie, A Giant Spider.
But come on, I can't give you the juicy stuff up front.
That's one of our cryptid stories of the week.
We're doing a cryptid, crazy cryptid story
every day this week.
So give me five to seven minutes of your time
to talk about this utter loser of a serial killer.
Now, this guy is, this guy just has nothing good going for him.
His name was John Eric Armstrong.
And now I've said before the reason why
they list serial killers and mass murderers
and stuff like that, mass shooters as three names generally,
is so people who have the name Jarmam Armstrong
don't get brought into that group.
They specify the middle name,
so it differentiates them from every other person
with just that person last name.
This guy though, this guy has a totally different reason
why his middle name is used.
And I'm taking great pride in by calling him John Armstrong.
So Jarmam Armstrong, this happened in Seattle,
so fairly nearby to us.
And this is back in the 90s.
And what happened was the police in,
or near Seattle, started finding dead prostitutes.
And they were all strangled or all had like crushed wind pipes
and the police were like, okay, we have a serial killer.
And so they kind of start hanging around the area.
They're starting to do their investigations
and stuff like that.
And they just threw good police work.
They zero in on this guy, John Eric Armstrong.
And they bring him and he just starts babbling like a baby.
It was a babbling, he just starts crying like a baby.
And he's like, oh, I killed those five women
and I killed 11 more around the world.
And he used to be in the Navy.
And he said that when his naval ship,
the Nimitz would dock at a port of call,
he would get out and murder a prostitute as you do
and then get back on the ship and go somewhere else.
And so that's that.
He was arrested, he was convicted in August of 2001.
The only interesting thing about this conspiracy case
so far was that the fact that he was in the Navy
and he was killing prostitutes around the world.
However, as I was, and I was kind of reading the article
and I was like, I don't know if this will make it
onto the show, but then I came across these nuggets.
These are great.
Whoever wrote this article really didn't like this guy.
Not saying that I'm a huge fan of him either
'cause I'm not, but I'm reading this article.
And okay, so it started, his motivation,
this is what he said his motivation was,
was that his dad used to abuse him, which isn't funny.
That's horrible, okay?
And then the reason why he started hating women
was he had this high scroll girlfriend
he was totally in love with,
but then a hotter guy gave her some gifts
and she dumped him.
And so he viewed that as prostitution.
So he just had this ingrained thing against prostitution.
And then you're like, Jason, it's a lot funny.
This guy was emotionally abused,
physically abused by his dad.
He's killing prostitutes.
Why are you laughing so much?
Okay.
So this is where it gets funny.
It might just be me, but this is where it gets funny.
Okay, so he hates his dad so much.
His dad's name is John Armstrong.
And so he hates his dad so much.
He's like, I'm not going to use my father's name.
I will no longer be known as John Armstrong.
I will be known as Eric Armstrong.
Okay, so fine, fair enough.
I've known people to change their names.
It's not a big deal.
However, this guy was so adamant
and people calling him Eric Armstrong,
when he got arrested, he was wearing a shirt
that just said Eric on it.
Like, I mean, almost like a Sesame Street character.
Like, I can imagine if you knew him
for years and years and years.
And you saw him after your period of time,
after he changed his name, you didn't know about it.
And you're like, hey, John, he just looks at you.
He glars at you and just taps his shirt.
Who wears a shirt with their own name on it?
And better yet, who wears a shirt
with not their name on it?
Okay, so then you're like,
Jason, this guy's mentally disturbed
while you're making fun of him.
Well, trust me, I think it's funny.
Maybe you don't.
Okay, so now, okay.
But then it gets even weirder than we're at right now.
So, Eric, John Eric, the killer, tells police,
and I can almost picture this.
It sounds totally horrifying as he was with the prostitutes.
Well, as John Eric was with the prostitutes,
he'd go, he'd pick up a prostitute
in the United States, across the globe, whatever.
He'd go back to their place, go to the hotel room.
At some point, he would turn around
and they would have his dad's face.
He would look at them and it was his dad's just face,
not body, but just a face on these prostitutes,
and then he would kill them.
So, it's so weird.
So, not only was it a motivation
that he hated prostitutes,
but also prostitutes would morph into his dad.
And my question wasn't like a morph,
like was it like a literal blink
and then all of a sudden his dad's face was there,
like, "Clean your room, kid!"
Or was it just like a slow shifting?
Either one is quite disturbing.
So anyways, you would hang out with,
he was married with kids.
This guy wasn't just like a total,
like he had a job and everything after he left the Navy.
So, he could function in a normal society,
but he would get a prostitute and he'd look at them.
They would have his dad's face and then he'd kill them.
My question is, his wife didn't have his dad's face.
His kids didn't have his dad's face.
His boss didn't have his dad's face.
If you don't want to see your dad's face,
don't go to prostitutes.
If the only time you look and you see someone
(imitates a growling)
morph into your father, all of the matrix,
don't see them, go a far away from them.
The article then, okay, so that's enough
about how just wacky this guy is.
The rest of the article says, basically,
yeah, so he says that he killed five women near Seattle.
And then for eight years as he was on the Nimitz,
every time he landed in a port of call,
he would murder someone.
The article multiple times says that that's not true.
He's totally making that up.
He goes, some of the places they've done investigations
and it's absolutely not true.
There's no evidence to back it up.
Other places are outside of FBI's jurisdiction,
but they haven't gotten any notification.
So in this article, it says,
academics say it is not unusual for serial killers
to exaggerate their body count,
to extend their feelings of superiority and domination.
Then there's a quote, a lot of these guys are very eager
to become the Heisman Trophy winner of serial killing.
So not only does this article basically
make this guy look out to be like a total loser,
but then it's like, he's making it up.
There's no way he killed so many people.
The article is written to laugh at this guy.
'Cause I laughed, I thought it was funny.
Like at the beginning, I mean,
that may say more about me than the article writer.
The article's like, yeah, he killed these five women,
but he's making up the rest.
And he has these bizarre visions.
He wears a shirt with somebody else's name on it.
And it just, it keeps going,
oh, the FBI investigated this, that's not true.
They went to Hawaii where they said that he killed a woman
and they're like, that's impossible.
The ship wasn't there long enough.
And they did find a dead stripper in a bed.
And they're like, yeah, but that wasn't him.
So the article basically, so this guy goes into prison.
And he's like, yeah, dude, I'm gonna go in.
I have this huge body count.
Never have to see my dad's face again.
And everyone basically just makes fun of him,
pulls his pants down, not like to rape him,
but like, I was thinking more of like, you know,
to embarrass him, but I guess in prison it works both ways.
My point being is that this guy
who deserves absolutely no sympathy whatsoever,
his last big moment in the spotlight,
he's called a loser once again.
And now he's again called a loser on my podcast.
So good job, John Armstrong,
here in prison for the rest of your life.
I have nothing to worry about.
Let's go ahead and move on to the next story.
We're gonna move on to a story that has been requested,
story that's on the iceberg conspiracy list,
and a story a lot of you guys have been waiting for.
But most of you guys probably have never heard of it.
And I'm not gonna be able to pronounce the name.
I'm gonna try it once or twice.
Then I'm gonna call it by its English translation.
The cryptid we're covering today
is the Jabba Fofi, Jabba Fofi,
which means giant spider in Congolese or Baku.
So we're back in Africa.
Yesterday we did the Groot Slang.
Today we're doing the Jabba Fofi.
And Jabba Fofi, like I said, means giant spider.
And what it is, is it is a giant spider.
Depending on the description,
it is either between three feet in diameter
to six feet in diameter.
And that's important.
We're gonna get into that in a bit.
That differentiation.
So we're gonna talk briefly about the spider
and then we're gonna get on to the porn video.
So this basically is a spider that is a legend
in these areas, in these parts of Africa,
where it lives in a hole and it covers itself with leaves.
But before it is that, it's actually really important.
It puts up webbing between two trees.
And when something disturbs the webbing,
it senses it, 'cause it's still tied to the web.
And then it comes out and sucks the blood out
and eats you and all that stuff, as a spider would do.
And people in the area are like,
no, this is 100% correct.
This isn't like some dinosaur.
This isn't the Groot Slaying.
This is an actual, this is a non-mythical creature.
This is a creature we have to deal with.
If it builds a nest too close to the town,
we have to destroy the nest.
And they're describing what the babies look like
and what the eggs are like the size of peanuts.
And in Africa, they're saying these things
are about three feet big.
And what happened was there was an author named,
I'm just, I know his last name off the top of my head,
Gibson, and he went and he wrote a book
about monsters in Africa.
And he was investigating stuff like Mola Mempiki,
which is like a bronosaurus.
He's investigating all like he's Loch Ness level monsters.
And he finds out about the spider.
And he said, the way that they describe the spider
was so matter of factual that he thinks,
Gibson thinks it existed or exists.
They say it's in danger now
because its environment is being encroached on.
But there's a difference when someone talks about
something like the Loch Ness monster
and something talks about a Jabu Fofi according to him.
They're just very matter of factual about,
this is the way it mates, this is the way it feeds,
this is the way it has it tied out,
this is where it lives,
this is the environment that it feeds on and all that stuff.
So he thought that led a lot of credence to the myth.
He hadn't seen one, to be fair, he hadn't seen one.
Could this creature exist?
Now, oh, and let me say this,
other people, other Westerners had said
they had seen the spider and it was six feet big.
And so those stories got out first
'cause people would go there
and they would see a six foot long spider
and they'd go back to Rhodesia
or they'd travel back to England
and they'd be like, it's all spider is six feet tall
and scientists would go, well that's impossible.
You can't have a six foot in diameter spider.
Its respiratory system wouldn't work
and its exoskeleton wouldn't work.
The biggest creature with an exoskeleton can get on land,
according to science, is three feet.
So when the natives in the area said
it was around three to four feet,
they would describe it as a puppy-sized spider
or the size of a terrier.
So when we think giant spider,
the first thing we think of is like she-both,
shulbeth, that one in Lord of the Rings.
These ones are actually the size of a small dog
which is in the realm of possibility.
There is a creature, the largest creature
with an exoskeleton on land that we have photos of
and you can actually eat.
They're called the coconut crab.
They sound incredibly tasty,
but I don't know if they taste like coconut.
I think they just eat coconuts.
They're three feet in diameter.
So you could have a creature that had a three feet
in diameter, a exoskeleton creature.
The question comes is can you have a spider of that size
because the way the respiratory system works?
In science it's like, no,
the biggest you could have is a foot.
But I'm going to say that based on the fact,
this is my professional opinion,
the respiratory system,
there may be a little bit of a work around there.
I have nothing to back that up.
But the fact that the early stories were saying
it was six feet and science were like that's impossible,
but when you go to the locals, they say three to four feet
and we have exoskeleton creatures
with three feet in diameter.
I personally believe that this spider exists.
I don't know if it exists right now.
It could be extinct.
It could have been super plentiful back in the day
like ancient times,
but I don't know enough about spider respiratory systems.
I know right now the biggest spider that we know exists
is one foot in diameter.
And I don't think it's like,
(breathing heavily)
you know, like that kid from Malcolm the Middle,
like man, that guy was, I love that show,
but that character was so annoying to watch.
It was funny.
It just, yeah.
Anyways, yes, they can't get six feet big.
Could they get three feet big?
Likely possible, possible.
So does this creature exist?
I think it could.
I think in the right conditions in the right areas
with the right food source and things like that,
you could have a spider that's three feet big,
three feet in diameter.
It's not like three feet tall.
Well, three foot in diameter.
It doesn't matter.
It's terrifying any other way.
So now let's talk about the porn video.
Now, apparently this is how I came to know
about the Jabu Fofi.
I think this is how most people know about it.
There was a porn actress named,
I'm gonna butcher this as well, Sabenshi Tomatovic.
She's Australian Serbian pornographic actress,
Sabenshi Tomatovic.
You know what, hold on one second.
I wanna see what she looks like,
'cause I don't know why I never googled her before.
Okay, well here's an interesting thing.
I just tried Googling her and I see no photos of her.
So I'm kind of thinking now that name is made up
or the whole story's fake, but not the spider story.
I believe in that.
But anyway, so this was some copypasta
that was going around for a while.
Australian Serbian pornographic actress,
Sabenshi Tomatovic reported to close friends and relatives
being sexually assaulted by a giant spider
measuring four foot in size.
She stated that the encounter propelled her rise to fame
in Japan's underground Genki Genki circle.
Genki means excited or pep in Japanese.
I think it's actually, yeah.
So that was copypasta that was going around.
People started looking in to see if it was real or not.
Now, based on what, there's two,
there's three things that are possible here.
One, it's completely made up
and no woman ever paying a spider on film.
Two, it's real.
And this actress who somehow, she's a porn actress,
but somehow has no photos on the internet, which is weird.
I'll keep, okay.
But she has no photos on the web.
This actress, they got a job of fofie,
some Japanese mafia gangbanger.
I guess that's kind of redundant, not the Japanese part,
but some Japanese gangster got one of these spiders
shipped over from Africa, 'cause why not?
You have tons and tons of money
and you put it on video of this woman
having sex with a spider.
I don't know how spiders have sex.
Maybe it weaved itself a dildo and penetrated her.
Maybe it just went down on her.
I don't know.
You think it would suck her blood out,
but besides the point.
And they have that on video somewhere
and it's this crazy video.
So that assumes that both she is real
and the job of fofie is real.
I have the third option here.
So we have it's fake.
We have the spider's real and she's real.
I have a third option that she's real
and she didn't have sex with a job of fofie
because they don't exist.
This is just my theory.
But she had sex with a coconut crab,
which, I mean, think about it.
You go to Japan, they tell you
they're gonna pay $10,000 to be in this video.
And all of a sudden they bring out a giant creature.
You're not gonna count its legs.
That's not gonna be the first thing you think of.
This three foot long giant crab walks into the room.
You're not gonna be like,
"Oh, actually that is from the genus Crabotoculus.
That is obviously not an arachnid."
You're gonna be like,
"Oh my God, I'm about to have sex with this monster."
So I think the most likely thing is
that that part of the story is fake.
There is no tape of Sabinech Tomatovic
because being sexually assaulted by a giant spider,
you think that the first thing you do
would wever up and eat her blood.
But maybe if it is true,
maybe she had sex with this coconut crab.
So if we assume that this story is true,
which I mean, why not?
It's on the internet, right?
And if the Jabba Fofi doesn't exist
because at the end of the day,
we don't have any proof of that,
but we do know coconut crabs existed.
Maybe she banged a coconut crab.
And that would actually make more sense
because it wouldn't immediately kill her.
You would just rub its shell on her for a while until it came.
I don't know how crustaceans have sex either.
I don't know if they have genitalia.
I'm sure they have something.
They pinch in each other's butts.
But if there's a video out there,
and this actually happened,
the most likely scenario is she banged the crab,
a coconut crab.
So if that's gonna cause you nightmares
or make you swear off seafood forever,
I apologize, it should have put a trigger warning in there.
I don't know, I don't eat seafood anyways.
So if you ever do see the Sabina Tomatovich tape,
count the legs and get back to me.
So this is a little addendum to the Java fofie
and the porn tape.
I don't remember exactly how to pronounce her name.
I don't have my notes in front of me right now,
but the Tomatovich tape.
So I was going back and I was kind of editing
and listening back to what I recorded.
And then I did some more research.
Now she does not exist anywhere.
And I get that sometimes when you have these stories
and you have like a person's name, there are nobody.
So you're not really gonna find them,
but she's a porn star.
And it's really hard to not be able to find anything
on a porn star.
Their information is constantly getting leaked.
I mean, once you do a video, it's everywhere.
You type in someone's name,
you can pull up 100 photos of it.
Sometimes you can show a photo of a girl's calf
and other people are like,
oh yeah, that's Amy Ash or whoever.
I don't know.
But so she doesn't exist at all.
So it means again, let me say this.
I think the story is a hoax
'cause I wasn't able to find anything about the story
of Tom Tomovich and the giant spider sex tape
other than the same creepypasta
over and over and over and over again.
There's never any additional details to it.
There was never like,
sometimes when you find these type of stories,
one source, you'll read the same thing over and over again,
but then one source will say that,
it was taken during this time period,
like it happened in the 90s
or it was in this district of Japan
or some additional detail that we can go forward is not.
Somebody made the story up
and they used a creature that may or may not exist.
Again, I think it has a likelihood of existing.
But so I hate to disappoint anyone out there
who went looking for this tape.
As far as I can tell, the tape does not exist.
It never exists.
It was just creepypasta.
And people say, well, I saw footage of it
or I saw a screenshot and maybe the reason
why you can't find anything on her
was because she was scrubbed from the internet,
but we know nothing gets scrubbed from the internet like that.
But the government could do it.
No, no, no, you have to be realistic about this stuff.
On a certain level.
I mean, we can have fun talking about a sex tape
with a spider and a woman,
but if you want to put it forward
that this exists in some way,
there's, you need something to back it up
other than my cousin knew a guy on 4chan
who saw a screenshot.
So unless further information comes forward,
the idea of this being a tape is completely ridiculous.
And it's a hoax.
Now, there probably are videos of people,
women having sex with all sorts of weird creature snakes.
Actually, I know for a fact,
there's, you know, bestiality videos out there,
but I'm talking about like exotic creatures,
like a six foot python and so on and so forth.
And I'm sure those exist.
And there's possibility that a woman has a porn video
of having sex with at least a coconut crab,
which we talked about during the episode.
But as far as the exact story
or something even coming close
to the story of the Tom and Tomage tape,
there's nothing to back it up.
She doesn't exist.
There's no additional information.
It's the same 40 some odd words posted over and over again.
And that is the biggest sign
that it's just creepypasta and it doesn't exist.
So that was your fetish.
I'm sorry to inform you
that it is likely not true.
I'm gonna put that in very, very, very, very,
very unlikely that it's true.
But I still hold out hope
that the Jabba Fofi is a real creature.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
or Twitter @JasonOCarpenter.
I think the idea of a giant spider.
Oh, and I have to say this quick too.
One of the first things that turned me on,
not in a porn way,
that turned me on to the idea of giant spiders.
I'm gonna include this link below.
Was there is a story in France back at the turn of the century
where near the entrance to the catacombs of Paris,
people were disappearing
and the cops increased their patrols in the area.
And one day a cop was walking on the street
and he heard someone singing
and he saw like a guy walking,
like he was hypnotized into this tomb of Isidor,
I think it's called.
The cop followed him in there and there was a giant spider.
And again, it's listed as a giant spider,
but when you read the definition,
it was the size of a small dog.
It was the size of a terrier.
So it would three feet is believable.
And so the cop tried shooting any could it
and the other cops heard the commotion
and they all shot it.
And apparently they killed the spider,
but the guy was dead
and they put the spider in a museum, the end.
I always thought it was a fascinating story.
I read that in 40 in times.
It was horrific enough and believable enough
to my 15 year old mind that it was true,
but here I am at 41 still believing
or still talking about the possibility
that giant spiders exist.
So some things never change.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy truth-run podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
(upbeat music)