What would you do if one day you woke up and you found yourself in another person's body,
Zoinks?
And then we travel to outer space to take a look at a bizarre new conspiracy theory.
Astronauts have often complained about how stinky space is.
Is it possible their smelling are violent past today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvider.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
This is the last week before my break.
AKA, this is, I'm so sore.
Everything hurts.
I'm sitting here in a recording booth, my body aches.
I went for this big walk today.
I walked down to Walmart and got myself some Dipepsi and Batman Hot Wheel.
That's literally all I bought.
I walked two miles and got that stuff.
I'm just sore and tired.
But here I am, once again, in your eardrum, Lil Jason's hanging out inside of your Cove
a Clave or whatever it's called up there, your cockle.
I don't know.
I'm dancing around in there bringing you some more paranormal news.
And I'm not alone.
I'm not the only voice in your head.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now.
Let's give it up for one of our Christmas livestream contributors, Thuja Magus.
Thuja Magus, everyone give a big round of applause as he magically appears in your other ear.
Thuja, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
Or the show financially, I get it.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Tell your friends, tell your family.
That really helps out a lot.
Yes, I said on yesterday's episode I had already done all of my Thanksgiving livestream
contributors.
That's not true.
I actually made a mistake.
I have a couple more of you guys.
So if I haven't called your name yet, do not fret.
You'll be coming in up coming episodes.
But Thuja is our pilot today.
And Thuja, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We will drive all the way out to a small town in suburban America.
I found this story on the X-Board the other day.
It's absolutely fascinating.
And we're going to take a look at it and say, that's, seriously bro?
This is clearly made up.
I know you need to take a break and all, but don't get this.
When I read this story, it did seem your initial inclination is this is impossible.
But so funny is we cover the impossible every single day on this show twice.
We do two impossible stories each day.
And I think the limits of what, why is this story impossible?
Keep that in mind.
Keep that in mind, because I tell you this incredibly impossible story.
So the other day of hair and this happened very, very recently.
There is this dude.
We're going to call him Bin.
So Bin is hanging out at his house and his best friend and his girlfriend show up.
They'll call the best friend, Marcus.
We'll call him Marcus and we're going to call her Tracy.
Tracy is the girlfriend and Marcus and Tracy are standing there and they said Bin.
You're not going to believe this.
We barely believe this.
If you've ever seen a Disney Channel movie, you'll probably believe it maybe.
Or you'll find it even more unlikely because it's a Disney Channel movie.
We've switched bodies.
So you see me here.
I am Marcus talking.
I'm actually your loving girlfriend, Tracy, stuck in this body.
And that over there, that should be my body and it's waving.
It's doing a little waving thing.
Hi, I'm Marcus.
I'm Marcus.
I'm trapped in Tracy's body.
We switched.
At some point last night, we switched bodies.
Now Bin doesn't believe this, right?
How could you believe this?
If your best friend and your girlfriend showed up and tried to convince you that they had
switched consciousnesses.
Conscious knee?
What's the plural of conscious nigh?
Anyways, that happened.
Right?
So they switched souls and they're in their new body.
And the only, I mean, obviously you'd think they were making it up, right?
Because the only time you ever see anything like this is in the movies.
With aliens and ghosts and demons, we have tons of literature and religious scripts and
all sorts of stuff and science, maybe with the alien thing.
There's not a lot of religious scripts about aliens, but you know what I mean?
We have all this other stuff plus movies.
But with people switching bodies outside of Freaky Friday and then that Zac Efron movie
where he switched bodies with Matthew Perry and they were hanging out.
Or did they switch bodies or did he go back in time?
I don't remember.
It was a good movie.
I don't remember the name of it or the plot, but other than that, it was a good movie.
Very rarely outside of a Disney Channel original movie do people switch bodies.
I've never read this type of account in the literature before.
So you'd think it was fake and you would do what Ben did.
He thought it was fake.
And then he goes, well, I have to quiz you, right?
Because I saw it in Freaky Friday.
We have no other testing for this.
So he started asking Tracy questions that only Marcus would know.
He brings Tracy aside and he's asking Tracy questions that only Marcus would know.
And Tracy is answering questions only Marcus would know.
So he's like, well, maybe Marcus is in this, but no, no, this is too weird.
So then he pulls Marcus aside and starts asking him questions only Tracy would know.
And so on and so forth.
And he, oh, he goes, this went on for hours, right?
I'm starting to run out of questions to ask him.
This went on for hours.
And finally, I'm not entirely convinced, but this would have to be one of the most elaborate
pranks ever set up.
Like they know stuff that only their original soul person would know.
I don't know what to make of this.
And that's not even the weirdest part.
Ben goes on to explain to the export.
When they first showed up, they were panicking about this.
They were really, really freaked out.
As I think most people would if you woke up in someone else's body.
But he goes, it's been about four or five days since this has happened.
And over that amount of time, Tracy, who has Marcus's consciousness in her body, is starting
to at first was acting like Marcus in Tracy's body because it is Marcus's soul in that body.
But over the past four days, Tracy, instead of acting like Marcus in her body has started
to act like Tracy.
And the same thing is happening with Marcus at first.
This was acting like my girlfriend.
But over the past four days, now Marcus is starting to act like Marcus again.
What is what's going on?
Is there any way to reverse this?
I mean, obviously the answer to this would be who was a prank and they're getting tired
of the prank and they're slowly reverting out of the prank and they'll explain it somehow.
But he goes, I kind of want them back.
I kind of want them back to normal.
I don't know how to fix this.
And I guess in a way they're kind of turning back to normal, but I don't understand that
because it's still Marcus in Tracy's body.
She's just starting to act like Tracy used to before the body swap.
What's really interesting is someone then responded on the expert.
Actually everyone first off was talking about sex.
Now you get to have sex with your best friend in the body of your girlfriend.
Could you ask for anything better?
And that's when he goes, well, it's actually turning back into my girlfriend like personality
wise is starting to act like Tracy did before the switch.
Someone jumped on the export.
I thought this was really interesting.
Someone jumped on the export and said, listen, what's going on is their souls did switch,
but muscle memory is so powerful that when you take a consciousness and put it into a
body that is not its own, if you took Tracy's soul and put it in Marcus's body, at first
it will act 100% like Tracy simply inhabiting a new body.
But over time, the muscle memory of that body, everything that body has done for the past
19, 20 years, however old these kids are, has been Marcus related.
All the little white blood cells in there had little pinnets that said Marcus and they
were all like, yay, it's his birthday, which means it's our birthday.
They were very Marcus centric.
So when a new soul moves in, it's basically that's the alien part of the body.
And it shows up in this guy saying the soul is so malleable.
It's such a malleable force that when you put it into a new body, it will in a very
short time begin to conform to the rights and the logic and the muscle memory of the
old body to the point that while the personality of Tracy will never completely disappear.
It will, for the most part, revert to being the Marcus.
And every show often this new Marcus may have a glimmer, may have a vision or a memory of
being a woman at some point, but it'll seem like a dream.
It'll seem like not part of the reality.
It will be more Marcus than Tracy.
Like if you don't reverse this, you will lose pure Tracy and you will lose pure Marcus
and what you'll get is something that is 98%, 95% Marcus with a 5% of Tracy remaining.
That soul remaining.
And the same thing going on.
He didn't actually give the percentages, but fascinating.
And we don't know how this ends, right?
This was just a post on the export.
We haven't seen anything to come else out of it.
But I think it's so interesting because it does answer one of the questions that I've
had a lot about the soul.
Not "Can I switch bodies?"
We'll get to that in a second.
But I've always thought if you take a baby, if you take a human baby and I believe that
humans have souls, what happens when the body itself has something different about it?
Whether that be something like a mental deficiency or a physical deficiency or something like
that.
How does the soul go into a body that can't process things in a logical way?
How does that work?
I've always figured the soul is such a powerful, undying force and then you take it and you
put it into a tiny body whose brain is just not working on the level of a human brain
should.
The brain's only capable of having like say an IQ of 65 or whatever like that.
The soul itself is in there.
How come the soul, this eternal being, this eternal life force, how is it trapped in this
body that can't process language, like even basic language?
But this would explain that.
It's because the soul conforms to the physical form.
The soul goes into a body that is not working at a basic human level.
The soul is still perfectly normal, but it won't like you can't, why can't you take
this soul that's been around since the dawn of existence and put it into a frail little
body and then it have the knowledge and the wisdom of a human soul.
Like that's something I've always been curious about because I've always thought like when
these people die, like when somebody dies, if you had all of these disabilities through
your life, your soul is not also disabled.
It's like back to its normal soul form.
So why if you took something that was that powerful and raw and put it into something
so frail and I don't want to use the term broken, but you know, just like not operating
on a normal level, whatever that is, you know, there's all sorts of levels of physical and
mental disabilities and stuff like that, whether it's like hardcore schizophrenia or you just
have math disability.
I wish my soul can do advanced trig, but I can't.
My brain just doesn't process math as easily as it does everything else.
So this would this answers that that there doesn't matter what the power level of the
soul is.
It's it part part of it is it gets stuck.
It conforms to the physical limitations of the body.
So that's an interesting answer to that question that anyone else was asking.
I've always been curious about that.
Souls are powerful enough to survive after death and haunt locations for hundreds of
years.
But if you if a soul that is that powerful is in a body that can't ever really speak,
you know, it just mute.
How does the body not how does the soul not override the body's limitations?
So that would answer that it just it doesn't.
It's almost like takes the path of least resistance in the physical form.
So I thought that was an interesting whole side of this.
And then you also have the thing is, is this possible?
I've never come across anything like this before.
Like how common is this?
And I'm wondering if that suggestion is true, like within four days, you may actually just
revert back to the your soul is still in that other body.
But you don't remember after four or five days, you spin panicking and trying to figure
out a way to stop it.
But then eventually you just become Tracy, living Tracy's life.
And if you didn't interact with her in that time period, you might never know something
happened.
I wonder how common this is.
I wonder if this is more common than we think and people switch bodies and then they get
used to it.
And then every so often they'll have a dream about that's weird.
I remember waking up one day and I was like, get ready for this track meet.
But it was like, I was like, dude, and I never really did track.
I don't know.
It's weird.
And they're actually, they had swapped bodies at some point and they'd gone on with their
life.
Maybe this is super common.
And this is one of the few times this has been caught.
This has been recorded like this dude who's into the paranormal was there right when it
happened because imagine if the friends didn't have a third party that they trusted and they
were trying to talk it out amongst each other.
And then over time they just got used to it and then they forgot that they had even swapped.
And who knows, they may even swap back at some point.
And then they also go back through that thing where they just kind of forget and their souls
kind of go back for this might be incredibly common.
If it is a phenomenon like alien abductions, one of the key things about alien abductions
is you forget about it.
Like almost every alien story, unless they're they're just like talking to the aliens, the
aliens come down and some farmer sees them in a field.
The aliens wipe people's memories.
Alien abductions may be far more common than we know of, but 98% of them get their memory
wiped.
For all of them get their memory wiped, 98% of them never ever have an inkling that anything
happened.
I wake up all the time with little scratches on my body and dots behind my ear.
I used to for the longest time wake up with blood coming out from behind my ear.
Not from my ear.
I know that's the thing.
But yeah.
I mean I'm just like whatever.
I figured I'd cut myself shaving.
I can never answer the question was I shaving in the middle of the night, but you know it
may be super common and this may be super common.
We may have all at some point in our lives switched bodies with someone else and panicked
about it for a couple days and felt out of place and felt like depersonalization or whatever
and then we got used to it and kept going on with our lives.
Fascinating story even though it sounds absolutely impossible because it's something we only
see in the movies.
Who knows?
I would love to come across other stories like this honestly.
But yeah and I really love the export.
I know a lot of people hate it.
Sometimes I hate it because they just have the same stuff that suck you just threads over
and over again.
But we've been getting some really good stuff out of there recently.
Really really dig the export.
Overall I think it is a pretty good spot to hang out.
Thuja Magus, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonicopter.
We're leaving behind this befuddled young couple in suburbia.
We can't help them right?
We hope they figure it out somehow or they just get used to it.
We're leaving them behind.
We're headed all the way out to outer space.
[imitates carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos'
carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos' carlos'
I know in the intro I made a comment about the smell of outer space.
And even when carlos was talking about this, you saw the same comment pop up a lot.
Now in the world, can you smell outer space?
You got space suit on, right?
If you don't have a space suit on, your lungs are outside of your body and your blood's crystallized
and your eyes have exploded and all sorts of other things I saw happen in a documentary
called Event Horizon.
How can you smell space?
It's actually some people consider it an urban legend.
And I pulled up this YouTube video called Astronaut Chris Hadfield debunks space myths.
He's talking about one of them is what happens in human body when you're in space.
And he's talking about all this stuff and he goes, "So, one of the urban legends about
space, put it in urban legend, one of the solar legends about space, is that you can
smell outer space."
And he goes, "That's true.
You can smell outer space."
So what happens?
We go, we put on our space suits and we go for these space walks.
Johnson, Johnson, get back in here.
He's like, "No, I'm going back home.
I'm running away.
You guys don't like me."
Little dude is space walking out, but he has that little tether and they're just holding
it.
They're holding it.
He can't get too far.
They wheel him back in.
You just throw in another tantrum.
What happens is when you go on your space walk and then, so you have the airlock.
When you put on your space suit, you go out into the, you go out into space and then you
come back into the airlock.
The door shuts and then you take your space suit off.
You don't have to wear it for the rest of this time up in space.
It's full of poop and pee by the time you get home.
You take your space suit off and what you can smell immediately is the smell of space
on your suit.
So when you are in outer space, it does collect a smell.
You can't smell it in space because you would die.
But when you come back in from a space walk, so you know what your space suit smells like
before you go out.
You wash it.
You wash it with Dove detergent.
It's the best detergent for astronauts.
And then you know what it smells when you come back from outer space.
It smells like burnt steak or welding material.
It smells like gunpowder or brimstone.
It's not a pleasant smell, but it definitely has a smell.
Being in outer space, when you come back in and you take your space suit off and you smell
it, burnt materials, welded metal together that instant like shh, that oxidized metal,
a seared steak, a lot of times it's a smell of burned meat, brimstone, all of this stuff,
right?
They don't know why it smells like this.
It's very interesting.
This YouTube video, he says this is his theory.
This is what astronaut Chris Hadfield said.
He says that he believes that when you go out into space, the vacuum of space is actually
pulling micro materials, trace metals out of the space station or the space shuttle or
whatever.
And it's pulling that stuff off of your ship and it's attaching to your suit.
It's just this slow off gassing of all of this man made material up in space.
And when you come back in, that's what you're smelling.
That's why it smells very metallic or very, very oxidized brimstone-y smell.
I don't know what it makes space shuttles out of.
I don't know if it's real cheap labor in hell or something like that.
That's why they smell like that.
But he goes, that's what I think the smell is.
I think it's all the off gassing that comes off the vehicle.
He goes, if for some reason you found yourself in space and you weren't near a vehicle, I
don't think you would smell like anything.
I think you're not smelling space.
You're smelling the effect of space on the ship that you're near.
And they actually do have a space candle.
There's a candle you can get that you can get if you've always wanted to smell seared
steak and brimstone at the same time in the comfort of your own home, not in the void
of space.
You can buy a candle for that.
So that's his theory.
You're not really smelling the air.
You're smelling repressurized space when you're coming in and it's all the off gassing.
That's the way it is from the vehicle itself.
Very very interesting, right?
The smell is real is Chris Hadfield's theory real.
Well tattoos, a guy who goes by the name tattoos by Carlos has his own theory and it's a chilling
one.
It's very, very good, creepy theory.
But I wanted to make sure I explained the science before at first because I know a lot
of people were wondering space doesn't smell, space doesn't smell and it does.
People who have been up there have said it does have a smell that attaches to your suit.
That's how they smell it.
I wanted to get that out of the way.
This is what Carlos is saying.
When everything is repressurized and the astronauts come back in and there are space suits and
they take their helmets off, they smell a combination of molten metal, organic material, this seared
steak smell, cling into their suits.
He goes, "What if you had a planet teaming with organic life, an advanced planet, a technologically
superior planet to what we have here on Earth.
Maybe this planet was in our own solar system at one point and it exploded.
A massive explosion tore a planet apart, creating the asteroid belt that we now see in our
own solar system.
What we're smelling is the organic material of the inhabitants of that world pulverized
into un-viewable, unnoticeable atoms just floating around through space.
All of their technology, all of the mighty wonders that they had crafted on their planet,
reduced to nothing.
What if that is the cause of the smell?
When you go out for a space walk, you're actually smelling a dead civilization.
Those little materials attached to the suit.
In great enough numbers that when you step back into the space shuttle and you take that
suit off, you get a whiff of seared steak.
But there was really billions of humanoids living on a planet that was vaporized.
You get that oxidized metal smell.
These buildings, these vehicles, this technology that had been overheated to a point that it
had disintegrated, but enough of those can still gather together on your space suit.
It just smells weird.
What would it smell like if a planet on that technological scale just exploded?
Millions of years ago, where would all of that matter go?
Where would all of those things go?
They wouldn't just evaporate, even though I used that word and disintegrate multiple
times.
They're somewhere out there.
I think you could even go so far that maybe it wouldn't even be a planet, but if some
giant vehicle at some point exploded in our orbit and these trace minerals and these trace
smells are still floating around, because they're not going to go away.
They're actually preserved by space.
They're going to stay in orbit.
You would smell them when you're out on your space walk.
What we're smelling is not off-gassing of a ship.
It's actually the ghost of a long, lost, and now dead civilization.
I think it's a really interesting theory.
Does it hold water?
You know what's interesting?
I've talked a lot about this.
I'm 45 years old.
When I went to school back in the 80s and the 90s, but I'm talking now in elementary school,
my education was ridiculously out of sorts.
I changed schools every two years.
I moved around all the time as a kid.
I tried looking this up online in the computer, but I don't know what you're looking at, dude.
Google's like, "Uh, you're an idiot."
I was taught when I was a kid that there was a theory.
In the theories change, right?
There was a theory that between Mars and Jupiter, there's this huge asteroid belt.
That's not a theory that exists.
But between Mars and Jupiter, there's an asteroid belt, and I was taught that it's possible
there was a planet there at some point that got ripped to pieces by Jupiter or some other
force, most likely Jupiter, right?
And then it disappeared.
Well, it's still there.
It's just a bunch of asteroids.
I had heard that.
And then when I tried looking it up today, everything said, "Well, Jupiter might have
flung."
There's evidence that there used to be another planet that Jupiter kind of bullied out of
the solar system.
Get out of here.
No one lives here.
It's like, "Aww."
It's flown away.
They think that a planet may have been here in its infancy, and it got turned into an exoplanet
and just floated away through the solar system.
But I was taught that now Google, my type of Google is not being my friend.
It doesn't seem like that is a theory nowadays.
But I was also taught that whales lived to be 500 years old and Venus had jungles on
it.
So I know that my education as a kid was not the greatest.
But even that aside, let's say it wasn't a planetary explosion, just a large enough
vehicle in our orbit, if that had some sort of calamity, would it still leave these odors
around to be detected?
Very, very interesting story.
I love coming across these theories like this, right?
It's something I never would have considered.
And I personally didn't know that space had a smell.
But could it be because of this?
And then, you know, we'll wrap it up like this.
I had a little personal theory of my own.
The idea when Chris Hatfield said, "It smells like brimstone."
Brimstone is usually a smell that the paranormal and the religious associate with the devil
and with hell.
I don't know how much of that is listed in religious texts, the actual smell of brimstone.
I don't know how much of that is added on by Renaissance authors later on, honestly.
But there is a thing, like when you look at the original definition of hell, it's separation
from God.
It's not necessarily this place of fiery torment and the original versions of most religions.
It's not actually on fire.
It's something that is kind of added in later books and definitely added in by Renaissance
authors and stuff like that.
It's complete separation from God.
It's being alone.
Like you die and you're in an infinite void alone and you don't get to see anyone and
you don't get to be near the Creator.
Because who cares if you're burning for eternity?
Like pain, eventually you'll get used to it.
You're like, "Oh, I'm waking up."
You're like, "They didn't make it a little bit out of the flames."
But the loneliness never goes away.
So the idea was that when you die and you go to hell, you're going to be separated from
God forever.
I can't think of anything that sums that up any more than you dying.
You having some sort of trip or fall or someone shoot you or, I mean, you're not to keep listing
ways that you die.
You're like, "Great, Jason, really uplifting episode.
I'm already afraid that I might have switched bodies three or four times throughout my life
and now this."
You die and you don't end up with some devil and red tights poking you with a pitchfork.
You're like, "Ah, you're floating through space."
You die and the next thing you know, you're in the void of space.
It's cold and it's vast and it's lonely.
I'm not saying your actual body.
I'm not saying if you got hit by a car, you go, "Woo!"
Your body floats up there, but your soul is there in space.
You go, "Jason, that's kind of cool, man.
I've seen Star Trek and stuff.
I can see Nebulae floating there and I can see like Supernovas."
Those things are so rare.
The universe is so huge that I could pick you up and throw you into space and the chances
of you ever being able to see another planet with your naked eye as you leave Earth would
be slim to none.
All those photos of Nebulae, first off, Star Trek, science fiction is not real.
Secondly, all those photos of the Crab Nebulae lens, that's so photoshopped.
A lot of that is all of these data points that they interpret into some sort of image
and then they do all sorts of color corrections.
If you were in the Starship Enterprise, you wouldn't be like, "Whoa, look, we're flying
by the Crab Nebulae."
You would obviously know that it wasn't there.
They're not idiots, but it wouldn't look like it does.
And again, if you just went in a random direction, the chances of you ever seeing anything like
that, you would most likely fly through the void forever and never come across another
planet or a star.
You would just be in the blackness of space floating forever.
And that does sound like the original version of hell.
Really, just being alone outside of God's presence without seeing any of his works floating,
that is actually saying that you float, right?
It doesn't say like aliens will laugh at you.
It doesn't say that in the book of Job.
But you know what I mean?
Like just floating through the emptiness of space, not seeing anything else.
Your consciousness just leaving the planet that you loved so much and you were taken
so quickly from.
And there you go.
That is hell in space and that would match up with the whole brimstone idea as well.
Just a theory, just something I came up with when they mentioned the word brimstone.
Just something that popped in my head.
Fascinating theory.
You know, my mind's creepy.
Carlos, that one is very evocative that there was a previous civilization somewhere around
here.
I'm not adverse to that, honestly.
I think there's a chance that Earth wasn't humans' actual home.
We did an episode on that not too long ago.
Like the fact that humans have back pain and we don't react well to the gravity here and
the way we age does make it look like we didn't evolve here.
I find that a very interesting theory.
Or just the idea that even astronauts up in space, they can go on these spacewalks and
even they are confronted by mysteries every single day.
These people who are literally on the final frontier.
Even they go out on these spacewalks and they come back in and they take their high-tech
space suit off and they're standing in this billion-dollar space station and they go,
"Hmm.
Wonder what's causing that smell?"
Even they, with all the technology at their disposal, they're doing these spacewalks,
they're in a billion-dollar space station.
Even they take out their space suit and they get a whiff of that smell and they're confronted
with these mysteries.
These people who are putting their lives on the line to expand human knowledge.
Even they don't know everything.
Even they can go, "Hmm.
I wonder what causes that smell?"
No one knows the answer.
It's one of those true mysteries that doesn't really affect our lives in any meaningful
way, but makes us wonder, "What is the truth?
Will we ever know it?
Even if we discover it, will we admit that it's true?"
[Music]
(upbeat music)