Is Kim Kardashian a witch who's casting spells on Kanye West? And then we look
at the popular yet controversial conspiracy. Are the Illuminati really the
good guys today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode actually it's episode 100 and
it is the start of season 3 of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I am having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. My
vacation was really busy. I really got a bunch of research done and I found a way
to streamline research so that was nice. You know just having a week to kind of
look at the flaws of the research process. Not saying that I did any
additional research than I normally do but I mean I did research more stories
but I think if you listen this far in the podcast it's not. You know people
complain they go man this isn't this isn't a news podcast. You're not a
journalist. Yeah that's kind of the point. I was talking to my little brother I
said my podcast is basically the equivalent of your best buddy. Read
something weird in the news and then plops down on your couch and proceeds to
tell you about it while drinking a beer. It's that's kind of the vibe of the
show. I didn't want to sit down and read Wikipedia articles and do deep dives
into the research. I do that but I think the way that it's presented is
there's a reason why it's presented the way it's presented. I do want to say
too now this isn't going to affect a lot of the listeners but it's going to
affect the listeners who use the Podbean app. We're actually changing our
podcast provider. We're going with a different podcast provider. It's going to
allow us more freedom, more stats. Really what I needed was a lot more stats. I
just needed a lot more room to grow. So for most of you you're not even going to
notice the difference. For the people who are watching it on YouTube you're not
even going to notice. We're still going to upload on YouTube. For the users who
downloaded from podcast addict or iTunes or anything like that there may be a day
or two where it doesn't look like anything's getting updated and that's
just because of the everything's being moved over but again your subscriptions
are going to stay the same. For the people who use the Podbean app you will
unfortunately probably have to listen to it either on the website which I will
present when we get it. So for the Podbean users there's going to be a brief
cutoff where we're switching from Podbean to Libsyn and Libsyn will also have a
website that you can just listen to the episodes on the website but in that
interim period what I would recommend doing is you can either go to our
YouTube channel DeadRavv at Radio or you can add me on Twitter @JasonOCarpenter
on Twitter and I'll let you guys know what the real website is going to be
there. It's going to be DeadRavv.com actually I don't know why I'm even
making it to be mysterious. It's going to be DeadRavv.com but if you're a
Podbean listener you will want to migrate over to that site or you know I
would hope that you guys stayed with the show so I'm sorry but yeah we
have to move to a different podcast provider. I just need more access to
the stats, less restrictions, things like that. Podbean's kind of an entry level
podcast site and we've moved past the entry level podcast site so we're going
over to Lipson but you know Podbean was successful in what it did and I
appreciate my days with Podbean but it's just time to move on. So I just got out
of a locked bathroom I guess I should say that too. I locked myself in my
bathroom that took about 10 minutes. At a certain point I realized I'm not
getting out of my bathroom so I just took a shower and then I got out of the
shower and sat and fiddled with it for a while. My door lock I only have half the
doorknob in my bathroom so this is actually the second time I've got locked
in a bathroom and probably the last three months the last time I was getting
ready to be in a play. I had to get down to the theater to do the show and I
locked myself in my bathroom and now I did it again. Speaking of shows nobody
cares but I recently saw the Adams family at local high school up here in
Hood River. It's pretty cool. I'm not I actually don't like going to the theater
anyways but but it was a good show. I just like being in theater I don't like
watching it. So that was pretty much everything I did during my vacation. Oh
and I got some weird emails from my dad but I'll talk about those tomorrow and
I got some great new artwork and we're gonna talk about that tomorrow as well
because it's gonna be ready to go up on the podcast and up on YouTube and all
that stuff. But let's go ahead and get to what I know you're all looking forward
to which is officially the start of season 3 episode 100 of the Dead Rabbit
Radio podcast. So I appreciate you guys have been there. I hope that you guys
stick with me as I'm moving from one podcast provider to the other and again
we'll be seeing what's for most of you but I hope we take the next 100 episodes
as a journey together because I'm having a lot of fun doing this and I hope
you're having a lot of fun listening to it. So let's go ahead and get started
with our first story. Now this recently happened well I guess let me let me
preface that this this allegation this story just recently happened so in
October of this year there's an actor named Columbus Short. He's on this
television show called Scandal which I have a very scandalous story about that
show. There is this yeah I'm not gonna get into it but anyways basically this
girl made me watch it. It's a much longer story than that and I can't stand it
because I can barely stand her. Anyways Columbus Short is on the show scandal or
was on the show scandal I don't even know if it's on the air anymore. I could
totally forgot it existed until this story popped up on my radar. So what
happened was recently there at Columbus Short posted something on Instagram. It
was a picture of Kanye West, Kim Kardashian, his wife Kim Kardashian and
this Ugandan woman and the quote underneath the Instagram post Columbus
Short wrote this. "I post this picture for one reason and one reason only." I'm
reading it like he's some member of like the royal family okay. What's a
better way to okay. "I post this picture for one reason and one reason only to
expose witchcraft." This is what it looks like. It's an unaddressed issue but real
and present right now. Both men and women all over the world are unknowingly
being tormented by witchcraft and this is what it looks like. You can call me
crazy but I suggest you guys do your research. Of course provides no links
for the research we should do so I actually have to do some of my own. We'll
get to that in a moment but Columbus in the future you want people to do their
research you should give them a little bit of a starting point. So the picture
like I said is Kim Kardashian, this Ugandan woman and Kanye West. Now full
disclosure I'm a big Kanye West fan. I didn't start off a Kanye West fan. I
wasn't his fan until graduation not my graduation the album. That was a bad
joke but anyways I wasn't a fan of his until graduation and then pretty much
threw and threw to the current day. I like him for his music. I like him for
his antics, his personality. I think he's kind of a modern-day you know Andy
Warhol type guy just like a totally out-of-control artist and I do have to
say I'm relatively a fan of Kim Kardashian in the sense that I admire
her business acumen. Of course I was aware of her from her sex tape
which is amazing but I think she's a good businesswoman. She seems to be a
relatively stable influence in Kim Kardashian Kanye West's life. She takes
the idea of prison reform very seriously. She went met with president. She's
talking about going to law school possibly. I don't think she's an idiot. I
think that she's kind of a Parrish Hilton type character where she's very
attractive and she's smarter than she acts because she knows that the dits is
what sells because from what she's done otherwise she seems to be fairly savvy.
But I am a Kanye West fan and like I said to a lesser extent a Kim Kardashian
fan. I think Kanye West is probably one of the best rappers working right now of
the new generation. Not like the little peep guys but in between like I'm
getting off topic but anyways so full disclosure and full disclosure Kanye West
is a eccentric guy. So in this photo it is Kim Kardashian beaming with this
smile. There's this very tall Ugandan woman standing in between them with a
big smile and Kanye West is staring off-camera blank look on his face and
this is the proof. This is what he's providing to post this picture to expose
witchcraft. Now here's the thing Kanye West I don't think could take a normal
photo to save his life. He's just is a he's an odd duck that's just who he is
and if two people are smiling in the picture he's gonna look off in the
distance. If the two people were had this very somber look because they were at a
World War One veteran memorial he'd have a smile on his face. He's just he just
has these weird tics about him. But you're saying Jason your judgment's
clouded because you like both of these people and that's true it could be
clouded but here again here's the thing. This guy in this what four or five
sentences that he posted on Instagram is supposed to be telling the world
exposing the world to the witchcraft that's going on. This is first off this
photo is terrible evidence. If it was a picture of probably somebody who is
normally on top of the world and they look this weird there might be a little
bit more behind it but again Kanye is just so weird anyways and he was always
been weird it wasn't because Kim Kardashian is a witch or anything like
that and that's really what he's suggesting here. He's being that Kanye
West is being tormented by witchcraft and then another user said it's someone
who responded to this Instagram post and said are you saying Kim Kardashian as a
witch and Columbus short responded yep so he's saying that yes Kim Kardashian is
somehow casting spells on him. Let's okay I'm not gonna say witchcraft doesn't
exist because I do believe in a certain element of magic that's possible. What I
find incredibly unlikely is that a practicing witch would use who's powerful
enough to control other people who's able to cast and curse hexes on people
would cast them on Kanye West and like I previously said she met with the
president why didn't she cast him on the president? If she is that effect if Kim
Kardashian is that effective of a witch why does she get so much hate shouldn't
her life be absolutely perfect yes she's rich and she's beautiful on all these
things but the general public looks fairly down upon her so she's this
powerful witch that can actually control people why doesn't she just meet with
like the heads of Fox and all these media outlets the heads of people and cast the
spell on them you have to ask these questions you these are questions that
have to be asked so again if I believe in an element of magic in the world and I
believe that there may be some people who are capable of using it I do not
believe Kim Kardashian is one of those people because the evidence doesn't prove
it she's met with world leaders she met with all these people and she's still
pretty much when she met with Donald Trump the headline I believe was what
was it the Trump and the Rump that's not how you would talk about someone who
had magical powers to control people it just doesn't wash so Columbus Schwartz
allowed to have his opinion and he does say you can call me crazy but generally
when people say that they kind of know they kind of know they they don't
necessarily think that they're crazy but they know what they're saying is
incredibly illogical which actually should be a term that's used more than
crazy you know you can call me illogical because it doesn't there's no logic
behind it it's a picture of three people and one looks off for all we know he saw
a duck getting decapitated by a chicken off camera and that's why he's looking
over there we don't know we don't have all the evidence but the evidence that
you've presented to me does not tell me that Kim Kardashian is a witch but I
will follow Columbus Schwartz advice Columbus Schwartz gave us the advice to
do our research we have to do our research to find out that men and women
all over the world are unknowingly being tormented by witchcraft so I did I
found a website that told me the signs of a curse let's take a look at a couple
of these a lot of them were pretty boring but I found some ones that were
quite interesting okay number one this is a sign you're being cursed so if this
happens to you guys you know something's up number one you discover
unidentified liquids on your doorstep or around your property I will let you and
your mind fill in what type of what's the worst liquids you could find outside
your door I know what mine is I've all walked outside my door and I saw urine
I'd go that's disgusting if I walked outside my door and saw blood my you
know what the thing is my first inclination to be like somebody got
hurt here or an animal someone dumped a dead animal off here if I walked outside
my door and happened to see I don't know semen I don't think I would jump to
witchcraft but I would think something was very very off so that would be but
actually no let's go back to this unidentified liquids I'm just gonna look
down and I'm see a puddle of something I don't know what it is that's actually
less scary than blood or semen if I walked out and I just saw a puddle I'd be
like that's water so let's go on with this one style of hex that a witch may
choose to use involves creating an enchanted potion upon spilling the liquid
in your in your home around your property or on your doorstep the curses
then evoked after cleaning up a suspected potion be sure to cleanse the
space with holy water I would love to meet somebody who every time like they
just see a puddle somewhere they're like looking around for a pointy hat sticking
out of the bushes number three now number two you know they go on a lot of them
are just very vague I just wanted to touch on the most ridiculous ones this
one here number three now I want to I want you to imagine for a moment a
growing adult a mature human being sits down next to you and tells you this
phrase with all earnest like they look at you and they go with complete
conviction they tell you this you notice that photos have gone missing film style
photography is said to possess a piece of your auric energy allowing for a
special connection to the person being photographed as such these photos are
often used as part of magic rituals you notice that pictures have gone missing
around your home a witch may have taken these now again I want you
to imagine an adult who's walking around their house and they notice a photos
missing now again I don't think they're talking about like framed photos let's
say you're let's say I want you to imagine adult who's going through their
photo album and they notice a photo is no longer attached to the page that it's
missing now I think most people are gonna go oh the glue must have come unstuck
or that you know the paper was frayed or whatever and it fell out it's behind the
bookcase that's where the picture is but I imagine that there are a sizable
group of people out there which might have taken this like that's what they
jumped to because they read rule number three that they're basically thinking a
photo missing equals a witch there's all there's a group of people out there that
is not a small group of people who would believe that it's shocking to me now
again yes people probably can harness some sort of unknown energy I'll accept
that that might be possible but that's a long leap to saying oh honey where did
you put our wedding photo she goes I don't know and he's like oh my god check
the house for liquids are there any liquids anywhere a witch a witch is loose
bizarre it's bizarre and it's interesting because it says the film
style photography is said to possess a piece of your arc energy so digital
cameras don't do that yet orbs which are ghosts apparently only show up for the
most part in digital photography so digital photography is good enough to
capture the soul of a dead person but not good enough to capture the energy of
a living person even though you think that a dead person's soul would actually
be given off more energy because it's penetrating the barrier between life
and death and then I have to say all the photos that I've deleted from my hard
drive was it really a little witch in there instead of a paperclip or any
other Microsoft assistant helping me so yeah this is completely ridiculous
but people believe this people believe this stuff so let me cap this off Kim
Kardashian is not a witch missing photos are not the sign of a witch another rule
here says that if your underwear goes missing it may be a sign of a witch if
your underwear goes missing it may be a sign someone's selling them on eBay
you're a woman if your underwear is missing and you're a man it may be a
sign that you're selling yours on eBay or they've simply disintegrated because
you never wash them a problem I commonly have when my underwear goes missing I
just figured out they just they just evaporated should have washed them
witchcraft now you know the signs look for those photos guys if anyone still
has actual film photos somewhere in their house check to see if they're still
there Kim Kardashian might have paid you a visit let's go ahead and get moved on
to the next story now the next story is a story that has been highly requested
it's one that I think most conspiracy theorists have thought about at some
point in their research this one this episode I'm thinking might end up
running a little long but it is our hundredth episode and there's the
season 3 premiere so we might have to just allow that because this is actually
a fairly complicated topic are the Illuminati the good guys that's really
what we're gonna be discussing here now of course it's gonna be a matter of
opinion we don't know who or what the Illuminati even are really but let's go
ahead and get as much facts as we can into this before we start breaking into
the opinion so the Illuminati was we know for let's go over the facts
Illuminati oh and let me say this too this was like I said this is something
people have thought about for a long time but it was this episode was
specifically requested by JC Bateman on YouTube so thank you JC are the Illuminati
the good guys let's go over the facts here real quick we're gonna go back to
the year 1776 we're going into Europe there was a man I going to butcher his
last name but his name was Adam Weishaupt something like that and he had a
couple beefs one he was a fan of the Masons but he kind of thought it was too
expensive to join and he thought that the church was interfering too much with
the Enlightenment too much with the advancement of man which to be fair
they were so he wanted to form a society of free thinkers and idealists to help
raise humanity up he originally they were called their perfected lists and he
thought that takes too long so then they decided to take one of two names they
were either going to be the bee order like bees or the order of the Illuminati
now it's funny as it would have been to have Alex Jones ranting about the bee
order taking over the planet they did decide to go with the order of the
Illuminati and they're standardly known as the Bavarian Illuminati today so they
formed in 1776 on May 1st this is a quote from Adam he said the order of the
day is to put an end to the machinations of the purveyors of injustice to
control them without dominating them so this idea was to get into positions of
power so they could begin to move society towards a more enlightened stage
hence the word illumination Illuminati and they were doing their thing and of
course with any they started to recruit from the masons they had this order with
these three steps that you can move up it was a very Masonic type organization
they begin to get into positions of judges and things like that and if
members of the Illuminati were brought forward into court they'd kind of get a
better deal than just an average person and what happened was eventually the
government of Bavaria said you know what we're gonna out there was too much
trouble they had so many secret societies that all these people they're
basically extra legal groups they had their own set of laws and they would
help each other out and things like that and the government of Bavaria said
we're gonna outlaw all of them not just the Illuminati all of them because all
the Masonic lodges and all that stuff Bavaria outlawed all secret societies
and that was officially the end of the order of the Illuminati in 1797 and
1798 two books came out and that's what really kept the idea of the so the
order of the Illuminati's gone but these books came out and these books kept the
conspiracy going the idea was that the French Revolution that later happened
was caused by the order of the Illuminati that they were still pulling the
strings behind closed doors or is it behind the curtain anyways they were
pulling strings somewhere sealed off it's kind of been retconned so now we're
getting into the stuff that's not actually factual this is all based on
people saying things there's no provenance to any of is it provenance or
provenance anyways there's no going there's no tracking back these actual
quotes where we're gonna go some people claim to say that the Illuminati was
behind the American Revolution which happened what a month Declaration of
Independence this happened in May June July so two months later the Declaration
of Independence was started some people say that the group was it caused the
American Revolution caused the Declaration of Independence to be
created my argument to that is you just had a whole generation of people who
believed in throwing off the shackles of tyranny some of them and were Warren
Bavaria throwing off the shackles of the church some of them were in America
throwing off the shackles of Britain but the idea that the Illuminati has now
through the ages controlled things controlling things behind the scenes now
of course Adam did say that's kind of what they wanted to do control them
without dominating them take control without actually having to you know run
everything you're just running the pieces of power what the Illuminati is
generally considered to date when you hear that term it is generally a insult
or a pejorative generally the Illuminati are considered to be saint
worshipers they're trying to create the New World Order which is a slave state of
earth they've been linked to wanting to cause mass genocide to cause food
shortages so millions of people die to controlling wars controlling race wars
to giving people vaccines to make them dumber or to control them to wanting to
install chips in people's hands so they can track and they can control them
rounding up people into camps and again controlling them but basically creating
a prison planet to where us normal people as civilians as normal homo sapiens
are ruled over we're cold there's only like five million of us left and we're
ruled by this satanic overall cold I'll say this there's and this should go
without saying but there's no proof to back any of that up at all there's
nothing like there are people who've said they've defected from the Illuminati
and they tell us a story but I could say I defected from Dairy Queen and tell you
what a terrible place Dairy Queen is and you have to take the idea and that did
happen but you have to take what I say with a grain of salt because one you
don't know if I'm making it up whole cloth and two you maybe I just have bad
blood which isn't proof it's something somebody else wrote and there's a
difference between that we have historical documents for the stuff I
just told about 1776 and the Bavarian Illuminati and stuff like that that's all
historical documents those are all records of that somebody telling an
author about his time in the Illuminati that's not proof that's one person
telling a story to another person so that is the Illuminati in a nutshell that
they started off as the secret order in 1776 and now the theory goes again
there's not any proof of it but well the theory is is that they're you're still
around and they are satanic and they worship Molok they worship this owl
in the Bohemian Grove and they put their secret symbols everywhere the the
pyramid with the eye you can see subliminal messaging and music videos you
can see subliminal messaging and kids shows on and on and on and they control
everything now so let's take that for a fact that there is an Illuminati that
controls everything there is a group of people that have evolved from a 1776 to
today and their plan and their plan to put it into the machinations of the
purveyors of injustice is still here today let's get into the idea that the
Illuminati are in fact the good guys one theory is that they started off as good
guys and then they became corrupted by their power they started off with the
intention of being this enlightened group that would arise humanity up past the
self-implied restrictions of the church and church thought they said science
will rule the day philosophy will rule the day instead of these religious
leaders ruling the day but over the preceding 300 years they've you know
the original good men died out and those who've taken their place and then after
them and after them they've just become more focused on power and money and
become part of the problem and no longer are part of the solution so that's one
of the theories there's another one that you have the Illuminati that runs
everything and then you have the garbage people and the garbage people are the
people who generally we associate with the Illuminati this the like baby
sacrifices the child porn peddlers the horrible like bankers and people who
start wars and stuff like that and the Illuminati are so well hidden that we
can't see past the garbage people when we see these horrible deals being made
behind closed doors or US government selling weapons to this country and
they're thinking that's horrible and chemical weapons being dropped in these
high-profile people getting away with child porn charges or getting like
slaps on the wrist and things like that and we go how was all of this horrible
stuff happening and I know there's an Illuminati I believe that but then on
under then I see proof of all this horrible stuff happening I think they're
connected and it could be that the actual Illuminati are so well hidden that
we can't see them we see all the people who are like you know would be real
funny to hide this pyramid eye and this Nickelodeon ad yeah and the garbage
people could actually be trying to give the Illuminati a bad name because they
know the Illuminati is fighting for good theory again there's no proof of any of
this but it's an interesting theory and I think it's one that would actually
stand up because when we look at powerful people getting away with doing
wicked things we go how could that happen and if you believe also that there
is a group of powerful people ruling the world you would your next step would be
like oh it happens because they're part of this group that runs the whole world
you just see the visible stuff and you go I can see this and I know this other
thing I can't see exists therefore the two must be connected and I think that's
one of the reasons why the Illuminati gets a bad name but I think the most
important reason again if you buy into the theory of the Illuminati if you buy
into the theory that the Illuminati are controlling the planet let me ask you a
question and it's a very very simple question is the world better off today
than it was in 1776 if there was a group that was founded in 1776 and their goal
was to enlighten humanity to bring them out of the dark ages of thought are we
immeasurably better off as a planet today than we were in 1776 global poverty is
down world hunger is down life expectancy is up technological advances are
mind-blowing to someone from 1776 we have our problems we have bush wars we have
political issues we have personal strife we have international strife but even
in my lifetime the world has gotten better from the brink of nuclear war when
I was growing up in the 80s I like I'm 42 years old so I was a little kid during
the 80s and we are on the brink of global nuclear war and it terrified me as a
child to now I simply worry about getting shot when I go out to a nightclub
you can see both are equally terrifying but one was the end of humanity and the
other one is an unfortunate terrible event that I'm still aware of can happen
to me but I think by any measure you could say that is an improvement that's
an improvement just that example people are living more fulfilling lives today
than they were in 1776 the average person you could say well the philosopher
got to sit around all day and just eat apples like Johnny Apple seed and read
books all day the philosopher maybe but for the average working person it's been
much better now than it was back then for poor people it was a hundred times
better than it was back then if there is an Illuminati if they have been acting
behind the scenes you can come up with all the theories about same worshiping
and stuff like that that you want with the Illuminati that they're trying to
create his prison plan and give people chips those are theories if you believe
that the Illuminati formed in 1776 and they've ruled a sense then you have to
believe that they have benefited this planet because it's better than it was
back then it's better for pretty much everybody rainforest you know a couple
animals probably not so much but people have more they have more time they have
more wealth they have more food they have the ability to communicate with
people in parts of the globe that in 1776 were almost fictional people didn't
even know those places existed we have grown so much as a species we've landed
on the moon we've sent probes out to the farthest reaches of the solar system
and we've cured diseases that back then they thought were curses if the Illuminati
has ruled the world since 1776 they're doing a damn good job dead rabbit radio
at gmail.com is going to be your email address you can also hit us up at
facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is @jasonocarpenter
hundredth episode I'm gonna get I don't know I figure we'll probably stop around
a thousand assuming nothing crazy happens I figure we got a thousand episodes
behind us in front of us dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you
listen to it today have a great one guys