Is the doll I purchased from eBay actually haunted? We'll do an update on that story.
And then we're going to take a look at two ghost ships of San Francisco,
both with extremely different origins. Is it true that a cursed boat still sails the waters
under the Golden Gate Bridge? Is it true that a boat that was cursed from construction
took the lives of three of their captains? Will set sail and find out the truth today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Quick update for those of you
who don't listen to every episode. Last week I bought a haunted doll or the week before.
I got it last week. I got it on Wednesday. Now I bought it on eBay. It was 30 bucks for a doll
that you could get at Goodwill for a quarter. And it said that these are the hauntings that it could
possibly do. Open and close doors. Now I can open and close doors. So that's not super spectacular.
I can do that. It can have a woman's voice say, "Hello, hello, hello." I don't know if it echoes,
but it would be creepier if it did. It can give you vivid dreams. And what was the other thing?
It, um, oh, the smell of a woman's perfume. It can make your house smell like a woman's been there.
So I got the doll on Wednesday night. No to the doors open and closing unless I'm doing them. Of
course. I'm like, why won't this door open? I have to use Veronica. I should take Veronica around
and use her as like a garage door opener and just squeak her. Because she has a little, you know,
I'm gonna, here, I'm gonna get her squeaky real quick. Okay, so I'm holding Veronica right now.
Here we go. It's one of those types of toys. I think for the thumbnail for this episode,
I'll take, I'll tell you this, the eyes are really spooky. The eyes are really spooky. It's kind of
scuffed up. That's Veronica talking. Now, again, the only doors that have been opening closing are
the ones that I do. I haven't heard a woman's voice say, "Hello." They usually go, "What's up?"
Because it's 2019. The ghost should get, how come there aren't any ghosts that are be like,
"What's up dog? What was the other, oh, smells like a woman's perfume." No, when I squeeze it,
I get a little bit of a weird, musty smell from her. So let's go to the last one, Vivid Dreams.
It was the, it's funny. That was the one when I was reading what she was capable of doing from
the eBay listing. I go, "Vivid Dreams." Because those are the easiest thing to misinterpret as
anything paranormal. Now, since I got Veronica, I have been having the most vivid dreams. The other
night I woke up and my hands were like typing like I was on a keyboard and I was going, "Minnesota,
have to find Minnesota." And that's what woke me up. The night before, I had an incredibly
vivid nightmare that I jumped up after I woke up and I was writing down notes. I was like,
"This would make a good story." So the dreams have been crazy lately. They've really been crazy this
past week. So is Veronica responsible for them? You know, back in my early 20s, I lived with this
girl. She was going to UC Davis and I needed a place to stay. And through a really bizarre setup,
like, okay, so she had two roommates that didn't like her at all and they needed to leave for the
summer, but they couldn't do something with their lease or whatever. They couldn't take their names
off the lease. So they went onto a roommate finder website, found me and then said, "Oh yeah, you
can rent the room. You'll just pay us." And they then told my friend, "Let's call her Blake." They
tell Blake, "Oh yeah, we know this guy. We've known him since high school. He's a really cool guy."
I go the very first day I'm moving in, we go out to dinner and she goes, "So, how well do you know
so-and-so?" And I was like, "I've never met him in my life. Like, I just rent an apartment from them."
Oh, she was so mad. She didn't know if she was housed with a lunatic and she found out in this
short while that she was. So me and Blake hung out. We lived together. It was really cool,
but it was technically a dorm. So whenever the house marm, the resident dean person at the school,
would come around, I would have to clean all my stuff up, but she was quite the task and leave
for the day. So they wouldn't know that there was a non-college student male living at this. It was
like off-campus dorms type of thing. Anyways, one day I had this towel that I took a shower with,
as you do, and then I threw it in the corner of the room. Fast forward three months and I had not
cleaned that corner of the room and the towel had grown this large globulous tubular mold
chunk. It would have to be at least five, six, and no, it was longer than that. It's probably like
eight inches long of this. It looked like a gooey sweet potato and the roots were actually like
bound in with the fibers of the towel. And I was like, oh man, I really don't want to go out and buy.
Now I was using another towel at the time. I still wasn't using this one, but I don't like
having to buy any stuff if I don't have to. So I showed Blake. I was like, dude, isn't this disgusting?
She's like, yeah, that's super gross. Now to be fair, she was super gross too, so it wasn't too
out of the norm for this apartment. But I said, let's see if we can wash it off. Let's get to the
laundry mat, the laundry mat in the facility, and we'll wash it and see if the mold just kind of
flies off of it apparently. So we do, we throw it in the washing machine, we go out, we're hanging
out. We come back. It's probably like a Friday night. I remember that. It was a Friday or a
Saturday night. It was a parting night. We go back to the laundry mat, pop open the washing machine,
pull the towel out, and it's still on there. For some reason, I thought that it would just tumble
off in the washing cycle. So pull out the towel and I was like, well, that's, I guess I have to
get a new towel. So I'll have two towels now. I never wash my, I use the same towel over and over
again. It's whatever. People get really like, it's water and soap. And then I wash my body with the
towel and put my towel up on the towel rack, right? And then the next day I use it again. And you go,
Jason, why don't you wash it? To my answer is, how do you wash a towel with water and soap? So
I'm just cutting out the middleman. I am the middleman. My body is literally the middleman
between the soap and the water transactions each day. Anyways, so take the towel and I rip off
the tubular mold. I'm all, curriculum strength. Blake's like, Oh, my hero. I didn't know you're so
strong. You could defeat micro organisms that have formed a colony. I'm like, yes, yes, I can, little
lady. Through the Talloway. Now I'm walking through the laundromat with this huge chunk of gooey mold.
And as we're walking through the laundromat, I'm looking in dryers because you know, they have the
big windows. I'm looking at the dryer and I walk by the next one. I look at the dryer and I walk
by the next one. I look at the dryer and I stop. I open up the dryer and I throw the mold into the
dryer. And you go, well, there's multiple things that I have questions about here. One, why did you
do that? Two, why did you pick that particular dryer? And again, the number one is the most
important question. Well, I'll get to number one in a second. I was looking for a dryer that had a
lot of clothes in it, a lot of clothes in it, a lot of like nice clothes. And I open up the dryer
and I throw the tubular mold in and I shut the dryer and Blake stops and she looks at me and
she goes, why did you do that? And I just look over and I go, I just kind of shrugged my shoulders
and said, I just wanted to ruin some girls night. And we walked out. Now I imagine at some point,
this young woman came to get her clothes. This totally true story, by the way. At some point in
the night, a young woman came to get her clothes before she went out for the weekend for the night.
She opened up, she grabbed all her clothes, scooped them into a laundry basket, took them back to
her apartment and as she began folding them or most likely dumping them on her bed to sort out
later, a big gooey living mass of mold just tumbled out next to her shirt and her pants.
The reason why I tell you that story, one, because I think it's hilarious and two,
because if you came across that as a person, as a human being, if you were doing your laundry
and you found a disgusting thing in it that wasn't there when you put the laundry in the dryer,
your mind would be racing, it would be looking for an explanation. First off, what is this?
Secondly, where did it come from? And again, first off, what is this? Like you would really,
really be trying to, it would really mess with your head and you would never know the answer.
You would never be able to figure that out because at no point would you think someone
must have thrown this in there. Somebody must have cultivated a, if it was a candy wrapper,
you'd figure someone threw it in there, but because it was this giant chunk of mold,
I had never seen anything like it, okay? So and I'm disgusting, so if I hadn't seen anything like it,
somebody who's not disgusting, it would have been as if they opened up their dryer and ET was
sitting in there. It would have been completely alien. So that must have tormented that young woman.
Now it's possible that she didn't even care, it's possible she took a bite out of it and she goes,
"I hunger!" and she like eats mold, of course. But there, if it happened to me, I would tell that
story to people for a while. I'd be like, "Dude, you want to hear something weird when I was doing
laundry? Assuming I'm not disgusting, let's say I'm you. Let's say I'm you and I'm doing my laundry
and I'm assuming you're not disgusting and something gross jumps out of the dryer." I would go,
"There's no way this could have happened." And people would be like, "Someone might have thrown
it in there." And I go, "What madman would throw this on my clothes at random?" So it would be
what we would call an unexplained event. You would have theories. You would go, "Maybe it came out
of the dryer. Maybe it was in your clothes to begin with and which would make you super petrified
about what was going on in your house." Maybe someone threw it in there, but then the question
has become who? Why? And what is it? It would be an unexplained event. It would be something that
someone made post on Reddit. That happened like 15 years ago, maybe 20 years ago, honestly. But it
would be something someone would post on Reddit, you know, weird things found in your laundry.
Some girls like, "Well, you know when I went to UC Davis?" The reason why I bring
this up is because it ties back to the Veronica story. There is a key piece of information that
is tied into the Veronica story, just like there was a key piece of information about why that
unexplained event happened to that woman's laundry. You see, in the past week as well,
I have stopped taking the nicotine losanges because I'm just tired. One, they were expensive.
Two, they were messing with my keto. And three, I was taking way too many of them. And I said,
"Okay, it's time to get off nicotine for good." So I'm stepping down using the patch, which has been
fairly easy transition. But for those of you who have ever tried giving up nicotine, and for those
of you specifically who have used the patch, they give vivid dreams, vivid, vivid dreams. So by simply
having that extra piece of information, oh, there is a rational explanation for you to have those
vivid dreams. And I think that's one thing we always got to look at. I feel like I'm becoming
even more skeptical doing this show because I'll read stuff and I'll go. There's information missing
that I know isn't true. Lana recently sent me the story about there's a spate of
cattle mutilations going on in Oregon. And Lana sent it to me. And she goes, "I thought this would
be right up your alley." And my response was, "I don't believe it." Like, I don't believe when
they keep saying, "All the blood is drained from the cows." All of it. I go, "That's just not true.
That's 100% not true." What happens is you're coming across the scene and there's no blood at the scene.
So there's no blood. I mean, are they literally going through every single
vein and artery and organ in the body and discover up? Nope. It looks like parchment down there.
It's completely dry. There's not a single drop. No, that's not true. There's less blood in the body
than should be. And there's less blood at the scene than there should be. But I can't go there to
verify it. I just know from steady and cattle mutilations, you hear these terms. There's no blood
in the body. When we look at the original news reports, they'll say there's no blood at the scene.
So when we lack the information to really look at it objectively, we are missing a key point.
Just like how I omitted that detail on purpose that I had recently quit. The loss in jizz,
I'm on the patch. Those are both will cause side effects of very vivid dreams. At the same time,
I got a doll that causes vivid dreams. You got to have all the information. Just like that young
woman who's probably in a mental hospital in Davis. She's like, "No, no, not that night again." She's
like, "We'll never go near another dryer." She's hand washing all of her clothes and just stands
guard with a shotgun. She didn't have all the information. To her, that was a gross unexplained
event. If she had all the information, she would realize there was just a maniac, a gross disgusting
man hiding out in her off-campus dorms. Let's go ahead and move on to our... That was the story.
That was a first story. A little Veronica the doll update. Let's go ahead and move on to this next
story. Now, and I'll keep you updated on Veronica the doll as well. I guess the moral of that story
is we got to have all the information. Now, these next two stories are kind of weird because they're
very, very basic ghost stories. But I'll be honest, man, I broke my back looking into these things.
You know what? Let's do a very, very quick Dead Rabbit Recommends here too. Let's do a quick one
here. This is probably one of my favorite horror movies. And I'm going to say right off the bat,
it has probably one of the dumbest killer motivations I've ever seen. And I watch a ton of these
B/R movies. There's a group of sorority girls named Theta Pi. Do or die, Theta Pi. They're sisters
for life. Sisters keep secrets. But recently, one of their brothers was like feeling up a girl who
was drunk and they wanted to like get back at him and show him how that's not cool. So they pull a
prank. And they make him think that he accidentally caused this girl to overdose. The girl's in on it.
And they do this whole thing where they drive out to this abandoned well and they're like,
we're going to dump the body now and you got to keep your mouth shut, Billy or whatever his name
was. You got to keep your mouth shut. And they're all giggling and laughing. And this kid is drunk
and he's high and he's overwrought with guilt because he thinks that this girl that he was trying
to make out with overdosed on a drug he gave her. And while they're debating how far they're going
to take this plan, he picks up a tire iron and stabs her in the throat. And so kills her for real.
And so they have to reveal, it's just a joke. It was just a joke. It was just a joke. And then
they do have to drop her body in the abandoned well and take an oath of secrecy. They'd apply,
do or die. Sisters always keep secrets. The movie's called Sorority Row and it's funny because it's
such a basic setup for horror movies. It's actually a remake of a 70s horror movie. But the directing
is phenomenal for this type of movie. It's not Dunkirk. But there are just beautiful shots in
the movie. The cinematography is on point. The acting is good. And the women are gorgeous,
which is always a good selling point. The deaths are really inventive. Really enjoy that. And
there's a level of tension throughout the movie because that's how the movie starts. So even
when they're not being stalked by a killer, there's this level of tension because we jump ahead
a year. And these girls have been living with the secret for this whole time. So you're trying to
figure out who's going to break. Like who's going to act because it's weighing on all of them. They're
getting ready to graduate now. And of course, a serial killer shows up with a tire iron. And it's
one of those tire irons. It's like a cross. So it's like, has the four. It's like a cross. You
know what a cross looks like. And the killer has tricked it out. So like one side has a blade and
the other side has like a saw and then one part has a drill. And the dude's like throwing it like
a ninja star and using it to break down the, it's a really inventive horror movie. And it racks up
quite the pot account. I'm recommending this one because one, it's one of my favorite horror movies
of all time. Two, a lot of the horror movies I've recommended for Halloween, they're very like
movies you want to sit down and watch. Sorority Row is a movie you can have on the background at
a party. You can have it on the background. It's just a funny, it's a very well written horror movie.
The ending, the killer's motivation is one of the worst killer motivations I've ever
seen. However, the third act is still really good. The third act is still on point. Like once they
reveal the killer motivation, I remember I was watching that with Lana and she goes,
that's terrible. And I was like, yeah, I know, but the next 15 minutes are still really cool. And
she's like, oh yeah, yeah, I mean, like it does end well. Because then you have this kind of set
piece after you find out who the killer is. One of the worst killer motivations on record. However,
other than that, it doesn't completely sink the movie because the movie is that good. Any other
movie would have completely destroyed it. Sorority Row. Check it out. Anyways, let's go ahead and move
on with our tale of ghost ships. Wait, there's no where on a ghost ship. What would the ghost,
you'd hear that ding ding ding ding ding like the little bell and the fog and then the
that's a that's either a ghost boat going through San Francisco Bay or a rocking chair
knocking over a glass of water. It's your decision. Let's start off with the story of the squando.
So the ghost story is this. There was a Norwegian ship named Squando. And from the very beginning,
it was cursed. What happened was a couple of people died building the boat, which
that must be difficult. Like how do you die building a boat? You're like, oh no, I fell off
into the soft stuff called the water. And then you just went back on the boat. It's not like building
a dam where you're like falling like two miles to your death or getting trapped in concrete or
anything like that. It's you fall and I get that boats can be high, but still. But what happened?
Did you get your timbers too shivered? How do you die building a boat? Anyways, like eight people
died building this boat. So I don't know if they were building it out of Ebola or what, but anyways,
the one of the wives of one of the dudes who died said, I curse this boat. She's like spitting on
the boat. She's like a cursit. And then to make the curse stick, she kills herself. So very, very
bleak beginning to the story of the squando. In 1890, it's parked at the Embarcadero in San
Francisco. And the captain finds out that his first mate is banging his wife. And so he goes,
okay, wife, I'm going to murder you unless you help me murder this dude you're sleeping with. And
she goes, oh yeah, totally down with the whole murder plot. Don't kill me. So she holds the dude
down and the captain jumps on top of him and cuts his head off with a hatchet. They throw the head
into a bucket. Throw, I don't know why we'll get into that. Throw the body overboard. They go on
the run. Eventually, the other people on the boat are like, Hey, where's our captain? Hey,
where's our first mate? Hey, what's in this bucket? Ah, they call the cops. The cops find the couple.
And the couple is executed for their crime. And the boat is still a boat. So they get a new captain,
the company buys the boat or however boats work. And then the company owns the boat and they hire
captain. Anyways, they go, we still got this boat. They hire a new captain on the first journey. The
crew mutinies kills the captain. So they have to get a new captain and they have to get a new crew.
No one wants to work with those guys. They get a new captain, new crew. That captain dies under
mysterious circumstances. They get a new captain. That captain dies as well. At that point, it's in
Bathhurst and New Brunswick, which I believe is up in Canada. And they go, no one wants to work on
the boat. Nobody wants to work on the boat. So when the company's trying to figure out what to do
with the boat, they have to hire these guards to keep watch over it, which if people go on the boat
die, I don't really think you need guards. Anyways, there are guards at the boat. And they said they
could see the specter of a headless man wandering around the deck. So they bounced. And then at
that point, the company goes, nobody wants to be on the boat. Nobody even wants to guard the boat.
And they scuttled it. And according to legend, sometimes you can still see the squando, the
ghostly shape of the squando out in the San Francisco Bay. Fascinating ghost story. The question was,
and going back to the tubular, we'll call this from now on the tubular mold theory,
is there information that's missing to make the story make sense? I had to really dig into this
one. Really, really dig into this one. Now, there's a lot of different variations of it. Some of them,
the head is thrown overboard. There's no head put in a bucket. Some of the versions, the couple is
not caught. They escape. They're never seen again. Some of the versions are that it wasn't cursed
because people died while the boat was being constructed. It was cursed because there was a
woman on board for its first voyage, which apparently is a bad thing. And people were like,
"What? You brought a woman on board? This ship is cursed!" And then that got retconned to people
dying. But who knows which version is true? Most likely just the woman being on board,
just because it's more simple than everything else. But you also have to go,
"My first thing was, is this story true at all? Is this story true at all?" And it's just all these
little legends. So, and I honestly spent a long amount of time trying to research this one.
And it's really real. It's still kind of up in the air. The boat itself did exist, but I found
it interesting detail. If you go to Bathurst, let's go to Bathurst in New Brunswick. We're
gonna take the rabbit rowboat. We're gonna sail over there. We're gonna do CSI as in
"see" scene investigation. See, like, the ocean? Anyways, so we're there. And we hop off the rabbit
rowboat. We're meeting some old salty people. Horses are constantly licking them. They're like,
"Get away. Get away." We're like, "So what do you know about this boat?" And this old salty man
sits down on a snail, immediately dissolves him, and then he sits down in a chair, as he should.
And he goes, "Yes, there is a boat called the Squando." Or, "There was a boat called the Squando."
And yes, it was in Bathurst. But there was no verification that it was ever in the
Embarcadero. It was no verification that it was on the West Coast in San Francisco. Not saying
that it wasn't. Because British Columbia, I think Bathurst is up in British Columbia. It's all on
the West Coast, but the idea of this murder taking place in San Francisco couldn't find any record
of it. You'd seem like that would be a really, really sensational murder. Husband and wife team
up to kill wife's lover, head found in bucket under bed. News at 11. Page 11, because there was no
television back then. So why don't we have any record of that? So you're thinking it must be
fake. Tubular mold theory. The detail is missing because it doesn't exist, right? There is an
issue of the Chat Ham Gazette. There is an issue. December 10th, 1887. So, three years before the
story supposedly took place in 1890 in San Francisco Bay. 1887, the Chat Ham Gazette.
The little newspaper over there. And it says the boat was stuck in the mud over in Bathurst.
And it was the storm had knocked it into this muddy bank. And the article goes on to say that
some guy bought it for $40 and they're going to salvage it, break it up, sell the wood or whatever.
So you're like, it was never over there. The story must be fake. If there's a news article three years
before the story supposedly took place, then someone just found out about a boat that was
scuttled and created a myth. The article in the Chat Ham Gazette, December 10th, 1887, starts off
with the sentence, "No more will Bathurst be agitated by the headless ghost of the haunted
squando." And then it goes on to say, "The boat was stuck in the mud because of a storm and some
guy bought it for $40." And they begin scuttling it. They begin taking it apart. And then the last
sentence of the article says, "The men engaged in the work were somewhat surprised to find,
in between the timbers of the vessel, a bucket and an old metal axe."
So is the story true? Fascinating. Fascinating little detail. That's from a news article.
So, and there's nothing else. Every time you look for this boat, it tells you this story about
something that happened in San Francisco. It's very sensational and detailed. And the boat had all
this stuff and the other captains and the mutiny and the gypsy curse and all that stuff. But we can
go back to three years before that story ever happened, 1887, and find this article. And they're
like, "Yeah, remember that headless ghost walking around Bathurst haunting us? Don't gotta worry
about it anymore." And that's all. Who knows? This is a fascinating story because there's enough
detail to make me think that at least the legend is true. It's not something that was passed around
on the internet. At least the legend was true. But the truth of the headless ghost, the bucket,
the axe, we have all these details that most likely are true. And then it got transformed into
this story that's super detailed that takes place in San Francisco. What was in the bucket? Was the
axe used to murder someone? Was there really a headless ghost walking around the deck of that
boat? And over the years, the story has just become this super detailed fake haunting, but based on
a real life ghost. Let's save the other ghost boat story for tomorrow. I've actually run out of time
on that one. So that was an anticlimactic conclusion. Tomorrow, though, we have another ghost boat
story that's fascinating in the same way and, again, found enough news articles, found proof
that this story may also be just as true. There really may be at least one ghost boat
still haunting the San Francisco Bay. We'll talk about that tomorrow on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabberadio. Twitter is @deadrabberadio. Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you
listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye.