The following episode of Dead Rabbit Radio contains highly disturbing audio.
Listener discretion is advised.
A recent scientific experiment shows what may happen if you traveled backwards in time
and had sex with a caveman.
Spoiler alert, nothing good.
Nothing good is going to come out of it.
And then we travel to Virginia to take a look at a bizarre mystery that is currently going
on and one that is barely being investigated by the Lynchburg Police Department out there.
When a young man is found dead in his apartment, the police quickly call case closed.
He died of natural causes.
But how could they come to that conclusion when not only was his apartment full of blood
and feces?
There is also videotape of him screaming for help as he is brutally being murdered today
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a great
day too, I hope you guys are having tons of fun.
Trust me, you probably won't be by the end of this episode.
We got two stories, one's a nice fun one about having sex with cavemen.
The second story is pretty disturbing even for Dead Rabbit Radio.
We'll get to that after the fun one after I've gotten you to laugh a little bit.
Oh man, it makes me mad, that second story really makes me mad.
But we'll get to that in a second.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command, right now let's give it up to one of our long
time Patreon supporters, everyone on your feet for Banked Sassy Pants.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in Banked Sassy Pants, walk on into Dead Rabbit Command.
I'm recording this episode at 10pm, I probably shouldn't clap so loud.
Banked, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's fine too, I totally understand.
Just helps to spread the word about the show, that really, really helps out a lot.
You can also right now help us with our wiki project, started by Jerm.
The Dead Rabbit Radio wiki is in the show notes, we're really looking at building that
up, so thank you so much.
Banked Sassy Pants, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the hare hovercraft.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Glide us all the way out to the Salt Lakes of Utah.
Banked is driving us all out there, he's doing donuts in the salt, everyone's eyes are all
raw by the time we get there.
Every show often I play this game with myself, I do a lot of this stuff.
I had the amnesia game, I talked about that before on the show where I walk around like
the movie section of a Walmart or a Best Buy and I pretend I had amnesia for the past 20
years and I'm amazed at all the movies, I keep myself highly entertained, I spend a lot of
time alone.
So I'll be like, oh my god there's a Transformers 4?
Like what?
I didn't know they made a Transformers 1 and I'm like looking on the back of the movie,
something like oh my god I can't wait to watch these movies and people are like okay maybe
after Transformers 3 you should curb your expectations because they get pretty bad after
3.
I play this game.
Wow, there's an Avengers Endgame, what?
And you find out, imagine if you found out today there was 20 years worth of superhero
movies, I mean only 7 or 8 of them are worth watching but that doesn't matter right?
You have 20 years of Marvel movies and you're like what?
You have that, like I play the same amnesia game with myself when I'm alone in a big store.
I'm like what Kiwi?
It's 3 for a dollar, what's Kiwi?
The other game I play with myself is sometimes when I'm walking down the street because I
always have a backpack on because I don't have a car.
I walk everywhere and shop and I'm carrying stuff around.
Like a hobo, I basically outed myself as an amnesiac and a hobo.
I play this game and I go what if I got teleported back in time right now?
I got teleported back to the Knights of the Roundtable age right?
Like that famous documentary The Black Knights starring Martin Lawrence, you get teleported
back and there's like castles.
Yeah I know that's on another continent, just play with me right?
You get teleported back in time and I'm walking around this castle and there's like this old
man and he's like I'm looking for a new dude to be on my court and then there's like a mean
bad advisor who's trying to take over the court basically.
I imagine that I've been at Disney Channel movie and walking around, you know the tropes
right?
And I think, here's the thing, if I traveled back in time right now and I had to defeat
an evil advisor to this aging king and I traveled back with the items I have on me right now,
how well would I fare?
How well could I get by?
Now in The Black Knight, Martin Lawrence had a CD player.
I don't know why that movie left such an impression on me.
If you guys don't even know what I'm talking about, Martin Lawrence worked at a medieval
theme park and then he fell into some hay or fell into the river and when he came out
of the river or the hay, I don't remember, he was back in time and it was basically the
same thing there was an evil guy trying to take over the thing and I remember it was
so funny.
Wait, actually another thing about it was this Martin Lawrence or am I thinking of a Disney
Channel movie?
It could have been in one of the movies and it was either in The Black Knight starring
Martin Lawrence or some children's film that I don't remember the title to.
They defeated the evil bad guy because the bad guy was really good with swords right?
They couldn't beat him with swords and they had a CD player.
Remember those little portable CD players and you know CD players use as a laser to
read the CD.
They use the laser, you can't do this in real life, which I also can't teleport back in
time either.
I don't know why I was so hung up on this detail.
As the bad guys coming at them to kill them with the sword, whoever was the star of the
movie opens up the CD player and shoots the laser beam out of the CD player, which is
again just used to read a compact disc and it blinds the guy and then he fell off the
building into the river or into hay.
I don't remember.
That was the end of the movie.
But the point is, imagine if I was walking on the street or you were walking on the street
and you were sent back in time 200 years with only the stuff you had on you.
So normally I have a backpack that would seem magical.
I have phones but the battery is going to die soon so I could be like I'm a wizard.
Look at this phone and they're like can I see it and you're like nope and you shut it
off because you'd have to conserve that battery power, right?
You could show them some images.
You're showing your like webm's and gifs that you have saved on there.
They're like oh that kitten is trapped in your phone.
Can I see it?
I'm like nope.
Well I'll pull it out in another convenient time.
But the magic only works every once in a while and once the better runs out and the magic's
gone.
I usually have, what else do I have in my backpack?
I have medicine.
I have like muscle relaxers so I can be throwing those into the Black Knight's mouth as he's
about to go in.
He's like oh I'm getting sleepy.
He can't hold up the sword anymore.
But yeah it's like what could you, I usually have like a knife and pepper spray and stuff
like that.
I mean those are actual weapons.
I probably should have named those first.
I think about this, I would say all the time but it does pop up in my head.
I do think what would happen if zombies attacked right now?
What would happen if a dog attacked right now?
That's a pretty constant thing going through my head.
I'm constantly turning my head on a swivel because we have a whole episode about the
dog attack.
And then I'll put it in show notes.
And then what if I traveled back in time with what I have on me?
Now obviously I would appear as a god because I have like all of this metal.
I guess they had metal back then but I have all these, I have these devices that I only
show them occasionally.
My clothes would be magical right?
I have really cool boxer shorts.
And actually that's a good segue because what I'm going to be looking at here is not,
this is not an episode about the things I do when I'm alone.
It's about, I've defeated the black knight right?
He's sleeping in the hay, he's dying of an overdose of muscle relaxers.
I poured him on his mouth, I go I'm the villain now.
And now it's time to boink the beautiful princess right?
That's part of it, that's part of the story.
You get to have sex with the princess because now you're the king and she's your queen.
That's a cool end of the story right?
You find true love, you're trapped back in time, you're going to die of dysentery in
about two weeks.
But until then you're going to have the hand of this fair maiden.
Now I always thought you know we'd be compatible.
But according to this recent science that's coming out, yeah we'd be compatible in some
ways, but is it possible that my 21st century body would actually kill?
Not on purpose.
Even though I just declared myself the villain.
Is it possible that my 21st century body could accidentally kill a 14th century princess?
It's an intriguing thought isn't it?
And it's quite disturbing.
Let's take a look at this scientific experiment that just went on.
There's a guy named Nicholas Rode.
Well I'll tell you right now, when he did this experiment he never once thought it would
be extrapolated to could Jason have sex with a princess.
He never once popped into his head.
But Nicholas Rode works for the Center for Functional and Evolutionary Biology and he
goes "I want to run a test on something."
He goes "See Monkeys."
See Monkeys, those little things you used to be able to get out of the back of comic
books.
They're, they're, they're, they're a little tiny sea creatures and what's interesting
about them and the reason why you can ship them across the country is once they lay eggs,
those eggs are dormant until the environment is just right for them to hatch.
So you can have these eggs last for decades, decades, these eggs can just sit there and
once you add the right amount of water they'll hatch.
Now the interesting thing about sea monkeys is that they evolve very rapidly because they're
constantly giving birth, right?
They're constantly having new little babies and so we can actually see adaptations in
our lifetime of the sea monkey.
And so Nicholas Rode goes "What if we actually introduced a current sea monkey to a sea
monkey from the past and made them have sex?"
Like what would happen, because what we know is the mating procedure of the sea monkey
is the dudes grab on to the girls and they don't let them go.
They'll hold on to them, they'll impregnate them and they'll hold on to them a little
bit longer, not because they want to cuddle, it's because they want to make sure that these
female sea monkeys don't go out and have sex with other male sea monkeys.
They want their genetic offspring to be birthed by this female.
So over time the sea monkeys have developed pretty, the male ones, have developed pretty
strong hands.
They've developed pretty well-defined strong hands and the ones who could grab on to the
females the longest and hold them the longest were the ones whose children would be birthed
and the ones with the tiny little hands they couldn't grab on to the women they wouldn't
pass on those tiny little hands.
Now evolution is always an arms race so the females, because they want the strongest males
of the species to have babies with, they've developed over time to become better wrestlers.
The strongest females are the ones who can get away from the dudes quicker and then they
choose their mate.
They make sure that they're mating with the singular strongest man they can come across
and they're passing on their wrestling genes to their female descendants.
So we've seen this within our lifetime and what Nicholas said is he goes, "Let's take
sea monkeys."
He didn't use the term sea monkey over and over again, that's me.
I just love that word.
Let's take some brine from the Salt Lakes in Utah because we know that they're there
and because these eggs last for so long and because we know the geological history of
these different areas, I'm going to gather eggs from 1985, I'm going to gather eggs from
1996, and I'm going to gather eggs from 2007 and we're going to hatch them.
We're going to put them in water, we're going to watch them hatch and then I'm going to
introduce them to each other.
It's a little dinner party.
He goes, "What happens if you took a 1985 female who has not evolved to be a strong
wrestler, she has not been giving offspring off this whole time.
Her offspring has not been getting stronger and stronger and stronger to counteract the
physical strength and the grasping power of the male sea monkeys.
If you take a female from 1985 and introduced it to a male from 2007 who has the little
hands, better articulation who has more strength.
If you introduce those two groups and they're separated by about 160 generations, you had
a 12% chance that the female would die.
She couldn't wrestle out of the grip of this guy.
He was too strong.
He was killing the women and not only that, this was during copulation, the woman would
either be killed just by the strength or the dude would never let go, like even after impregnating
it.
So, just hanging out, now the dude, now the dude's just swimming around doing his own
thing.
The woman couldn't feed.
The woman could not escape to go and raise the children, to eat, to just get a second
alone.
They died, 12% chance.
So what I thought about that, like if I went back in time, let's pass the princess, let's
pass the European Fifedom Princess.
If I went back in time and banged a cave woman, I think she would probably kill me.
I think she would probably physically be so much stronger than me, right?
She sure she'd probably be enamored by my charm even though she can't understand a
word I'm saying.
I keep holding up my phone and like, huh, huh?
She would probably physically be able to overpower me.
I'm sure a cave woman, a Neanderthal woman, could overpower a modern man.
So I don't know how well it correlates to humans, right?
But I imagine like if I went, I'm just, if I had sex through the ages, I'm sure by the
time like the Egyptians were walking around and you had like Cleopatra, I think we would
have sex and that would be fun because the only thing about Cleopatra she was played
by was Elizabeth Taylor.
I think like there are certain time periods where I could have sex with women in the past
and not die.
And then you, I think you would start to hit a point and I'm sure some pilgrim woman,
I don't know why these women are all trying to kill me.
I'm not saying that they would ride me so hard.
But you know what I mean?
Like I'm trying to think like at what point would I as a 21st century man, because I think
like pilgrim, let's take pilgrims for example, if you had a pilgrim dude and a pilgrim woman,
that pilgrim dude is stronger than that pilgrim woman.
But I'm going to bet a dollar to a donut that a pilgrim woman is stronger than me.
Because she's out there with like pitchforks and stuff, throwing hay, finding Martin Lawrence
in the hay.
She's like, get out of there.
Sewing, I imagine that's really good for your forearms, right?
They didn't have sewing machines, so she's constantly sewing stuff.
She's like, oh, another flag.
How many of these do I need?
50?
Oh man.
I'm sure like she, I'm sure like pilgrim women were pretty like, I wouldn't say like
I yoked, but I'm sure one of them could take me to Christmas, basically what I'm saying.
The European princess, I don't think could kill me.
Let's go forward in time.
You're like, no, Jason, please stop.
Go to the disturbing story.
This is actually creepier than I thought it would be.
I wonder if I went forward in time, would I be able to have sex with women from the future?
Because I imagine that they would be like frail and stuff because they wouldn't be doing
nothing.
I imagine robots to sew all those flags.
You just have robots walking around.
I could probably beat up a dude from the future.
I bet you there is that moment where you could look, you could pretty much take any warrior
from the past and they could beat me up.
And then you could probably take any peasant from the past and they could probably beat
me up.
But in the future, like when everyone's kind of just like walking around being all philosophical
and stuff and being like, what, robots do everything.
I just get to sit and do art.
Dude, I would.
I would control.
I would be like Wesley Snipes and Demolition Man and just be walking around pushing everybody.
I think I could take them.
And I think that's where the danger would be.
Like if I went far enough in the future, who knows how frail the human body will be, right?
So I probably could have sex with people from the past is what I'm saying.
I think I could be in danger.
I don't think they would be in danger.
But basically, I'm just about to warn women of the future.
Look out.
You might be killed if I have sex with you.
I'm talking like hundreds of thousands of years that future women that I meet from here
on out.
Don't be worried.
I'm talking about like evolutionary wise.
Is it possible that the huge, because I think that's kind of the theory, right?
One of the theories is that great aliens are humans from the future.
The human body becomes more and more frail.
So if I went into the future, that might be cool because I get to like float around on
Saturn and stuff.
But I would be super celibate.
I'm like, oh man, I don't get to have any sex.
And they're like, well, we got these sex robots.
And I was like, OK, that'll work.
And then I get crushed by one.
So I guess the moral of the story is be careful who you have sex with.
This is a really long PSA because people in the past could probably physically kill you
if things gone wrong.
In people in the future, you might accidentally kill them.
Let's go ahead, banked sassy pants.
Let's go ahead and move away from that fascinating story slash fascinating look at my psyche.
I'm going to toss you the keys to the carbonar copter.
We're leaving behind the salt lakes.
Take us all the way out to Lynchburg, Virginia.
This is an interesting story.
And it was sent to me by someone on Twitter named psych for fun.
I'll admit.
First off, thank you very much psych for fun.
When psych for fun first sent me this story, I thought I was being trolled.
This story is so unbelievable.
I thought this might have been a parody news website.
Like I actually started googling some more and I was like, what, this is this is insane.
This story is nuts.
Like I skimmed it at first and I was like, this can't be real.
This can't be as bad as this article is making it out to be.
And the more I dug in the way it is true, it's horrifying.
And I'm going to play a piece of audio in a bit.
I will warn you before it comes up.
It is terrifying.
And I debated whether or not to play it for you.
And the reason why I want to play it for you is because it will make you mad.
It will infuriate you at the Lynchburg police department in Lynchburg, Virginia.
Let's go ahead and get this story started.
And again, psych for fun.
Thank you so much for sending this over.
Also want to give a shout out to Noreen Turin.
She covered this for ABC 13 news.
That's pretty much the only media outlet covering this.
This story is shocking.
It is graphic.
It is disturbing.
And it will make you mad.
April 14th, 2022.
Very very recent story.
In Lynchburg, Virginia, there's this young man named Johnny Cashman.
He's 38 years old.
Johnny Cashman, Jr.
Johnny's family, they lived in Maine.
He was living in Virginia.
And even though they were apart, he stayed in contact with them every single day.
He talked or texted his mother every single day because he struggled with depression and
alcoholism.
Two very horrible things to be dealing with.
And he knew that his family was worried about him.
He was worried about himself and keeping in touch with his family was a way to let them
know that he was still there.
He still loved them.
So April 14th talks to his mom.
Everything's totally fine.
April 15th, he doesn't contact them.
April 16th doesn't contact them.
April 17th doesn't contact them.
They're very very concerned about what could be happening with Johnny.
So on April 19th, 2022, his mom calls the Lynchburg police and asks, "Can you do a welfare
check on my son?"
He normally talks to me every single day.
I haven't heard from him in five days now.
So they do.
They go to his apartment and they do a welfare check on him.
And then they call the mother back and they give just the worst news that any parent could
hear Johnny's dead.
Johnny has passed away in his apartment.
The father starts talking to the police and the father goes, "So what happened?
What happened with my son?
Was he murdered?
Was there any sort of violence?"
Like he specifically asked those questions.
So the police said to the father, "It looked like he died of natural causes.
Like that's what it appears to us that he just died of natural causes.
He was just kind of slumped over as if he had died instantly."
The father goes, "Totally natural?"
You're like, "Yeah, totally natural causes.
We're not going to do an autopsy on him.
We know how he died.
It just happens, you know.
We're not planning on doing an autopsy on him.
Sometimes these things happen.
We know it's sad for the family, but it's just medical illness."
The father goes, "Are you sure?"
The police said, "Yeah, the case is closed.
It's just natural causes."
So the family from Maine contacted a mortuary service in Lynchburg.
They had the body picked up from the morgue and cremated.
And the ashes sent back to Johnny's family.
On April 29th, Johnny's ex-girlfriend and the girl's mother, the girlfriend's mother,
will call her Trisha.
She didn't give her real name.
That's totally fine.
I'm just making the name up.
Trisha, they contacted Johnny's family and said, "Hey, you know, I have some of my stuff
at Johnny's apartment.
Do you mind if I go in there and get this stuff?"
And the family said, "Sure.
No problem at all.
You can do that."
So Trisha and her mom show up at Johnny's apartment and what they saw boggles the mind.
Trisha walked in to a blood bath.
There are bloody fingerprints on the wall.
There's blood streaks across the chair.
There's blood on the floor.
And in the bathroom, there is so much blood.
It looked, I thought I was being trolled.
It is like a human exploded like a Pennywise balloon and not just blood.
It's blood and fecal matter in this pool on the base of the toilet.
Like just if someone just blew up, it's all over the bathroom.
Trisha gets freaked out, obviously, by this, right?
She was told that he died a natural death out of some sort of medical thing.
Now, listen, you can have gastrointestinal issues, right?
One of the ways that you die, like they always say this, when you're taking too much ibuprofen,
you can rot a hole in your stomach.
You begin bleeding out your stomach, your poop's black.
You're dying a very, very short period of time.
It's very painful.
You have to get to the hospital right away.
He has an alcohol problem.
Any sort of medication he takes can cause stomach bleeding.
So it is possible, right?
Medical illness, but the blood's everywhere.
Now if that was it, if that was it, if it was just these photographs, these horrific photographs,
the police could argue, "Yeah, I know it's gross, and I know it's horrific, but you've
got to understand, we go to crime scenes all the time, and we've seen people die from
murder, we've seen suicides, and we've seen natural causes, and sometimes natural causes
are super gross because someone's running around the apartment.
They're freaking out, they're vomiting blood."
That's what the police were saying, that a lot of it looked like someone was vomiting
up blood, and then they die.
Not just this neat, tidy thing like Elvis on a toilet.
It can be very graphic.
If that was it, if it was just the fact that we had this young man who bled seriously,
seriously bled out in his own apartment, that's not what's at stake here.
That's not the only piece of evidence.
What happens next is jaw-dropping.
The fact that it exists, and the fact that the police continue to just sit on this story.
Check this out.
She leaves the apartment, right?
She sees all this stuff, she's horrified, she comes out of the apartment.
She just happens to run into a neighbor out of this apartment complex, and she tells him,
"Oh my God, I just came out of the apartment, there's blood everywhere.
I thought it was natural causes."
That's what I was told too, natural causes, but I mean, it just looks like a crime scene
in there, and it's just disgusting.
The neighbor goes, "Well, Trisha, I have a door cam.
I have a camera that records everything in the hallway.
It won't let us know what happened in Johnny's apartment, but maybe it'll give us some idea.
Let's take a look."
So the video footage is basically three clips.
The first clip is Johnny walking up the stairs, and this is about like 3.03 in the afternoon.
You see Johnny, and this is on April 14th, the last day he talked to his family.
The footage is just a long stairwell leading up to a little hallway, and then to the right
is Johnny's apartment.
That's the whole shot.
You just see the stairways kind of descend into darkness.
Going back to the first floor, presumably.
The first piece of video footage you see is Johnny walking up the stairs.
Now this is footage of Johnny the day he died.
We know for sure this is the day that he died for what's about to come up.
He's walking up the stairs, and this is not what a man who's about to poop out a gallon
of blood in a bunch of vehicle matter would walk like.
I don't have any scientific experience.
I don't have any scientific experience on what you would walk like.
He's just John Talley walking up the stairs.
He goes in the apartment.
Now what's interesting is he showed the neighbor when the police were there.
He told the police, "Yeah, I also have a camera," and he says, "We watched some footage."
But when Noreen was doing the interview on him, he goes, "Listen, I don't know exactly
what footage we watched," and I'll tell you this right now.
We didn't have any audio.
He didn't have any Bluetooth speakers or anything hooked up, so we were just watching
the footage.
But even if, and we'll allow that, right, the police did not hear the audio that you're
about to hear.
They've heard it now.
They heard it back when Noreen started talking about this, when the family started playing
this audio for the police.
The police, the Lynchburg Police Department of Virginia, has still been sitting on this
story.
Absolute incompetence.
They are not investigating this.
You have video footage of Johnny walking up the stairs and going into his apartment.
That's at 3.03, at 3.11, just eight minutes after he enters the apartment.
Now, this is very, very graphic audio, so if you want, jump ahead about two, three minutes.
Same camera angle.
You're looking down a stairway.
To the right is Johnny's apartment door.
You hear this audio coming from Johnny's apartment.
What the fuck?
One minute after Johnny entered his apartment, we have audio of an assault.
It's a video of a murder.
Same shot all the way down the staircase, Johnny's door to the right.
You hear that sound coming out of Johnny's apartment.
If you skip that part, here's the transcript.
It says, "Dude, what the F?
What are you doing, man?
Yo, what the F, dude?"
Then you hear banging noises and you hear someone yelling, "Stop multiple times."
Eight minutes.
Eight minutes passed watching that video footage.
They have all this footage in this article on ABC 13.
Eight minutes after Johnny walked in, seven minutes after you hear those noises, a man,
an unidentified man whose face is clearly visible on camera.
This man on video leaves the apartment, walks all the way downstairs, turns around, walks
back up, covers his hand with the sleeve of his jacket, wipes his fingerprints off of
the doorknob, walks back down the stairs.
And then there's a few moments of silence and you begin to hear Johnny yell from inside
his apartment, "Help.
Help.
Help."
So the family contacts the police and they go, "You told us that this was a natural death
and we cremated his body.
All of that evidence is gone.
All of it."
And this is an actual quote from the detective regarding this.
You said it was okay.
We could cremate the body.
In this case, close.
The detective said, "What I was trying to convey was it was a medical emergency and
I was talking to your mom and I tried to clarify what I said originally and explain what I
meant by the medical emergency being vomiting blood everywhere uncontrollably."
He is not saying we were wrong.
He is not saying sorry we need to investigate this as a murder.
He was saying, "Oh sorry, miscommunication bro.
Sorry you destroyed that evidence when we said case closed."
Here's a quote from the notice of the medical examiner case record.
"I actually got this screenshot from a really cool video done on this by a channel called
Analyze This."
I'll put that in the show notes.
They really went over a lot of stuff.
One of the things they said was he wasn't slumped over.
He was flat on his back in the living room.
They really went over all these documents.
It's a cool channel.
It doesn't have a lot of subscribers.
So if you're into true crime, it's a good place to check out.
I got this quote from the screenshot.
It said, "Blood with fecal matter mixed in found around home likely gastrointestinal
bleed per investigators.
No trauma, no drugs.
Nothing suspicious."
So they looked at this guy.
They saw the blood and the poop and go, "I must have just blood and pooped himself to
death."
Which happens, you rot your stomach out, right?
The family says though that he had just had a recent medical checkup in January.
He had no gastrointestinal issues.
Too much ibuprofen can do a lot of damage in a very short time period.
It's not going to make you scream out what the FU do and do.
Stop, stop, stop.
And then a guy wipes his fingerprints off of a doorknob.
Ibuprofen doesn't do that.
Ibuprofen doesn't cover its tracks.
Now what's so interesting about this is I was digging and that's the end of the story.
The police have completely been like, "Well, we're kind of doing an ongoing thing now because
now we got a bunch of egg on our face because it turns out that they're not actually even
saying we got egg on our face that we were wrong or anything like that."
And not only that, they're actually intentionally or incompetently misleading people because
what happened was I started looking more into this.
On May 2nd, 2022, they started the police released images from the stairwell and they
said, "We're looking to talk to this man."
They identified him in the video at Stephen Church from Elizabeth Town, Tennessee.
On May 23rd, they located him and he provided a statement.
There was no arrest.
And I was like, "What in the world?
You have video footage of this guy entering the apartment.
You hear a guy screaming for help and we see him wiping his fingerprints off the door.
We see that."
What is his statement?
What was the statement he gave to the police?
What is the clarification?
Now the police said they were specifically looking for him.
They said that he was, quote, "seeing leaving an apartment just before another man's death
from apparent medical complications," unquote.
So they're still sticking with that.
They're still saying that this dude died of medical complications.
So let's play devil's advocate for a second.
Let's play devil's advocate for a second.
Adding this in because I'm editing the episode and I thought, "Let's look at the other side."
Because here's the thing.
In the articles, it never specifically says it is Johnny's voice going, "What the F, man?
Stop, stop.
What the F?"
Never specifically says that.
We know he's the one yelling, "Help, help," because he's the only person in the apartment.
After Steven leaves, there's probably about a minute of Steven walking down the stairs,
walking back up, wiping his fingerprints off the door knob.
It's so ridiculous.
I mean, the devil's advocate thing will do it, but we have video footage of Steven church
leaving the apartment right after we hear these noises, right?
We hear somebody, either Steven or Johnny, scream out, "What the F, man?
Stop, stop, stop."
Steven walks down the stairs, comes back up, wipes his fingerprints off the door knob, and
then walks away and then probably about 30 seconds pass and you hear a voice from inside
the apartment, which is Johnny.
It's definitely going, "Help, help."
So let's play devil's advocate.
It's just because I don't want to accuse a man of murder and get sued.
Let's play devil's advocate.
It's possible that this was the scenario.
Steven was in the apartment.
Johnny walks into the apartment.
A couple minutes later, we hear, "What the F?
Stop it, stop it."
And I guess it's possible.
I guess anything's possible.
I talk about ghosts all the time and banging princesses.
That voice was actually Steven.
And what was going on was Johnny walked in and began vomiting blood everywhere.
And Steven's going, "Stop it, dude.
Stop.
Stop."
And all the banging you hear and everything is just Johnny running around the apartment
vomiting blood and pooping out blood.
That's the devil's advocate thing, that it wasn't a murder, it wasn't assault, it was
a medical thing, even if that's the case, even if that's the case.
So if you just saw someone running around their apartment vomiting up blood, your reaction
is to leave them while they're still alive because you hear Johnny clearly yell out,
"Help."
Your reaction, I mean, I guess you would want to get away from somebody if they were vomiting
blood, but think about it.
Steven, let's say that devil's advocate, it's a medical emergency.
Steven then leaves the apartment very, very calmly, walks down the stairs, walks back
up the stairs, appears to wipe his fingerprints off the doorknob, covers his hand up with
his jacket, wipes the doorknob, goes back down the stairs.
You just watch someone have a medical emergency.
You're not calling 911, you're not knocking on the neighbor's door, you're not alerting
anyone, your calmness can be, you just walk away.
And the police go, "Yeah, we're looking for him because he was there around the time or
before the time of a medical emergency that may result in a..."
The devil's advocate theory, while possible, right, Johnny walked in with this gastrointestinal
disorder.
It's possible, but that shows such callousness as well, that someone who you were letting
stay at your apartment could watch you vomit blood and then just very calmly leave and
not contact the authority.
Remember, it took five days before his body was even found, the family in Maine cult.
So that's kind of what the narrative is.
The police are going with this story, with this medical condition story, and it's absolutely
nuts.
It's absolutely nuts.
Now, I'm adding this part in because I was editing it and I was thinking, "Okay, I got
to do the devil's advocate thing, even though this is a conspiracy theory podcast."
And I do think at this point there is a conspiracy theory to cover up this crime.
Let's do the other side.
I also want to make a correction as I was editing this podcast.
I was continuing to read articles because this totally fascinates me.
I say articles, really, it's just Noreen's article reprinted in different websites.
There's not a lot of people talking about this.
And as I was working on this, I see another podcast, a much bigger podcast than mine called
Generation Y, I think it's called, covered this just a couple of weeks ago.
So I didn't know that when I was doing this story, and I'm glad that other people are
covering this.
They're starting to.
That's cool.
I found that out while I was editing this.
I was kind of looking around.
I was trying to get that audio clip that I played for you.
I was like, "Jason, I wish you had it."
And I found that another podcast had covered this story.
Good.
Awesome.
More people should know about this.
But while I have this time, I wanted to make a correction.
The neighbor, it's a minor correction.
The neighbor was a woman.
I kept referring to her as a him.
That was just me.
I didn't catch that the first time when I was writing my notes down.
I put it down as a he.
So that was my mistake.
So it's either incompetence or it's a cover-up.
Maybe a little bit of both.
I think generally, I think they probably were incompetent.
They walked in, they saw this guy.
He's an alcoholic.
He had run-ins with the law.
They knew this guy.
Who cares?
He's just some drunk.
You know what really pisses me off about this story when I read it?
I thought, "That's me."
Right?
You know what I mean?
I don't know what this guy did.
This guy could have done some disgusting crimes.
I don't know.
But even then, I go, "That's me, man.
I'm just a dude.
I'm just a guy floating through life.
Maybe that's you too.
Maybe you're Johnny as well.
And if something happened to you, the police, it's just something that happens at 3 p.m.
on this cops afternoon, whatever.
He probably made a couple of jokes about it back at the station when about his day.
Now, if it had just been a natural death, fine, dude, whatever.
Like I understand that.
But it wasn't a natural death.
It was not a natural death.
You heard that audio, and I played that audio because it pisses me off.
He was pleading for help.
You know what I mean?
Like, that's...
He's one of us.
He's just a guy going through life, facing problems, fighting his demons, sometimes winning,
sometimes losing.
And he died brutally, and the police rode it off like nothing.
Pisses me off.
Pisses me off to no end.
I get it.
Listen, I get in trouble whenever I say this, but police are people too.
You know, sometimes that job gets boring, sometimes you check out, just like when you're
working retail or working at a corporate office.
Some days you come in and you're not doing 100%.
You're doing like 50 at best.
You've been doing the job too long.
You're underappreciated.
You don't get the raise.
You probably have personal problems at home.
And the same way that you half-ass stuff at your job cops half-ass stuff at theirs.
It happens because they're people.
But the difference is that when I half-ass at my job, murderers don't go free.
And if I did half-ass at my job and I got caught because of who I am, I don't know.
I'd say, I'm sorry.
Like, yeah, we didn't have the audio at the time.
I just saw the video footage of one guy walking in and 10 minutes later, one guy walking out.
I mean, like, I didn't really think of it.
We don't know what footage they have either.
The neighbor says they took some of the footage, but I don't know actually what he recorded.
But he just walked in.
He got a welfare call.
They said they had to go back multiple times to get into the apartment because he wasn't
there.
He wasn't answering the door.
Finally, they got a hold of the manager.
They went in.
They found him dead.
This was a whole day ordeal.
And I get it, dude.
They're burned out.
Then own up to the mistake.
That's what pisses me off even more.
I get it.
Not everyone's 100% all the time.
I do.
But when you make that mistake, when you realize you have the audio recording of something
happening to them, who knows what?
For all we know, they made them swallow a ton of ibuprofen.
It doesn't sound like it.
It sounds like a man being beaten to death.
When you make a mistake, you own up to it, right?
And you double down your efforts and you put out, "Find this guy."
But see, if they do that, the police don't want to publicize this case because then all
of the stuff that goes with it, they have to admit, "Yeah, we dropped the ball.
Yeah, we did this.
Yeah, we did that."
And they have this investigation.
Hopefully they're having an internal affairs investigation into all of this.
But you know what I mean?
Like now, it could just get even more messy for them, but I don't care about them.
Johnny's one of us.
He's just somebody living life.
Just a dude who died brutally and the police rode it off as a natural cause.
Think about all the pieces that had to fall into place for this to be uncovered.
The ex-girlfriend had to show up and the apartment hadn't been cleaned up by the manager to be
re-rented out.
She had to have...
That was the big part was the ex-girlfriend showing up because she knew the neighbor.
See?
And he goes, "Yeah, I got video footage of this."
What if he didn't have the camera?
If one of those two things were missing, his family would have just been like, "Johnny,
you know, poor Johnny, he struggled through his whole life and then he had this medical
event and he died.
He died far away from us.
I wish he was with us."
But now that family's embroiled in a murder mystery with a suspect that the cops don't
really seem that keen on catching.
Absolutely bizarre.
Absolutely infuriating.
It's sad, right?
Sad.
Sad story.
Young man dies.
It's always sad.
Young people die, you know?
Absolute incompetence, followed up by a cover-up.
The Lynchburg police of Lynchburg, Virginia, should be ashamed of themselves.
But the problem is, they're not.
Because if they were ashamed of themselves, they would do whatever it took to catch this
guy.
I love being proved wrong.
I really do.
When it comes to stuff like this, I would love it.
They catch him tomorrow.
I love being proved wrong.
So Lynchburg police, please.
Prove me wrong about you.
I love you.
(upbeat music)