Can your boss force you to get an exorcism?
A little girl goes missing and the culprit may be a character from one of our previous
episodes.
And then finally we take a look at the story of the Loveland Frogman, or Frogmonster cut.
And then we take a look at the Loveland Frog.
A cryptid who has friends, a magic wand, and quite the adventure until the police open fire
on him today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We're coming up to episode 200.
Episode 200 of Dead Rabbit Radio might be some surprises in the store.
You don't know.
I don't even know.
That's how much of a surprise it may be.
Or simple lack of being prepared.
I think when the 100th episode came around I just was like, "Oh here's a normal episode."
And then afterwards I was like, "Oh man I should have done something cool for that."
Or the way my memory works.
We may have done something totally awesome for episode 100 and I've just forgotten right
now.
But we're on episode, I think this is episode 193, 194.
But we're close to 200, so that's awesome.
We're also close to the end of season 4.
We're going to be going into season 5.
I don't know if I'm going to take a week off.
Normally I do.
I think I've kind of found a bit of peace with certain things for the show I can't control.
Or I'm like, "I just want to take a little bit longer for me to go into the YouTube system
and add the tags."
I used to be really religious about going in there and putting the tags up the first
night and hitting all these buttons and da da da da da.
And it was totally wearing me out.
And it was taking like an hour and a half a night to do all this back in stuff that
you guys don't even see.
It helps other people find the videos, but I was totally freaking out about it and now
I'm just like, "I've made my peace with that."
Because the show is fun to do and that stuff sucks.
I know it's important to do, but it was just taking up way too much of my time.
Responding to the comments, I love doing that.
I love responding to comments.
Sometimes that takes me a while too.
But you got all the back in stuff I don't like.
But anyways, I guess I should say I really appreciate it when you guys do market the
show for me.
Because that's great.
Telling your friends and you're like, "Jason, you won't even do it yourself."
I do.
I actually put up flyers and I do a lot of word of mouth stuff.
YouTube algorithm sucks.
Anyways, I love it that you guys get the word out, wink wink, and I have flyers that you
can print out just like I do.
Wherever you frequent, you can get those images in the show notes in the links below.
I really appreciate that.
We have a merch store too, but there's just something real punk rock about walking around
with flyers.
Oh yeah, and you can wear a dead rabbit shirt while you're doing it.
But yeah, just walking around with flyers passing them out to people.
I love doing that stuff.
Okay, that's enough of the back in stuff.
Let's go ahead and get started with the episode here.
Now, the first story we're going to talk about actually just happened.
Well, I should, let me clarify that.
I just found out about it, which there's probably a difference between those two things.
We're going, I didn't know this place was real by the way.
We're going to Kentucky, I knew that place was real.
We're going to Kentucky, we're going to the city of hazard, Kentucky.
Now is that where the Dukes of Hazard took place?
I'm pretty sure, but I thought the Dukes of Hazard was spelt with two Zs.
Apparently this one's just one Z like the real, but the Dukes of Hazard town, we're
going, Dead Rabbit Radio is going to the town of Dukes of Hazard.
If you don't know what the Dukes of Hazard is, then I hold my head for the childhood
memories that you didn't share with me.
Dukes of Hazard was, it was a story about basically vigilantes in a race car.
Were they vigilantes?
They basically just didn't do what the cops said.
It was a small town with like this corrupt sheriff.
It was super bizarre because it was like this corrupt Southern sheriff who was basically
just like bullying people around and then the Dukes brothers, the Dukes brothers, Bo
and Luke, Duke was it?
Bo and I don't know.
But anyways, the Dukes brothers, you're like Jason just gets into the stupid story, but
the Dukes brothers basically were like Robin Hood type characters and then Daisy Duke walked
around that was their cousin I believe and she wore Daisy Dukes.
She wore the shorts that just came up right to her butt cheeks.
So anyways, that's the story of the Dukes of Hazard.
Oh, I also should mention they had a Confederate flag on the top of their car and when they
honked their horn it played Dixie.
So yeah, I guess I should throw that in there too, but they weren't racist.
They weren't.
They just really liked the Confederate flag in the song Dixie.
So anyways, anyways, we're in Hazard County.
Sorry, no, that's the show.
Well damn Duke boys, don't know what's going.
Okay, okay.
So we're in Kentucky.
We're in the city of Hazard.
Now there's a dude there named Jason Fields and let me say too, this is all alleged.
This is all alleged.
This is going through court right now.
So Jason Fields works at a hotel and he's talking to his boss, his boss's name Sharon
Linden.
Jason goes, Hey, it's on her and you know, I'm going through some marital trouble right
now.
I'm getting a divorce and Sharon's like, really?
And he's like, yeah, yeah, I just, I don't think things are going to work out between
me and my wife and that damn Roscoe Peacow train stole my girl.
And so Sharon go, okay, okay, that's the lab.
Trust me, that's the last hazard joke because I don't know how many of you guys get the
references.
Anyway, so Sharon Linden says, you know, I've had trouble in my life as well.
I had trouble with them Duke boys.
So she goes, I had trouble in my life as well.
What you need is a cleansing.
Jason's like, huh, that's kind of weird.
Now Sharon is Jason's boss and he kind of is like, no, no, I'm fine.
You know, he has his own religious beliefs.
He doesn't really know what the cleansing is.
He doesn't really want to know what the cleansing is, but Sharon goes, well, it's kind of like
an exorcism and you get this cleansing.
You basically, your marital problems are being caused by demons.
We got to cleanse the demons from you, Jason.
We got to get them out of you.
Now he says that that made him feel uncomfortable, but whatever.
So he'd simply politely declined the offer and went about his business and she kept saying,
Jason, you need to get the demons out of you.
You need to get cleansed.
I've had four cleansings myself.
Look at me.
I'm fine, which I would have to wonder why you would need four of them.
Not just the first one doesn't work.
There's there is it like washing clothes like you got to keep working the stand out.
There are like a couple of demons still clanging on to you or does she keep doing bad stuff
and the demons keep finding her again?
I don't know.
But anyways, at one point, Jason Fields, this was kind of the straw that broke the camel's
back.
There was two straws.
One, one day he walked into work.
Imagine the scenario.
You walk into work and you see your super weirdo religious boss standing there in the corner
with her back to you like the Blair Witch.
No, she's standing there and she's like, I'm so glad you've come to work.
And then you see like 15 people who are members of her church.
You've never met him before, but you can just tell their members of her church because
they get in front of you and start praying in front of you.
And she's like, we are cleansing you.
We are cleansing you.
I don't know if she actually said that, but they were cleansing him and he got really
uncomfortable.
It'd be super bizarre.
I mean, I get it.
Like sometimes people at work will be like, you know, I'm praying for you.
And I'm like, okay, no, I appreciate that.
That's cool.
But it's totally different if someone like bows down and actually it'd be kind of cool.
Someone bow down in front of you and started praying.
But 15 of them, especially if I wasn't down with their religious practice would be a little
weird.
But really what ended his employment there?
What finally made him quit?
Was one day his boss came in with a questionnaire and says, you need to fill this out.
He's like, oh, okay, it must be like for benefits or something.
Am I getting life insurance?
And she's just like, fill it out.
Oh, you're getting life insurance.
Eternal life insurance.
And then she just walked away and he's like, oh, great.
This is what some of the questions were on the survey.
His boss gave him, were you a planned child?
Were you conceived out of wedlock?
Those kind of go together.
Have you ever visited heathen temples?
He's like, yes, stone temple pilot saw him in like 95.
Were they even around back then?
Do you have any witches?
Here's another question.
Do you have any witches such as good luck kitchen witches in your home?
What is that?
Is that a thing, a good luck kitchen witch?
Is it like an elf on a shelf, but it's all year round and it's just like this crone who
hangs out in your kitchen other than your ex-wife?
Duh-duh-ch.
To your knowledge, was there, here's the other question.
To your, I'm not asking you this directly.
To your knowledge, was there evidence of lust in your family line?
That's kind of vague and probably because they've had kids.
They may be using the biblical term lust, but if you just ask, has anyone in your family
ever been lusty ever since they've had sex multiple times?
That's why I exist.
She asked also, do you have lustful thoughts?
Do you frequently masturbate?
Check check for me.
And have you ever sexually fantasized about an animal?
Weird.
That one seems probably the weirdest one there.
Because it just kind of popped up.
Everything else you're like, yeah, I can understand someone.
But why that?
That's super specific.
But anyways, so those are just some of the questions.
He didn't turn it in.
He actually quit, suitor, and they're now facing a lawsuit.
But this is in America, and I'm sure it's true in most countries, there's a thing called
hostile work environment.
When your boss is forcing you to get exercised, that is pretty much the definition of a hostile
work environment.
You can't talk about, you can't really make religion part of your job unless your job
is the pope or priest.
But you can't really.
And so no, she's going to lose this lawsuit.
She'll probably lose the lawsuit if he kept that form, which is what he should have done.
Weird story.
Weird, weird story.
Okay, so our next story actually is a real short one.
Now I don't know, I announced it at the beginning of the week and then I cut it out for time,
but this was supposed to be Missing Persons Week.
And now we're like three episodes in.
And I was like, oh yeah, I edited that out.
Because that first episode was like an hour long, and the second episode was like an hour
long.
And I was like, I'm going to go on and remove whole chunks of the show.
So some of it got lost.
On yesterday's episode during the Pombero, I talked about this little guy named the Yisi
Yacera.
He's also a little troll man who lives in South America.
I'm just saying it now because I cut it out yesterday.
He's a little troll man who lives in South America.
What he does is he kidnaps kids and plays with them and then he licks them on the face
and gives them epilepsy and makes them mentally disabled.
Or drowns them.
Pick your poison.
You're like, Jason, that's incredibly out of place for this episode, but I just wanted
to fit that fact in somewhere because it's actually in the show notes for yesterday's
episode totally got cut for time.
But this story here is part of Missing Persons Week, which you're now just being made aware
of.
Very short story, tragic, but it's a call back to a cryptid or a ghost that we have
covered in previous episodes.
We're going to Chisholm, Minnesota.
And there we see the grieving family.
You're like, great Jason, another one of these ones.
And there we meet the grieving family of the Warners.
It's June 14th, 2003.
Liana Warner has just gone missing.
They can't find her.
Little five-year-old girl.
She goes missing.
She went to walk to her friend's house a couple streets away, which she had made this walk
multiple times before.
But she gets to her friend's house, there's no one home, and then she starts walking back
home and that's the last time anyone sees her in the neighborhood.
Totally gone.
And I know you think, in five years old, who's walking through the town by themselves, and
it's weird.
But it was normal when I was growing up, and it was normal every single time she did this
journey this time she just happened to go missing.
Huge search party, they can't find her at all.
Now the cops said, listen, after they keep searching and searching and searching, they
go, we think it's foul play.
We think if a five-year-old set out on her own, we would have found her by now.
There's only so many places you can go into town.
We've got this massive party looking for her.
We think she was kidnapped.
So that was the path of investigation they were taking.
They do find a child's footprint near a lake.
They drained the lake.
Nothing.
And they're like, okay, well, back to square one.
But we will keep looking for this kid.
But what's weird about this is that you have, generally when children go missing, you have
the usual suspects.
All of a sudden you find out your town is full of perverts because the cops immediately
start going through their logs and they go, this guy was arrested for this.
This guy was arrested for this.
So they talk to one guy.
He had been caught with child pornography.
They go and investigate him.
He kills himself.
But the cops go, we don't think he had anything to do with her disappearance.
We think he killed himself because he was about to go to prison for child porn.
So other people in town think he was murdered.
But a weirdo suspect.
Another weirdo suspect, a guy who kidnapped two girls a couple years earlier.
He was writing in his journal.
Who keeps journals?
He was writing in his journal saying, I'm afraid I'm going to get blamed for the kidnapping
of Leanne.
But you know, he was, they investigated him and he wasn't real suspect.
She's never been found.
But that's not what made me want to cover this story.
This is the weird part.
Before her disappearance, Leanne comes home with a case full of Barbies and clothing.
She puts it on the table.
Opens it up.
Her mom's like, where'd you get those?
Where'd you get those Barbies?
Those aren't yours.
Did you get this from a friend?
And she's like, no.
The old lady gave them to me.
That's weird.
And then about a week before she goes missing, her parents see her packing a suitcase.
They go, Leanne, what are you doing?
She's like, oh, I'm getting ready to go live with my new family.
Shuts the suitcase.
Now the police have said that they don't think that that has anything to do with their disappearance.
But when I read that, I immediately, my mind went back to the candy lady of Texas.
The woman who was supposedly leaving candy on kids' window sills, enticing them to come
out.
And she didn't hide outside your window, and once you reach for candy, her clawed hands
grab you and pull you up.
She heard, the goal was to get you out of the house to come with her willingly.
She wasn't a monster underneath your bed.
She was like a monster in society, again, if she existed at all.
But I think it's interesting that you have that same parallel hair.
You have this old lady who this girl met, and she gave her these toys.
Here, you can have these toys.
Could have been totally innocent, but could have also been a total creep weirdo.
Given her these toys.
And then being like, you should come stay with me.
I'll be your grandma, and you'll have a new grandpa and a new mama.
It would be so fun.
And the girl's like, that does sound like fun.
We don't know how many times this little girl, Leanna, interacted with this old lady, whether
it was a one-off thing, where some old lady was throwing away a bunch of stuff, and she
goes, hey kid, come here.
Come here.
You want some Barbies?
Or if it was a grooming process.
But what I know is this girl got these Barbie dolls from someone the family didn't know.
A week before she disappears, packing a suitcase to go visit a family the family doesn't know.
And then she disappears.
I just think it's creepy, because it's almost like, what if the candy lady of Texas isn't
so much like a serial killer or a ghost or an urban legend or whatever.
What if it's just like an archetype?
What if it's a blueprint for how old, creepy women can kidnap kids?
Like they can't overpower them.
That's not in their, they don't have the ability to do that, because their bones are already
made of like dust.
Their skin is this thick as paper.
But I, okay, that's, I'm talking about mummies at that point.
But you know what I mean?
Like, an adult, a healthy adult can overpower a kid.
This is getting grim, but an old, the older and weaker you are, the more you have to use
guile to get them.
There may be candy ladies all over the world who aren't trying to be like, come check out
this puppy or jump out of the bushes.
They could just be leaving a trail of toys or sweets or just words of encouragement to
finally get that kid out of the safety of their own home.
But let's go ahead and move on to a fun story.
A fun story.
It does involve a couple things getting blown away, but it's a lot more fun than that last
story.
This story was actually in a roundabout way a request on Twitter, because I asked if we
had a cryptid Olympics who should be involved in it.
And the first people to respond were on Twitter, the cafe in diner, which is cafe underscore
and underscore diner.
I really, really recommend checking them out.
It's a really cool Twitter account.
And then also Jester, who also is a follower of cafe and diner.
Yeah, check it out.
I've recommended that Twitter account a couple times.
They got some really cool things going on there that I think is just right for the fans
of the show.
But they said, "Lovelyn Frog."
That was the fur, they're like, "Lovelyn Frog, Cryptid Olympics, he has to go."
And I have, I was familiar with the name, Lovelyn Frog, but never looked into it.
This guy's pretty dope.
I don't know if he'd win the Cryptid Olympics, but let's take a look at his resume here.
So we're going to Lovelyn Ohio.
Did you guys ever see that old show from the 70s, the Dukes of Lovelyn?
This is where it took place.
Lovelyn Ohio, the year is 1955.
Now I can do my doo-wop music that I didn't get to do yesterday.
This guy's driving down the road.
This businessman is driving down a road late at night in Lovelyn Ohio, turning up a little
bit of his doo-wop music.
And he sees on the side of the road three humanoid figures just kind of standing up.
And he's like, "What?
What is this?
They look weird.
They're on two feet, but they just look kind of lumpy and their eyes are in the...
They're frogs."
And what he's seeing is three, four feet tall frogs standing up, having a conversation on
the side of the road.
He starts slowing his car down and then at one point one of the frogs turn, one of the
frogs sees him, sees the human now watching them, and he turns, he looks at the human,
he pulls a wand out, not the human.
The frog man pulls out a wand, a big metal wand, like a magic wand, and then sparks shoot
out at the top of it and the businessman drives away totally scared.
So that was really the origin of the Lovelyn frog.
It should really be Lovelyn frogs, but became a local phenomenon.
It basically became their big foot.
Everyone at Lovelyn was like, "They hear this story?
They're like, 'Oh my God, they're frog people out there.'
Now it was passed down from generation to generation.
Dads would tell their kids and kids would tell each other in the schoolyard and all this
sort of stuff.
Better be careful.
There's a frog man in the woods."
Now what's interesting is this, the first sighting, there's multiple variations of it,
which tends to make you think it's an urban legend.
Sometimes it's a businessman, sometimes it's a vacuum cleaner salesman, sometimes I think
he's walking, sometimes he's driving.
There's different variations, but they're slight.
They all involve three frogs, a magic wand, and sparks.
So the fact that those variations as small as they are do lend it a little more weight
than the typical urban legend.
Like Bloody Mary, say you have a baby, sometimes you say Bloody Mary three times, sometimes
you say it ten times.
Sometimes the urban legend's a little more concrete, gives it a little more weight, which
is what concrete tends to do.
But everyone's talking about this thing.
It's their big foot.
So in 1972, when a police officer is driving down the roads of Loveland late one night
and he sees it, everything changes.
It's March 3rd, 1972, and officer Ray Shockey is driving down the road.
He sees a four foot tall creature, reptile, standing up by the side of the road.
And it's fully illuminated by his headlights.
He can see it perfectly.
It's this giant reptilian creature that's four feet tall, standing up, and it climbs
over a guardrail and kind of jumps down into the river.
And he it scares him to death.
Absolutely.
And he reports it.
And everyone makes fun of him.
They're like, "Oh, Shockey saw the frog, man.
Shockey saw the frog, man."
They're like giving him squirrelies and wedges.
He's like, "Nah, I'm an officer of the law.
Don't do this."
But he got teased.
It would be the same thing.
That's why Air Force pilots don't report that they've seen UFOs or regular pilots or whatever.
You're gonna get ridiculed.
And he was ridiculed.
But he had a good buddy on the force, Mark Matthews.
Mark Matthews.
Now, he was also an officer.
And he was like, "You know what?
I believe Shockey."
He had a button that says, "I believe Shockey."
He's like, "Do you want to wear this?"
He's handing them out around town.
People are like, "No."
I don't know who that guy is.
But anyways, so Mark Matthews was on a mission.
He wanted to prove his friend right.
But then, you know, he was also a cop.
He also had to arrest people and do traffic stops and stuff like that.
He wasn't like, he wasn't a one-man mission of like, proof.
He also had other stuff to do.
But he's like, "You know, I'm gonna run into this creature.
I just know it."
And I'll prove that Shockey was right.
And then I'll win his heart.
So one night, about two weeks later, very short amount of time, Mark Matthews is on patrol
and he sees something in the bushes.
A big reptile.
And he blows it to pieces.
Doesn't investigate it at all.
He just shoots it to death.
Could have been an alien visitor.
Could have been a last of its species.
Could have used that magical wand technology to create sparks that would help in the Cold
War.
But he didn't even worry about that.
Those are all the birds flying away from the gunshot.
Not the sound of this creature dying.
Now when he shoots it, dead, he walks up to it and he goes, "That's not a frog."
But I don't know what it is.
It's four feet tall.
It's a big dead reptile with arms and legs and a little reptilian head.
And that was it.
No tail.
And he's like, "What is this thing?"
So he picks it up, throws it in the back of a squad car in the trunk, takes it to Shaki.
Now Shaki's at home.
He's drinking some single malt.
He's like, "They'll believe me someday.
I know they'll believe me."
Or, "I'll show them.
I'll show them all."
And before he can enact his plan of vengeance on his bullies, Matthews shows up and says,
"Hey Shaki, you want to come check out my trunk?"
Got some junk in it.
And he's like, "Yeah, yeah, let's go."
Opens it up and Shaki looks and he goes, "That is exactly what I saw."
That stands up on both legs and Matthew goes, "I didn't see it stand up on both legs necessarily,
but I did blow it away before I'd have the chance to like, you know, Carl Owens out of
there."
So, at this point they're looking at a giant reptile.
It's not an alligator.
It's not a crocodile.
It's not a frog.
But it's definitely some sort of unknown creature to them.
So they have to go take it to get it tested by like a scientist.
So I imagine in real life they took it to like a college or a vet.
But I would have loved to see them roll it down into the autopsy room of the police station.
He's like, "Hey Clark, you ever seen one of these before?"
And Clark's like, "Oh dude, yeah, I can't wait to dissect this thing and find out what
it is."
Looks like straight-up alien autopsy.
But anyways, for whatever the reason, whether they took it to the autopsy dude, the coroner
is the word I'm looking for, or they took it to a veterinarian, what it was, what
Shockey saw and Matthew saw was a giant iguana that's tail had come off.
So to be fair, it didn't look like an iguana.
It just looked like a monster.
And when it was standing up by the side of the road, it was actually preparing to climb
over the guardrail.
So it wouldn't be able to walk like that.
It wouldn't be able to jog down the street like that.
But it was holding itself up and then fell over.
And it looked like it was standing on both legs.
So at that point, the thing is, is like, if you ran in, if this series of events happened
in any other location, a man says, "Oh dude, I saw like a 4 foot tall lizard walking around
and fell on the river."
And then two weeks later, someone blew it away with a shotgun and then said, "Oh, it's an
iguana with no tail."
That would kind of be it.
But this, because it took place in Loveland where the beloved frogman lived, it was this
crazy chain of events. And what's really weird is that outside of that first story, and then
the story of the officers, there's no other real proof of the frogman.
There's a few blurry photos of it.
Really, the best photo that's come out was when some nerds were playing Pokemon Go, running
around in Loveland, and they clipped a picture of a creature standing in the water, looking
at them with glowing eyes.
Probably most likely fake, because what Pokemon Go player is going to stop playing Pokemon
Go long enough to open their camera up, none.
Also, technically they should have caught them, but they didn't.
So I think it was fake.
If the Loveland Frog monster, I keep wanting to add that qualifier on the end of it, if
the Loveland Frog is real, I think the most likely thing is they were simply passing through.
I find it interesting that they seemed to be monsters, but they were talking to each
other.
Oh dude, I just remembered something.
I did an episode, probably about three episodes back.
I can't believe that I totally forgot about this.
I did an episode three, about three or four episodes back, called "The Man Who Was Addicted"
or "Addicted to Abduction" or "Addicted to UFO Abduction" or something like that.
And it started this guy, it was featured this guy named Peerzan Fredov, who talked about
being abducted multiple times and I said the whole story was made up.
But an interesting thing is when he was abducted on that ship, and that story took place in,
if I remember correctly, in the 70s, he was taken aboard the ship and the aliens were like
here, look in this vat, this is our most hated enemy.
And it was a giant frog.
Now it's possible that Peerzan Fredov still made the whole story up, and he just read
about the 19th story, the story that took place in the 1950s with the businessman.
That's actually, it's possible, but I know it's possible, I can't necessarily say unlikely,
but I would say my instinct tells me that if the loveland frog sighting is real, they
were aliens.
They were from not this planet.
Because three four foot tall frogs with magical wands would be really hard to not see until
1955.
There's like stories of like old legends in the areas of frog people, but people think
that's been retconned.
It's really hard for three giant frogs to hide with a magic wand, get sighted and then go
completely off the grid again.
Unless they were simply passing through, or passing through our planet or dimension.
I think it's for, and that would be why there would be no more frogmen sightings, because
they were just there for that night.
They were partying in the level in Ohio, then they had to get to somewhere else.
I wonder what, it's funny because when I think of the story, I'm not so curious about the
frogs because I deal with cryptids all the time.
I'm curious about that wand.
Very rarely do we see cryptids wield technology, which again makes me think it's more likely
that they're alien than some sort of monster.
You gotta wonder though, we hear these stories of businessmen driving around at night, seeing
something out of the blue, or out of the black, because it's night.
They see a bigfoot across the road, they see a man bat in Chicago, they see a loveline
frog and his buddies on the side of the road.
But how many of those people don't make it to their destination?
And all that's ever found is an abandoned car, or a rowboat in the middle of a lake,
or a house where the tenant just seemed to up and leave, or a little girl goes missing.
We never hear the start of those urban legends, those cryptid stories, those alien encounters.
Because the only witness was a victim.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is gonna be your email address, you can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabberradio Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast, you don't have to
listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.