Books bound in human skin. We go and visit the dirtiest man in the world.
Then we look at the winding mysterious tale of a stone head found in Guatemala.
What starts off as possible proof of an ancient civilization or UFO
encounter becomes even odder today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great... huh? I'm having a great day. I hope
you're having a great day too. I'm battling something in my ear.
You listeners are probably like, "Dude, you're always sick." You just got done with
the sinus infection, but now I got some ear pressure. Actually, it hurts to talk.
So we're gonna go ahead... so yeah, we still got to record the podcast though.
So we're gonna go ahead and get started though, not because I want to hurry up
and get this done with, but because we actually have a lot to cover. So first
thing I wanted to talk about was books bound in human flesh. Now the idea of a
book having a fleshy cover is kind of something that... it's one of those
things that I think you would expect to be real. You wouldn't be surprised to
know that they actually exist, but for the most part we see them appear in horror
movies or horror novels or things like that, where it's like the net
cramming on, it's bound in the flesh of a tortured human and so on and so forth.
They do have pretty good provenance. Provenance? I know I never get that
word right. I think it's provenance, like the history of something. They do have
pretty good provenance on human-covered books. Books with human skin covers? As of
2016, there are 47 supposed books, the covers flesh. 18 have been confirmed to
have the flesh. 14 has been disproved and others are currently being tested. I
don't know why it's taken them so long. Just run a normal book cover, does not
have DNA. If it has DNA, it is human. There. I just saved you guys a ton of time.
What's weird though, so you go, "Okay, Jason, yeah, there's books bound in human
flesh. No big deal." What's bizarre is the the small amount of them. Now, I thought
they'd be everywhere, because people have been around forever. Books have been
around for what? Since the Gutenberg press, roughly? And I love it how you can
often see the gaps in my my history. But so books were around probably like
1484, but there's always been like tablets and papyrus and like scrolls. I'm
sure scrolls are made of human flesh, but they say we only have these 47 books.
1568 was apparently the first time that they're like, "This is the oldest book
with human flesh." It was a medical book, and that was actually quite common. It was
medical books that mostly have been discovered having human flesh covers.
Because medical staff had easy access to cadavers, you know, I would be really
cautious to go to a doctor who all of his patients have an 8x12 patch cut
out of their skin. I mean, not his alive patients, but he's like, "You know,
obviously the medical guy, the dude doing the tannery, gives it to the the
mortician." The mortician's like, "Why is this guy always missing a peachy's binder
size of skin from his torso?" Whatever, I'll just burn the bunny. So a lot of
these were medical texts. There were a couple famous ones. So you know, the
gunpowder plot in England, remember, remember the 5th of November? Guy Fox,
all that stuff. One of the guys who was caught up in that, his name was Henry
Garnett, he in 1606 when he was executed, they made a book out of his skin
about the event. So I mean, that's, you know, throwing salt on the wound. Your
failed event and then we're going to immortalize it in a book and the cover
is your skin. There was rumors during the French Revolution that there was a
tannery set up just outside of town, basically, where they were cutting skin
off people to make books. And so again, like, sure, that was probably just a rumor,
but you'd think there would still be more than these 47 books. Now, you had the
people, you had the medical doctors doing it, you had condemned prisoners,
their skin was also being turned into books. There's two famous examples. There
was this guy named James Allen, he went by the alias George Walton and he,
there's a book called The Highwayman, narrative of the life of James Allen,
alias George Walton. And it's by James Allen, who when he was dying, he's like,
"I want you to, I want you to take this book. I want you to use my skin to make
the cover." And people are like, "Okay, I guess." And he's like, "And then, this happened
in 1837, that's why I'm doing an old-timey voice." But he's like, "Ugh, I got the
consumption and other old-timey diseases, plus I'm being executed for my crimes all
at the same time. And I want you to, I wrote this book, I want you to put my human
skin, my epidermis for the cover." And they go, "Okay, so I want you to give this book
to this dude who I tried robbing once and he was so brave, I want him to have my
skin book. Now, that's cool and all. I don't know if I would want that. Like, if
some guy put a gun in my face, an old-timey gun, like a big old revolver,
and I was brave, which is cool, and I survived. And then years later, I get a
book in the mail and it's his biography and I'm like, "Oh, that's interesting. You
know, I wonder if I'm in it." And then you touch it, you realize the cover has
follicles. Yeah, I don't think so. The other interesting, this, I don't understand
this. I don't, do not understand this example of a human skin book. There is a,
it is the biography of Abraham Lincoln, bound in the human skin of, and this isn't
my word, this is the word off Wikipedia. This, I, it is bound with the skin of a
Negro. So, I think you're kind of missing the point of what Abraham Lincoln was
trying to do. It's like, hey, remember when, remember when that president freed
all those slaves? Here's one of them! Here's this book! Why would you, what was the,
who was thinking that through? But apparently you can read a biography of
the life of Abraham Lincoln and the cover is made out of the skin of a
black man. Super bizarre. Now, here's the thing. Like I said in the beginning, I
think there's far more books out there than these 47 that are made with human
skin. In the article I was reading, they said there's a lot of legends of books of
erotica and occult manuals being bound in human flesh, but that's mostly just
rumors. I'm sure there's a ton of them. I'm sure there is a lot of a, especially a
cult books that are bound in human flesh, because why not? The world's been,
we've been around for so long, we've been book binding for so long. I'm sure
there are not like vast amounts, it's not like a Barnes and Noble of human skin,
but I'm sure there are a lot of books out there, because these books are the
ones that are like in libraries. But if you had a personal collection of erotica
bound in the human skin of young maidens, or you had like dark grim walls of, you
know, I'm sure there's even probably Bibles bound in human flesh. I'm sure
that there are just mainstream religious texts that are like, "Oh yes, this one's
made out of some priest dude who fell over and I figure no one was gonna
discover the body. He always wanted to be in the Bible, so now he is the cover."
I'm sure there are actually, I mean, not, when I say common I don't mean like
comparatively to all the total of book bindings in the world, but I would bet
money there's more than 47 books out there that have a cover made from a
living human, a previously living human. But dude, just do a DNA test and it's a
human or it's cardboard or maybe like a lamb. It really shouldn't be that hard.
It shouldn't take you that long to figure out how many books have human flesh on
them. That's a good reason to get tattoos. That way if your skin ever gets
turned into a book cover, it's beautiful. It's already illustrated. Next story we're
gonna look at. This one is an interesting story because it's basically a story of
degrees. It's a story of lots of little small steps that lead to you being
discussed on a podcast called Dead Rabbit Radio. This one's actually a
recommendation from YouTube user David. David, I always leave out people's last
names because I don't know if they want that much attention. But anyway, so David
on YouTube was like, "Hey, have you ever covered the story of the dirtiest man in
the world?" And now I was aware of the dirtiest man in the world, but I hadn't
done an episode on him yet. This is legit. You go, is he gonna list ten
people who are the dirtiest? No, there's actually a guy who's considered the dirtiest
man in the world. So let's hop in the carpenter copter. We are leaving the
books, the human skin book place. So I'll hop in the carpenter copter. We're gonna
fly over to Iran and not get shot down. We're gonna land in southern Iran, far away
from any sort of missiles. I'm assuming, I don't know why. Anyways, the carpenter copter
flies over the Middle East safely, lands in southern Iran, and that is where we
meet Amu Haji. So Amu Haji is 84 years old. He's an old man, live in in the desert.
He's 84 years old. He has not had a bath in 60 years. He's so dirty looking and
all leathery that he looks like the dirt around him. Other people, and that's not
me being racist, other people in Iran go, "He looks like the dirt. He looks like a
bunch of rocks moving around." So like I said, this is a story of degrees. The
question is, how do you become the dirtiest man living in the desert? This,
okay, so the story goes like this. The legend is that when he was a young man, a
young woman broke his heart. Aww, that's so sad. I wonder if they have Valentine's Day in
Iran. Anyway, so this young girl breaks his heart and he's like, "I don't want
anything to do with anybody. I'm totally heartbroken. I'm just gonna leave town."
So he runs out into the desert. Now that's, I get that. I get that emotion. You get
your heart broken when you're young or even when you're old, but it hurts more
when you're young because it's, you know, you haven't had it broken that many times.
You run away. Now again, here's the first degree. Most people go, "You know what? I
this isn't, I just gotta get back on the saddle and go back to town and try to
find my way in the world." But he doesn't. He goes, "Yeah, I have whatever. I'm gonna
live out in the desert." Now he's living out in the desert and while he's out
there, whatever reason, he goes, "You know what? I'm gonna also do while I'm out here.
I'm gonna stop bathing. I'm just gonna stop. I'm just gonna stop bathing." And you
might go, "Okay, Jason, that's it. You're in the desert, so you're gonna be dirty all
the time. You would spend all day long taking baths. It could have been a, a,
just could have been a logistical issue. You didn't have time or enough water to
bathe all the time." But he actually believes that if he takes a bath, he gets
sick. So he runs out into the desert because he gets his heart broken. He
decides to stop taking baths. And then he makes the decision to start drinking
water out of a rusty oil can, a rusty old dirty oil can. And you're like, "Why? Go
back to town and get some nice ceramic mugs. Get a beer stein." But no, he finds a
dusty, rusty dirty oil can. He uses that to drink water. He drinks five liters of water
a day, so that's good. He's not gonna get dehydrated. He may get several oil-based
illnesses, but he's not gonna get dehydrated. So what does he do for food? You
ask, "Well, for food, what would you do for food if you're in the Iranian desert?"
What animals are out there? Vultures, worms, I don't know. But he decides to
eat rotting porcupine meat. That's his favorite meal. He eats rotting porcupine
meat. See what I mean? It's a story of degrees. You want to be a hermit? Fine.
You don't want to take a bath? Fine. But at what point do you go, "I'm just gonna eat
rotting porcupine meat?" Because if there's rotting porcupine meat, there's
porcupines. Just get a porcupine and kill it and cook it and eat it. You don't have
to eat it rotting. Just eat one that you just killed. So apparently in Iran, there
are vultures, worms, and porcupines because there's enough rotting meat for
him to eat it. So he's sitting there, let's say at this point he's probably
like 40 or 50. He's been out in the desert for a long time. He's covered in dirt,
drinking water out of a rusty oil can. He's eating rotting porcupine meat, but
he's like, "You know what, man? I'm so bored. I didn't bring any of my human skin
books out here because I didn't bring any of any entertainment. I don't
got my Game Boy. What am I gonna do for fun?" So what would you do for fun? You
would of course do what Mu does. He starts smoking dried animal poop. Now at
this point you're like rotting meat, dirty water, no bath, and for
entertainment he smokes dried animal poop. Why? Like that's what was so... if it
was just this guy was the dirtiest man in the world, I'd be like, "Yeah, it doesn't
take a bath. No big deal." But it's all the other little things that he does that
just paints this sign of insanity. Now he says that he's totally fine. He says one
of the biggest trouble that he's had was a group of men from the nearby town
showed up and tried to force him to take a bath and he ran away. Like that was one
of the big moments of his life as a hermit. Now he's been covered in media
quite a lot because again it's kind of an intriguing case. It's usually
intriguing when people just kind of brush off society and go out on their own.
But the latest article I read was that he is currently looking for love. He wants
to rekindle that fire he once had. Bring that love back into his life. I think
before that happens you're going to have to take a bath and that's probably the
least of your things. You're gonna have to find something else to eat and stop
smoking the animal dung. But at 84 I can't imagine like even if he came back
and did like a whole "she's all that" makeover thing. I think after spending 60
years out in the wilderness that just being inside like having to go back to
sit inside and then you're like, "Whoa, what's this thing?" And they're like, "Oh,
that's a SpongeBob SquarePants." He's like, "Oh my god, people these these drawings,
they automatically..." He's not that old. He knows what television and cartoons are,
but it would be such a culture shock. So he can either hope for to go back into
the real world or for one day him to wake up and there is a hot young woman
sitting there just slightly dusty going, "Man, I'm thirsty. Is there any rusty oil
cans around I can drink from?" Like he would need to find someone on his viable
level. But you know the world's big enough. I'm sure there are women who read that
article and were like, "Hmm, it's kind of sexy. He's a rebel. The ultimate bad boy.
He doesn't let society tell him what to smoke. He'll eat whatever he wants." I'm
sure if he had a mail address, women would write him love letters like they
write serial killers in prison. But Hamu, Haji, Dead Rabbit, Radio Salutu, whatever
you want, I hope you get. You don't... you seem relatively harmless. I just think
it's so bizarre that you go from just saying, "I don't want to take a bath to
smoke an animal poop and eating rotting porcupine." Like I really wish I could
figure out where those decisions happened because I don't think all four of
those things happen on the same day. I don't think as he was leaving town, he
saw a rotting porcupine and goes, "I'll be back for you later." First I gotta go not
take a bath. But then I'm gonna eat you. I'm gonna smoke some animal poop. It's just
weird how those steps all progressed. Okay, for our last story of the night, this
one was really weird. This was also a request from YouTube. And I'm not gonna
be able to pronounce the name right, but I'm gonna try it. Holly Coraris? Holly
Co... Coris? Holly Coris? They hit me up and they said, "Hey, have you ever done an
episode on the... Have you ever heard of the Guatemalan Stonehead?" And I hadn't.
I looked it up and I saw the picture and I was like, "Oh, that's intriguing." And I
kind of filed it away. Every so often I would kind of take a brief look at it
and it didn't really investigate it. It was intriguing. I was like, "Okay, I'll do
that on season three." And today I sat down and I said, "You know, I'm gonna do
Guatemalan Stonehead." I've been doing some changes with the stories this
week because some stuff has popped up, Thanksgiving conspiracy and all that for
next for tomorrow. So I was kind of looking for a good meaty story to tell
today. Guatemalan Stonehead, I looked into it and it is bizarre. The whole... It's so
wrapped up in these... Okay, let me just... It was not what I expected the story to be.
So, but let's get into the basics. So the carbonic copter we have to leave in Iran
because the dirtiest man in the world was sleeping in it and it smells like
rotting porcupine meat. So now we're gonna have to take the... Oh, now we're stuck
again with the Dead Rabbit rowboat. So it is a long journey from Iran to
Guatemala. We're going to row all the way from the desert of Iran somehow to
Guatemala. It's a long journey, but we get to know each other better. And he gave
us an ample supply of dried animal poop to smoke. So we are ripped. We are totally
off our heads by the time we get to Guatemala, which is probably gonna help
for this story. So we're tied the... Tied the rowboat up to the... What's that thing
up here? Now we've got to get our sea legs back. We're kind of walking weird.
Severely vitamin C deficient. We both have scurvy. But now we're on land. We're in
Guatemala. We're gonna go get a beer and a bunch of oranges. We're gonna eat a ton
of limes now. So anyways, we're on the land. We're in Guatemala. 1987, Dr. Oscar
Rafael Padilla-Laura got a picture. We'll just call him Oscar. Oscar was a
ufologist. So he was a guy who was into conspiracy theories and UFOs and all
that stuff. He gets a picture and there's a picture of a little Volkswagen bug
parked next to a giant stone head somewhere in the jungles of Guatemala.
Is what is the letter included with the picture says. It's somewhere in the
jungles of Guatemala. Now what's interesting about the face of the stone
head, it has Caucasian features. So it has like a sharp nose, thin lips, high
cheekbones. In that region where this head was discovered, there are other stone
heads. They're very popular. They're the Olmec stone heads. The civilization, the
Olmecs and the Mayans lived in the civilization. They carved also these
massive stone heads, but they had facial features that were reminiscent of the
civilizations that lived there. So they had puffier cheeks, flat noses, and their
eyes were a bit crossed. And there are still people in the region who match.
They don't have giant stone heads, but they look like a... the stone heads look
like the people who did live there. But out of the middle of the jungle you have
a head that is listed as being Caucasian features. So he gets this photo in 1987.
The photo is dated like the 1950s. And he writes an article for like this UFO
magazine. He's like, "Look at this picture. This picture. This head
shouldn't exist in this area. There was no white people in the area when this
head would have been created, when the Olmec heads would have been created. This
is an anomaly. Could it be aliens? Could it be a previous race?" So on and so forth.
So of course people start to ask questions and they're like, "Oh, where's the head at?
You know, what's going on? How do we find out more about this? We need to know
what's going on." Doc Oscar. We'll call him Dr. Oscar. Dr. Oscar says that he was
just able to, from the brief information in the letter, able to track down where
the head actually was. So he goes there and the head is shot to pieces. The
lips are gone, the nose is gone, and the eyes are shot away. We're blown off by
anti-government forces. There was a civil war. There was a lot of civil strife in
that area. And he was like, "I'm never going back there. I'm not gonna tell anyone
where it's at, but this is a real stonehead and here's the proof. Here's
this photo." And he didn't take more photos of it with all the stuff blown off
of it. So people were suspicious, but also very intrigued. Because this wasn't just
some dude that he was a well-respected UFOologist, especially in Central America,
lore, things like that. The story had pretty much disappeared. Like, it was
just kind of... there's so much stuff that comes out in weird news that it's... unless
something is constantly developing, stuff will kind of fall the wayside. This
story pretty much disappeared until there was a documentary being, quote-unquote,
documentary being made called Revelations of the Mayans 2012 and
Beyond. And this is where the story gets really bizarre. So this documentary is
being made. And they believe that it is either an ancient civilization that
predated the Olmecs that built this head. So before any indigenous people of
Central America, South America were there, there was a previous race of white
people or Caucasians in that area. And it's funny because that ties a lot into
the theory of Hitler's master race and then wanting to go to South America to
build colonies and use and all that stuff. But anyway, so they positioned
themselves as either there was an older race that existed in Central and South
America or aliens built it. This documentary, they got a letter from
Guatemalan archaeologist Hector E. Maji. And this is what the letter said. "I
certify that this monument presents no characteristics of Maya, Nato, Olmec, or
any other pre-Hispanic civilization. It was created by an extraordinary and
superior civilization with awesome knowledge of which there is no record
of existence on this planet." That's quite the bold letter. So what's funny was
that this documentary was going to be made. They got this letter going. Theories now
again were starting to fly. Was this stone head, was this stone head created by
the Olmecs? And it's an anomaly? Is the stone head proof of an older
civilization? The fact that the stone head is slightly looking up, is it proof that
it's looking for aliens? They have the alien race that are known as the
Pleiadians, which are Arian. They're white and blonde hair and all that stuff.
We'll get into them in a later episode, but the idea that it could be modeled on
them. So here, this is, it's, this story was, when I was researching it, I was like,
"Okay, stone head, different theories." I read an article and the first article I
read there, kind of like, "This is kind of weird, this is kind of weird." As I kept
reading more articles, the stories just got weirder and weirder. So the
documentary, Revelations of the Minds 2012 and Beyond, was being made by Rawl
Julia's son, which I don't know why I think that's funny, but I think it's funny.
Because when everything a Rawl Julia, I think a street fighter in the movie. I,
everything else he did, that's all I can remember a street fighter movie. Anyway,
so Rawl Julia's son, and by since son, is making this documentary. They include that
letter by Hector E. Maja. Hector eventually says, "The letter that they presented was
completely altered. I never saw the statue. I never visited the site. I saw the
photograph." He goes, "I don't believe it's anything extraordinary at all." So the
documentary actually cast more doubt on the fact that this head even existed at
all. Because all anyone had was this photo. Now, there were other researchers who
were looking into this over the years. No one could ever find it, because it was
just, and basically an undated photo that one guy said that he visited, but
wouldn't tell anyone where it was at. And there were researchers who were
looking at it saying, "This is proof of the white master race that white people
existed here long before anyone else." And then, I guess if they're the master
race, somehow they died off. But anyways, this is proof of that. Other people are
like, "This is proof of aliens." Other people said, "No, there's an archaeological
reason. There must have been other Olmecs who made this head for whatever reason."
Lost in all of the shuffle, predating even the photograph from the 1950s, the
answer was there. And a lot of these researchers could easily access this
information, and they either weren't, or they saw it and just completely disregarded
it. This is the tale of the Guatemalan Stonehead. It actually did exist. The
photograph is real. It is a real Stonehead in the middle of Guatemala. In 1941-1942,
the Carnegie Institution Reconnaissance Survey was going through the area, taking
notes of everything. They came across the story of a guy in 1936 who used soft
volcanic pumice and carved a monument to his dead wife on his form. When the
Carnegie, they weren't there specifically to look for the Stonehead. They were just
doing reconnaissance of the area, archaeological stuff, history stuff, all
that stuff. They come across the Stonehead. They talk to people like, "Hey,
what's that doing there?" People in town are like, "Oh, Joe made that." We don't know
who, we don't know the name of the guy who made it. A lot of the stuff had been
lost, but they'd be like, "Hey, Joe made that." Yeah, he made it for his dead wife,
and they're like, "Oh, that's interesting." They talk to other people in town. They're
like, "Hey, do you know anything about the Stonehead?" They're like, "Yeah, yeah, the
farm administrator over there, he lost his wife, he was really sad. He basically
carved this monument." It is huge. It's bigger than a Volkswagen Bug, but it's a
very soft stone. He's like, "Yeah, you know, he sat and carved it for his dead wife.
It's a monument." And so, the Carnegie Institution was like, "Okay, this is what
this is." They ended up, so there was a historian back in the day, wrote an
article. Lee Parsons wrote this article called, "A pseudo pre-Columbian colossal
stonehead on the Pacific coast of Guatemala." And this article is explaining
the Stonehead and where it came from and the history behind it. And this is an
interesting part of this article. Here's the quote here, "Whatever the inspiration,
its very existence could confound future archaeologists and lead to unwarranted
explanations of trans-pacific contact or even mysterious pre-Columbian
megalithic complexes. Anticipating such interpretations, I have titled this paper
a pseudo pre-Columbian colossal stonehead. Actually, there was no intention
whatever to defraud. But through the years, the sculpture has become increasingly
difficult to identify. Therefore, it is here recorded that the lost Victoria
stonehead is recent, having been carved in 1936. Further, it has no meaningful
relationship to any American Indian living or dead. I regret that I am
unable to supply the name of the Guatemalan for who the monument is a true
modern memorial." So the person who made it, his name has been lost and unfortunately
the person who it was made as a memorial for was lost. Apparently, there was a
plaque at one time at the base of the stonehead. Plaque's gone. And the idea
that it got shot to pieces by anti-government forces, the theory is
that it was a soft pumice. So really, it wouldn't have lasted the ages. Just
erosion will take care of it. But this Lee Parsons was like, "Listen, I know what's
gonna happen. People are gonna stumble across this stonehead and they're going
to think that it is proof of something that it's not. This was a modern
memorial that was made. But he knew how historians and archaeologists and stuff
like that would think. And he's also thinking 100, 200, 300 years in the
future. Like, again, the nose is gone, the lips are gone, the eyes are gone, but
it's still different looking enough. And they were going to be like, "This is proof
of something. We don't know what it is. We're gonna start looking into it." And
he's like, "No, no, no, don't. I'm writing this. I trust that people in the
future will be smart enough to find my article. And I am telling you this is a
history of the stonehead." So that's it. The stonehead does exist. How much of it?
It's possible that Dr. Oscar went there and saw the head. And it had been either
blown up, piece of it blown up, or just because it's softer stone parts of it
were eroding away. His story may be true that he went there and he's like, "It's
too violent here." He could have went there and realized, "This is more
modern than it looks in the picture. So I'm just not gonna tell anyone where
it's at." And it is weird that he didn't take any additional photos to go all the
way out there and not take any... I mean, we rode all the way from Iran. He just
showed up in a car and couldn't even take a photo. There are still people who
believe that this story is a cover-up. That the stonehead is actually from an
ancient white Caucasian civilization or aliens. And this story that was planted
20, 30 years before the UFO story even started. That this story is fake. I mean,
you would really have to do some like vast retconning. I really... this was a
really enjoyable story to research because again, I went in thinking, "Oh,
there's gonna be the stonehead. There's not gonna be... the questions are gonna be
who built it, why, and when. There's gonna be no answers." And it actually turned
into this winding mystery that actually has a conclusion. Which my favorite
mysteries, my favorite like conspiracy mysteries, true crime, paranormal, are
the ones that have a definite conclusion. This is what happened. The open-ended
ones are fun to speculate on. But when you can actually go back and say, "This is
real and this is what happened and there's no real speculation behind it,"
that is what I find the most fun researching. Because there's an end. Just
like this is the end of today's podcast. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be
our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but
I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
(upbeat music)