The worst marketing gimmick that is possible. A bizarre ghost slash cryptid
that only appeared once in the most unlikely of places. And then we end the
story of Sherry Schreiner. Is it possible that by littering you can defeat aliens
today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host
Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. This
episode will probably be shorter and the first two stories are definitely just
little tidbits, little tasty little appetizers, bites of stories that I
think are interesting but not like full fleshed out segments. So we're gonna kind
of bounce around here. The first one, okay, and I actually discovered this product
when I was researching the Sherry Schreiner stuff. So this is fitting that
it's in this episode, the last Sherry Schreiner episode, I hope. She talked about
this product called Thieves Oil. It's a product that you can get that like helps
build up your immune system from the draconians or some nonsense like that.
But because that's not important. Why she was recommending it isn't important. But I
did have to find out what this stuff is. Thieves Oil. It's a real thing. It's like
eucalyptus and lime, not lime, but it's like eucalyptus and like oils and stuff
like that you rub on you. It smells really good. Actually you know what? I will let
the website tell you exactly what it is. This is from the website Secret of the
Thieves. Sorry, no, Secret of Thieves. So if you tried Google Secret of the
Thieves, you're probably gonna find out how to steal stuff. Secret of Thieves is
the website for Thieves Oil. This is their gimmick. Okay. Thieves Essential Oil is a
powerful... they actually have Thieves as a registered trademark which is kind of
weird. Because I mean it's just an occupation. I can't trademark Carpenter, but
Thieves Essential Oil is a powerful combination of essential oils for an
aromatic, aromatic blend that fills any space with a rich, spicy aroma.
Inspired by the legend of Four Thieves Vinegar, this blend is one of Young
Living's most popular products. You're like, "Oh, okay Jason, it's this oil that
you can put on you. It smells really good. You can also put it in like your
dish soap or your toothpaste." That's what they're saying, not me. It's just like a
yummy, yummy oil, right? So they go on to say that what it does is it's like good
for cleaning. It's like a... smells good. You can put it in all these different
products. It's based on this stuff called Thieves Vinegar. Now on their website,
on their website, they have that little description and a little more going into
detail like what it can be put into. And then in that same block of text, so you
have a little image of a little bottle of Thieves Oil, you have the stuff that's
written underneath it in the text right above it. It's isn't hidden somewhere on
the site. This isn't there in their frequently asked questions. This product,
quote, "Based on the legend of thieves," so that's how they get their name,
Thieves. Thieves, this is based on some sort of thief legend. I'm enthralled.
Healthy Living. What are you guys called? Young Living. I'm enthralled
Young Living Company. "Based on the legend of thieves who covered themselves with
mixtures of herbs and spices." Ooh, okay, so these are yummy smelling thieves. Maybe
they're trying to break into places where people have bad senses of smell.
Actually, that doesn't make sense because then they would detect you. So you're
like, hmm, interesting. Let's start over. "Based on the legend of thieves who covered
themselves with mixtures of herbs and spices before robbing plague victims." What?
You, your product is based, your product is based on a thing that people rubbed on
themselves so they could go into black plague infested areas of Europe and rob
the dead and the dying. And this is a real thing. So I had to go, I was like, what?
Why would you make that product? Okay, it's one thing to make that product. It's
another thing to put it in your selling points, to have it visible on your front
page. So apparently, back when everyone was dying of pestilence as boils were
erupting from their body and exploding onto the vicar who's like trying to give
them prayers, all of a sudden they're covered in black goo. I'm one of you now!
Now, look, they get blisters. They pop all over the place. That's how I imagine it
to be. I imagine streets filled with ankle deep pus everywhere. You couldn't
even find your cat. It was just covered in pus. Must have smelled disgusting. Must
have smelled like sweaty socks that had fish stuck in them just sitting out in
the summer heat. That was all of Europe for about 400 years. Sorry for that
description. Sorry if you were eating fish and/or socks while watching this
episode. Anyways, there was this thing that, I guess they've done some studies
that like French doctors would chew garlic and they actually had less and
they would rub garlic on them so the French people smelled a little bit
better. That's such a stereotypical French joke. Okay, but it's sorry
French listeners. But anyways, they would rub garlic on their skin. They would chew
garlic and French doctors actually had lower rates of getting the bubonic plague
than their English counterparts. And there was a story of these thieves
that did do like this Ocean's Eleven-style heist of plague victims and
they covered themselves in these scented oils and were able to walk
un molested through the bubonic plague towns and just rob people. Now, there's
been some pushback to whether or not the four thieves is actually a real story.
They think it might have actually been based on a guy named Four Thave who
invented this little oil that was like, "Hey, take this and you won't get the
plague as he's hiding pustules all over his body." He's like, "Look at me, I'm
totally fine." They're like, "Take your shirt off." And he's like, "No, I'm shy." But
buy this stuff. You won't get, "Oh, oh," and then just puss, puss starts coming out
of his shirt. He's like, "Oh, that's an unrelated disease. You can buy my oil." All
of that aside, whether or not it's based on Four Thave, a guy who sold bubonic
medicine, or a group of thieves who preyed on on these dying humans full of
mucus coming out of their body, don't put that in your marketing slogan. The last
thing I want to be reminded of when I'm buying a product to put on or in my
body is the black plague. Whether or not it protected them from it is irrelevant
because I'm not facing the black plague today. But when you tell me that this was
used by thieves to rob plague victims and then you list all the products it's in,
cough drops, dental floss, toothpaste, mints, and wipes, the last thing I, if my
butt hurts and I need a wipe, I don't want to think about plague victims. I
definitely don't want to think about them while I'm flossing my teeth. Such a
bizarre marketing. It's almost like I don't understand why they thought it
was a selling point. They could have just said, "Hey, this is called Thieves Oil. It
was based on some old thing that thieves did." Don't look it up. Just put it in
your mouth and on your body. The last thing I want to do before I buy a product
is to be reminded of, what was it, like one-third of Europe's population dying?
Terrible. Terrible, terrible, terrible. I don't think there's many
concrete companies walking around touting their product as made from
recycled 9/11 rubble. You just don't want to do that. Even if it is, even if they
had the best rubble possible, no one's putting that in their in their marketing
campaign. But these guys did. So the next story we're going to talk about is super
short. It was almost one of those things that I was like, it's bizarre because it's
only one, only one person ever saw it. It's only happened one time. My notes are
literally five sentences. But it's kind of bizarre and creepy in its own way. This
was in the book Weird New Jersey, which we've had issues with the weird books in
the past. One in particular. I can't count for all of them. I should actually start
buying them and reading them because I think they're really kind of like gold
mines for this type of stuff. And when I say this kind of stuff, I don't mean
weird stuff. I mean poorly sourced stuff. They'll pretty much put anything in
there. If you wrote in one of these books and said I was walking on the street and
I stubbed my toe and I turned around, there wasn't a rock there, it would
probably end up in one of their books. Weird Oregon, Ghost Rock, page 78. So this
is a story from Weird New Jersey. There's a bunch of kids. Okay, let me set the stage
here first. There is no explanation for why this group of people are at this
location. It just is someone telling a story, someone wrote in a story to
Weird New Jersey and it's printed as being like, isn't this weird? But the weird
part is how the people end up at the location. It's a group of kids at a
nudist camp. No explanation given. And you're thinking, oh teenagers, you know,
porkey style poking through the grass. No, the guy's nine. Nine-year-old. Now I'm
going to assume for the sake of my sanity that the nudist camp is closed and
abandoned and stopped operation a hundred years before these kids are running
around. But anyways, this kid known as R.E. Baker, sorry, R.E. Barker, sorry
fictional pseudonym, sorry that I got it wrong because I doubt this is his real
name. Anyways, Mr. Barker as a young boy is hanging out with his friends at a
long abandoned, no longer an operation, nudist colony, nudist camp, whatever it is.
Anyways, there's an abandoned barn at the desolate nudist colony and the kids
start basically daring each other to go up into the barn and Mr. Barker, young
Mr. Barker goes up into the barn and when he gets into the loft, the one thing
you don't expect to see at a nudist colony, whether or not it's an operation
anymore, is close. So he climbs up and he looks into the loft and is not standing
there but floating there a couple feet off the ground is a pair of fresh, brand
new, fruit-of-the-loom underwear, tidy whiteies dancing around in the middle of
the sky, like in the middle of the loft. So like if someone was wearing them but
the person isn't there, he just sees them moving and he totally freaks out, he
jumps out of the loft, he runs away, and that was it. That's the end of the story.
That's all that appears in that part of Weird New Jersey and you're thinking
Jason, that was a waste of your time. But it wasn't because think about it. If the
story is true, it probably isn't. Well let's assume it's true just to dissect it.
One, anything moving out of the ordinary. We talked about this with the
grinning man. Actually you know it's funny, as I was looking at my notes, his name was
more like the "girning man". It was used interchangeably but "girning" is a
different facial expression. But a couple episodes back I did an episode about
"girning man". It's creepy when things do stuff that's unexpected. Like a mummy
holding his arms out walking down a hallway going "Uhhh" towards you is creepy.
But if he wasn't walking towards you, if he was like crawling towards you,
like a cat, that would be even creepier. Because you'd be like, your brain's
trying to recognize two things. One, an ancient living dust monster coming at
you. And two, it's not acting in any sort of way a human acts. So the floating
underwear is actually kind of a creepy image because that's not something that
you would ever expect to see. A pie floating. I remember there's a lot of
stories of cabbages flying around, ghosts throwing cabbages at people. And I
always thought it was so fascinating because you never hear about it. I hear
about it all the time. I've heard it not all the time. I've heard about it a
couple times but I've always like cabbages. That's weird. Like what's the
connection between ghosts and cabbages? So I always look for that type of stuff.
But so the underwear dancing around is bizarre by itself. But I think the fact
that the underwear is at a nudist colony is just again that is like not
supposed to be. It's the one place where underwear shouldn't be at a nudist colony.
So was the underwear always dancing up there? Like is the underwear still in
that barn now still dancing? Or is it only dancing when somebody observes it?
Have we discovered Schrodinger's tidy white eats? Like is this something... It's
weird to think that if that boy had never gone up in that barn just silently
underwear's moving around in that barn it's abandoned no one ever goes there.
All day all night there's just a pair of underwear kind of floating. To me
that's creepy. Like observing it you're able to go "hey look at that's out of the
ordinary" but to think that there's just a desolate place somewhere out in the
middle of nowhere and there's just this underwear hovering in midair moving
around. I don't know man that's actually creepier than your standard ghost walking
through a hallway. But rock on underwear I don't think you exist and I don't
think Ari Barker is real but still is an interesting story. But we talked. We
talked about the underwear we talked about Thieves' Oil. Let's go back one more
time to the vault of Sherry Schreiner. Again Gary opened up this whole can of
worms by sending me an email. Quick overview on Monday we did an episode
about a murder that was related to her cult. Second episode on Tuesday we did a
story about the life of Sherry Schreiner in her own words which is quite
interesting. Yesterday's episode was her frequently asked questions and magical
prayers you can do to fight aliens and then you're like "Jason I'm not a
religious person. I don't pray." Fair enough. You want the witch doctors to get
you? That's your business. But you're a man of science or a woman. You are a person
of science. You want to take the fight to the aliens directly. Well you know what
Sherry has an answer for you. Sherry has a device that you can actually but not a
device. A collection of materials that you can scrape up off the ground assuming
your ground is a home depot but you can get these materials and you can take the
fight directly to the aliens by littering with these materials. Let's go back in
time. Let's go back in time for a bit. We're going back to the year 1939. We're
gonna meet this guy in 1939 named William Reich. Now he was like this
socialist dude who's like a Marxist and he was watching this political protest
one day and he saw like all these people like "Oh yeah I go into government. I don't
know what country this is so I'm just gonna do a variety of accents but yeah
oh yeah yeah the government's like totally horrible and they're awful and
the masses said but as they were protesting the government they weren't
walking on the grass because there are signs saying keep off the grass and
William Reich goes hmm that's an interesting thing like these people are
out here protesting and rebelling but they won't do a simple rebellious act
is walk on the grass. He came to the conclusion that the reason why the
working classes were limited politically was because they didn't have
good orgasms in their life. If they had better orgasms it would enlighten them
to the struggle of all mankind. Now I don't know about that politically but I
do agree everyone should have better orgasms. That I think is fine. That's
totally good. But his views are so wacky other political activists were like "Hey
Willie, why don't you not come to our next meeting? Keep telling everyone to
masturbate?" He's like "What not man? I'm telling everyone to practice free love."
They're like "However you want to put it but okay he didn't actually start
telling people to masturbate in meetings. I should make a difference between a
joke and the historical fact." But he was basically other other political groups
are like "This guy's a little too wacky for us." Now he was a scientist he wasn't
just some bum hanging out which I mean some scientists are but he was he was
also into the belief that life could appear spontaneously. So you would have
he would get like soil and he'd be like looking at it and he goes "I know amoebas
are just gonna show up here one day." And through the course of his experiments he
ended up getting some different type of dirt than he normally does and he saw
like this blue outline around the dirt under his microscope and he said that he
had discovered the force. Now he didn't use that word because it wasn't
the exist fact then but that's basically what it is. It's the binding life cycle
that travels throughout the universe like everything comes from this stuff and
he found it in a sample of sand that is devoid of life and technically
everything should have and he starts like writing all these papers and he names
it "Orgon" or "Orgon" based on orgasms. Again he's still thinking about busting
in that the whole time he discovers a new source of life he names it after getting
off. So after his miraculous discovery he starts pushing all these papers on
"Orgon" or I'm gonna call it "Orgon" I think it's "Orgon" but I I'll just call it
"Orgon" okay? "Orgon" it just sounds weird. He starts writing all these papers on
"Orgon" and there he's turning them into scientific journals there why the page is
so sticky and he's like "uh sorry" but he was they can only read like the first
three pages the rest of it is glued together. So he believed that
"Orgon" held the universe together and it was also the key to having more
powerful orgasm so again like he was selling it as a curel and a sexual
fix. He also said if you're around enough "Orgon" your hips will start thrusting
back and forth and I'm doing it right now so you want to imagine me doing that you
probably even hear my chair rocking. If you're around a good supply of "Orgon"
you can't control your hips going back and forth it's basically like this
action that's going on this physical action that you can't control unconscious
action you can't control. So if you're ever walking on the street and you see
some weirdo just kind of swaying their hips back and forth you're like man
that guy is really in touch with the universe. He ended up building these huge
cabinets called like they were "Orgon containers" "Orgon containers" that wasn't
the actual it's like an "Orgon box" it was a box that you'd sit inside it had a
metal wall like metal lining on the inside and on the outside was all
natural wood and what the way it was set up was that the wood would attract the
"Orgon" to the box to the case it's a human size you'd sit in it in a chair I
think you know where we're going with this the maybe don't the the natural wood
on the outside would attract the "Orgon" moving through the universe it would
soak through it and then the metal inside would keep it trapped in there so
you're just getting all this "Orgon" right into your bloodstream right into your
brain right into every cell of your skin and you'd sit and people swore by these
things they were like these great medical devices people had and people were
buying them people were just jacking off in them I can almost guarantee that that
was just something I could I know that the people were just buying them to
masturbate in and being like is it think about it it's sold to give you good
orgasm and to cure some other stuff but people are only focused on that the man
of the house is like hey I'm gonna go recharge my "Orgon" kids see you later
mom will take care of you and then he just goes in there sits in there for five
minutes comes out that's what people are using them for it was basically a
private room for you to masturbate in now that's not a story that people won't
admit to that historically but come on come on that's what you're using them
for but other people said that it was actually this great medical device that
really helped him out and made him feel young and all that stuff but
masturbation does that too so a side note before I end that up he was selling it as
a as a cure all the FDA the Food and Drug Administration of America said none of
your claims are real you gotta stop doing that and he kind of did like he would
only do it in his lab you could then go to his place and rent and you could rent
an "Orgon" chamber at his lab which is gross because now he probably has like
five of them and there's probably like glory holes drilled in the side and all
sorts of gross stuff just manner showing up every day they're like hey do you got
room in the chamber they're bringing magazines with them he's like oh yeah
you can use chamber C but the FDA said you got to stop selling them and someone
else took one of his and sold it and the FDA actually threw him in jail for not
following their orders and they went to his laboratory destroyed all of his
research and all of his equipment and he ended up dying in jail a couple years
later of like a heart attack not enough "Orgon" in jail apparently that's the
story of William Reich and you go what is that any of that have to do with
Sherry Schreiner well that is what he's the one who discovered and kind of came
up with what "Orgon" is from that from that Sherry Schreiner and many many many
other people believe this as well that "Orgon" is not simply an element to cure
your rheumatoid arthritis that you got from masturbating all the time for the
better orgasms you got from the "Orgon" it's a vicious vicious cycle you can
actually use it to destroy UFOs aliens are allergic deadly allergic
anaphylactic levels of allergic to "Orgon" and their UFOs can burst into flames
among the presence of too much "Orgon" now again we just told you that it's all
throughout the universe the guy who discovered it it's all throughout the
universe it's for curing people it's for letting you get off harder here comes
been five minutes in my box and I'll show you how well it can work for you
Sherry Schreiner's turned it into a super weapon which would be the equivalent
of turning a fleshlight into Iron Man's arc reactor but it somehow she's able to
turn this sex toy slash quackery medical device into a weapon she's created
these things called "Orgon" I'm just gonna call it "Orgon" from here on out I'm sorry
you guys are getting frustrated but it just flows better for me "Orgon Blasters"
no I said it the other way whatever okay she made these things called "Orgon
Blasters" and they're actually she has that term trademarked because only she
can call it that not only can you make "Orgon Blasters" but you can infuse water
with "Orgon" just drop a couple of these things in here and I'll tell you how to
make it get a super soaker and then just start spraying aliens with "Orgon"
infused water catches them on fire generally the opposite of what water
does but you have that option now if you're ever fighting aliens and you have
to use one hand to carry a super soaker in the other hand to carry a bucket of
water you're probably not gonna last very long so she gives you more options
first she's gonna teach you how to make them so you take a muffin pan you know
the one with those little muffin slots in it so we're obviously talking about
high-tech sci-fi level technology you take a muffin pan you take some like
silicone resin type stuff you take metal shavings when she said you can cut up
aluminum like baking sheets but she goes that takes forever I'm sure she spent
weeks cutting these things up she goes go to a hardware store get some aluminum
shavings get your silicone get a copper swire and then you twist it clockwise not
counterclockwise but I don't understand that because if you flip it over won't
it be the opposite of whatever it is you put the spring in there you put the
metal shavings in there into the muffin can throw some pennies in there but they
have to be pre 1983 pennies because they have the most copper you fill a full of
resin and now you have this gross-looking mold that is full of a bunch of metal
copper and aluminum how do you fight aliens with that you litter she gives
you advice throw them out of your car as you're driving down the road you can
hide them in bushes you can actually keep one in your car it'll have lower gas
mileage you can put one under your electrical box at your house your
energy bill will go down it will go down because the meter reader won't come
around your house anymore because they'll think you're a lunatic because you
got all this weird metal stuff hanging outside around your house but throw them
outside your car while you're driving down the street hide them behind trees
hide them in trees bury them put them everywhere you're going to create a
circle a penetrable force field if you will around your house where the aliens
will be like something feels weird here but I don't know what it is maybe it's
all that copper and they run away that's not enough though she also tells you how
to make ones where you use a metal bucket and you put a giant steel rod in it I
don't know where the steel is coming from and then you do the rest of the stuff
the copper and all that stuff she recommends you take these five foot
tall monstrosities of metal and resin and to drop them in lakes rivers streams
and the ocean she even says this is a quote from her we have found that the
Oregon we are distributing and using across the country is defeating them
them being the reptilian alien demon overlords we need warriors who will make
or buy or go and distribute it around their areas you can throw it in ditches
trees bushes lakes ponds deserts who lives by a desert and that's a big thing
you just put like you just roll one of these out and you're like all done lakes
ponds deserts anywhere won't easily be found you can even bury it she wants to
litter the place the whole planet with these materials with these disgusting
litter and that'll make the aliens not come around so again Sherry Shreiner not
just the leader of this bizarre cult but actively encouraging people to litter
and pollute the oceans to defeat an invisible menace her beliefs indirectly
or directly depending how you feel about it ended up in a murder her beliefs
seem to have kind of set her life off course her beliefs have helped create a
delusional group of people who believe that they are ready and destined to fight
in a war against these alien demons to the point where they're donating tons of
money to her her beliefs have also led to a whole gaggle of followers who are
believe this stuff and are becoming more and more delusional the more of her
writings they read because it's not true none of it's true and now you could say
ah you know she didn't have anything to do with the murder what she does with
her own life is fine what other people do with their own lives are fine but now
she's actively encouraged people to destroy the environment to fight a group
of things these alien demon overlords controlled by Lucifer and actively
destroying the environment to fight this phantom menace if you will she's
hitting us on all points like there's almost there's no group of people she
hasn't offended she hasn't come after dog lovers yet but that might just be
down the pipe but here's the thing and we'll wrap it up like this here's my
conspiracy theory in the future the environment is completely destroyed
there's this weird magnetic energy coursing through the atmosphere and
future scientists cannot figure out what is going on they're like for some
reason everything seems to have aluminum in it and copper and not just copper and
not just any copper copper from pre 1983 pennies and the scientists are like what
could cause our rivers and our oceans and our deserts bushes to become infused
with aluminum and copper and scientists are like we have no idea but look look
outside the window desolate landscape everything tastes like wet pennies it's
completely destroyed the food sources it's completely destroyed the water
supply it's just a hellish landscape but we have this time machine and the other
scientists are like hey where'd that come from and he's like I went to the
future and got it they're like oh that makes sense we got this time machine we
don't know where this pollution is coming from but we know how to
counteract it first we're gonna go back in time to when we believe the pollution
started then I have a plan it's called chemtrails I believe chemtrails can
counteract whatever this pollution was and they go why why'd your voice sound
differently now and he's like ah cuz I had to fix something in editing it
doesn't matter the plane still valid I've come up with this thing that I want to
call chemtrails we're gonna put it in planes and we're gonna fly around the
earth no one's gonna know we're doing it we're gonna be super stealthy about it
won't ever be caught on video or YouTube and by releasing chemicals into the air
it will actually counteract all of this horrible horrible pollution that's been
mysteriously done a hundred years ago and other scientists are like yeah it's a
great idea and as they're discussing it they look out their window and the
world starts to bloom and get better and the trees come back and some guys
eating chicken and goes this tastes like chicken scientists are like yay just
by talking about time travel we made it happen now obviously that's a facetious
theory but maybe not when you're dealing with such bizarre things as witch
doctors laser beams coming through your windows alien demons being directed by
Lucifer and an unemployed single mom in Ohio realizing that the Bible is
telling her that she is one of the prophets who will help protect the
universe from Lucifer when all of those other bizarre things are in play
anything you can make up is just as valid and that is a scary world to live in
dead rabbit radio gmail.com is gonna be your email address you can also hit us
up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is @jasonOcarpenter
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast you
don't have to listen to it every day I'm glad you listen to it today have a great
one guys
[Music]