Here I am.
It's rocking me like a hurricane.
Is that not the song?
Wait, no, I'm sorry.
This is supposed to be somber.
[singing]
That's Enya music playing.
Enya sitting in the darkness.
We're in the pitch darkness of Dead Rabbit Command.
I have a special announcement for all of you.
I wasn't originally going to include this on the opening of an episode, but it was kind
of bringing the mood down for the episode.
I knew this was going to happen, and I've been predicting it for hundreds of episodes
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
We're sitting in a pitch black room in Dead Rabbit Command, and there's like a lump in
the middle of the room.
And you're sitting on it, and I'm like, "No, no, get off that lump.
It's sacred.
Come sit by me."
I knew this was going to happen.
The YouTube channel is done.
Dead Rabbit Radio YouTube channel is absolutely done.
I'm including this as a separate feature, because some people want to know this, and
I think it's important to know for just the future of conspiracy content and paranormal
content on YouTube.
But if you don't want to know about it and just want to hear goofy stories, I totally
respect that.
What is going on was last Sunday, I was just, I don't remember what the episode was, and
I got hit with a content warning for an episode I did 200 episodes ago.
I got hit with promoting harmful or misleading information.
I was like, "What could possibly, what was it?"
It was nothing I said.
I included a link into YouTube, because I included my show notes, because I think when
you make crazy, it would be really easy for me to say, "You won't believe what this guy
over here says, and just make a bunch of stuff up."
And I'm lambasting this guy.
I'm lambasting this person who says they're a super soldier or whatever, some stupid belief.
We're just making it about a whole cloth, and you'd be like, "Oh, that is crazy, and
there's no way to check my work."
And it's also important, because I considered this paranormal research for other people
to continue from the research.
So I include the show notes.
It was the episode about Civil War of the Worlds.
It was the episode, this guy had a website, it was a Civil War fan website, and he had
an April Fool's article about space aliens invading during the Civil War.
And I covered it, because I was like, "What?
I've never heard of this story before."
The Mysterious Universe covered it, I covered it off of them, and then it turns out that
it was an April Fool's joke, which made the story even better.
And I got to talk to the author of the article.
It was a great way to end the whole saga.
But now we are 200 episodes later, which is 40 weeks, which is almost a year later.
And I get hit with promoting harmful or misleading information, and I thought, "What in the world?"
I thought, "What?
A tarnation?"
I turned into a cartoon character.
You know, Sam and Sam says that right now.
I don't know.
It has nothing to do with the somber mood.
The point is that I filed an appeal.
I got that warning last week that said, "Hey, this is content warning.
You're promoting this stuff."
I filed an appeal, and I was kind of flabbergasted.
I guess I am a cartoon character.
I'm flabbergasted.
I said, "Hey, it's a..."
You know, I covered the story.
It's in the show notes.
I go, "It's an April Fool's joke."
Like, sure, it didn't really happen, but it's an April Fool's joke.
But I found that...
My thing was that 90% of the stuff that we covered could be considered harmful or misleading.
In some way.
Someone goes, "Ghosts don't exist.
It's very misleading that this guy's talking about ghosts exist."
He labeled this as a cult.
That's not a cult.
It's just 12 people who hang in a barn who just like murdering people.
That's not a cult, though.
Don't infer they're a cult.
You can call them a bunch of killers.
That's harmful to that religion.
So you could do that with pretty much everything we talk about on this show.
It's harmful or it's misleading.
I was like, "Okay, this must be some sort of glitch."
I filed the appeal and then one week later, exactly one week later, I just recorded and
uploaded yesterday's episode, which would have been the Orangevale episode, which I
really enjoyed.
It was a slog.
I recorded an episode.
I had to re-record it.
I recorded the Orangevale episode and at the end of it was the episode, the segment about
the man who built a hidey hole in a men's restroom and he stuck his head underneath the urinal
and people were peeing on him.
Now I got, the first one was a warning because of that story, I got another content strike.
But it wasn't because of what I said.
It was because of the link to the Vice News article, which was listed as nudity or sexual,
is what it said.
And I thought, "Well, listen, the person who's flagging on YouTube might really find it sexy
when people get peed on.
There's definitely no nudity in there."
And if you read the article, there is no explicit, like, "Oh, he must have been doing this and
it must have filled this good."
It's a guy telling a story to the reporter.
It's very like, "Hey, you won't believe what happened.
I worked at a pub and pretty much the same narrative I told you."
So it's nothing I'm saying, it's my links.
But at this point, I cannot upload or comment or post anything, livestream or anything to
YouTube for the next week.
So I'm done.
Because I'm not gonna, I tried for the past couple of episodes, if you look at YouTube,
I started going into the document and making it so goes, if you wanna see the show notes,
go to this page on my DeadRabbit.com website.
I'm gonna show you the show notes for that episode.
I started doing that, but this one happened within 10 minutes.
This one happened before I could, and I didn't think it was gonna happen, but within 10 minutes
of me uploading the episode, I got a content strike.
The fact of the matter is, if I'm getting hit for a website that I posted 200 episodes
ago, there's 642 time bombs out there on my channel that the algorithm or someone at YouTube
is personally going through and going harmful, misleading.
So I'm not going to play that game.
I am making a decision to stop uploading to YouTube.
The YouTube episodes are going to end at 642, and we're gonna go ahead in other 600, 800,
1000 episodes.
They're not gonna be available on YouTube.
I am making the decision that I'm, the main reason, because I could basically just burn
it to the ground and just keep putting out content until it gets copyrighted, striked
into existence, or content striked into existence.
I could do that.
I kinda like the fact that I have a platform for, I can hit a button and I can start live
streaming to a channel where I have a bunch of subscribers.
I'm still thinking in the future I may live stream to advertise for the podcast.
Maybe once a month pop in and go, "Hey, this is what you guys have been missing if you
haven't been watching the podcast."
I might do that.
I don't know.
I like having the opportunity of live streaming.
Definitely like the opportunity of live streaming, but I have to kind of weigh the pros and
the cons of that.
But definitely no new content on DeadRabbit Radio outside maybe live streaming.
And really that will only exist until I figure out a way that I can make a Twitch thing.
What do you kids call that?
A Twitch account?
No, I have a Twitch account.
But until I can know that if I hit a button that you guys will be notified.
Because a lot of you guys would jump, when I start a live stream, I'd get 40 people
watching right away, which was really good on YouTube.
So I want to keep it for that.
And I can advertise the show as that.
And all that content and all the community that we've built, all those comments, all
that interaction I've had with you guys.
If I just nuke the channel, if I just start keep putting the stuff out and don't let this
get-- And even if they resolve this in my favor, I'm still done.
I'm still done.
I'm total-- Because they're both still in appeal.
Both of these things are both still in appeal.
The first one, I go, dude, you didn't even let the first appeal play out.
And I'm getting hit with this other one.
I go, it's a vice.com article.
There's nothing sexual about it.
There's nothing nude about it.
And then, you know, but I do think it's fitting.
I thought it was funny as when I saw that that happened, I thought, great, the last
episode that I post on YouTube is the episode where I say, you know, it'd be really cool
if everyone could just forget their differences.
Not forget their differences, but acknowledge their differences, but work towards a better
and brighter future for everybody.
I said it's a very childish way of looking at the world, but it's something I've never
grown out of.
I think eventually we can all work together as one human race and still have our differences.
YouTube's like, nope, nope, this is the type of content this guy's putting out.
Let's hit him with this nudity strike a week after his first one.
We're not going to let this appeal process play out.
We're not going to let him upload for a week.
YouTube's like, nah, we don't want this content on here.
We don't want this stuff.
We don't want someone disputing conspiracy theories.
Nah, nah, we want 6 hour videos on flat earth.
You know, to be okay, that's not fair.
That's not fair.
I don't want to have a persecution complex.
My actual fear about this isn't so fine.
I'd been predicting this for years.
I've had backup plans.
I mean, I thought, you know, we'll eventually move to Twitch.
I knew YouTube was pretty shaky.
I've been saying it for a long time.
I'm showing people are saying, you're paranoid, you're paranoid.
My concern is that I am, and I think, I hit the peel button a week ago and haven't heard
back.
I've been doing this everywhere and I bet you they're getting hit with tons of appeals
and I think a lot of channels are going to get shut down.
I think a lot of channels doing stuff like this, but they're coming for Wendigoon.
They're coming for all of this content.
They're coming for that chapter.
They're coming for Nexpo.
I think they're really going to start just sweeping all of this stuff up.
I'm not going to bit shoot.
I don't think that that's the right format.
Also, it's extra work.
YouTube, I just hit a button and it automatically uploaded to YouTube with a static image.
I'd have to do video processing again like I did in the early days.
I think that this is a harbinger for things to come.
I think that, and I knew it was going to happen.
I 100% knew it was going to happen when I saw, and I would joke about it, I go, that's
why Hans Wormhatt's channels are getting shut down all the time.
Even though I talk about stuff in a way that I'm like, I don't believe this.
It doesn't make sense.
The algorithm I knew would eventually start just real life thinking that I was part of
the conspiracy promoters.
There's some, even the stuff right at the end, let's put on our conspiracy caps.
Let's look at it this way.
I knew that it was coming.
We are sitting in a dark and dead rabbit command and I throw a torch.
I was holding the torch this whole time.
You didn't know it.
You just didn't right next to me.
You had a torch in your face.
You're like, "Ah, I throw the torch onto the lump in the middle of the room."
It is the YouTube channel in effigy.
It's burning and we're just standing there in your music playing.
It's still burning.
We're just standing there.
Forgot we're doing this indoors.
Smoke inhalation.
We go outside a dead rabbit command.
We're looking through a window as we're watching the YouTube channel burn.
I'm no longer going to upload on YouTube.
Keep it around for the live streams.
I think it would be really cool to figure out a way.
I couldn't do it weekly because it's too much work, but figure out a way that we could all
get together and talk on YouTube.
I don't know.
We're just going to stop posting new content on there.
Also, if you do listen to the show, obviously you're hearing this.
There's a lot of people who listen to it on YouTube who don't know what's going on.
They're going to spend a whole week going like, "What?"
If you do happen to see them online or in real life, you have a buddy who just always
watches YouTube and be like, "Hey, Jason is now primary only on podcast channels and
dead rabbit.com."
So that's how you will be able to listen to him from now on.
Fire is burning.
It's just the end of a chapter.
It's not the end of the show.
It is something that I expected.
If I can figure out a way to alert everyone when I'm doing a Twitch live stream, we will
just do that as well because I just don't want...
Right now, I'm having to download as much content as I can because for all I know the
channel's gone while I've been recording this.
I could be racking up strikes from past content.
We're just doing that.
That would be not...
I'm not going to do bit shoot.
But yeah, maybe we'll see about Twitch.
I got some other tricks up my sleeve.
Some other tricks up my sleeve.
But the show is not going anywhere.
The podcast is completely safe.
Spotify doesn't work like a certain episode of mine, but that's fair.
The same thing.
YouTube is a private...
It's a private business.
If they want to get rid of all conspiracy and all paranormal content and all true crime
content and clear it up and just have makeup channels, that's their right.
That's their right to do that.
But we will not be a part of that anymore.
To all the friends that I made on YouTube, you guys are still around.
You guys are still going to be able to talk and I'd like to figure out a way that we could
still meet up.
And that's why we may still do a live stream every now and then.
But that...
We will decide on later.
So let the Ineon Music play us out.
And I'll have an episode coming out in a couple hours, guys.
I love you.
Thanks for sticking around and I will see you soon.
[singing in foreign language]