When a woman hitches a ride with a creepy trucker, you will guess what happens next.
And then we go hunting with three Indians in Canada. The year is 1938.
They're looking to just shoot some elk, bag a deer or two, but instead they find a bear
fighting Bigfoot today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I think
you guys can hear I'm feeling much, much better. Still a little short-winded, still can't
breathe through my nose, but I'm A-OK on everything else. It's funny because I've been
in self-isolation for about four days, four days in a row, but at a certain point it's
like I gotta go outside, right? Going crazy in here. So I went and I don't have the coronavirus,
okay? If I do have it, everyone in town has it. But anyways, I'm walking down the street
and we're after the day where everyone flooded the Walmart, flooded the Rite Aid, the Walgreens,
the Rosars, bought all the stuff. The day after everyone panicked. Walking down the street,
everything's kind of back to normal. People at the coffee shop, people are buying overpriced
toys. It's just the way Hood River is. But every so often I'd go and I'd have a little
cough. I felt like the guy in a zombie movie who's gotten bit, but doesn't want anyone
else to know that he's bit. I'd be like walking around and I'd be like, I have to cough and
I'm like, I'm like duck into an alley and go coughing on my elbow. Did anyone see that?
Expecting cops to come and trank me. And the next thing I know, I wake up in some isolation
ward in China, but I am still taking the steps to self-isolate. I'm still doing all that.
I have one more grocery run to do tomorrow and then I'm sitting well. I have a lot of
stuff now, but I'd like to diversify my food and drink supplies. But I hope you guys are
doing great. And honestly, other than like funny stories like I just told you, feeling
like I was the traitor in a zombie movie, we're really not going to talk about the coronavirus.
We're going to treat the coronavirus like I treat politics on this show. You get enough
of that just turning it on the television set. Doesn't mean it's not important, but
you get enough of it. So every show often I might tell a funny anecdote or two, but
we're not going to talk about any conspiracy theories. I'm sorry. Actually, I'm not. I
already read too much of it and it gets kind of overwhelms me and then I will just have
to, you know, go and start playing balloon invasion. Just some flash came from like
2011. It's like my comfy game or I'm playing Minecraft and stuff like that. So we're not
going to talk about coronavirus unless a huge news pops up about it. I think there's major
outlets that can cover that. We're going to cover fun stuff like our next story. Now,
our next story is fun for us because we weren't involved in it, but there's multiple people
suffered because of this story. Still very fascinating. And I want to give a shout out
to a classic Patreon. I want to give shout outs to people who continue to support the
show. Dave, Dave is one of the earliest Patreon supporters. Thank you so much for supporting
this show. Really, really helps a lot. We're going to give you the end of your cancer where
the Patreon. You can always help the show just by getting the word out. I always want
to give a shout out to the people out there too who can't financially support the show.
You can still help get the word out about the show. That helps a lot as well. But thank
you so much Dave and all my other Patreons as well. Dave, take the keys to the Jason
Jalopy. We are hitting the highways checking the highways, going down the road. I can't
sing the rest of that. You guys don't even know what song that was, you lunatic. If I
sing the rest of it, the video will get taken off YouTube. But let's just say some people
are born to be wild. That's unrelated to the tune I was just singing. It's May 22, 2019.
So very, very recent. Those are cars driving by. Or in Fort Campbell, Kentucky. And it's
Interstate 24 in this woman's car, this unnamed woman. She should be named. We'll know why.
I'll tell you why she should be named at the end of it. Her car is out of gas. Oh no. What?
Did I forget how to operate a car? Actually no, I shouldn't make fun of her. I've had
cars run out of gas multiple times. So we're not going to mock her. Because I'm empathetic.
If I never ran out of gas, I would totally make fun of her. Cars are driving by her.
People are nowhere. And then a truck, like a big rig pulls up. It slows down. I really
got my sound effects on point today. I should get sick more often. Birds are chirping. Okay,
that was pushing it. That was pushing it. Anyways, truck pulls over. The trucker's name
is Roy Nelsch. Roy Nelsch. And he's like, "Hey ma'am, you need a lift?" Now, we're not
going to make this an interactive episode. But if you were in this situation, your car
is out of gas here in the middle of nowhere, a semi pulls up, and a guy offers you a ride.
Would you get in? If a truck... I've had people offer to give me rides because I walk around
Sacramento all the time. Did I tell you guys about this? I did tell you that guy was like,
all super creepy and trying to get me in his car because he wanted to bang me. I know I
mentioned that a couple episodes ago. You're like, "No, you never told us that story."
Yeah, but I'm not going to tell it now. But anyways, sometimes I'm walking through the
hood of a river and people will pull up and be like, "Hey, you want a ride?" And I'll
be like, "No, stranger danger. I don't tell them that, but I don't get in rides with people
I don't know." So anyways, you wouldn't get in this truck, right? I wouldn't get in this
semi at all. I wouldn't get in a semi truck of someone I knew because I still think they
were a serial killer. But anyways, this woman goes... I don't know what time of day this
happened, but this woman goes, "Sure, I'll get in your truck." So anyways, you know what
happens next, right? But you don't. I love this story. Truck is driving the ladies in
the passenger seat and the truck driver's driving. And she needed to get off at this
next exit. The truck driver's like, "Yeah, totally." Pass that exit. And she's like,
"Oh, no, no, no, no. I'm supposed to get off that exit." He's like, "Oh, sorry, sorry."
Passes the next exit. Now she's getting nervous. Sweatin', hearts racing. Pass the next exit.
She starts freaking out because now she realized she made a mistake. Roy, the truck driver,
pulls out a gun and says, "I'm gonna kidnap you and I'm gonna rape you." Now I don't
know if he said it like that. He probably was a little more menacing and he probably
like, "I don't know. I don't know if he built it up or sugar-coated it or something, but
I don't know if he was that blunt." But the point is, is that now she's aware that she
got into the wrong truck. She's gonna be kidnapped, which she's currently being kidnapped and
raped and possibly murdered, right? He didn't threaten to murder her yet. Get in the sleeper
part of the cab. She's a little like box room if you're not familiar with semi-trucks. Behind
the driver's wheel, I'm apparently not familiar with semi-trucks, but you know where the driver
wheel, you know the steering wheel, that's what it's called, the place where the driver
sits and steers it. Behind him is like a bed. So imagine if it was Optimus Prime, it would
be like in where Optimus Prime's head is. That's where the sleeper area is. So she gets
back there and he, or he's trying to get her back there and she starts fighting. She starts
putting up a fight. So he's driving the semi and he's fighting this girl and she gets the
gun and she points it at him and pulls the trigger. Click. Now, it's unknown whether
or not the gun was unloaded or the gun misfired. I think the gun was unloaded, honestly. I
think if you looked at serial killers, like if you really like delved into serial killer
stuff, I bet a lot of times they use unloaded guns because that's even more like you could
have got away, but I tricked you with my gun. Serial killers are so just like mentally ill,
mentally deficient, and they're so powerless in normal life that any amount of power they
can get is what they crave. Generally, I've said this before, serial killers, serial killers
are men, really, men whose dicks don't work. When you bake it down to that, it's men who
can't get off unless they're killing people who remind them of their mom or the girl who
broke up with them in high school and they never got over it. Like all serial killers,
even the serial killers who are trying to bang their dad or the boy who broke up them in
high school, like John Wayne Gacy, it's all, their dicks don't work. I should have said
this is going to be an explicit episode. So they need every sense of power. So having
a loaded gun and pointing it at someone is a sense of power, but tricking someone, being
like, oh, you could have got away if you knew the gun wasn't loaded. Now you're chained
up and you can't get away. I think, because John Wayne Gacy did that. He'd go, hey, you
want to see a magic trick? It wasn't so much the fact that he overpowered the kids, it was
the fact that he tricked them into their own demise. John Wayne Gacy would put handcuffs
on and then put his hands behind his, or have his hands behind his back to the handcuffs
on and then go, ta-da. Look it, I did it. It's a magic trick. You want to see how to
do it. The kid would be like, yeah, sure. He'd get handcuffed behind the back and John
Wayne Gacy would say, the trick is to have the key and then he would kill the kid. And
so that's the part of that power trip. Now, John Wayne Gacy, his dick didn't work unless
he was in that situation. He was a powerless little man. And that's this guy too. This
guy had no respect for serial killer. We've done episodes on this in the past. Long time
listeners are like, oh, I'm fast forwarding. I've heard this rant. But it's important because
I think they're punks and I think they're little babies. They didn't get enough love
in their life. So now they think that he can kill a couple prostitutes and then everything,
now they're powerful. Whatever, bro. Disgust me. But anyways, let's get back to this piece
of filth. He's driving on the road. She grabs the gun. She pulls the trigger. Nothing happens.
He pulls another gun out and pistol whips her handcuffs her throws a blanket on her. Now
I'm assuming at points he was at least slowing down the truck. I don't know if he was going
60 this whole time, but and he actually is still driving because I know now remember
this part. I remembered as an I looked over my notes. So he is still driving because what
happens is she's handcuffed. She's underneath a blanket. She slips one of her hands out
of a handcuff takes the blanket throws it over his head gets him in a chokehold and
begins grabs the wheel and begins swerving the semi side to side across the freeway.
At this point, the guy pulls over and kicks her out of the truck. He's just like this
is not this whatever my intent was totally not worth being kicks her out of a truck.
Her car is driving down the road and sees kind of what's going on pulls over and she
goes oh my God you won't believe what just happened. He's like yeah it's all you get
kicked out of a car and you have handcuffs on. Yeah yeah call the police. The police pull
over this truck. The trial is going on now. This is why this is in the news. Roy ends
up getting arrested pretty quickly and the trial is going on now. So we're getting all
this information out about him. So first you're thinking maybe he's just some guy who can't
get it up and then he decides to pull a gun out and try to like rape this woman or try
to have power over this woman. What the police have found so they found in his property trucks
and home and all that stuff a ledger full of the names of women and children which is
weird I don't know how they'd have how they know the names are of children unless it was
like Bobby or like current names like all the names are like Edward and Bella you'd
probably be like oh there's a kid names but other than that they must be able to connect
it to some living people. He had in his possession not only to have this weird ledger but he had
10,000 images of child abuse. He had bloody underwear in his truck. He had chat conversations
with other people offering children for abuse. Blood on his steering wheel. Blood on his
driver's seat. Blanket with blood stains. Rope handcuffs. Stun gun. Which is funny because
it's good that's not funny not owning a stun gun is funny but it's a good thing he didn't
use that on her because it could have went somewhere else. So they don't know if Roy
Nellish is some sort of sicko serial killer if he's just a sicko if he's a poser if he's
a pretender who knows but he's currently on trial and hopefully he goes to prison for
a long long time and I'll say this the reason why we should know that woman's name because
that's pretty badass right that's badass like that woman and I could understand her not
wanting to get her name out there but especially it's kind of creepy that he has like this
chat combos with others offering these kids for abuse. Who are those other people? Why
aren't they in jail? Hopefully they're headed to jail. Maybe she just doesn't want the attention
to something like that but that's a hero. We applaud you nameless woman on Interstate
24 because you took every step you needed to to survive and when you're dealing with
a sicko creep like that you stopped him. His reign of terror ended because you were totally
badass so that applause is not is not sarcastic really I mean you are an honorary member of
the fluffle which is the name which is the scientific name for a group of rabbits. You
are a honorary member of our patreon nameless woman that's weird. You are a dead rabbit
radio person I don't know you guys get it I'm trying to instill an honor on her but
I don't really need to because nature made her an awesome butt kicking person that's
all the honor she needs. Anyways maybe she's traveling America now killing other serial
killers so I thought that story is really interesting that guy's disgusting and I was
able to go off on another serial killer rant because it's just been about 200 episodes
since I've done that because I don't want to beat a dead horse but god I hate those
guys. Let's go ahead and though and move on to our next topic so Dave let's go ahead
and fire up the carbonar copter we're gonna park the Jason Jalopy we're gonna take the
carbonar copter because we got a long way to go from Kentucky we're headed up to I
think so I don't know I don't know where's that on the map we're headed up to British
Columbia and we're going to a place called Chillowack now we're gonna talk about a very
bizarre news article and when I first saw it I go hmm there's a large possibility this
news article doesn't exist we've run into that a lot on this podcast where we find a
news article and find out that it's forged or it's some viral marketing for some movie
or something like that. This one I actually found the article it was published in a newspaper
called the Chillowack Progress you can go to the link it's in the newspapers archives
this article is 100% real whether or not the events are the article is real so that's
a good sign because we've covered we've uncovered a lot of hoaxes on this show but anyway so
we're headed up to Chillowack and that's in British Columbia we're going back to the
year it's 1938 it's February 23rd 1938 and we're going to land and first we're gonna
pick up a newspaper because this is an odd this this every news article should have a
lead like this leads always the first paragraph of the article in a newspaper newspapers are
written like an inverted pyramid the way they do it is the most important information is
at the top in the further you read in the article the less important information gets
it's very easy to edit and you just stop reading halfway through and then there's a thing called
burying the lead where you have the most important stuff at the bottom but this one that's from
journalism that's from a journalism degree but every article in the world should be written
with this every article should just start with this paragraph actually but if you can't
start with this paragraph you should start with this style here we go a terrific battle
a fight for life of prodigious strength matched against savage ferocity between a hairy giant
of the Sasquatch so right in the article they're just like oh yeah by the way Bigfoot exists
this is a real newspaper this isn't a tabloid this is an actual newspaper still around apparently
a terrific battle a fight for life of prodigious strength matched against savage ferocity between
a hairy giant of the Sasquatch and a huge bear which after 10 minutes of wild struggle
fury and rage dot dot dot I'm not gonna give away the ending they do there's a thing called
burying the lead there's a thing just giving away the ending in the opening paragraph they
should have just ended it there but that's how every article should be it's just one
of that that just get your heart pumping so in this article it explains the story of
these three Indians they're Harrison River Indians so let's join them in the forest this
happens only a week before February 23rd so we don't have far to go back in time and there's
three dudes walking through the forest they're hunting just hanging out they're looking to
shoot living things in the brain and then consume the meat for energy and maybe make
some new shoes I don't know but they're walking through this forest and they haven't shot
anything yet they're really disappointed that nothing is dead they're like oh dang it and
you know they're probably hungry too but anyways they can't find anything and then in the forest
now in this article the main guy being quoted of the Indian I wanted to say Native Americans
but they're in Canada the Indians is a guy named Jimmy Craneback he's being quoted in
this article and he's saying they heard this roar they're dealing the forest they hear this
roar birds scatter out of their nests fly off into the sky they hear trees they hear
trees getting pushed like something's pushing against them they can hear the trees crack
they can see the leaves sway through the tree tops okay maybe they didn't see that part
but the fact is that they're not eight feet tall they can't see over the tree top but
they hear the crack of tree branches snapping and loud thuds like two things are just going
to war in the middle of this forest throwing each other up against trees a true battle
of the beasts so these three dudes are like okay here's the thing that's super spooky
right we don't want to go anywhere near that but it's February and bears are super hungry
around this time they're really lean they're really angry and we got women in the woods
doing the gathering thing we're doing the hunting thing women are like picking up mushrooms
and collecting berries and all that stuff so we have to at least see what that is because
if it's two bears fighting we'll go kill them both we'll bring home some bear meat or we'll
just scare them off so everyone else here doesn't have to worry about getting mauled
to death so the three men begin walking through the woods towards the sound of the commotion
rock keep her in it again closing so now at this point when they get to the ravine they
go okay now we got to make a decision because there's definitely two bears fighting here
if they they look like they're gonna fall over the wrestling it's so it's such a violent
match looks like they're both gonna fall under the river then they're just they're both
gonna die and no good comes out of it let's shoot them now and then we can at least eat
them they're both gonna die anyways but we get something so they raise their rifles they're
ready to aim and right before they can take a shot one of the creatures one of the supposed
bears says something echoes through the forest then Indians look at each other and they're
like oh it's the Sasquatch and they know that they said if he had said nothing they both
would have been dead it was shot him both and then they'd been like oh no Sasquatch we
shot this mythological creature in the brain I guess we're still gonna eat it I wonder
if anyone's eaten Sasquatch I wonder if anyone's eaten Bigfoot meat that would actually be
an interesting thing like you always have like the ultra rich like oh they inject the
blood of the young or they're eating babies we should start a conspiracy theory that the
ultra rich dying on Bigfoot meat that's why you can never find them because George Soros
has eaten all of them he's like mmm I love the yeti but North American Sasquatch has
a particular meaty they're all meaty it's meat but anyways new conspiracy theory the
ultra rich eat Bigfoot they though realize that oh this is Bigfoot like we've heard
about Bigfoot in our area let's not shoot them and let's start cheering they're like
yeah go on Bigfoot go so with the cheering behind him Bigfoot turned like oh me feel
better now me and oh get home turf advantage he gets the bear in a headlock a chokehold
really and chokes him out they say that the bears tongue sticking out of its mouth as
the Bigfoot got the chokehold even tighter tighter tighter and then finally the bear
went limp and then died but that's not enough for Bigfoot boys he's not that type he's
not just gonna choke you out and leave your body there he then picks the bear up and
throws it into the river and the Indian dudes clapped as Bigfoot walks away so then they
came back to town and they told everyone this story now whether or not that story is true
who knows it does raise a couple interesting questions one Bigfoot would be beating the
crap out of bears constantly bears are very violent territorial Bigfoot he doesn't really
have many places to go he lives in the woods they're both giant I think if you and I we
could do math on this or I could probably watch a YouTube video on this but a gorilla versus
a bear I think the gorilla stronger I think the bear has like the big old claws all the
muscle to punch through but I'm pretty sure the gorilla could to break them up and I don't
think it would be a controversial statement to say that Bigfoot stronger than a gorilla
so I think it at least would be a savage battle but you go Jason so we have the story of three
men back in 1938 there's no evidence for this whatsoever it was printed in the newspaper
it's a very entertaining article you can read it in the show notes that's I mean any three
dudes can go walking through the woods the story is over a hundred years old there's a
shh because that's not the only encounter of a Bigfoot and a bear and not only is that
not the only encounter with a Bigfoot and a bear that is the encounter you would tell
a little baby to put them to sleep oh Bigfoot is nice and chokes the bear out and throws
them in the water let's go to Russia it's autumn 1989 we're in the Ark Ark Angel's
Ark Angel's region in Russia there's a guy he's a professor of medicine his name is
doctor in Alutsk collecting herbs in the middle of the forest so we have a story that's much
more recent in time with a doctor supposedly assuming this guy exists well just exists
for the for the entertainment value of the story we have a doctor who's most likely still
alive and he's a professor of medicine again assuming that's the author didn't just make
this up this is taken from a magazine a paranormal magazine called periscope it's written by
Paul Stonehill but anyways doctor Alutsky is hanging out in the forest he's collecting
herbs and stuff like that he's probably nerd this is his hobby he's like ooh a particularly
delicious herb I heard this the herb that I'm supposed to eat but I don't want to throw
up well I eat disgusting herbs oh yes we'll take a lot of these herbs are gross and he's
sitting there he's by the river there's a it's funny because there's some parallels in
this story this one the guys collecting herbs in the first story the Indians were afraid
of other people just kind of randomly collecting herbs both of these stories take place by a
river both of these stories involve a big foot and a bear that's where they end because
in this story he's sitting there he's collecting herbs and berries and all that stuff and he
sees a bear cub kind of walk out of the forest and begin yelping at him and he's like are
you kidding me and then he hears also in the forest the mama bear coming and he's like
okay herb mission herb mission is over I'm out of here all he has is a knife on him he
gets up and he starts running because he knows that he it's already too late like he knows
the fact that he can see the baby bear means that he's already in trouble and he begins
running and then he hears a horrible sound from behind him his brain can't even register
what could possibly be making the sound and under what circumstances would cause anything
to make this sound and he turns around and he sees the mama bear now out in the open
by the cub and standing behind the mama bear is a gorilla like creature that's two and
a half meters tall eight feet tall he said it was a female had large fangs and it was
holding the mama bear by its back legs it then in one motion with no visible effort hoisted
the mama bear up holding it by its hind legs and then ripped it apart like a wishbone
within a matter of seconds he said it was like nothing picking up this big Russian bear
and just splitting it open fur and muscle and blood spilling out into the river it's
funny because humans really anthropomorphize nature I was watching videos of bears in
preparation for this story little bear cubs walking around I was like oh they look like
dogs oh look at the way like I can see the way the mom looks at those cubs kind of looks
like she's a little tired because you had a long day work she doesn't work she eats
stuff but we put our emotions on stuff and I think we do the same thing with Bigfoot
we see Bigfoot as always like this lost cryptid of this tribe or he's some species that hasn't
been encountered but maybe they have rituals and they bury their dead and that's why we
can't find them or maybe they get angry and they throw rocks if they exist they are beasts
of the wild if they exist they fight every day against savage creatures it's less hairy
in the Henderson's and more like dirty hairy like you would have to Bigfoot's would have
to be violent by nature because nature is violent you may be able to live out in the
woods as a human and grow a little patch of patchouli and eat that all day long and live
off four leaf clovers and live a peaceful life but if you didn't even have a hut if
you were living in a cave you'd be strangling ducks all day long and beating up raccoons
and eating them that's what we used to do we become civilized and now we live in buildings
and we just eat duck we let someone else beat it up at a farm but the Bigfoot's never
become civilized like that definitely not in these two circumstances and because Bigfoot
are already so hard to find they could be doing this 24/7 they could constantly just
be walking through nature stepping on the backs of bobcats picking up skunks and like
putting their hands up their butts and using them as boxing gloves is like punching elk
in the face a Bigfoot is a wild creature and all the Bigfoot hunters and Squatch hunters
and all that stuff desperately seeking Squatch all of them they hope they're gonna run into
the Bigfoot that's like me Bigfoot me friend but the truth is Bigfoot's a big old monster
and yeah it could be nice just like you may run into a bear and it looks at you and just
like walks away and you go I had a good encounter with a bear not all bears are like that bear
I met was totally fine and didn't maul me but you're really taking your chance between
Bigfoot greeting you giving you a high five and Bigfoot grabbing your legs and as the
Bigfoot is tearing you into you're the one making the horrifying noise that scatters
the birds from trees and makes the rest of nature go silent be careful how their Bigfoot
hunters you can't find them if he's right behind you
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up
at facebook.com/deadratvoradio Twitter is @deadratvoradio and Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day and I'm glad
to listen to it today have a great one guys.
[Music]