Today, we look at two cases where ghosts helped solve their own murders.
First off, we head to Australia, where a man who's gone missing may have left the ultimate
clue.
And then we travel back to the United States to meet a grieving mother who prays every
single night that the spirit of her daughter will give her a message.
And then one night, her daughter arrives.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover, so we're gonna get started.
Order in the court.
Today we're talking about ghosts that helped solve their own murders.
So let's hop on board the carpenter copter.
First off, let's pack it full of all the stereotypical Australian stuff.
We got shrimp on the barbie.
We got Foster's beer.
We got Knot Knives.
These are knives.
We're all ready to go.
We're flying to Campbelltown in New South Wales, Australia.
It's flying over.
It's a dusty little village.
I'm assuming we land.
We hop out of the helicopter.
And it's 1826, so it's super old-timey.
It's extra dusty back then.
June 17th.
Walking around Campbelltown.
It's a nice old place, right?
Not a place you would want to live.
It's where convicted felons from England are still being transported.
So everyone there is a felon.
That's why we have our...
Those aren't knives.
These are knives.
We're all pulling them out.
Walking out of the street with our blades ready.
No one's gonna mess with us.
We go to the helicopter currently.
They're currently scuttling the helicopter, taking everything they can carry.
We go on a local saloon and there we meet George Worrell.
Hey, George, what's up?
He's like, "Hey guys, have a seat.
You can have any drink you want as long as you pay for it."
That's how bars normally work, right?
So we're like, "Okay, fine."
Now, George is friends with Frederick Fisher.
They actually both wore convicts from England, but it served their time in Australia.
And Frederick was like, "You know what?
I own some property here, but I'm done.
I got my farm, but I just...
I don't like it.
It's gross.
It's dusty.
There's like snakes everywhere.
A helicopter landed in the middle of my farm destroying my crops for the season.
I'm out.
I'm gonna go back to England."
And George's like, "Well, okay, but what about all your property?
Like you built this."
And he's like, "Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, but here, I'll give you a will.
Here you go.
I'll sign this.
And now you own all my property.
I'll give you power of attorney too, whatever.
I'm out."
So he leaves and George Worrell's like, "Okay."
He takes the property.
October 1826.
Four months later.
John Farley runs into the hotel.
We've been sitting in this...
It was the exact same table.
It's drinking the exact same beverage for four months.
Trapped in our own personal hell.
John Farley runs in.
"Guys, oh my God.
You won't believe what happened.
Oh my God.
It sounds like you're having an orgasm."
John is like, "No, no.
Just personally, it's making my voice.
Making it sound weird is all."
John's like, "Not having an orgasm."
I saw a ghost.
And at that point, we re-animate.
We were frozen and suspended animation for four months.
We turn around.
I saw a ghost.
I saw a ghost out at the bridge.
Now what he saw, John Farley said he was walking down the street, and he saw a ghost
sitting on the rail of the bridge.
Now I'm going to assume it's middle of night because it's super spooky then.
It might have been early in the day, but let's assume it's nighttime.
Super spooky.
And he's walking down the super spooky bridge.
He's walking and he sees this ghost sitting on the rail, and then the ghost just kind
of points over to an area down underneath the bridge where the creek disappears.
Now John Farley tells the story, and it really kind of scares everyone.
Everyone's like, "Oh man, I live next to the bridge.
I have to cross the bridge to get home."
Dang it.
And I don't have flashlights because you know it's 1826.
You just got to walk in the dark.
Sucks.
They're all jumping in kangaroo pouches.
The kangaroos are too scared.
They're like, "Get out!"
Pushing them out of the pouch.
That and the kangaroos are horribly scarred from all the people jumping in their pouches
all the time.
They're like, "Ugh.
No more Uber.
Kangaroober?
Huh?"
Anyways, that was good.
I like that one.
Anyways, let's move on because I know you guys didn't like that one.
Let's move on.
I could have heard, I drew space and time.
I heard you groan.
I was listening to this episode three years from now.
I could still hear you groan at that joke.
Anyways, the point is that people were scared and multiple people in town while crossing
the bridge start seeing the ghost of Frederick Fisher pointing off underneath the river.
Sometimes when they walk, they see the ghost just standing there and then he jumps off into
the darkness below with despair.
And the local constable is like, "That's ridiculous.
That's super stupid."
And they're like, "No, no, no."
And the first time when John Farley talks about it, he's like, "Okay, John, you saw
a ghost."
Whatever.
Like, I don't believe in ghosts.
But towns people kept saying, "I think there's something down there."
Listen, Frederick Fisher's missing.
Well, George said he went back to England.
"Yeah, but George is a convicted felon.
You're a convicted felon.
I'm chief of police.
I'm a convicted felon.
We're all convicted felons.
If that's the thing that we need to trust each other, then no, it's going to trust each
other at all."
But the towns people were persistent.
Just go down there and see if there's anything down there.
To the cop, put a little siren on the top of his kangaroo.
The kangaroo's hopping.
He goes down to the riverbed area.
And I could imagine there's a bunch of people on the bridge pointing, pointing, being like,
"No, he was pointing this way."
"He was pointing this way."
Eventually, the cops like, "Right here?
Is this where they were pointing?"
And they're like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
They start digging, and lo and behold, they find the body of Frederick Fisher.
George Worrell, very shortly afterwards, was arrested and confessed to the crime.
And then he was found guilty, and he was eventually hanged.
Now, what's weird about this?
In fact, the fact that the ghost helped solve the crime, there's two actually weird things
about this.
To this day, in Campbelltown, New South Wales, if you're down there, you already know what
this is, they have a festival of Fisher's Ghost.
It's 10 days long.
That's longer than spring break, right?
10 days of a Fisher's Ghost festival.
They really must be nothing in this town.
They have things like a parade.
So a parade for a man who was murdered.
That's always great.
Children's events, a fireworks show.
Each firework goes up, it's just the, like, "Pshh," it's the shape of a skull.
"Pshh," the shape of a bat bledging in a man's head.
They have a thing called "Miss Princess Quest," which is like, I'm assuming it's like, you
know, the girl who waves her hand at people, it's the parade's going down the road.
And they've actually canceled that because no one wanted to be that anymore.
No joke.
The last time they had it was in 2016 and girls were like, "No, I'm good."
I'd rather not be the symbol of a murdered man's parade.
And a Fisher's Ghost art award, which I imagine is just little kids drawing pictures of a
slowly rotting body in the dirt.
That all stuff is interesting about.
This is the fact that people can celebrate this for 10 days.
Secondly, the story is half-fake.
Now this is what's interesting.
The murder is true.
Frederick Fisher was murdered.
George Warrell did confess to murdering him, all that stuff.
They did find his body buried.
However, people now believe that John Farley, the initial guy who reported the ghost, knew
of the murder and was threatened.
If you tell anyone about this murder, I'll get you to.
You'll end up at the bottom of that bridge, too.
So he couldn't directly report it.
So instead, after about four months, he's guilty.
He can't sleep.
He's thinking, "Poor Frederick's just rotting away down there.
No decent burial.
George Warrell has all this property, but he can't rat him out."
He tells the story of the ghost and mass panic strikes.
Other people start seeing the ghost.
John Farley, his report, the cop isn't going to do anything.
But after multiple towns people saw this and are pestering the police, they investigated.
So a ghost didn't actually appear.
A man's guilty conscience created the ghost story to get a guilty man thrown in prison.
And you're like, "Jason, that's lame.
You told us this wasn't happening.
You started this off.
You're all mad at me.
I'm all backing up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Put down.
That's not a knife.
This is a knife, dude.
Seriously.
You're approaching me towards the side of the bridge.
Jason, I'm tired of your bait and switches.
Whoa, dude.
Hold up.
Yes, I did lie to you.
However, I do think it's more interesting than this.
I think this is more interesting because not only did you have a guy, this story is 100%
true, which always makes more interesting.
You had a guy with a clever way to catch a murderer and you were able to show.
You think that whole time John Farley was like, "Other people are seeing this ghost?
What is going on?
I made this up."
And I wanted people to believe that the body was down there, but now other people are actually
seeing the ghost.
That must have been really trippy for him to deal with.
But a murderer was caught, a man's death was avenged, and Frederick Fisher was eventually
placed to rest, not just right into the bottom of a ravine.
So real ghost or not, and it wasn't.
It was a story that I just told you.
I find it fascinating nonetheless.
Now let's pack up our gear.
Here, no, you walk ahead of me.
I don't trust you at this point.
You keep turning around.
I'm going for my blade.
You're-- no, no, no, no, no.
I will not stab you in the back as they podcast those.
I promise to not stab you.
And as my listener or as we recently learned, a group of wild rabbits is known as a fluffle.
So as we are one fluffle, both rabbits at heart, we agree not to murder each other, although
you still are a little-- you're a little peeved that I tricked you.
But anyways, we're getting on the helicopter.
We're getting on, and we are headed out to Greenbrier, West Virginia.
Here in the switches, and I keep looking over my shoulder because I don't entirely trust
you.
You're like, Jason, no, I swear I'm not going to stab me in the back.
You're definitely not going to stab me in the back as we start to take off, because now
we're-- I don't know how high helicopters go.
We're 1,100 feet in the air.
All right?
That's pretty high.
You're like, Jason, you're flying a helicopter.
You've been flying it for 400 episodes.
You never ever looked at how high a helicopter can go.
Great job, pilot.
Now you're not going to stab me.
You're just being really sarcastic.
And kind of mean.
Okay, guys?
The little teardrop flies from me.
We're flying to Greenbrier, West Virginia.
The year is 1897.
And there we're going to meet Mary Jane Hester.
She's a grieving mother who's currently sitting in court, and a defense lawyer is kind of
pacing back and forth in front of her.
Now luckily, we have some interesting court documents for you.
But again, this is 100% a true story.
We have some really interesting court documents from all of this stuff.
So we actually have a transcript of this.
The defense lawyer asks her, "Are you telling the court that your daughter came to you in
a dream?"
And she says, quote, "It was no dream.
She came back and told me that he was mad that she didn't have no meat cooked for supper.
She came four times and four nights.
And the second night she told me that her neck was squeezed off at the first joint.
And it was just as she told me."
Defense lawyer walks a little bit closer, quote, "And was this not a dream founded upon
your distressed condition of mind, Mary Jane?
No, sir.
It was no dream, for I was as awake as I ever was.
She wore the very dress that she was killed in.
And when she went to leave me, she turned her head completely around and looked at me
like she wanted me to know all about it."
And Jerry's like, "Uh, she was spooking one of the jurors, puts a blanket over his head.
Let's go back in time a bit."
Mary Jane had a daughter named Elva Zona Hester.
And Zona became a mother herself, an unmarried mother, at age 22.
Well, you know, we're talking 1897, so not a good time to be an unwed mother.
Mary Jane's making the best of it.
They're doing what they can do in this little town in West Virginia.
And eventually a blacksmith comes to town.
He seems to be a pretty cool dude.
All the ladies want him, all the men want to be him.
And everyone who needs blacksmithing or blacksmith supplies have to go to him because he's the
dude in town.
His name is Edward Shoe, but he goes by the nickname Trout.
So you know you're cool when you can pull off a nickname of a big old ugly fish and
people are like, "Hey, what's up Trout?"
Within a month, these two are married.
Whirlwind romance.
Three months later, it's January 24th, 1897, and Trout's ching, ching, ching, working
to the blacksmith, hitting that metal against other metal that's like hot and informing it
into something.
And he's like, "You little boy, little boy person who works at my shop.
Yes, Mr. Trout.
Go home and fetch some eggs.
You guys want eggs?"
Everyone's like, "Yeah, eggs on me."
They were like, "I'm planning on putting eggs on the anvil, cooking them on the anvil."
They're like, "Mmm, tastes like solder."
So anyways, the kid goes home to his house to pick up some eggs.
Kids like, "Yeah, I'm gonna go get some eggs."
And he goes in the house.
Hello? Hello? Apparently they live in the Grand Canyon.
And there at the bottom of the stairs lies the broken body of Zona Hester.
Little boy lets Trout know authorities get called when the police get their Trouts already
at home.
He's beside himself.
He's absolutely grieving about what happened.
Sobbing.
He washed his wife's body down, put on her favorite dress with a really, really high neck.
Really, really like, really hold, hold to that neck in place.
Didn't it Trout?
Really, really got that turtle neck on.
Put that on that dress.
He's like, "Oh, you know what she always loved?
She always loved this scarf.
Oh, yes she did.
And let me wrap this scarf around her neck."
And everyone in town, well I shouldn't say everyone in town, but a lot of people in town
are kind of suspicious because normally the job of preparing the debt, like washing the
body down, putting it in nice clothes is what, it's women work, right?
Men don't do that.
Men work with their hands.
Well, that takes hands.
Women don't do it with their feet.
But you know, like men lift up trees and like smash iron with their bare hands and make
swords.
I thought the women put the clothes on.
So they thought it was a little weird that Trout was doing this.
But some people go, "Maybe he's just grieving."
And maybe she really did like that scarf wrapped super tight around her neck.
Maybe she'd enjoyed it.
She had been currently being treated by the local doctor, who was actually the guy who
was coming to check the money on.
And when the doctor gets there, he goes, "She had been being treated by the doctor for,
quote, 'female trouble.'"
And then her cause of death, decided by the same doctor, was first listed as everlasting
fate.
"Oh my stars, there was no handsome man there to catch her.
She falls down, she dies."
Then that condition, cause of death, was changed to childbirth.
Which was interesting in town because not many people thought she was pregnant.
Her mom especially, Mary Jane hadn't heard anything about her daughter being pregnant.
But the doctor was like, "Nope.
She came down with a case of the kids.
She came down with a case of kids in the belly and it killed her."
Delicate, delicate woman.
She died cause she had a little baby in her.
People are like, "That's not really how it works.
You know where babies come from, right?"
And the doctor's like, "Nope.
I do not."
Now every time they had to do something with the body, trout was always there.
They're like, "Okay, let's move the body."
He's like, "Okay, here, I'll stand by and sob really loudly right in your ear so you
can't think."
They take her down to the funeral home, crying like tears are actually falling on the coroner's
face.
Get off of me.
The cops go to like look at the body.
They think it's a little weird, you know?
Again, people don't normally just fall over dead due to child.
And he would be crying, "Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh