How does a young man go from being completely sane to a cold blooded murderer in only the
matter of a few months?
And then we travel to Jolly Old England to take a look at the story of a young girl hanging
out in her garden.
She was hoping to simply smell some flowers or sing along with a bluejay sitting in a
tree.
She found herself face to face with something that would change her life today on Dead Rabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jesus Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I'm a little sick.
I'm a little under the weather.
I think that's how most people get this time of year.
But still I'm having a great day, right?
Still, I'm going to talk about this guy brutally murdered somebody and then a girl who had a
life-changing paranormal event.
That's fun, despite the turmoil in my own tummy.
But someone who never makes me sick to my stomach walking into Dead Rabbit Command is
one of our Thanksgiving livestream contributors.
Everyone give it up for Callum Frazier.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in.
Callum is bringing in a bottle of Tums and a garbage can for me to throw up in.
Callum, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the show financially.
I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
I just got all of my Spotify results.
And you guys, you guys, this audience is in the top 5% of all podcast audiences as far
as sharing the show with your friends.
I got that statistic today.
That's amazing.
Top 5% of all podcasts on Spotify, you guys, share this show with others.
And I really, really do appreciate that.
I really, really do.
Callum, I'm going to go ahead and hook you up to the hair hang glider.
Everyone grab onto his ankles as he jumps off the highest point at Dead Rabbit Command.
Let's glide all the way out to Italy.
And first off, I want to give a shout out to Fabio Nurbon, a longtime supporter of the
show, a longtime guy who's had his name mispronounced multiple times on the show.
He sent the story over to me.
It's a fascinating story, so I really, really appreciate it.
Let's go back in time to summer of 2022.
So not far at all, right?
We're in June, July.
This is what, four or five months ago?
This story starts.
We're in the town of Trevisio.
We're in the town of Trevisio in Italy, and there's this young dude, this 24-year-old
man named Ricardo Di Filiis.
And Ricardo was just a normal guy.
He was just a normal dude living in Trevisio.
He lived with his mom and his dad.
This younger brother had to move it away, but this was a good family unit for these
guys.
The news report describes this.
This is how I would hope to be described as something tragic ever happened to me.
They were described as, quote, "Good people with a passion for cats."
Now I do realize that this was an Italian news article that I had to translate to English
so it's possible there's a translation error in there.
But I mean, listen, man, if the last thing you're remembered for is loving cats, that's
dope, right?
That's pretty good.
You can chase it.
I know there's way better things to be known for, helping orphans and building libraries,
but loving cats is up there, guys.
But anyways, Ricardo's living at home with his parents, hanging out with his friends.
Life is good.
But his best friend said, "The summer of 2022 is where everything changed."
He goes, "Ricardo was a totally normal guy.
You never would have thought anything weird about him."
And I've known him since I was a kid.
We grew up together.
He was totally fine, but this summer, everything changed.
He begins to exhibit mental problems.
And by the time summer ended and fall began, Ricardo was convinced his life was a television
show.
He suffers what's known as the Truman Show delusion, or the Truman Delusion.
We did an episode on it a long time ago, way long time ago.
I'm gonna put it in the show notes.
But it is, if you've seen the movie The Truman Show, Jim Carrey is a guy who is raised on
the set of a television series, but he doesn't know he's in a television show.
It seems like it would be a boring show with him as a baby, right?
It would just be him pooping in his pants.
But it would get compelling as he got older and he saw this little boy.
It's the ultimate reality show, right?
You're actually watching someone live their life.
It's recorded 24 hours a day.
The set is a whole town.
Everyone else is an actor except for Truman, and he doesn't know that he's trapped in the
show.
And this movie has actually sparked the Truman Delusion, or Truman Show delusion.
There are people who believe that they too are also trapped in a television show.
Maybe I'm looking around for cameras and if they can't find them, that's just proof,
right?
That the cameras are so well hidden.
In the Truman Show, he doesn't really know anything's up until the lighting fixture falls
from the heavens and smashes into the ground in front of them.
And even then they're like, "Oh, there was a satellite.
That was a satellite that came down."
But then he starts to kind of piece stuff together that he might not be living in the
real world.
And it's interesting because we do know that mental illness tends to track with the highest
level of technology.
In the 1950s, people believed that the Russians were beaming radio waves through metal fillings
in people's teeth because the radio waves was the highest level of technology.
Nowadays, the paranoid delusions involve things like miniaturized cameras, constant surveillance,
being trapped in a reality show, being trapped in the matrix.
And it's always interesting to think where will madness be in the next 100, 200 years
as technology continues to grow.
The delusions will change.
If this guy had been born in medieval times, he probably would have thought that a local
witch cast a curse on him.
If he was born in the 1950s, he would have thought that he was being hunted by the KGB.
But he's 24 years old, so he believes that he's trapped on the set of the Truman Show,
or he is, basically he's not an extra in the Truman Show, that he is being surveilled.
He's constantly being videotaped.
Somebody else is watching his life unfold.
He begins to become incredibly paranoid, which is what you would expect from somebody who
thought there were hidden cameras everywhere.
If you showed him and be like, "Hey, Ricardo, what's up?
I bought you this zinger, this Hostess zinger.
You want to eat it?"
You would assume that your friend isn't actually giving you a delicious treat.
You would assume your friend was doing product placement.
You would assume your friend got some sort of ad deal from Hostess.
"Hey, you want to try some Denison's chili?
Or how about a diet sprite?"
People don't normally talk in brand names like that.
But you would think that, "Man, this guy must have a brand deal."
He begins to become paranoid.
He begins to become physically violent.
He's attacking people.
Now, I was like, "Oh, I don't want your zingers?
I don't want your diet sprite?
Get away from me.
You're trying to sell me on that stuff."
Okay, to be fair, there's nothing in his paper that said.
He thought people were doing brand deals.
I'm adding that as an example.
I don't know why he was physically attacking these people, possibly because he was going
mentally insane.
He ends up becoming physically violent.
He ends up fighting with his best friend, so they actually stop hanging out.
It would be tragic, right?
And you wouldn't know.
I mean, me and you, we've done research on this stuff.
We know about the world of the weird.
If our friends started talking, they thought they were on a television show, we would know
that this is a, while not common delusion, it's not rare either.
But a normal person whose best friends start saying, "I think I'm trapped in a TV show."
I don't think a normal person, it would freak you out.
It would freak us out too, but it would freak you out.
You would have no sense of context.
We are explorers in the land of the strange.
So we would be able to classify this as, oh yeah, this is actually documented mental illness.
We may have been able to intervene.
I'm not blaming, I'm not blaming this guy's friend because he doesn't listen to the podcast
or spend all his days reading about weird stuff.
But you know what I mean?
What would you do if you had no context of listening?
Your friend started saying that he was being filmed everywhere.
You wouldn't know what to do.
You'd just be like, "Bro, chill out with this ice cold classic Coke."
Ah, refreshing.
Summer turns to fall and he starts to go through this delusion that he is being filmed.
He's the star of the reality show that no one else can see, but he knows that it's happening.
He ends up losing his job.
He ends up becoming suicidal.
And by November of 2022, so really just a couple weeks ago is when this story hits the culmination,
he finally decides it's time to see a psychologist.
It's time to get this checked out.
Something's not right.
And I don't know how much of that was strictly Ricardo and how much of that was his parents
and everyone else in the community.
But he was the director of the show.
He's like, "Oh, I got Fraser Crane lined up for a guest episode."
He decides I need to go see a psychologist.
The decision's been made to get him treatment.
His behavior is still becoming very erratic.
And on November 15th, 2022, so just a couple weeks ago from recording this episode, the
family's getting ready to settle in for the night.
Ricardo goes to his bedroom.
His mom goes to her bedroom.
And the father, who normally does sleep with the mom, decides to stay up late this night
and watch some television set.
His father, Francesco de Felice, a 56-year-old veteran, says, "I'm going to stay up, watch
some television, and catch you later."
What's about four in the morning?
Now we're at December 15th.
Ricardo runs into his parents' bedroom and his mom is deep asleep and he starts screaming
out, "Dad's dead!
Dad's dead!"
That's going to get you up, right?
That's how you don't care how deep of a sleeper you are.
You're awake when someone runs in screaming that.
The mom woke up and she sees her son standing there.
Ricardo's just screaming up, "Dad's dead, dad's dead."
And she gets out of bed to go check on him and Ricardo won't let her leave the room.
I don't want you to see it, I don't want you to see it, but Dad's dead!
And she wants to see it.
She has no idea what's going on.
Her son's nuts.
So maybe he's hallucinating it or, you know, that'd be the best case scenario that you
go down there and the dad's sitting on the couch watching Hogan's Heroes.
And it was just all hallucination, but she wants to get out and she wants to go see her
husband.
Ricardo won't let her out of the room and Ricardo actually barricades her in the room.
Now, at some point the police are called.
I don't know if it doesn't specifically say that Ricardo called the police or the mom
called the police or neighbors called the police because there's a guy next door screaming,
"Dad's dead, dad's dead."
The police show up and when they come into the house what they find is they find Francisco
de Felice had been killed in a both savage and lightning fast attack.
Ricardo had taken a weightlifting bar, like a dumbbell bar, a little handheld pipe, and
while his father was sleeping on the couch he just fell asleep out there watching time.
He began beating his head in with this pipe and began stabbing his dad in the neck with
a kitchen knife.
And the attack was so fast Francisco didn't even wake up.
He died in his sleep as his son was pummeling him with both a pipe and stabbing him with
a knife in the neck.
Now Ricardo has pretty much confessed to this crime.
I don't know what libel laws are like in Italy, but he's pretty much confessed.
He made a statement to the police saying that he didn't mean to do it.
That he didn't mean to do it.
He didn't mean to bash his dad's head in and stab him several times.
He didn't mean to do it.
But that would imply that he did confess to doing it.
But then he changed his story.
He goes, "I didn't mean to do it."
And then later on he told the police, "Listen, my dad was trying to hurt me."
"My dad was trying to hurt me."
And then he added later on during this police investigation to ask him these questions.
First off he said, "I didn't mean to do it."
And then the second time he goes, "Well, he was trying to hurt me."
And then later he added, "My mom was trying to hurt me too."
And I don't think he meant in the sense that it was self-defense.
I mean, his father was asleep.
In the sense that he saw his father and his mother as part of this conspiracy, that they
were part of this Truman show set up as well.
And that's really chilling, right?
Because obviously if it sounds like had the situation played out slightly differently,
he would have killed his mother as well.
Because he also saw her as part of this faceless organization that was trying to harm him.
And it's terrifying.
It's an absolutely terrifying story.
Long time listeners of the podcast know people snapping, people going crazy, just out of the
blue scares me.
Now on a snapp-o-meter, this one's a little less scary because he went crazy over a matter
of months.
To me it's more spooky if you're sitting there and then your friend's totally normal
and then he starts like stabbing you.
I mean, listen, it's creepy if he threatens you for four years before he does it, or if
he does it right away.
I still don't want it to happen to anybody.
But people who snap, people who seem completely normal up until that night and then they begin
murdering their family, because that happens too.
It's still, I'm not saying that the story isn't creepy or I don't find it tragic in any sort
of way, but I think that most likely like mental illness for young men, this is the
right age for it to start.
It's like 19 to 30s when we see things like schizophrenia, things like these deep mental
illnesses just pop up in young men.
And it's awful.
And I mean, obviously he's not trapped in the tournament show.
Obviously that is just the delusion.
It would have been great had he got some help early.
But at the end of the day, like he didn't, and he murdered somebody and he was probably
planning on murdering other people.
There's another version of this story, right, where he didn't run into the bedroom screaming
dad's dad, dad's dad.
He ran into the bedroom and he killed his mother as well.
But for whatever reason, luckily, right, for whatever reason, and we're glad that this
happened, after he murdered his dad, that part we're not glad that it happened.
But after he murdered his father, he had some sense of clarity.
He became lucid.
Whatever delusion he was going through for a moment in time, he realized what he did
was so horrific he ran upstairs and told his mom.
Like snapped out of it.
And he didn't try to murder her as well.
Terrifying story though, and it goes in, we talk about this a lot on the podcast too,
these people who feel that the tournament show is kind of the offshoot of the gangstalking
thing, that there's this huge conspiracy against them.
I feel like, and we've been covering a lot of these, I don't want to just cover these,
right, I tried to space them out.
This one was just sent to me a couple days ago, but I think that the gangstalking conspiracy
theory has the most potential to cause people to become violent.
People are really going to blow up buildings because of flatter, they're not going to blow
up buildings because 9/11 was an inside job unless they're testing out their theories.
But you know what I mean, there's a lot of conspiracy theories out there that don't
cause people to go nuts.
I mean the conspiracy theory itself may be nuts, but I'd say most conspiracy theories,
even if you thought space was fake and NASA was a satanic organization controlled by the
Illuminati to make us not believe in God, that's a pretty popular conspiracy theory
out there.
Those people aren't out there blowing up space shuttles.
Most people aren't out there shooting, assassinating NASA scientists.
Gangstalking we are starting to see really story after story after story after story of
people who believe this and taking action.
The reptilian one we do get, that one gets kind of violent as well, but you know that
reptilians are taking over the planet because the idea is well I can kill them, it's just
a reptilian.
That guy who killed his two daughters, what was it like two years ago because he thought
they were reptilian foot soldiers.
So yeah we do have that Chris cry.
I think the Venn diagram between conspiracy theorists and violent people isn't that connected
but there is a connection and unfortunately we get stories like this.
Mental illness leading into the conspiracy theory, he thought he was on the Truman show
and irony of all ironies he's going to be in the prison system where he will be monitored
24 hours a day.
So if he wasn't in the Truman show before he's definitely put himself in that position
now.
Calum, let's go ahead and touch the keys to the carboner copter.
We are leaving behind Italy, fly us all the way out to jolly old England.
There's this old saying, I don't even know if it's a saying, it might just been a movie
quote.
And the saying goes, they should have sent a poet.
They should have sent a poet.
I've heard it used in the conjunction with astronauts, right?
Because astronauts listen man, like they're cool but an astronaut is if you took a joc
and a nerd and they had a baby.
And it's an astronaut.
It's an astronaut.
You didn't know that?
That's what happens at the end of season all that.
Little astronauts born.
They have a joc and a nerd.
You have someone who like Neil Armstrong, take him for example.
I know he's a super old man who might not even be alive anymore.
But you take like nowadays you look at him and you're like, dude, those people are neither
jocks nor nerds.
Generally though, you take some of their peak physical fitness because they make them spin
around really fast in that cyclotron thing.
And then they got to be smart.
So as they're spinning around, they have to be like, if I throw up now the velocity will
be eight times the center of gravity.
I better hold it on my vomit until this stops.
You got to be able to do like advanced math because it's not like you're just hitting
buttons and flying around.
You got to figure all this stuff out.
But you also don't, you can't get like super nerd up there.
You can't get some point dexter because then like if something goes wrong, if an alien attacks
a space shuttle, you want them to be strong enough to punch them and go get out of here.
So that's the type of people they send up there, right?
Well, nowadays it seems like they are all a bunch of nerds, but I'm talking classic astronauts.
I'm talking the square jawed dude who was like kicking the moon.
They're like, Neil, stop that.
You're sending it out of orbit.
I don't care.
I'm a jerk.
What I'm saying is that we got nothing but nerds up there today.
It used to be nerds at peak physical fitness, but there's no poets.
And this idea that you can send someone up there who is able to triangulate a star moving
past a meteor as an asteroid is jumping up and down and go, don't hit none of that stuff.
But they can't write eloquently.
They can't put down what they're seeing.
They're viewing things that no human has ever viewed, right?
How many, if you look at the total population of the world since the beginning of time,
the amount of people who have been in space is what?
Like at this point, maybe a couple hundred.
That includes like just like people floating around the Russian space station.
Let me in.
They're like, no, not until you finish your green beans.
How am I supposed to finish my green beans if I'm floating outside?
You know what I mean?
It's been such a small percentage.
And the idea is if you sent a poet up there, someone who could this is going somewhere.
It's totally going somewhere.
I feel this intro might be longer than the story.
So when you take a poet, when you take a wordsmith, when you have someone who knows
how to translate the unknowable and the unseeable into words that humans can understand and
not only understand because when Neil Armstrong is up there and he goes, the moon is super
dusty.
I get what he's talking about.
But if you put a poet up there, he could tell us exactly how dusty it is.
Does the dust look like Gossamer Webb trailing across the Arabian Peninsula?
Or is it the same dust I might find in the background of Aunt Matilda's house covering
her precious moment figurines?
Now those samples off the top of my head.
I know I'm not a poet either.
But you get what I mean.
We sent scientists up there.
We should have sent a poet.
So let me tell you what the story is because this is fascinating to me because what we're
going to do is we're going to take a look at the story of Hillary Mantell.
She's an award winning author.
She's passed away now.
She passed away a couple of years ago.
It's a shame, Hillary Mantell.
She's been knighted by the Queen of England.
Very very famous, very beloved author.
She wrote historical fiction and short stories and articles and things like that.
She's a wordsmith.
And when you have someone who experiences a paranormal event, they can explain it in
a certain way.
But I want to read this to you.
I very rarely read things verbatim.
But this I think is awesome.
Because we have someone who spent her entire life writing.
And when it came time to write her memoirs, she explains the most life changing event
that she had ever gone through.
And it happened when she was seven years old.
Let's take a look at this.
She starts off by saying, let me give a little bit of context here too.
She starts off mentioning the location Brosscroft.
That is a residential neighborhood in Derbyshire, England.
So let's take a look at this.
"I am seven and I am in the yard at Brosscroft.
I am playing near the house, near the back door.
Something makes me look up.
Some shift of the light.
My eyes are drawn to a spot beyond the yard.
It's gates in the long garden.
It is, let us say, some 50 yards away among coarse grass, weeds, and bracken.
I can't see anything.
Not exactly see.
Not the faintest movement, a ripple, a disturbance of the air.
I can sense a spiral, a lazy buzzing swirl like flies, but it is not flies.
There is nothing to see.
There is nothing to smell.
There is nothing to hear.
But it's motion.
This insolent shift makes my stomach heave.
I can sense at the periphery the limit of all my senses.
I can sense the dimensions of the creature.
It is as high as a child of two.
Its depth is a foot 15 inches.
The air stirs around it invisibly.
I am cold and rinsed by nausea.
I cannot move.
I am shaky as if pinned to the moment.
I cannot wretch my gaze away.
I am looking at a space occupied by nothing.
It has no edges, no mass, no dimension, no shape except the formless.
It moves.
I beg it.
Stay away.
Within the space of a thought it is inside me and has set up a sick resonance within my
bones and in all the cavities of my body.
I pluck my eyes away.
It is like plucking them out of my head.
Grace runs away from me.
Runs out of my body like liquid from a corpse.
I move from the spot.
My body weighs heavy.
My feet have to be hauled up from the ground as if they were sticking in gore.
I walk out of the sunlight through the glass place into the enclosed dimness of the cold
kitchen.
I say, "Mom, I want to come in now.
Can I do some drawing?"
I see myself through her eyes.
Sweat running from me.
My cheeks falling in.
My chest heaving to control the thick taste of blood and sick that's in my mouth.
I pray, let her not look at me.
"Yes," she says sweetly, her back turned.
"Of course you can."
It is the best yes I have ever heard.
It is the best yes I have ever heard in the course of my life.
If I had been sent out again into the secret garden, I think I would have died.
I think my heart would have stopped.
She wraps this up.
She talks about a, there's a old comic novel is what it's called back in the 1930s called
Cold Comfort Farm.
And one of the characters in it is called Ada Doom or Aunt Ada Doom.
And she keeps going on and on in the book about how she saw something nasty in the woods
shed.
They never reveal what the nasty thing was, but Aunt Ada Doom says when she was a child
she saw something nasty in the woods shed.
This novel is a comedy, right?
And so she does kind of laugh it off.
She says, she finishes off by saying, "When I grow up I laugh at this.
I say I'm like Aunt Ada Doom.
I saw something nasty in the woods shed."
She explains that when she's talking about this with other people, she has a laugh about
it like, "What did I see?
What did I see?"
Just like Aunt Ada Doom.
But she finishes this up.
She goes, "And what was it anyway?
I don't know.
Something intangible had come for me to try its luck.
Some formless, borderless evil that came to try to make me despair.
When I'm on my own and I think about it privately, then I scarcely laugh at all."
It's a fascinating story.
At the end of the day it's a story of this formless evil, this unknowable darkness that's
in the light of day.
It's standing first outside the garden and then it's in the garden.
And she's describing, I just love the way that she describes this.
And it's interesting because there is no description of it, right?
She can't see it, she can't smell it, she can't touch it.
But then you also have dimensions given, right?
It was the size of a two-year-old child, it was about a foot and 15 inches, some 50 yards
away.
So it's just such a fascinating story.
To have someone who can write so eloquently, explain something that is impossible, I wanted
to share that with you.
That's not the only reason why I wanted to share it with you because we're going to
talk a little bit more about this next week.
Hillary goes on to say, she writes, "The memoir is called 'Giving Up the Ghost.'
It's not just writing about paranormal stuff.
But she's open about this, which I love.
I love it when people are open about these experiences."
She'll talk about it in interviews and she said, "Had this not happened to me, had this
afternoon, really only minutes had passed," right?
She goes, "I think I would have been a different person.
I think I would have been a much more rational person."
And I could 100% see how that is, right?
There is a large contention of us, and I definitely fell into it, that believed in the paranormal
long before they had any paranormal events.
I was a child hearing about demonically possessed people and we lived in a haunted house.
We lived in a haunted house.
I'm not one of the fun haunted houses.
It wasn't a spirit Halloween store.
And then I would hear, my dad was a Southern Baptist minister.
Everybody would hear from him and other ministers and deacons about demons that had been interacting
in and around the church.
But weird stuff happened.
It wasn't until I was 18 when I actually heard a ghost.
And then throughout my 20s, which again is the time when people, especially young men,
have psychotic problems, I began to see, I thought I was going nuts when I started seeing
ghosts everywhere and shadow men everywhere.
I mean everywhere.
But here I am.
And I'm not nuts.
So you have people who believe in the paranormal just because it's really cool, right?
And then some of them never have a paranormal experience.
I've had several throughout my life and continue to have them.
But to have one at seven and to have one that's so frightening.
My buddy Steve, when he was a little kid, he got chased down the hallway of his house
by a ghost stagecoach.
But I mean that's terrifying.
Actually I was going to use it as an example.
So that's not that bad.
That's actually terrifying.
That's a bad example.
But my point being is let's say that you lived in a house.
You were a seven-year-old kid and you were throwing toys down the hallway because your
imaginary friend wanted to play with your toys.
That's what we talked about in yesterday's episode.
That's not as terrifying as standing out in your garden and seeing an unexplainable evil.
And she didn't just see it.
It entered her body.
She saw it and then it was instantly on top of her or inside of her.
That's another thing we see in the world of paranormal.
These things don't move normally.
Sure some of them walk down hallway or right ghost stagecoach is down a hallway.
But a blink of the eye.
I've seen that too.
I mean you're looking at something from across the room and then it is on you.
It is the weirdest thing in the world because we don't measure distance and time like that.
Even the fastest man, if you're standing there and Usain Bolt is running towards you, he
will tackle you.
He'll catch you before you can get out of the way.
But you intrinsically know that he's moving according to the laws of physics.
He's just moving faster than you can move out of the way.
But that's not, I mean you're looking at something and then it's on top of you.
And in this case inside of her.
So I just think it's interesting when you do have such a traumatic metaphysical experience
early in life.
It would change the way you looked at things.
And even you may not have, I think it's a jolly good time to sit around and talk about ghosts.
Right?
Because you've seen something beyond ghosts, beyond the paranormal.
Something truly malignant.
And I also wanted, because this is where we're going to talk about next week, I wanted to
end it like this.
Hillary never made this connection to be fair.
Hillary never made this connection.
But Hillary, she did have another paranormal experience.
At least one other one that I saw.
She saw her father's ghost walking down the stairs one day.
And honestly I think that one predated the creature in the garden.
But seeing her father walk down the stairs would give you comfort that there is life
after death.
What was this thing?
And it changed her life.
She goes, "Listen, I would have been a more rational person.
I would have approached the world differently had I not gone out in the garden on this afternoon."
It's that simple.
She also had some pretty serious health problems.
When she was in her 20s, she was sick all the time.
She was sick constantly.
And she was diagnosed with having a mental illness.
But she wasn't mentally ill.
She had what we know of today as endometriosis.
Endometriosis.
I have friends who have suffered from this.
What it is, if I can describe it correctly, it's basically the uterine wall.
It's the material that's supposed to be inside the uterus is outside the uterus.
And it's covering up the fallopian tubes and the eggs.
It's extremely painful.
You have very, very terrible periods.
You're sick all the time.
And it's something that can be diagnosed nowadays.
It's something that can be corrected nowadays.
But the way to fix it is to have your uterus removed.
Have a hysterectomy.
Well, Hillary, she was diagnosed as being mentally ill because she was complaining about
an illness that they couldn't figure out what it was.
They put her on antipsychotics because she wasn't psychotic and she's on antipsychotics.
She became psychotic.
She went nuts from the medication.
She finally lost all faith in the medical profession.
She's like, "You guys don't know what you're doing."
She got off the medication and she just goes, "I guess I'm just going to be sick all the
time."
She ended up in Botswana.
She seemed to be a pretty well-established traveler.
She ended up in Botswana at one point.
And there she was diagnosed with endometriosis.
And they performed what she calls, and I think this is pretty apt, a medically induced menopause.
So, when they corrected this, when they gave her hysterectomy, she was no longer able to
have children after that.
And that was something that she had wanted to have.
Now, apparently, something that can help with this, we know this now, something that can
help with this condition is giving birth, is getting pregnant and carrying a child, can
actually help this.
I don't know the science behind it.
I guess I have a couple friends who have suffered from it.
But it's a fascinating story.
She never connected the ghost in the garden to her unknowable medical troubles.
As far as I know, she at least never made that public, as far as I know.
But was there a connection?
And this is where we get into that really interesting/very, very controversial thing,
like how much of illness is caused by spirits.
I think, honestly, a very, very, very, very small amount are.
I think I'm sick right now.
I think my stomach hurts because, I don't know, but I don't think it's because I brought
a cursed basketball home.
We'll talk more about the cursed basketball later.
I don't think it's cursed, but it's been weird since I brought that basketball home.
But I don't think it's because of the basketball.
But I couldn't say for sure that every, I couldn't say for sure out of every person
who's sick, all 8 billion people at any given time, that at least 10 of them aren't caused
by a ghost?
Probably not.
She probably had this.
That was, I had to say all that stuff for the skeptics.
But you and I know the reason why you have a runny nose is there's a ghost in your boogers
right now.
I don't think much illness, but it'd also be foolish for someone who believes in the
paranormal to say it's none, to say that physical health and the spirit world are completely
unrelated.
Because we do know that mental health and the spirit world can be related.
There's a lot of dark spirits out there that want to drive you mad, want to push you to
the point of depression, want to have you walking around in a stupor.
So it could be.
And now we're getting a double-barreled attack.
And her life would have been more rational.
She would have approached the world with a different lens, a mentally different lens,
had she not seen this thing in the garden.
And there is a chance, however slight it is, that her ability to have a happy life physically
as well.
To not spend years and years and years sick and be put on anti-psychotics and all this
stuff.
That also could have been caused by the formless evil in the garden.
And next week we're going to take a look at a story that takes this theory that the darkness
that surrounds us can also be sometimes a cause of the illness.
Because we're going to meet a family that is so tormented by a demon that peeks into
the bedroom while they're deep asleep.
You wake up and see this demon watching you from the darkness of the hallway.
This demon is so powerful that its goal is to use physical sicknesses to turn the family
into demons themselves.
We'll cover that next week on Dead Rabbit Radio.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Stick Talk is at DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day but I'm so glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)