It's the start of Spooky Ghost Week.
Ooh.
First we're gonna go to a college where the ghost of a young woman
still plays the piano late at night, and it has implications that are scarier than you think.
And then we take a trip to a haunted mine, but not just any haunted mine.
This one allows us to do an interactive adventure today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. It's the beginning of Ghost Week.
I actually just came up with an idea. I did a bunch of research this weekend, and I came up with all
these great ghost stories. I was reading, well, because I was reading a book on ghosts, I came
up with a bunch of stories in general, but I go, "I have so many stories about ghosts. I think we'll
make this a theme week. Now not every story is going to involve ghosts, but every episode will have a
ghost story in it, culminating with Friday being one of our, and I always say this, that it's the
most requested topic, but this one here is actually the most requested topic from the conspiracy
iceberg. We're going to cover it Friday. I'm not going to spoil it for you. I will give you a hint.
It involves ghosts, but it's more than that. But let's go ahead and jump on in to our first story
for Ghost Week. Now this one is interesting because a lot of times when I poo poo ghost stories,
I start to bring in physics. Like how can a ghost stand on a boat? Like wouldn't they fall through
the boat? If the boat was moving, wouldn't it fall off? Like I'm constantly trying to figure this
stuff out. Can a ghost be in an airplane? Is the airplane taken off? They're like, "No, no, wait,
wait, and they just haunt the runway?" Like how does ghost physics work? And this story kind of gives
us an idea of what it could be, but before we get into that part of the story, so there's two ghosts
that we're going to cover in this first story. So there is a college in Arkansas. So we're going
to go to Arkansas. You know, we're going to put the carpenter copter aside for right now. We're
going to take the dead rabbit dirgeable again. Now first off, I'm not going to do that stupid
sound effect joke again because it totally failed. I listened to that episode a couple days ago and
I was like, "That was a stupid joke, but it's there. It's recorded or whatever." And I want to let you
guys know, actually, I did an episode on the ghost blimp and there was a YouTube commenter who
made a remark saying, "Now I know why you use a helicopter instead of a blimp." And it was funny
because he put this little nugget in my head. Later on when I invented, I mean, the dead rabbit
dirgeable is real. It's totally real. But later when I remembered I had the dead rabbit dirgeable,
I was like, "Wait a second, that guy. So I am a naming guy with the headphones. He is our co-pilot
for the dead rabbit dirgeable." And we're going to take this dirgeable all the way from Hooda River.
Okay, we're going to go to Arkansas. It's three years later now. It's 2022. The blimp is incredibly
slow. Anyways, we're in Arkansas. We're specifically going to Harding College. So get your college
books. Get your number two pencils and your scantrons. But then put those away because we don't
need those. We're just going to walk around college. So we're at Harding College. I'm sorry,
you already bought those school books. You can return them. You'll get half credit. But anyway,
so we're at Harding College now and we're going to meet a ghost named Gertie Sue. Now, Gertie Sue
is one of those ghosts that I'm not a huge fan of. They just kind of walk around. I always thought
I was boring. Ghosts in a white dress walking down the hallway or something like that. I don't
find that particularly compelling or scary or anything like that. And you're like, well,
Jason, why are you wasting my time and telling me a story like that? Because it's not the main
part of the story. Shut up. Don't interrupt me. It's not the main part of the story. And I think
her origin is hilarious. So to cut to the chase, she is a ghost who there's like a brick path
along Harding College. And her ghost will walk through the college and like, you know, just kind
of like walking through at night. But anyways, her ghost just walks around campus, you know,
looking, she's at Starbucks. She's like, oh, come on, man, where's my stuff? She's at the food court.
She's like, oh, this food's disgusting, but I don't want to leave campus and lose my parking spot.
And everyone else is like, she's basically slimer at this point. I basically turned into slimer.
Her origin story, let me get to it. Her origin story is she woke up one night. She's like,
so tired, I need to walk down the hallway for some reason. She's like walking through the halls of
her dorms late at night. She's like, I'll just keep my eyes shut as I'm walking through here.
It's not like I believe I'm going to become a go.
Falls down an elevator shaft. Now, you might not find that humorous, but I find that I've realized
doing the show that 90% of people die in ways attributed to Looney Tune characters. Like,
how hard does it have to be to avoid a giant hole on the third story or second story or whatever
it was of a building, of a door sized, multiple human hole? How hard is it to avoid that?
She just walked into an elevator shaft and fell. Now, again, the couple problems I have with that is
you don't just walk into an elevator. You're just not like, hey, Barry, and like face through the door.
It just takes a lot of effort to open up an elevator door. Now, I had heard that story before
and I read it a couple times when I was researching this. Then I found another version and they're
like, there was a black thing. They totally sexed it up. They're like, all the girls in the dorm
heard a piercing scream. They left out the squish noise and heard a piercing scream and as one of
the girls ran out of her room, she saw a dark figure run away and all that was left was Gertie's
broken butt. That didn't happen. That, come on, that didn't happen. You're just making that part up.
Now they're just trying to add a murder plot to it. No, that didn't happen. That wasn't sourced in
any other article. Gertie, you just fell down an elevator shaft, down a hole that never moves.
The second ghost, however, is far more fascinating, also at Harding College. This happened in the
1930s. Now, the thing with Gertie, people have said that they've seen her and that story may or
may not be true. This story also has probably some faults in the telling of it as far as how
factual it is because we don't have things like names and stuff like that. We just have vague
time like the 1930s. But again, it's very, very interesting story. It's kind of out of the
normal ghost stories we hear. 1930s. There is a dormitory. No, they didn't have an elevator,
as far as I know. There's this young woman who falls in love with a young man. Now, she lived on
the third floor of the dorm, but it was an old girl's dorm. So you couldn't have boys over, but
you could have some fun, a little sorority sexiness. You know, pillow fights and pajama parties,
and maybe you're getting a little too drunk and you're doing the flapper dance. It's the 1930s,
so they're doing the flapper dance and the girls are getting a little too close, but the room
feels heavy and hot. Just things happen sometimes. It doesn't mean anything. Young 1930s ghost,
eventual ghost woman, it doesn't mean anything. It's okay. You're just experimenting. You're in
college. But my fantasy aside, the real story is that there was this girl, as I kind of wandered
off into dreamland. There's this young girl who falls in love with the young boys. She goes to
Harding College. She's in her dorm. Her dorm's on the third floor, but she wouldn't meet up with her
with her boyfriend. I'm assuming they just held hands. That was like considered a home runback
then. But he died tragically in a car accident and she was just completely inconsolable. She kind
of broke off all of her social contacts and on the third floor of this, well, now I'm thinking it
might not be a dormitory because there is a piano up there, but we'll just assume, we'll just, for
the sake of the story, the point is, is that on the third story of this building, this young
four-lawing girl that may or may not have been her dormitory, played the piano all day long. Super,
super sad piano music. That was just the only way she could console herself. So she's up there.
She's playing sad music. She's playing the theme song to the incredible hulk up there. And people
are like, that's really catchy. She should try like selling that to a TV show or something. And
people are like, what's a TV show? It's the 1930s and they started doing the flapper dance. Anyway,
so she's playing the sad piano music on the third floor. That's all she ever did. Now, again,
this is a point where I have to ask a question as a skeptic. They didn't kick her out of school.
They just let her keep attending school and they're like, hey, you need to come to your
classes and she would like play one key for yes and two keys for no. She's like,
and they're like, whoa, sorry. So I mean, obviously they wouldn't just let her play the
piano all the time. She'd have to go to classes and stuff like that. But a couple months later,
she mysteriously died and the implication is that she died of a broken heart. So again,
there's some factual problems with the story, but this is a legend at this school. She's up
there. She plays the piano all day long. She's super sad. She passes away. Now they say to this day,
on the third floor, you can still hear slow, sad piano music every so often. It's not all the time.
You're not like trying to study. It's like, it's not like that. Like she, every so often,
you'll hear like a sad piano song. But here's the interesting part. That building was completely
torn down. And now there is no third floor. It only goes up two stories. So the building was torn down.
And when they rebuilt it, they're like, oh, we don't have to build it that high.
They got lazy. They're like, there's a bunch of awnings still like set up. They're like,
yeah, whatever. The building's only two stories high, but people on the second floor will hear music
coming from the sky above them. Before the building was torn down, people would say the music came
from the third floor. And now they say the music is coming basically from the roof. That's an
interesting event because you don't see that happening a lot in ghost stories. I'll come
across the story every once in a while, where something like that happens, where they will have
a building that is burned out, and there'll still be a ghost in the area that originally was haunting
that house. But the idea of a building actually being destroyed and rebuilt in a different way,
and the ghosts still haunting the original location of the haunting, that's very, very rare. And I
think this is the only example off the top of my head I can think of. And the top of my head,
I'm looking at notes, but there's one or two more that I've heard of. But in all of Ghost Lore,
it's very, very unique. And to me, that makes it a little more plausible. The area, if you believe
that the area that you haunt is the area that you haunt, whatever is done there shouldn't matter.
So if a bunch of people die in a church and you build a museum on top of it and the ghosts haunt
the museum, people are like, well, yeah, because a church burned down. But if you have someone on
the third floor become a ghost, and then you raise the building, build up another one, and it's coming
from the air, that would also logically still make sense. So ghosts don't stand on stuff. But here's
the scary thing. Think about 9/11. Are there a bunch of ghosts like 80 stories up just wandering
around? There's just nothing there anymore? They have that new building, but I mean, it's not like
the exact same profile. Like, could you look out your window like late at night, three in the morning
in New York, look out your window with a pair of binoculars and see like a guy in a business
suit like doing his daily routine, just walking around in the sky? That's creepy. It's creepy idea.
Because it totally offsets how we think of physics and reality and spatial things and stuff like
that. So I thought that's that's that was really interesting. I really like that story. But I had
to get through the elevator falling person first because I just thought that was hilarious. Okay,
so now we're going to move on. Oh, and I want to say this too real quick. There is a Twitter
account called the Cafe and Diner. It's @CafeandDiner. If you are into paranormal stuff, check them out.
Check them out. It's an interesting Twitter account. It's an interesting Twitter account @CafeandDiner.
Very interesting. Dead Rabbit recommends @CafeandDiner. Okay, I just wanted to get that out there.
Now we're going to move on to our main story. Our main story is a story of haunted mine shafts. Now,
mines are creepy to begin with. They're basically big old holes in the earth. Of course, I mean,
that's literally the definition of a mine. They're giant holes in the earth. And some of them we make
and some of them do you make a mine? Do people see a mountain and go, I wonder what's in there and
start drilling into them into a mountain? Or do they find existing mines and go, Hey, look at
there's like this hole in this cave. Let's make it bigger. Or let's start like taking our pickaxes
and like knocking stuff off. I think it would probably take a lot of effort to have like a
I just realized for some reason, I assumed scientists would have access to Cobra Commander's
drilling machine. I don't think those really exist. I don't think there's really like a vehicle,
a tank with a Cobra logo on it has a giant drill in the front. And they're like, let's mine boys.
I don't know. I thought that was real for a second. They're always, I think they're almost always holes
that are already in mountains. I don't think they're using 1980s cartoon technology to mine.
But anyway, so we're going to Bodie State Historic Park in California. Now, in 1902,
there's this mine that people were mining for a while. But in 1902, these dudes are mining it.
And for whatever reason, maybe in 1902, they didn't have access to like,
like maybe this was state of the art equipment back then, but they had a white mule in the mine.
Now, not the fact that it was white made in high tech, but I guess you had a mule to help move the
ore carts around. But I thought they had like those little pump thingies like when two guys are on
both sides again, everything I know about the world is from cartoons. But anyway, so I guess
that's probably why the mule was down there. 1902, they have this white mule deep in the mine is the
500 foot drop 500 feet down the mine. It was called the fifth level. And then or cart broke loose.
And like went down in the end of challenges sitting in it. They're like, no, in the end of no,
it goes down the the track and hits the mule and breaks its back. And so the people there are like,
that sucks. So they shoot the shoot the mule in the head. And they're like, well, you know, he was
a good mule. He was a good mule. I don't know if they said that they may have hated his guts for
all I know. But miners began. So now like people just go about their business. But over time,
on the fifth level, 500 feet down, they begin to smell the smell of fresh mule droppings.
Hey, Barry, do you smell that? And the other guy's like, dude, well, man, lay off the sasperilla.
And he's like, there's no sasperilla around here. And it's not me. And sasperilla doesn't even do
that. Oh, smells like mule droppings. My first question when I read that was, well, how do you
know the difference between mule droppings and any other beast of burdens drop means the other guy
could have been like, no, that's definitely camel. Other guys like, no, that's horse, probably a female
horse. They're like, what? But anyway, so they would smell the smell of fresh mule droppings.
It could have just been methane in the in the cave, but maybe they'd all be dead. And then
people are like, well, whatever, we'll just get over it. It smells down here, but we'll keep working.
But then people started like rounding a corner and they would see the white mule standing at the
end of these tunnel, which is terrifying. A ghost girl walking down a pathway into college is not
scary. It's kind of like, oh, that's kind of interesting. A ghost mule 500 feet into the earth
is terrifying. And it got to the point that people wouldn't even work that level of the mind anymore.
They're like, I'm not going down there. Smells. And I can deal with that. But then when I saw a ghost
mule, like I'm walking it working down there with my head of lamp and I turn and there's just a
mule at the end of a tunnel. I'm not, no. So they weren't basically that part of the mind no one
would work. There was also an interesting part in that same mine where there was a 1200 foot shaft.
There's like a drop and reportedly someone one day picked up a rock and threw it down the shaft.
And when it hit the ground, they heard someone go, Hey, you. Now that I think is 100% made up.
Because again, if you did that, after you left your own mule trappings in the mine,
your first instinct would to be to do it again to see if it's replicated. But the mine is closed
off now they blew it up. You can't get in there. So who knows. But I think the mule story is creepy.
However, now though, what we want to do is we're still in the Bodie State Historic Park. We are
going to Lucky Boy Mine. And in Lucky Boy Mine, we are going to play an interactive adventure like
we have before. I saw Bandersnatch, by the way, it was okay. Kind of lost the novelty in a bit,
but I'll give them an A for effort. I think they can perfect it, but we're doing our own version,
but very, very low tech. This is after World War Two. So fairly recent, fairly recent.
After World War Two, shortly after World War Two, right now is after World War Two,
I should be more specific. After World War Two, Lucky Boy Mine was closed down. And the town
that was built to support Lucky Boy Mine became a ghost town except for six people. So go ahead
and pick a number between one and six. Okay, so you got your number. That number will determine
your fate in the course of this story. So you got your number in your head. You might have written
it down. I don't know because I told you to get your number two pencils earlier. You're like,
why, I bought these. I got to use them for something. Bodie State Historic Park, Lucky Boy Mine.
The town is empty except for six people. Now I know the name of one of them. One of the names
has been recorded historically. The other five we don't know the names of. So I've had to give
them names. Ed, that is a real name, his wife, Misha, a young Indian woman. And then there's four
other members of the series. Ed and his wife, then you have four other members of the town. Tommy,
Philbert, Mackenzie, and Jonas. They're just, I mean, it sounds like a boy band. Those are the
names they came up with on the spot. I don't know many Indian women named Misha, but again,
you just got to cut me some slack. Cut me some slack. So we're in the town surrounding Lucky
Boy Mine. Spooky little town, spooky little ghost town. Only six people in a town, which
would be creepy anyways. Ed was not a nice person. He was not known to be a nice person. And if you
pick the number four, you are Ed. So you're not a nice person. You're not, and you're like, Jason,
that hurts my feelings. And I'm like, no, no, no, no, no, no, you, you might be a nice person in
real life. But for the sake of the story, you're kind of a douchebag. Now he's especially not nice
to his wife, Misha. And if you picked one, you're Misha. One night, he gets really,
really mad. Ed is just had it with whatever minor thing Misha has done this time. He grabs his
shotgun. So sorry, number one. He grabs his shotgun, blows her chest off, just kills her. She doesn't
die right away. It's a very slow death. Well, not relatively slow. Because it's a slow death,
you'd be living to your 80s and dying your sleep, but she didn't just die immediately. She blew part
of her chest off as she bled out for a while and died. Now, there's no law. There's no law enforcement
there. There's no cops. There's only four other people there other than Ed and his now deceased
wife. And three of them, McKinsey, Tommy, and Philbert, could not let this injustice stand.
They thought that the murder of his wife was just, you have to be punished. So one night, they grab
Ed. "Let go of me, you vormit! What are you doing? Get off me!" They lead him down to a creek. There was
a creek nearby the town. Now, they tie him up. "What do you get to do when I get loose of these ties
and get my shotgun? I'm gonna show you stuff." They throw him, this might be one of the most
inefficient ways to murder another human. They throw him into the creek to drown him.
He doesn't drown, obviously, because he can just lift his head a couple centimeters, and he's fine.
So then, there are three guys who're standing around and they're like, "Well, we didn't really
think that one out. There was like a raging river 20 feet away." And they're like, "We don't know why
we took him to this creek, and we're kind of lazy, so we don't want to pick him back up."
They then proceeded to kick him in the head. But, not to kill him. They kicked him in the head
until he became unconscious, so he would drown. Now, there's another way. One, they could have just
kicked him to death. Two, they could have just held him underwater. But the idea of kicking
someone into unconsciousness so they will drown is so ineffective. But anyways, well, I guess not
because it works. McKinsey, Philbert, Tommy, they all jump in the air, give each other a high five,
at the same time, even though the high five hadn't been invented. Fun fact, they invented the high
five and the freeze frame when they all stood up there. And Ed had drowned. So, if you pick number
four, you're a drowned victim. And it was fun. You got kicked until you became unconscious. I wonder
what he dreamt about. I wonder if he dreamt about not getting kicked in the head. It's like,
"This is a beautiful dream. I'm not getting kicked in the head anymore." Two months go by,
and these four dudes, now they have to town to themselves. I'm going to make an assumption.
Probably got a little gay. Four guys in the town, middle of nowhere. You know, just hanging out,
doing little after World War II dances. But the room's hot. It's heavy. And it's okay. You're
just prospectors. You're just experimenting. It's okay. Doesn't mean anything. It doesn't mean
anything. But anyways, so two months later, they're the only ones in town. And one night,
McKenzie's laying in bed. Jonas is next to him. No, no, no. So, McKenzie's laying in bed, and he sees
the ghost of Ed, the frightening form of Ed appear in front of him, shaking his fists silently at him.
I imagine him thinking, "Why you little!" And fades from view. And McKenzie wakes up and
was like, "Oh my god. What the hell is that?" Next day, he tells his friends, "I saw the ghost,
I saw Ed's ghost, and he was shaking his fists furiously at me." And the two other guys who helped
murder him, Tommy and Philbert, were like, "I saw him last night too." Now at this point,
Jonas is very, very happy he didn't take part in the murder of Ed. Very, very happy. He's just
sitting there drinking his sasperilla. He's like, "I told you. Told you you shouldn't have kicked him
until he drowned." And they're like, "Shut up, Jonas. We'll take you down to the creek too." And he's
like, "Gulp." Short time later, Jonas is walking through the empty town, whistling a song, and he
turns a corner, and he sees the body of Tommy with a huge gash in his head. It's just split open.
He turns to you and goes, "If you pick number three, that's you." And then he just goes back to
this loon, drinks more sasperilla. So Tommy got his head split open. Nobody in the town knew why.
None of the three other people knew why. Maybe he fell. Maybe a bear or a crotty chopped him.
Nobody knew. Short time after that, Jonas is hanging out. He gets a phone call at home.
Well, I guess they don't even need phones. They just yell across the street. All of a sudden,
he hears Philbert go, "JONES! Jonas! Jonas, come here!" Jonas is like, "Damn it.
I've got other stuff to do, but apparently I have to go over here." He goes over to Philbert's
house. He sees Philbert's head. "Hey, let's make this dramatic. He walks into the house. All the
lights are off, and there's a roaring fire." And he just sees the silhouette of a man hunched over
the fire, and he's like, "Philbert? Philbert, are you okay?" And Philbert slowly turns towards him
as the fire crackles. And Jonas goes, "Sounds like you're just crinkling paper!" But no, no, so
Philbert keeps turning, and his head is swelling up in front of Jonas. He has this massive hemorrhage.
Like, you can just see the blood pouring out of his skull and brain, but it's not splitting the skin.
His head is inflating like a balloon, and he turns to Jonas and goes, "Help me!"
And dies. And then Jonas turns to you and goes, "If you picked number five, that was you!"
He goes back to the saloon. At this point, Jonas is having a real hard time telling it
between fantasy and reality. He's like, "For some reason, I feel like I'm in a podcast in
the year 2019. What's going on?" Short time after that, there's only two people left in town. There's
Jonas and McKinsey, and then one day, there's just Jonas. He's like, "That's weird. This town's even
more deserted than it normally is. What's going on? There should be two people here." McKinsey,
McKinsey. His dog comes running up. He's like, "Oh, I forgot I named my dog McKinsey,
but I wasn't asking for you." McKinsey. His voice is just echoing through the town.
McKinsey. McKinsey's body is never found. Jonas just kind of shrugs and he goes, "If you picked
number two, you're never found." But I have my made-up way, because I don't want you to just be a
missing person, because then you can be like, "Well, fine. I just went to Vegas." Ed grabs you and
brings you into the hell realm where he pokes your eye out, pulls out your teeth, puts him in
your eye socket, and gives it to a devil baby as a rattle. So that's you. So you would have much
better off than having just a hemorrhage or your head split open. If you pick number six,
you're Jonas. You're the one who survived to tell the tale of the lucky boy mine and one of the
most frightening examples of a ghost returning from the dead to kill his murderers. DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com
is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter. DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime
podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]