A dancing ghost
Raise interesting questions about the afterlife and then we touch on Bigfoot one last time this week when we explore the mystery
our aliens turning us
Into the Bigfoot today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you are having a great day - it's Friday
Unless you're listening to this on any other day where it wasn't uploaded and then it's just a great day
Hopefully in general. This is gonna be our last episode for the week
We're really blazing through these things run episode 180. This is awesome guys. I really really appreciate all the support
You're giving the show been a crazy trip guys
Thank you for listening if you're a new time listener welcome if you're a longtime listener. Thank you for coming back
It's always a pleasure to be telling you these crazy stories now earlier
And though I didn't get to this because the episode was running a bit long and I had to I edited it out for time
But we're talking about the Miley Cyrus thing here's I'm not gonna go back into Miley Cyrus in general
But this is a little conspiracy theory that I've had do you think it's a little thought a little thought game for you guys
Do you think there is a real Hannah Montana out there? Not as in that fictional character
But you know I did that episode on what's the scariest movie ever made the hypothetical movie that that no one's ever seen
That's out there. That's not been released to the public. I didn't episode on that. This is kind of along those lines
So we're gonna set up some ground rules. I'm asking is there a possibility
There is a real Hannah Montana-esque person out there and this is the ground rules one an A-list celebrity
that people in the world know but
Outside of their immediate family so in their neighborhood or at their school
Nobody knows that they are the A-list celebrity. They have to be A-list too. Can't be making some direct-to-DVD movies
Which is cool as those are I'm not knocking those but it's not like they're making some direct DVD movies for some horror company
And then no one at work knows that they do that. I'm not talking about that
They have to be A-list is what I'm looking for because that's you Hannah Montana was she was a
International pop star everyone knew who she was to no porn
Because a lot of people in the porn industry do keep that secret
So that's kind of a given a lot of times you'll have porn stars that are very very well known
But people close to them don't know it. So those are really the two ground rules one no pornography and two
They'd have to be an A-list star. I'm talking and this is really I came up with this idea a couple years ago
Let's take a guy like George Clooney
You have him and he's a super recognizable actor, but in his real life his family knows that he's George Clooney
but he also has a
Quiet life where he goes shopping and it would have to be consistent
I'll just putting on a fake mustache to go to the grocery store
He has an alternate personality that most of the people that know him personally
Do not know that he is George Clooney at all for a period of time that would be two more rules
I guess it should add it be or another rule for a period of time
So not just for a weekend like for a couple years. Do you think that is possible?
Do you think that it's possible that you could have somebody who is a Ariana Grande or a Brad Pitt and
The people of their family knows but the people around them they have a jaw like maybe they are an accountant
maybe they just walk around town all the time and everyone knows them as
Joey pumpkin or whatever just a totally different person and they've never made the connection that that is really Brad Pitt
Do you think that's possible?
I think it was possible more possible a couple years ago before the explosion of social media
But maybe not because I think people would cite them that was always Hannah Montana was always
Basically a little girls version of a superhero where her superpower was being famous
It was basically the story of spider-man
She was a teenage girl that got picked on at school and she had a close group of friends who knew her secret and her family knew her secret
I guess that spider-man didn't have those things will the Avengers are his friends
But you know what I mean like she would face the trials and tribulations of high school and get picked on and bullied and have to go through all
This stuff and her superpower was the fact that she was very wealthy and very famous
It was a really interesting twist on the superhero genre. That's really who Hannah Montana was that was it basically a superhero show
She just solved emotional problems rather than fight crime, but that's the question. Do you think that it's possible?
I think it's possible. The question is is is anyone doing it? I guess it's the better question
Do you think right now anyone is doing that feel free to comment shoot me an email?
We'll have a discussion, but I think it's an interesting story nonetheless
So let's go ahead and get started with our first story here now. It's funny because our first story
It's one of those stories that I basically read a version of and thought oh, it's kind of cute
That's kind of sweet and then I read the more realistic version of it
I was like and then that made me think of some more
Interesting ways to look at how it concluded
So the story I heard was there was a guy named
Grancer Harrison and Grancer was an old-timey word for grandpa Grancer Grancer
Can I get some candy? Why yes young lad that was a term. It means the grand sire. It's really really old school Grancer Harrison was
From Alabama were in the 1800s like the mid 1800s. He loved throwing parties
He had this giant dance hall constructed and every Thursday night
He'd throw on his wooden clogs and his fancy dress suit and he'd hire people to come out and fiddle
And they'd make music and everyone would just dance all night long
It was his favorite thing that when he died he said I want to be buried in my dancing outfit with my clogs
I don't want to dance for the rest of time so they did they humored him and they buried him in his beautiful dancing outfit
It wasn't like a ball gown. It was probably just like you know a dudes a dudes dancing outfit
Probably had lots of sequins, but anyways the dress him on his dancing outfit put him in his clogs buried him and
To this day people say in this area, which I should have said earlier the area is I
Didn't write it down, but anyways, it's somewhere in Alabama
That's real specific if you want to go find this ghost, but
the
The rumor is that if you go somewhere in Alabama and unnamed location in Alabama
You can hear fiddle music
Playing late at night in the graveyard and sometimes at his old dance hall, which actually he was buried near
He's basically buried on his property next to his dance hall
Sometimes when you're out there and people are like dude Alabama's a really big state
We're not gonna find this place, but if you sometimes you're just randomly walking through Alabama
You want your fiddle music and I thought that's a good that's kind of a cute ghost story
You know the guys like he really loved something. He was passionate about something
He passed away. He wanted to experience an afterlife and it came true even to this day
He's dancing somewhere in Alabama
So that was the story that I heard and when I went to go online to get some links to share with you guys and do a little
More information. I got a little more details and I don't know why some of it
Slipped by me in the beginning. One of the points is super obvious, but it went by me. So let's go back here real quick
Okay, and I went I looked it up. It's in Kinston, Alabama
Kinston so if you do want to go find his ghost
You no longer have to roam the entire state of Alabama
So here's some of the details that were left out of the charming version
I heard and again the first one is kind of a no-brainer
Grants your Harrison was a wealthy businessman wealthy enough to build a music hall for him his own party
So that was kind of given with the first story. He's a wealthy person
He lives in Alabama and it's the mid 1800s
So he had a ton of slaves now again when I first read the story. It didn't connect with me
That a wealthy man. Oh, oh, not just any wealthy man. He was a wealthy cotton farmer
I guess I should add that detail in
That was all left out of the original version, but being wealthy in the 1800s in Alabama you most likely had slaves
But being a cotton farmer you definitely had slaves and not only did he have slaves. He went all out
He loved the whole slave thing. He had one third
In the county that he was in he owned one third of the slaves. Yeah, I mean he's like pokemon. He's got to catch them all
That's a ton of slaves
He owned one third of them
So he goes I want to build a dance hall
Make the slaves do it. So the dance hall that everyone had parties at was constructed by slave labor
So that kind of makes the story a little less charming. I don't know if the musicians were slaves
I don't know if the slaves were forced to dance as well. I'm not for sure on any of that
But they did construct it. He did hold the dance parties. This is a historical person
He and there's still ruins out there in kinsten, alabama. See I I remember
um, they built they built the dance hall
And the story goes on as normal except now there's slaves everywhere
So the original charming story now every part where the little kids like grand sir grand sir
Can I have some candy there's enslaved human beings standing around
There are people who've been pulled from their families and are now slaves in that story. Here you go. Here's some candy
Terrible. So anyways, he does say I want to be buried
With my dancing clothes on so I can dance for the rest of time
I didn't actually say for the rest of time. He just goes I just want to be buried in my dancing clothes
And he wanted his mausoleum built and he actually wanted to be buried in his bed too
So we're talking it's going to be a big structure slaves make the slaves build it
So the slaves build this giant structure for him to be buried in
And they do and they take his bed when he dies. They don't do it while he's still alive
He's like I can still breathe and they're like wheeling it into the vault
After he dies they put his bed into the mausoleum
Put him in his nice fancy dancing clothes
put on his good wooden clogs his dancing shoes seal the door and
After he died people still kept going to the dancing hall in his memory
But it without him it wasn't the same the place eventually fell into disrepair and it kind of is
No more it's ruins now or it might just be a foundation, but his grave is still there his open
His above-ground grave like a mausoleum
To this day people can still hear music in kinsten alabama fiddle music and the sound
Of good old grancer harrison dancing in his clogs
Now I after reading about all the slaves and the slaves having to build the dance hall and the slaves having to build the mausoleum
I have another take on this story
What is the most uncomfortable activity that you could do for the rest of time?
in wooden shoes
it'd be dancing
While running track or walking up the flight stairs, but you know what I mean like that doesn't sound like something
That doesn't sound like a pleasurable experience to dance until the heat death of the sun
And the planet earth is destroyed
That sounds quite the
Punishment so here's my theory
Yes, he didn't want to be dressed in his dancing clothes and his shoes because he loved dancing so much
But when the slaves were building that structure
I have no proof for this, but as the slaves were building that structure. What if they put a curse on it?
What if they basically cursed that structure so grancer would spend the rest of time dancing in his shoes?
And that fiddle music as jaunty as it may sound even though it's coming from some sort of
Astral plane and leaking into our dimension the phantom
Dancing in that field. He's not happy
Just tears of pain streaming down his face
Now I don't know if any of that's true, but I do have to say that I think if I I think if I had to choose between
walking into a house and seeing a ghost staring at me from the corner or a ghost walking down the stairs
or
A ghost dancing looking at me with wide eyes is dancing a jig
One of those things is far more terrifying
That would be okay. Forget the ghost thing. Let's say you walked into a mcdonald's
And you saw someone standing at the counter, but they're staring directly at you
You looked and you saw someone coming down some stairs
This mcdonald's is two stories for some reason or then you turn and you see someone staring at you
Dancing a jig which one would be more terrifying ghost or not?
I don't think gran sir is having a lot of fun in the afterlife. Oh, and I do have to say they thought it's uh
Like 100 years later people thought there was gold in his grave and they blew it up dynamite
So I mean his ghost apparently is still dancing even though his bones got scattered all over the graveyard
Okay, and oh and I just say there was no gold and they just blew it up
So
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story now our next story is interesting and I didn't I don't want to do too
much bigfoot stuff this week, but this one I kind of mentioned on my vanishing bigfoot episode where I said
Talked about bigfoot aliens or something more chilling and I thought this I was going to save this
I was like no, I'm going to just wrap up the week with this because I already kind of referenced it
And I think it's a very interesting story if if it's true
If it's true, which is always the caveat
This is a recommendation from Bennett again from email. He did the vanishing bigfoot one as well
It was kind of just a bigfoot centric email. We're looking at the theory that bigfoot and aliens are connected
So you get two cryptids for the price of one you get two creepy things that want to get you for the price of one
And I was reading this article and there was a couple sightings they can piece together with the bigfoot phenomenon
It's Humboldt County
It's not full of marijuana or marijuana farms or mysterious disappearances because a lot of people go missing up there
And most likely it's because they're stumbling across illegal marijuana. Do they still grow marijuana illegally?
Or can you just grow it in the forest now? I don't know. I don't know
But anyways, this is in Eureka County in 1888
This trapper is talking to these native Americans and they go, oh, you want to see something weird
Which generally you shouldn't if someone says you want to see something weird in your middle of the woods and you don't know them
It's not a good idea, but he goes
And the native Americans take him to this cave and there's this huge hunched bear
Sitting in a cave like cross legged indian style
But the trapper can see that it's not a bear. He sees that it's some sort of
creature
Not necessarily a bear and the natives go
Three crazy bears were dropped into the woods
A couple days ago these moons came from the sky and dropped them off
Dude's like what?
Now that's the end of that story
So i'm a little suspicious because you think he probably would have poked it with a stick or shot at it or something
But according to the story then they all just kind of walked away
And they described it as being a big humanoid with long black
shiny hair
And no neck now this is starting us off and i'm not going to list all of them. There are a lot of encounters
Where we have ufo's and bigfoot in the same area and a term has actually been coined for this
It's called high strangeness. The idea of high strangeness is this nothing exists in a bubble in the paranormal world
You will see crossovers between things that we didn't think there was any crossover between
i.e aliens and bigfoot you can have areas that may have
ufo activity
And ghosts that's not quite unlikely. We don't hear a lot of reports of that. I think it's because
Yeah, why don't we actually have reports of those two things happening in the same spot?
Because high strangeness is the idea that these things all have some sort of connection that we don't know about yet
But why is there not a place that has a bunch of ufo sightings and ghost running around?
It's interesting
That's interesting to me at least but i never really thought of that before but we do have a lot of connections between aliens and bigfoot
We have a lot of connections between
There's the theory that demons are actually aliens. There's
Places where you have alien activity and then we'll have like portals and all sorts of stuff
Like the pyramids would be a good idea of a high strangeness area
there's a lot of there's like curses
and
Free energy and all sorts of weird stuff like you can put a bunch of theories into the pyramids who built them
It's a conspiracy all that stuff kind of high strangeness
We know who built them, but i mean okay how we built them but all of that stuff so
But yeah, go i wonder why there's not ghosts and ufo sightings like there's anyways, okay, so
There's a lot of ufo sightings though that involve bigfoot
people seeing objects in the sky and then a bigfoot being found in the area
objects flying near the ground like people this mother and this kid
saw a like
Or but flying by and then like a bigfoot jumped out
So i mean like what's going on, but
There's a lot of reports of that
There's a lot of reports of that type of stuff what i want to look at specifically is
One report in general now this one's interesting because i think it may have another answer to what bigfoot is
But you're gonna have to go on a journey with me a journey
To fight it pay it pay it county, pennsylvania
The year
Is 1973 three years before i was born
i'm still
On the tree of life just a fruit ready to be picked and dropped into this mortal plane, but at this time i don't exist
But these people do there's these people have all been born already in this story. It's nighttime
There's a group of 15 people in Fayette county, pennsylvania. I don't know what they're doing
Just hanging out 15 people at night. I don't know
Probably not up to no good or maybe hunters because they also had guns
So they're out in this area and they see a large illuminated orb
Floating above a pasture
These two seven to eight feet tall figures begin walking
around the orb
Now there is a quite a distance between there's a couple hundred yards
I believe between the group of humans and then there's a fence and then about 25 yards behind that
Is the orb and they're seeing these people
So I think it was like 200 yards to the fence and so on but they see it's so bright
They see these giant tall figures walking around it. So these guys with guns open fire
Because what else are you gonna do when you see some sort of bizarre event and giants walking around you're gonna open fire
None of the bullets hit them
But they did find out later that their bullets were hitting at least one or two bullets hit the fence in front of them
So they were at least aiming in the right direction
One of the creatures one of the giant seven to eight feet tall monster men
Touches the other one on the shoulder
The light disappears
And the two creatures begin to walk away into the forest and they're still getting shot at by these dudes
Don't even care they just walk away very slowly
One of the group runs to a house to call the cops because they don't have cell phones back then cops show up
And the first thing they realized other than the fact that there's four now 14 guys out there with guns just had completely
Just open fire. They could hear the gunfire people are like and what in tarnation is going on out there
Why is everyone shooting their guns?
They get there and the area at night where that orb was and where the people are is completely lit up
Somehow one of the cops said I could read and I could have read a newspaper out there
That's how bright it was even though now the orb was completely gone
Somehow that light was still lingering in that area
The group then decides with the cops involved. We need to get to the bottom of this and find out what those things were
Could be the russians
So they start moving around and they start to notice some weird things one
There's a barn farther down on the property and as they're getting closer to it
Just lights up for a brief second as bright as the sun they said not as hot because then the barn and the planet earth would be destroyed
But as bright as the sun in the barn they could see all the light just appear in the barn and then once again
The barn was pitch black
They noticed there was a bull. This was an odd detail. There was a bull and a dog in the field
And the bull and the dog weren't paying attention to the humans. They were in instead staring at the forest
It's like I don't know. I don't know how bulls normally react at night. So that detail really didn't do anything for me, but
What happens then is that somehow and this is where the story gets a little suspicious to me
But let's just keep going on with it right now
The person also called some paranormal investigators some paranormal investigators also showed up at the scene that night which
That's a little weird. I mean, I don't know if they're just driving around and they're weirdo wagon
looking for like
Bizarre stuff or have a police scanner and they're like we just cornered freddy kruger get to the corner of eighth and ninth street and
Which would be a very odd design city if there's a corner of eighth and ninth, but you know what? I mean like somehow they get to the site
Sounds a little convenient for me. It makes me think that it could be fake
That's all made up. But anyway, so these paranormal
Investigators and their weirdo wagon show up and they start interviewing one of the guys
As all this stuff is still going on. They're like, what did you see in the beam of the light where they sex squatch or where they bigfoot?
Was it a yeti? Like I was like, I don't know was a giant monster in front of a giant light
Anyways, this is the interesting part
They're interviewing and you know what now that I think about it
Story is probably made up like it's one of those things like all right notes
I think people think I have a script for this show and I think I need to put a quash on that right now
None of this stuff is scripted all right notes
I'll read about it all right notes and then a couple days later. I'll do an episode and sometimes when I'm reading the story
I'm like that is fascinating
And then once I start reading it. I realize that it's there's
Some serious problems with this. But anyways, let's just keep going
Let's just keep going with this. So anyways, the weirdo wagon shows up these paranormal investigators are like
Tell us what you saw tell us what you saw when the bright light appeared and this guy starts going
And starts like growling like an animal
So I mean come on anyways, he's growling like an animal
And the paranormal investigators and his buddies are like dude, what's wrong? What's wrong?
They're kind of freaking out the dude's own dog
The dude's own dog actually gets so scared of what the this guy's like
Freaking out his own dog tries to attack him and then he goes
The dog runs away scares the dog. So the paranormal investigators are like, whoa, this is a little out of our league
He starts running off into the the crazy guy now runs off into the field screaming
And everyone else is like what the hell is going on and the dude just collapses
So the group goes over there and they help him up and they immediately smell the rotten eggs
Okay, they immediately smell rotten eggs and then he gets up and he goes what what happened, man
And they're like, you don't remember you were just making a bunch of animal noises and ran away and and uh,
Scared the dog fell down. He's like
All I remember is seeing visions of a horrible future
Mankind is doomed
The world is going to end
And that's kind of the end of the article
Of because so when I told you the paranormal investigators showed up just out of the blue
This article is from I should have put two and two together guys. I'm sorry
This article is from their website and to get and then it says there's even more craziness and then you have to buy their book
so I
I'm sorry for not telling my due diligence on this one. I was so
Entranced this was okay. Even when I started this episode what 30 minutes ago the intro
My idea was that what if
Aliens are turning humans into bigfoot people and this is how he was in this and this is how I was thinking
He was in that area and he got like all like
Like starting to turn into a monster and what's the first thing he wanted to do was to run away
Why did he want to run away because he was in a state of panic?
He was having these visions of mankind destroying itself. Here was my theory
That bigfoot are actually people who have been genetically engineered by aliens
and driven mad to avoid humans
And they get all
And get all furry but the crazy beastal nature of this guy
I was thinking like whoa, what if bigfoot are actually like
bioengineered humans
by aliens
And that's what I believed 30 minutes ago
But as I was going back over the story in my head. I'm thinking
It doesn't make sense that they showed up so quickly and again. I should have
I should
So I should have I should have figured that out. But I mean here. This is my other thing
It's super easy to fake being insane
I can have let's say that I do a live stream of this show
I can easily go
Okay, are you out there? Are you out there ghost in my claw? Oh?
And then just freeze the camera and and then come back and be like, I don't know what happened guys
I don't know what happened. I have a little more moral
I have a little more morals than to do that and it would totally ruin my brand to pull something like that off
But it's very easy to do and it's even easier to just make up and just to write it somewhere on a website
And say buy my book if you want to learn more stuff
But all that aside all that aside i'm gonna salvage this episode as best as I can
I do think that that could be I think I could think that is a possible theory that the bigfoot is actually
Humans turned into these creatures
By aliens or some sort of force
And what this guy went through would kind of mirror that reverting to a beastal nature
Trying to run away and being told having visions in your head that the world is going to end due to mankind
You would want to eschew everything mankind
And it explains two things it explains one it would explain one why there's not a lot of big feet
Why they're so hard to find
Why they can hide berry bodies and stuff like that because they don't they're actively trying not to be found
And it explains stuff like
People going missing in the middle of the woods and never being found
They are the bigfoot
The person who goes missing in the woods
They send out all the search parties looking for them and they're huddling in some cave and they're starving
They don't know what to do next
And then a white light appears in front of them
And fills their heads
With apocalyptic visions
The rescuers may never have found that missing person
But that missing person in a new body
Is watching them
And hiding
From all of us
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great weekend guys
[Music]