A ghost points out his murderers to a group of assassins.
And then we take a look at the story of Sada Abe.
Part-time prostitute, part-time restaurant employee, all-time one of Japan's most notorious
criminals today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover today, so we're just going to jump right into it.
But I want to say, hope you guys are having a happy Monday.
Or if you're listening to this episode in the future, I hope you're having a happy
blank day.
Let's go ahead and move on to our first story though, and that is going to be the story
of Wong.
We don't have his first name.
That might be his first name.
But there's not a lot of details to the personal who Wong was, but it's an interesting story
and on the lesson, we'll kind of dig into it a little deeper.
A little deeper.
Because I think there's some, I have some questions about it debunking-wise, but it's
still an interesting story.
Hold on.
The year?
The early 1900s.
It's a little saloon town.
Beautiful women.
We'll back for them.
They're probably really gross thinking about it now.
But you had saloon town.
You had Rootin Tootin saloons, gun slingers, but mostly gold miners in this town.
We're in the town of Whiskey Flat.
It's this little town in California.
Okay, enough of the music.
But anyways, we're in the town of Whiskey Flat.
And there we find a young man named Wong.
He's a Chinese cook.
He's a cook who happened to be Chinese, I guess would be a better way to say that.
He wasn't making Chinese food.
He was making Chinese food for, I mean, he was making food for miners.
Not little kids, but he was making food for miners.
You know what I'm saying?
Gold miners.
So early 1900s.
Little kids may have ate it.
I don't know.
Well, one day he's making dinner and a white woman comes in and starts making moves on
him and he's like, "No, I'm good.
I'm kind of busy right now.
Plus you're really, really drunk.
So I'm going to kind of say no to this."
And she's still kind of like coming on a woman.
He's like, "No, listen, I have no means no."
And the white woman leaves.
And she tells these five loggers nearby that Wong had raped her.
Now I got to say this as an aside.
How, it's been 20, 30 years since I'm 42.
So it's been a long time since I've been in school and especially like high school, middle
school.
How do they, do they, first question, do they still teach to kill a mockingbird in school?
And two, how do they teach that part of it?
Because a huge part of that is the white woman making up the rape allegation.
Like how do they teach that today?
But you know, it did happen.
It did happen where a white woman would accuse an ethnic minority of rape and then, never
had a good result.
Never had a good result.
So she points him out and says, "That guy raped me."
And these five loggers, they go.
So the five men walk into the Chinese, not Chinese restaurant.
The five men walk into the kitchen and they grab the cook and they pull him out.
They string him up and they hang him.
They lynch him.
And then they go into the kitchen and eat his food that he was making for them.
Very, very cold blooded.
Now there was an investigation into the murder of Wong.
It wasn't just like, "Aye's just a Chinese cook.
We don't got to worry about this guy."
Like people were like, he was well liked.
People were like, "I wonder what happened to that guy."
Like they found his body.
He didn't go missing.
But they couldn't find any proof that anyone did anything.
Everyone was keeping their mouth shut.
But a few months later, these five other Chinese men come to Whiskey Flap.
They didn't look for work.
They had a bunch of money in their pocket, kept to themselves.
Everyone was thinking, "That's weird."
I mean, it's not like seeing Chinese people was weird, but they come here for work.
And these guys are just kind of walking around the town, not doing anything.
So one of the men that the woman had grabbed to help her with Wong, he goes missing.
Never found him.
Never found a body.
And then another one of the men goes missing.
Couple weeks later, another one of the men goes missing.
One by one, eventually, all five of the loggers go missing.
And when the last logger who was involved in Wong's murder disappeared, the five men
left town.
Now the idea in town was that the five men were a member of the Dong.
It was basically the Chinese mafia.
And they used Taoist techniques to contact the spirit of Wong.
And he pointed out each person who had something to do with his murder.
And after they were done seeking vengeance, they left town.
Today, the city of Whiskey Flap is no more.
It was actually flooded and it's at the bottom of Lake Isabella.
Lake Isabella is near Kernville, California.
And sometimes the lake gets so lowered you can actually see the tops of buildings because
the town was just flooded in there.
I wasn't able to tell whether or not it was flooded naturally or they built a dam.
I was looking for that.
I couldn't figure that out.
But people still say that to this day, sometimes hovering over the lake, you'll see the spirit
of Wong pointing his finger at the men who killed him.
Now that's the story.
Here's the thing.
When I read it, I go, "That's a fascinating story, but I have a couple things to debunk
at one.
Why wasn't the woman killed?"
There's no mention of the woman ever again.
And why would the ghost still be pointing out in the middle of the lake?
Like just pointing at random people in rowboats.
And how would you be able to see it if you're on the coast of the lake and you saw something
pointing at you?
You'd be like, "What?
Why are you pointing it?"
And behind you, you'd be like, "What?
Are you pointing it?
Who are you pointing at?
You're pointing at me?
What did I do?
I just came here and the little ghost guy pointing at you."
The reason why I wanted to cover this story, I don't think it's true.
I don't think it's true.
Some of the details are true.
Whiskey Flat was real.
The really is the city at the bottom of Lake Isabella.
We know those two facts are true.
But the reason why I wanted to cover this is because I almost feel like somebody worked
backwards.
Because the story itself doesn't really make sense.
How would the five guys be able to contact...how would they know he was killed in the first
place and then they go there and they're talking to his ghost and he's pointing people out
but he doesn't point out the woman and he points them out one by one.
And here's the most interesting thing in thinking about this as a debunker.
No one in the town knew who killed him.
So if the story is true, why would they think those five people who went missing in a mining
town which is fairly transient to begin with?
If nobody knew who the suspects were in the first place and five people went missing, how
would they make the connection?
It'd be one thing if the people in town knew who did it but they couldn't prove it.
But they didn't know who did it.
Just five people left and they're like, "Oh, there must have been the guys who hung Wong."
So there's a lot of weird coincidences.
This is what I think happened though.
This is how I think...and I think this is why I wanted to talk about this story as well.
There may or may not be a ghost pointing over the lake of Lake Isabella.
There may or may not be a ghost there.
Could be a trick of a light.
Could be an urban legend.
Could be a ghost.
But what I think happened was...and we'll talk about a couple other stories this week
where this has happened.
Is that somebody...let's say that there is a ghost floating over the lake of Lake Isabella.
Pointing at people.
Somebody created the story to explain the ghost.
They saw a ghost of...again, how are you supposed to tell his ethnicity on a lake?
You're in a rowboat.
You're hundreds of yards away.
I don't think they were super close to this dude.
Otherwise he'd be picking their nose.
He'd be poking them in the eyeball.
You saw a misty figure 300 yards away.
I don't think you'd be like, "Hmm, that guy's probably from Bulgaria."
You'd just be like, "It's a ghost."
But anyways, so unless he was wearing a super traditional Chinese outfit.
He's a ghost.
He doesn't look like Liu Kang or anything like that.
He's not dressed in traditional clothes.
He's just wearing cooked clothes.
Anyways, what I think happened is that somebody saw a ghost and then the story was crafted
to create this narrative.
That really doesn't make sense when you put any weight on it.
And the reason why I think that's interesting, it makes you think how many other haunted places
may have this same thing.
They're like, "Oh, if it's a ghost, something tragic must have happened here."
And we actually, we saw that with the town of Dudleyville.
Where people thought the town was haunted and then they made up this whole backstory
about this guy pissing off the king of England and getting sent to Dudleyville.
And none of that stuff was true.
None of it was true.
Interesting take on the ghost story are sometimes, are there real ghosts, but the stories we
create to explain them are the thing that's made up and the thing that's easily debunkable.
Is there really a ghost pointing at people out in the middle of the lake?
Who knows?
But it wasn't Wong and that story almost 100% never happened.
Like I'll debunk the story before I can debunk the ghost.
So our next story is the story of Sada Abe.
Now yes, I do know in my episode about the guy who loved euthanasia, I called the president
of Japan Shinzo Abe and I was corrected very quickly, not just on YouTube comments, but
a friend of mine in real life punched me in the arm and said "It's Abe!
And then when the guy who sent me this story sent me this story via email, when I got the
email, he said "Now, Jason, this is how you pronounce the girl's name.
It's Abe."
And I was like "Yeah, yeah, I know.
But you know, he's just looking out for me.
So thank you, Abe.
Thank you for this suggestion.
Now this is the story of Sada Abe.
Bizarre, bizarre crime.
And it's one of those things that I think if you're not in Japan, you've never heard
of this ever.
I've never heard of this before.
And it's quite gruesome and incredibly famous.
We're going back to the year of 1905 and we see a little baby girl named Sada Abe.
Her mother loved Sada, taking care of her.
Her father was also pretty appreciative of her, but he was a little more stern.
She had an older sister and an older brother.
And from all accounts, her early life was fairly normal, normal in the sense of Japan.
So her older sister was a little slutty, a little loose.
And apparently this was the thing back then.
You know that thing, like if you get caught smoking a cigarette and your dad's like,
"You like cigarettes?
You like cigarettes?
Here, smoke a whole pack."
And you're like, "Ugh, ugh, ugh."
And you eventually get nicotine poisoning and you get really sick and throw up and you're
like, "I'm never smoking another cigarette again."
In Japan, they did that for sex.
So when Sada's older sister was sleeping around, the dad was like, "Oh, you like sleeping
around?
You like banging dudes?
Bang 30 dudes!"
And he dropped her off at a brothel and she just started banging dudes.
I don't imagine it works the same as it does with cigarettes, but apparently that's what
they did back then.
So you kind of know where part of the story's going.
Sada, as she's getting older, she starts to get, first off, she actually starts taking
singing lessons and she started learning this instrument called the shamisen, which back
then was more connected to the geisha culture and geishas were still basically like, had
a foot in the prostitute culture.
And they had legal brothels and unlicensed brothels and stuff like that.
And geishas, you had high level geishas who would just perform and then you had lower
level geishas who were there to bang the people, bang the dudes you came to visit.
So, but anyways, she starts singing, they didn't have any YouTube back then, so singing
would really only lead to one thing.
And she's learning this instrument and she starts to become really rebellious.
She starts hanging out with the wrong crowd, she starts skipping school, she starts wearing
a lot of makeup.
So all really early warning signs of someone who may have trouble in the future.
At this point in time, she ends up getting raped by a friend.
She's still fairly, she's like in high school at this point, the equivalent of high school
in Japan.
And her parents are, you know, defend her and are like, okay, we have your back.
But then she starts to become even more uncontrollable and lashing out at them and not going to
school and stuff like that and sleeping around all the time.
So at that point, the dad goes, worked with her sister and he sent her to a brothel.
She liked banging dudes, banging 50 dudes.
So she's at the brothel, she ends up becoming a prostitute.
Now we're jumping ahead to the 1930s.
So at this point, she's around 25 years old.
She ends up working at a licensed brothel, she still has money from them, she gets in
trouble.
She goes to an unlicensed brothel, she's not supposed to be working there, I think the
place gets raided, she gets in trouble.
She's kind of moving around and in this time period, she actually went to a geisha house
because she's like, oh, I can be a geisha because I have all these skills.
When she goes there and she realizes that to be a traditional geisha, you have to start
practicing full on geisha training at a super young age.
So they said, you can come and work for us, but you have to be a low level geisha, you're
just going to bang dudes.
So basically, she's still a prostitute now she's just wearing geisha makeup.
But that's when she starts meeting all of these high profile people.
And one of them says, you've got to start thinking about a career path, you've got to start thinking
about the future, you can't do this forever.
You should open a small restaurant.
You go into business for yourself.
And it's funny because I imagine like as he's giving her this fatherly advice, he's
banging her.
But he was trying to help her and saying, you know, you just can't do this forever.
And he goes, why don't you go to this restaurant, get a job, learn the trade, and then in a
couple of years, you can go and open your own little restaurant.
And she thought, that is a good idea.
Because you're right, I can't do this forever.
Now we're jumping into the year 1936.
She does get a job at a restaurant.
She's a server.
And she meets Kichizo Ishidi.
Kichizo Ishidi, he's the married owner of the restaurant.
She's smitten by him.
She has no problem sleeping with a married man.
She was a prostitute.
She'd done it all the time.
And she starts to kind of try to seduce him.
And it works very, very quickly.
Very quickly.
Young woman.
He's like 42.
He's totally into her.
He's like, yeah, let's do this.
And basically it's one of those things where, hey, let's go away for the weekend and have
sex.
And they did.
But the weekend became two weeks.
They just couldn't get out of bed.
Now she had always talked about how no one could really, she probably had nymphomania
at a certain point.
Because she was constantly talking about how she couldn't be sedative.
Like she needed a man who could really satisfy her.
She found one in this man.
He could pleasure her like nobody else could.
But after two weeks, he's like, you know, I do have a restaurant to run.
Plus, my wife.
So I'll see you at work tomorrow.
And he bounces.
And she becomes insanely jealous.
Super, super jealous.
She pawns.
This is one of the details that I thought was quite odd.
She pawns some of her clothes off to buy a kitchen knife.
First question.
How expensive were kitchen knives in Imperial Japan?
Second question.
She works at a restaurant.
Couldn't she have just gotten a kitchen knife there?
But for whatever reason, it must be a jewel encrusted monogrammed kitchen knife.
She pawns some of her clothes, gets this fancy, dancy kitchen knife.
And the next time they meet up, she says, I'm going to kill you.
And she pulls a knife on him and puts it to him.
And he laughs it off.
He's like, ah, whatever.
And they bang each other.
Now I'm all down for crazy chicks.
I think every guy loves a little bit of crazy in their chick.
But there's a limit.
Like, that's the limit.
That is the limit.
Pulling a weapon on me is the limit.
If you pull a weapon on me and say you're going to kill me, then I'm done.
I don't care how hot you are.
But anyways, so they start making love again.
And at one point, in between their lovemaking, I'm assuming, otherwise she has a death wish,
she takes the knife and she puts it to the base of his penis.
Now I'm going to let you guys know there are going to be several parts where you may want
to cross your legs during the story.
This isn't even close to one of them.
She puts a knife to the base of his dick and says, I'm going to make sure you never take
another woman as a lover.
And he laughs it off.
He's like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
which is far more scary, far more scary, because you're going to run into those people, you're going to run into the normal girl who seems normal, who seems pretty, who has all the right things to say, and when you're not with her, she's ponning her clothes to buy a knife.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]