A man believes that he can talk to ghosts using running water from a kitchen sink.
And then we end the week by taking a bizarre journey and looking at this woman's life as
she is living it right now.
Is it possible that she has connected with an entity that is giving her instructions?
Or did a blood disease boil her brain today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvin, and I'm having a good day.
I hope you guys are having a good day too.
I hope you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend.
Just a quick reminder again, May 14th I will be at the McMinnimin's UFO Festival in McMinnville,
Oregon.
Not as a speaker, but as the person who paid $125 to get a vendor table.
But I'm gonna be there, I'm gonna bring in all these haunted items.
Veronica Mahonadal is going to be there to get her autograph.
We'll put a little pin in her hand.
It's gonna be lots of fun.
And there's a bunch of UFO people there as well.
Whitley Stryber.
If I'm not a big enough draw, Whitley Stryber, the author of Communion, is going to be speaking
at the convention.
He'll be there May 13th.
So you gotta pick a day.
You can't stay there for both.
It's a festival they immediately kick you out if you stick around for too long.
But someone who never sticks around for too long is actually one of our long term Patreon
supporters.
Really, really appreciate this.
And give it up for Cindy Perrariya.
Wooo!
Everyone give a big round of applause as Cindy is walking into Dead Rabbit Command.
Cindy, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the Patreon.
I totally understand.
Just helps read the word about the show.
That helps out so much.
Cindy, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're gonna float all the way out to some dude's kitchen.
Giant Durgible's knocking over all of his dishes.
Oh no!
That's Fiesta Ware.
But we don't care about any of that.
And even if we do, even if we demolish this guy's collection of dishes, it's okay because
he can talk to them from beyond the dead.
Still doesn't fix his dishes.
Still doesn't clean up his kitchen.
But we're gonna take a look at this dude.
His name is Grant.
And he has a YouTube channel called Optimal Frequency.
I don't remember how I even came across these guys.
Optimal Frequency is the YouTube channel's name.
And what they do, they have a gimmick.
Every YouTube channel should have a gimmick.
Mine is.
Mine is to have the least amount of recommendations.
YouTube is completely shadow banned.
My channel, I don't even think most of my subscribers even know when to put out videos
anymore.
But my gimmick is being run off YouTube.
But let's take a look at Grant here.
He runs this channel Optimal Frequency.
What he does is he, you know, on one hand this is kind of ingenious.
And on the other hand, this is the highest level of cherry picking when it comes to any
sort of ghost audio.
So let me tell you what it is for.
What he does is he has this new technology.
He turns on a faucet.
You're like, "Water!
Whoa!
Where's this magical thing at?"
He turns on like a kitchen faucet and he records the water going, "Shhh!"
You don't know what water sounded like.
You didn't even know running water existed until this podcast.
And then he has this thing.
He didn't invent this.
This is a software you can buy.
It's called Crisp.
And what it does, it's intelligent software.
It filters out white noise for zoom calls or anything really.
For ghosts, for ghosts and water.
You didn't know that was possible.
It's to filter out weird noises or white noises if a ghost is floating around when
you're trying to do a job interview.
You're like, "Uhhh!
I want to work at Microsoft.
My place is currently haunted.
I need a move.
I don't have any money."
But anyway, so yeah, that's what Crisp, this software is.
You can like, it's a monthly fee.
I think it is your buy it out, right?
So the way Grant has it set up is that he records the water running.
He asks questions.
And then he goes back and using the Crisp software, it makes the water say something,
right?
It's punching it in the stomach and it's like, "Come on, water molecules, tell us the truth."
I'll play you a sample.
So because you guys are like, "What in the world is this guy talking about?"
That's what I was thinking the whole time I was watching these videos.
And of course I had a pick on the most clickbaity video this guy recently did.
Because if you're going to ask the ghost in your kitchen anything, ask them about the
current war in Ukraine.
Because why not, right?
Why not?
You're just going to hear a bunch of white noise and you're going to pick words out
and go, "Oh, it says that."
Then he posted a video on March 29th, 2022 called the Ghost of Kiev, Part 1.
Yeah, there's two of these.
He has a lot of videos overall.
What he does is he'll ask this question.
So let's say for example he asks, "As of today, how many Russian generals have been killed
by the Ukrainians?"
Oh, again, I'm talking about the ghosts.
I'm sure they have better things to do than be like going to CNN.com and trying to figure
that information out.
"As of today, how many Russian generals have been killed by the Ukrainians?"
And it says on the screen, "He knows, Grant knows, that the number is five at that time.
Five Russian generals had reportedly been killed by the Ukrainians."
This is the ghost answer, though.
Okay, section two.
How many Russian generals have been reportedly killed as of today by the Ukrainians?
So if you didn't understand what that was saying, which I'm fully aware that probably
most of you are like, "Huh?"
That said, "I heard that they were wrong."
Well, okay, let me back up here.
This is what he says the ghost said, right?
"I heard that they were wrong.
It's only an empty theory."
If CNN.com can tell you how many Russian generals have died, I don't know why the ghosts give
such a cryptic answer.
And the ghost is constantly saying, I feel bad, I'm actually putting this on the ghost,
this technology, optimal frequency, this website, this YouTube channel.
And what's weird, right?
So all of his questions are weird.
That was one of the most sensical questions that he asked, and it was something that could
be verified.
"How many Russian generals have died?"
And then this ghost is like, "Ahhh," gives that answer.
But he asks questions, so he has a partner.
I guess normally it doesn't work with him.
This guy named Gary Reid.
So Grant is also working with this guy named Gary Reid.
And he asks the ghost, he's asking the ghost about, "What do you think about me working
with Gary?"
What?
He's in your house.
It's a little too late to be asking the ghost.
The ghosts are like, "Look out, he has a knife."
It's a little too late to be asking stuff like that.
He's asking questions about that.
He's like, "Is my audio setup okay?
Is everything okay?"
You should know this stuff.
You've been doing a YouTube channel for a long time.
And the way it's set up is you record the ghosts talking through the water, and then
you put the crisp technology over that to clean up all of the non-ghost stuff, aka running
water, right?
It's just going to eliminate everything.
And then you try really hard to hear something.
And then, so you record the voice, you record the sound, I don't want to humor if it's saying
these actually recording voices.
You record the sound, and then you run it through the AI program, and then you're sitting
there in your editing bay at home, and you're playing it back.
You've already recorded everything.
If it gives you any advice on your recording setup, you've already taken it apart.
You've already removed everything, right?
So it wouldn't even make sense.
You don't hear it in real time.
It wouldn't even make sense if you were asking how everything's okay.
Now maybe, watch, I don't know if this will be a video that he finds.
Maybe he'll say, "No, I do listen to it in real time."
I just have to say, it doesn't seem that way, sir, because you keep asking the question,
"How's my audio setup?
How's my audio setup?"
If you could hear it in real time, and when they say...
This is their answer, by the way, how's his audio setup?
[Metal clattering]
They compliment his monitor.
They say that his monitor is cool, or something like that.
I'll play the actual clip.
[Laughs]
They didn't actually say that.
People are gonna be like, "What?
You quoted the ghost out of context."
They did not say the monitor was cool.
But anyway, so whatever, dude.
This kind of goes on and on and on.
At one point, he starts going about the go...
This is what made me click on this video in particular.
We know now, for a matter of fact, that Ghost of Kiev does not exist.
It didn't exist.
He never existed.
It was a video game demo footage someone put together from War Thunder, if I remember
correctly.
We did an episode on it.
He didn't exist.
So right...
I do have to give this dude credit, because he didn't take the videos down.
It would be the same thing as if I did a video where I used a Ouija board to contact the
count from Sesame Street.
And the thing kept going to the numbers.
Then it went, "HA, HA, HA, HA."
And I was like, "Oh my God, we've made contact with the count from Sesame Street."
And then someone informed me, CNN informed me, "The count is not real."
Right?
I think most people would have taken it down.
So as far as when I'm recording this, the Ghost of Kiev episode is still up.
Because he doesn't exist.
And we all know he didn't exist.
But they're asking like, legitimate questions.
You're like, "What's the thrust like on your jet?
How many afterburners?
How many Gs can your jet take?"
No.
They actually ask questions like, "How many confirmed kills has the Ghost of Kiev got?"
And the answer, the ghost didn't say it's not real.
It's not real, Grant.
The Ghost of Kiev is a propaganda tool.
They said, "50 at least.
Check it."
They asked the ghost if Zelensky, who what?
Is the prime minister or president?
I don't know the exact position of.
But prime minister Zelensky from Ukraine.
Is he the Ghost of Kiev?
And no.
If you were on your edge of your seat for two seconds there thinking that was true,
the ghost said no.
I don't think that was a joke.
I don't think they actually believe that.
Now you could go Jason, you're cherry picking.
You're cherry picking kind of the funny moments and stuff like that.
And I am.
But you also gotta remember that that's what this is as well.
They're cherry picking the ones that fit the answers.
They could have been doing this for hours on end.
And these are the ones that make any sort of sense, right?
My thing is, is like, so we've talked about this before.
There's things like, obviously, EVP is just putting out saying, "Is there anyone in here?"
And then you go back and you listen to the audio and see if there's an, see if you cut
an EVP.
That's kind of the most, that's like the base level.
I think the base level is walking in a haunted house and you hear in a disembodied voice
go "BOOM!"
Like that is, that is the caveman's version of the EVP.
And then you have an electronic recording device, which does it.
And then they have things like spirit boxes.
Those have come about maybe in the past five years.
I could be a little bit older.
They've definitely blown up in popularity in the last five years.
And that's where you have basically a radio, a broken radio is what it is, where it spins
through the dial super quickly and every so often over going through the AM/FM band, you'll
pick out individual words.
I am here behind you.
Boo!
And then you turn around and look because large, large maybe standing there.
That again, like all EVP, the spirit box, I've never used the spirit box myself.
EVPs to me are the most reliable because when you ask a question like, "Are you here?"
You either get silence or background noise or something.
And then once you have something now, you can start debate over what does it say.
But whether or not, if I say, "Is anyone in here?"
And there's a disembodied voice that says, "My name is Margaret.
I died here."
Or a disembodied voice said, "Waffles, tomorrow!"
It's still a disembodied voice.
I mean, the ghost may be an idiot, right?
The ghost may be a moron, but it's still a disembodied voice.
That's what I like about EVPs.
You could go, "I don't think it said that.
I think it said this one more quivley.
The point is, is that it's saying something."
There's a voice from the ether saying something.
It may not be answering my question, but it should not exist.
It's saying something, right?
The haunted boxes are a little more prone to, I'm not completely dismissing them.
I think I did in earlier episodes, I think.
But I looked into them a little bit more.
I do think though they're more prone to, it's a random thing.
And so if it clicks to 10 different stations, you might be able to hear, "Buy now!"
And you happen to be standing outside of a hot dog cart in New York City.
And you're like, "I must get a hot dog."
The ghost told me to, but then it picked up all this other stuff.
Again, I've never used one.
I've looked into them, I've done some research on them.
I'm less dismissive of them than I used to be, but...
And maybe someday I'll be less dismissive of optimal frequency.
Probably not.
Because when you look at other videos, and you know what, here's the thing.
Who cares what I think, right?
Who cares what I think?
I watched two videos by this dude.
What is my opinion matter, right?
Like, honestly, this is my thing.
He looks like he's having the time of his life.
He looks like he's having a ton of fun.
There's a lot of people who enjoy watching his videos.
I think it's goofy, but who cares, right?
I'm not the end-all be-all of paranormal research.
Who cares what I think?
They honestly grant looks like he's having fun.
Is there a better way to spend the afternoon, right?
When you're into this stuff, I go to the bagel shop and just read spooky stories for hours
on end and type up notes.
That's how I spend my Saturdays.
A lot of people would think that was a waste of time.
Who cares what people think, right?
I'm saying the same thing to you.
Grant looks like he's having the time of his life.
He does look a little perturbed every show often.
He seems to lose his patience with Gary in the basement.
But you know what I mean?
How awesome is it to be able to not only spend a day recording the water coming out of your
faucet and having...
I don't think he's talking to paranormal.
I do think it's all...
He's just putting together patterns.
But he's having time of his life and he's putting out content and people are enjoying
it.
It's so funny because sometimes I'll lay into people who I think are grifting and I think
are spreading harmful messages to people's health.
That's kind of the difference because sometimes I've gone really hard.
I did a whole week about Vampire Kevin.
I'm like into this anonymous dude on the internet.
And yeah, I just thought like...
He was running...
Well, legally I can't say he was running a grift.
But let's put him in the category of people that I go.
This is dangerous.
These guys just having fun.
I don't believe it's ghosts personally.
But his...
And this is one of the reasons why.
His other videos, he's talking to the ghost of Kiev, I guess, or he's just talking to
ghosts hanging out by his water fountain.
But he's done videos where he's talked to specific people.
He's talked to Freddie Mercury, dude from Queen, right?
Anthony Bourdain.
And you know, at one point I was like, "Oh dude, I should listen to that one.
We actually did an episode about Anthony Bourdain."
But then I thought, "He's actually there, Jason.
It's the dude's water flossing."
It's not like you're going to go there and learn anything great about Anthony Bourdain.
So I was like, "Oh yeah."
So he did...
He's done a bunch of them.
He's done a ton of these videos.
But he's done ones on...
These are the most notable for me.
Freddie Mercury, Anthony Bourdain, Stephen Hawking, right?
That's pretty recent.
And I wonder if it had the electronic voice, right?
Was the ghost like...
Like when Stephen Hawking died, would his ghost sound like a robot?
Probably not, but then you wouldn't recognize his voice.
And we're thinking about whether or not Stephen Hawking...
I guess ghosts don't care whether or not you recognize their voice, right?
It's a ghost.
Because then he would be like in the little motorized wheelchair.
And I don't think that's possible.
He's probably walking around as a ghost.
But Freddie Mercury, Anthony Bourdain, Stephen Hawking...
These are all very fascinating people.
The bog...
I was like, "Dude, this would be..."
Anyway, the Boggy Creek Monster.
Not the soggy bottom boys.
That would be pretty interesting too.
Except they're not real.
The Boggy Creek Monster, which who knows if that guy's real.
I'm like, "What is this dude's real?"
Boggy Creek Monster is basically a swamp bigfoot.
And I saw that one and I was like, "What?"
That would be the only...
I would interview that guy every single week.
Wouldn't you love to know the weekly adventures of a cryptid?
He's like, "Almost got caught today."
You wouldn't believe it.
My buddy Stephen Hawking showed him in his ghost wheelchair and saved me once again.
Thank you, robot ghost.
I remember once I saw...
I don't remember where I saw this online.
I think it was just a passing comment.
But someone said, "I never understand.
You watch shows like Ghost Hunters.
They come out to a house.
They set up their cameras for the night.
The next morning they're like, "This is a confirmed haunting.
Listen to all these EVPs we caught and these moving shadows."
And then the next week they're at a different house.
You go, "Stay in the same house.
Stay in the same house.
Collect as much data as you can at that one house.
If this is a confirmed haunting, you should put your gear there for like a month."
I was like, "I never thought about that."
That's super interesting.
You made contact with a cryptid, with the Boggy Creek Monster.
That would just be your YouTube channel.
Every week you'd have a new video of you talking to this monster.
He's just talking like Cookie Monster.
He's like, "Yum, yum, yum.
Meet another camper."
If you could make contact with a cryptid, that is all.
I would talk to the Boggy Creek Monster all the time.
Freddie Mercury, he's not going nowhere, right?
He's a ghost, right?
They're stuck there forever.
You can save him for another YouTube channel.
But yeah, if you could talk to a cryptid, talk to a cryptid.
But anyways, you can check out Optimal Frequency.
I had a real...
It actually started making me sick to my stomach.
I don't know what it was about the ghost.
The ghosts were flying in my stomach every time I played them.
I don't know if it was the white noise or whatever.
I watched two videos of them, but yeah, it just kind of made me sick to my stomach.
But with that recommendation, it'll make you notches as you listen to it.
They look like they're having fun.
It doesn't look like they're trying to rip anyone off financially or mentally.
They're not running any sort of weirdo cult.
Like so many other people we see in the space.
So good on you, Grant.
Good on you for being a step above most people in this sphere.
Again, I don't think you're talking to ghosts, but it's fun.
I'm not gonna knock that.
Cindy, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the world famous carbonicopter.
We're leaving behind this dude's kitchen.
It's still in shambles from the dirgeable crash.
Let's fire up the rotors on this copter.
Knocking everything from side to side.
It created a few more ghosts, unfortunately.
Cindy, take us out of this dude's house.
We're headed all the way out to a suburban neighborhood.
Somewhere in America.
This is one of those stories that I kind of stumbled across.
I found this post.
It was titled Being Contacted by an Entity.
I was like, oh, okay, cool.
I do love me some entity contact.
It's one of my top five contacts.
I'm looking into it and generally what I do when I come across this stuff, I read the
post and I'm like, okay, that's weird.
That's good enough to be covered on Dead Rabbit Radio, I say.
Because I stuff another jalapeno cheddar bagel into my mouth.
And then I'll go back and I'll look at people's posting history if that's available.
Sometimes stuff's posted anonymously on the X board.
And there are other forms and stuff that have more availability.
You can check this stuff out.
And that's when I really started digging through this person's past.
Now we're going to call this person.
This is, I got to be real careful about this one, honestly.
Like part of me wanted to contact this person and clear some stuff up, but this is a weird
one.
We're going to call this, it is a whole shot in the dark.
If it's your real name, I'm not connected to the entity.
We're going to call this person Wendy.
Wendy.
And let's go through a couple of the posts.
I want to take you on this journey because I read the entity post first being contacted
by an entity and then I went and found all this stuff.
On March 28th, 2022, Wendy posted on a forum asking the question, healthy at every size.
And this person, Wendy, I don't think we ever get it in exact age, but we do get a whole
host of health problems that Wendy is suffering.
And we, this first really comes to the forefront on this March 28 post.
Wendy is going, you know, I'm talking about giving up, trying to lose weight.
Like I've been trying to lose weight for so long and I've actually gained 30 pounds while
I've been trying to lose.
I mean, coming back to my calories and all that stuff and I'm actually gaining weight.
Now either she's not actually cutting her calories or she has such a serious medical condition
like water bloat, right?
Like she can't actually lose weight.
You have to go to the doctor.
She goes, maybe I read this online that I can be healthy at any size and that all of
the health conditions that kill fat people are due to medical discrimination.
Like you don't actually die of a heart attack from being overweight.
You die of a heart attack because you go to the doctor and they say, oh, for us to treat
your heart, you're going to have to lose weight.
And so you die of a heart attack.
Now if they had just treated your heart in the first place and hadn't discriminated against
you because you were overweight, then fat fatalities would go down.
And what's interesting is when I go to the doctor, that's something that always comes
up no matter what medical condition I'm in.
People say, you know, you've gained a lot of weight.
I'm actually a lot lower now than I used to be.
But I have never felt discriminated against personally, right?
I knew that my weight, I got up to 350 pounds.
I'm nowhere near that now.
But that would be issue, right?
Bad knees, your heart issues, breathing issues, stuff like that sleep apnea, that's due to
your weight.
And there's been this push recently, sure beauty at every size, right?
But health is a more complicated issue, right?
Health at every size is far, far more complicated.
And speaking from experience, I don't necessarily think that that's accurate.
But she posts that she says I'm having a hard time losing weight and maybe being larger is
healthier than being skinny or of a normal weight is her exact quote.
Being larger is healthier than being skinny or normal weight.
And that's what she had been told.
That was on March 28, 2022.
On April 7, she posts again and she says in this post completely unable to lose weight.
At this point, she gives us some more details.
She is five foot two and 530 pounds.
So that's quite heavy.
It's very, very, very heavy.
She goes on eating 1500 calories a day.
I cannot lose weight and I don't know what's going on.
And I'm going so in this might see you're like Jason, what does any of this have to
do with an entity?
Is the entity like a weight trainers, the entity like a personal instructor, personal
fitness guy who's going to help around.
The reason why I'm laying all of this out because we get when we talk about someone
who's contacting entities.
It's very, very interesting.
We cover a lot of this stuff where people are hearing voices in their head and we get
a very clear picture of this person's not just mental health, but physical health.
And that is something that is constantly missing from a lot of these stories.
We covered a story last week where the woman started hearing voices.
She also said she was overweight.
Now that I think about it, she had lost 50 pounds in her story.
I'm going to have to look into that.
That's really interesting.
I also saw a meme recently and it said that American paranormal hosts are all overweight.
I want something to go like anyone who's like puts out paranormal content is overweight.
So that's weird.
But again, it's America.
We have this.
So that's kind of why I'm dialing into this.
And this does play a part.
I'm not just here to be like, "Ah, look at how heavy she is."
Because that's not the point, but we have a picture of this woman's health.
She's five foot two.
She's 530 pounds.
Going through her post, it turns out she doesn't eat 1,500 calories a day.
If you ate 1,500 calories a day to 530 pounds, you are guaranteed to lose weight unless you
have a serious medical condition.
You're retaining water so much that you're basically a water balloon and you would have
to go to hospital and get that taken care of.
530 pounds eating 1,500 calories a day.
It turns out that's not true.
And I think we would have all known that.
She eats 6,000 calories a day by her own estimate and she goes and that is her guessing the calories
of restaurant food.
So she's eating probably 5,000 calories a day of stuff she can read.
Like actually look at the nutritional value of.
April 13th.
So what is that?
Six days later after that, completely unable to lose weight, she posts, "I will die soon."
From April 7th to April 13th, she's gained 10 pounds.
She says doctors are telling her that at any moment her heart can stop.
Her health is so poor, she can die at any time.
She makes an interesting, she's kind of going through her health issues.
She also adds to the comment, "No money can't stop eating."
And it made me think someone must be enabling her because one of the things you need to
eat is money and especially if you're ordering restaurant foods, very expensive.
So I'm wondering if someone's enabling her, right?
Anyways, she's up to 540 pounds.
She's posting on all of these other subs and forums to lose weight, looking for advice.
She mentions that she's bedridden and she's mentioning that she might be evicted.
She has someone who's taking care of her, you wouldn't need someone to take care of you
in the state where your heart can literally stop at any moment.
And that person is going back to college, so she doesn't know, Wendy doesn't know how
things are going to work out.
That was April 13th, April 22nd, being contacted by an entity.
She says this all started three years ago.
This entity situation started three years ago, but it's definitely come to a head.
She said she started seeing a three-digit number appear randomly around her.
Now not like a hallucination, but look at your clock, it's a three-digit number.
You're checking your stock, three-digit number on the ticker tape.
Apparently your Scrooge McDuck and a ticker tape is coming out all the time.
She said, "I'm not going to tell you what the number is.
I'm not going to tell you what the number is for reasons that will become obvious."
But I keep seeing this number appear.
Another thing that's going on over the past three years is I begin to feel disconnected
from reality.
The world begins to seem more and more like just a dream.
They're so vivid it's almost like I can't tell when I'm asleep and when I'm awake.
And then the voices appear.
The entity comes into her life.
And this is always so interesting.
She's laid out a very personal health journey online and yet when people get cagey about
certain details, which you perfectly whine, right?
You don't have to tell everyone everything.
But I find it interesting when you talk about very, very detailed things about your weight,
how many calories you're taking today, and then you leave other stuff really vague.
It makes you think the worst, right?
Not of her, but of what could be going on.
She says the entity kept telling her to do something over and over and over again, but
yet she refused to do it.
But she won't, she doesn't reveal what that thing is.
That's troubling, right?
Because you think, you know, the worst, hurting herself or hurting other people.
She says during this time she begins to see visions of the dead when she looks into mirrors.
She sees ghosts standing behind her.
She's simply trying to check out her own reflection.
She believes she's going crazy, which I think anyone would have.
Anyone of those things, right?
The voices, depersonalization, seeing the specters of the damned behind you.
Any of those three would make you feel like you were going crazy.
She's having all of them.
She then says she got COVID twice.
She suffered from, this is very recent.
This is like in the last year, got COVID twice, suffered with strep throat, anaphylaxis,
which I think is a reaction to medicine, anaphylactic shock at least, or some sort of allergic
reaction.
Cellulitis, the flu, that's a bit of a downgrade there, right?
You're like, oh, you won't believe it.
I almost died of an anaphylactic shock.
And I had the flu.
You're like, dude, dude, you need to learn how to actually organize stuff from least
scary to most scary.
But she does end it on a pretty scary one.
I think called mastitis, which is inflamed breast tissues.
I had to look that up.
Didn't look at photos.
Please don't send me any.
I was like, what's mastitis?
And I found out what it is.
She said she went to the urgent care 10 times.
Now here's the thing.
When I'm reading this, this is where you start to think, hypochondriac.
Remember, I'm reading this post first.
I have no idea about her health history.
I'm reading this post first.
And I was like, wow, either this person's the unluckiest person.
She got the flu.
Oh, no.
I'm so worried about her.
Either she's very unlucky health wise, or she's a hypochondriac.
I had no idea that she was 530 pounds or 540 pounds at this point, which I would go, okay,
yeah, that totally makes sense.
That totally makes sense that you would have a whole host of health concerns.
But she's going to urgent care over and over and over and over again to get taken care of.
And then at the very end of this whole thing, she gets a severe blood infection with no cause.
The doctors at the urgent care facility, if you don't know what that is, if I don't know
if these are all over the world or even all over the United States, it's basically in
between your regular doctor that you can make an appointment to see and the emergency room.
It's drop-in clinics.
I've been to them hundreds of times throughout my life.
Show up.
I got some weird malady.
I've stepped on something.
I've got cut open.
I go to the urgent cares all the time.
But yeah, so you just show up and you get treated right there.
She gets a severe blood infection.
They can't tell what it is.
They tell her to go to the emergency room and she says, "I don't have any money."
So she went home.
So don't do that, right?
Most emergency, if you don't own a home, if you don't own any assets, just go to the emergency
room.
They'll send you a bill and they'll work with you.
They'll work with you.
Usually, I know the Catholic ones do.
I can't speak for all of them.
I can't speak for a greedy Memorial Hospital United or whatever.
But yeah, if you're going to die and you don't own any assets, I would recommend going to
the ER, at least to do that.
You own a house, then that's a little more tricky.
But she goes home and her fever rises to 106.
And at this point, she's basically just laying on the floor.
She's cooking to death.
Her brain is boiling.
And that is when she looks up at the television set and appearing on big block letters right
on the television set.
Are the words, "Listen and you will live."
So Wendy in this horrible fever with this horrible blood infection, all these other horrible
health problems, the flu, she gets to her feet.
She uses all of her strength to get to her feet and she's begging.
I'll do anything it takes.
Just don't, I just don't want to suffer anymore.
She collapses.
She blacks out.
A couple hours later, she wakes up.
Totally fine.
Blood infection as far as she can tell is gone.
I don't know how she would diagnose that.
She's cutting open her finger.
She's like, "That looks like good blood."
That's not infected at all.
She said her blood infection is gone.
She feels great.
She says she hasn't even been sick since.
And she started to think, "Maybe I'm not crazy."
Maybe I was never crazy.
And then she says, "This is one of her quotes.
Since that moment, this entity tells me everything."
She says, "By listening to the entity, it is told her about her mission in life."
See there are people out there that she needs to help.
And the entity will tell her what she needs to do.
Word for word, the entity will tell her what she needs to buy and what she needs to learn
to help these people.
And then she starts getting, she says she starts getting messages from burner accounts
on Reddit with nonsense phrases and the three digit number.
One of these makes references and in-jokes about stuff she's had dreams about, things
she's never mentioned to anyone.
This account will kind of reference stuff.
That firefighter's hat sure was big, wasn't it ma'am?
I don't know if the post had an accent.
It said, "Hey seed in mouth."
She's like, "Ah, the accent."
But she said that one only pops up on Reddit when she doesn't know what to do next.
She says she has refined her ability to contact the entity.
Instead of it just putting voices in her head, she has a decatero cards and she hasn't used
them as normal tarot cards but she lays them out and it makes a pattern and it will tell
her what the entity is trying to express.
She says the voices of the entity no longer mentally torment her.
In fact, it seems playful and friendly when it wants to be.
April 22nd she posted this, it seems fairly uplifting, right?
These uplifting voices in your head can be saving her life, giving her direction.
And I started looking through the posts around this time period and I did see people respond
like she had posted something about weight loss and someone would leave a very cryptic
code.
Like that's what the dollhouse said.
And then she would respond, "Why are you here?
Why are you here?"
So, that's why I didn't want to write anything or email her because I was like, "Someone
obviously is messing with her and I don't know how far back she's been posting."
I mean, I guess I'm going to look at it but Steve is eating bagels.
You, I can, someone or some people are messing with her or it's possible that she's doing
it herself or not that she's trying to fake it which is obviously always possible but
she could be so disassociated that she has multiple accounts herself.
I think someone's messing with her, a couple of people are messing with her.
I think she's probably posting somewhere that she sees these numbers and da da da da da
and people are posting them and which is cruel really at that point.
Like this person seems to have, seems to have some sort, definitely a whole host of health
problems and seems to be on a very, very serious mental health journey.
So I mean like cracking jokes that make her think that she's being contacted or being
harassed by agents against this entity or whatever she thinks this thing is.
That's why she doesn't want to reveal the three digit number so that way she can verify
when people actually do use the three digit number that they're correct.
And you could go, "Jay, seeing as a paranormal researcher, how do you say that this is insane
versus other people who communicate with entities?
You yourself, you've had interactions with demons and angels and shadow men and all this
stuff."
And you know what's interesting is each time that happens I think I'm going crazy.
Like every single time that has happened, and it's not happened a bunch, but I go, "Oh
my god, I've lost my mind.
I've totally lost my mind."
And I'm not, the only person who does that, there's tons of people who've had communications.
Grant, Grant has them coming right out of their faucet.
It makes her, why do you lean towards mental health on her story versus the other story?
It's a feeling, I can't even really tell you.
Like I can't say this is specifically why.
Who knows, right?
It's not that, it's not necessarily health problems, it's just sometimes you have a
hunch.
But here's the frightening thing about this one.
I think she may be contacting an entity.
It may be real.
It's possible that her brain got cooked by a 106 degree fever.
That will do it.
That's enough for an adult to cause some at a very least short term brain damage.
And someone who was already struggling with mental health stuff, remember the story started
three years ago, the fever was fairly recent.
She might have connected with something.
And that's what scares me.
I would much rather have people, I had to choose, right?
I'm not like, woo!
If I had to choose, I would much rather a lot of these stories be mental health because
mental health can be treated with counseling, or with medication, or with observation and
things like that.
The paranormal stuff is much harder to take care of.
Far, far more difficult to deal with.
It's not only are you really trying to handle it from a mental health perspective, and this
is a spiritual issue.
You don't know what the power level is of this entity.
Is it an imp?
Right?
Is it just a little demonic creature that's crawled out of the depths of somewhere?
Dark?
Old?
That's attached itself?
Is it a solar plexus clown glider?
Is it a demon?
Is it a cosmic horror?
These are all totally different things that require totally different methods.
Now you could say exorcism would probably get rid of all of them, right?
A good old fashioned religious exorcism, but you don't know, right?
We covered that story about that guy who they did like a 10 hour exorcism on and then they
had to take a break and they said, "Well, we got all of the demons out of them except
for two.
Wrath and murder, but I'm sure he's fine going home."
That's one of my favorite episodes of Dead Rapper Radio.
I'll put that in the show notes.
That really is one of my favorite stories I've ever covered on this show, which says
something right, which says something that's totally terrifying.
Gave me nightmares.
I had nightmares after recording that episode.
But yeah, what is this?
I would much rather Wendy have this mental health.
I would much rather, oh first off, I would much rather her not have any of these issues,
right?
And not have a story to tell on Friday.
If I had to be 100%, I'd much rather do a four episode a week podcast and not have
a story like this of this poor woman suffering through this.
But if I had to choose, again, I would choose that it would be a mental health struggle
versus a spiritual battle.
But it's telling her what to do and it's laying out these plans and I found this one
odd post someone had left.
I'll try to find it again.
I didn't, I don't remember the exact page.
I'll see if I can find it again.
But she was talking about something and one of these random people jumped in and left
a code and she said, please, please, I can't wait another year.
Tell me, tell me the plan.
I'll do it.
So she's like begging random people online that she thinks might be part of this grand
conspiracy involving this entity.
So weird and sad.
And then the very last thing that I've seen her post was the day afterwards.
It was April 23rd, 2022.
The post itself was removed, but the title is still there.
Quote, does anyone want to go to the void with me?
What is this?
It's just such a bizarre journey.
As far as the recording of this, she's still posting on stuff, but it's weirdo stuff.
She's not like, I don't want to get my scientific calculator to work.
The batteries, I need to charge the batteries.
It's more weird stuff.
She's glomming on stuff and people are posting all these series of numbers and she's like,
oh no, help me on my journal.
It's like, dude.
But mental health issues, most likely, right?
I'm not going to say probably.
I've pretty much gone through pretty good evidence.
Some mental health struggles here.
But what I want to end this note on, what I want to end this very depressing Friday episode
on, I thought about this while I was reading the story, because last week we talked about
a young woman who was also hearing voices from this entity.
And this is something we cover a lot on this show.
We've done, I'll try to put a couple other episodes in the show and it's, I find all
of this stuff very fascinating.
But I started to, let's put on our conspiracy caps and wrap the episode up like this.
Very, very short wrap up.
It's kind of just an open-ended question.
We have all of these people hearing these voices all over the world.
What if they're all coming from the same source?
What if there is something dark and ancient and powerful talking to millions of people
with mental health struggles all over the world?
Millions of different voices, but one voice.
You may hear it as a woman.
He may hear it as his aunt.
She may hear it as just an anonymous dude's voice yelling in her ear while she's trying
to sleep.
Words of encouragement, words of hate, statements that drive you so mad you find yourself walking
down the street.
You've lost your job.
You've lost your home.
You've lost your family.
You've turned to self-medicating yourself with the strongest street drugs available,
the voices are still there, but they're all coming from the same source.
And the source knows what it needs to do to push you.
This person needs a word of encouragement to bring them into my fold.
This person needs to think they're worthless to break them down to make them my servant.
Millions of different voices screaming millions of different phrases in the minds of millions
of different people spread across this planet.
Millions of different voices, but one voice.
Is there a terrifying puppet master living worlds and realities far beyond our own, slipping
its tendrils into the minds of the most vulnerable people on the planet?
Somewhere in the darkness, somewhere in the void, sits a monster with a million mouths.
DeadRabber80 with gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Tiktok is at DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm so glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend guys and I will see you soon.
Bye bye.
(upbeat music)