Missing Persons Week continues with a terrifying incident that happened this month.
And then we try to outrun a carnivorous cloud that strips the meat from bones.
Doesn't matter if you're alive or dead, it will eat you if it exists.
And then pick a number between 1 and 8 because we're going to the Gladiator arenas today
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Missing Persons Week continues and I'm actually pulling an audible because I actually found
out a terrifying story that just happened.
Absolutely chilly.
This has been pretty big news but they just solved the crime.
Over the past couple days I've seen all over the news there's this young attractive woman
named Samantha Josephson from Columbia, South Carolina.
She was popping up in the headlines for a while, gone completely insane.
And this all happened within probably about like two or three days.
But it was new.
I was seeing her face pop up.
But it was just confirmed what happened.
So let me take you back here to the beginning.
The year is 2019, the month, late March, early April.
This happened super recently.
Samantha is out with her friends partying in club.
College student.
She's getting ready to take her finals or do whatever you do in college around this time.
But she's also having fun with her friends and at some point in the night she's separated
from her friends like "Now I'm going to go home."
It's 2am and she decides to call an Uber.
I've used Uber before and it's really dicey.
I've used Uber when I was in Sacramento for my brother's wedding and I was like "I don't
know these dudes man.
I don't like getting in other people's cars."
I'm always cautious about getting in cars with strangers.
I'm actually kind of cautious in getting in cars with people I know too.
But she calls for an Uber.
By 1.30pm the next day she's reported missing.
And a couple hours after that her body is found in the woods by some hunters.
So very very quick wrap up to this.
The first article was she's missing.
Second article, the second day I think they were still talking about she was missing and
then later that day they mentioned that she had passed away because they were waiting to
notify the family.
But here's what happened.
This is what they, because they've arrested the guy who was responsible for it.
The way they found him was this.
She called for an Uber and the Uber, it will tell you the description of the car that's
going to pick you up.
Generally the license plate is well I believe.
But it's late at night you may not necessarily be thinking.
That if you ordered a car and it was going to be a black Chevy Impala pulling up to
your block.
And you happen to see a black Chevy Impala on that block.
She just got in it.
Car drove away.
The Uber driver comes up a little bit later, waits there, no one gets in the car.
Puts it in saying hey someone called me but no one ever came and picked it up.
So when the girl goes missing the cops then begin searching for black Chevy Impalas and
they find one, they pull him over, rest the guy.
He had in the car, he actually had a passenger in the car at that time but she's been totally
cooperative with the police.
She wasn't there that night.
But he had like bleach and a little bit of blood and some germicidal wipes and all that
stuff.
She died because she got in the wrong car.
That is absolutely bizarre.
I can imagine her walking up to a car and being like oh hey, she gets in and the guy's
like whoa, what are you doing?
And she'd be like oh I'm sorry, I thought this was my Uber.
No, no, no, I was just parked here.
I live here.
Oh, oh sorry, sorry.
That would happen 99% of the time.
Maybe 0.5% of the time she'd walk up to the car and it would be someone in there doing
something nefarious and being like yo bitch, what are you doing?
Get out of my car.
Oh, I'm so sorry man.
Dude.
She gets out, she finds her Uber.
In an infinitesimal amount of the time she would get into a car that happened to have
a murderer in it.
Bad luck.
And you could say well she should have done this, she should have checked the app.
Who would have thought that if you happen to get in a car on accident that looks like
a car, I don't blame on her at all.
I think it would be very easy late at night to see a similar car and at least walk up to
it.
It would be a drug deal going on and then you get shot.
That's something different.
You walk in and you see a criminal activity, they chase you down.
She got in the car and he just murdered her.
What are the chances of that really?
For her, unfortunately it was 100%.
I'll be shocked, shocked if this is the only person he's ever murdered.
Shocked.
Because if I was driving down the road and a super hot woman got in the back of my car,
the first thing that pops in my head isn't going to be oh I'm going to murder her.
She's in my car.
I mean might as well, right?
He had to have done this before.
Had to have done this before.
Crazy, spooky.
I read that and I was like that's chilling.
That is an accident and you get murdered.
Sometimes people have accidents, they fall off of bridges, they get hit by trains, paint
bucket comes, hits them on the head because they're trying to accidentally break into
this kid's house.
All sorts of stuff.
But to accidentally actually get murdered by a murderer, that honestly might be the
first.
People walk into scenes where there's drug deals and get shot, that's pretty accidental
too.
But I can't think of another time where a person just happened to get in a vehicle and
drive away on accident with a murder.
Actually I guess that's pretty much every hitchhiker story but you know what I mean,
it's still really, really weird.
Just trying to get home from a party.
Weird man.
Okay but let's go ahead and move on to something a little lighthearted.
Oh wait, no.
This isn't lighthearted.
Actually it might be lighthearted because it might be a, it kind of looks like cotton
candy.
So we are going to Sunny Sunny Florida.
Wasn't we here recently?
Oh we went here for that dude who got murdered and then yeah, that was a couple episodes
ago, a guy got murdered by his buddy and now retroactive spoiler alert.
But now we're going back to Florida.
We are going to go hunting ourselves, not hunting literally ourselves, which actually
be the most dangerous game, but we're going to go hunting as well along the Tomaca River,
which is west of Dayton.
We go, we're in Florida, we're in the Tomaca River.
We're walking by it with our rifles.
Walking through the woods.
Dogs all hehehehehe.
We go, we get the ducks that we just killed and then we notice something.
It's early in the morning, it's a little cold outside.
We're standing there in our full hunting gear and we start to see a pink mist kind of roll
through the forest.
Looks almost like a cotton candy color.
Looks pleasing to the eye, but we start to notice that the forest around us is getting
very very quiet, like all the animals are leaving.
We kind of start to back up from this cloud.
It's rolling about from the ground to your waist coming towards us.
You see a little bunny rabbit with the little broken paw.
It can't run away like the other ones.
It's like meh meh meh meh meh.
I don't know what sounds rabbits make.
I am one, so that's kind of weird, but anyways, and we see the cloud roll over and we hear
a "Ugh!"
And before the mist completely covers the rabbit, we begin to see its flesh dissolve.
So we book it.
We run all the way back to the carbonar copter, jump inside, take off.
Dude, you left the dog, not my fault.
I would've rescued him, you left him.
Hopefully, he'll make it.
But we can't land now, the mist is everywhere.
So what is this mist?
It's known locally as the Carnivorous Pink Cloud or the Cannibal Cloud.
It was sighted as far back as 1605 when Spanish to Explorish ran the area.
But most of the sightings, the recent sightings, have been between 1955 and 1966.
Some people have said it's possible that it's some sort of just mist that is colored by
the morning sun and has no carnivorous properties at all.
Some people say that it's nothing supernatural, but it's pollution that's rolling in and
rolls in every once in a while and it does burn your skin if not eat it off.
And the reason why these legends have popped up is two things.
One, people will find bones in the forest, sometimes human bones, and there have been
reports of multiple people missing in this forest.
The third explanation is not chemical or that it's just regular mist that's beautiful.
Apparently in that area there was natives, they weren't Native Americans, they were
just natives in the area.
There was a golden cup and they had access to basically a sacred fountain.
But they weren't supposed to use either of them.
If you use the golden cup to just like drink spring water out of, that was bad.
And if you drink out of the sacred pool of water, that was bad.
There was a guy named Chief Tomkey who did both.
He grabbed the golden cup, stuck it in the water and drank it.
And the other tribes declared war against his tribe.
There was massive battle in the area.
And his entire tribe was slaughtered.
Chief Tomkey was the only man left.
He had this magical healing liquid in him.
At that point though, a beautiful young maiden from one of the rival tribes named Olita shot
him with an arrow, killed him, and then she ran to get the cup for herself almost like
Gollum for the ring and then another tribe member killed her to keep her from getting
the power as well.
So some believe that this rolling mist is Chief Tomkey.
I think it's even possible that the healing powers from the cup and the water made it
so Chief Tomkey isn't dead, but he still needs to feed.
He turns into this pink mist and he still, his spirit is still almost trapped in a hell
where he's not alive, he's not dead, he's immortal.
Now he's just this cloud that creeps through the forest of Florida, eating everything in
its path.
Now everything I just told you is an urban legend.
None of it is verifiable at all.
It's a really, really interesting story, but there's absolutely no proof behind it whatsoever.
And I know you're thinking, "Jason, great, you just told me this cool story and now you
- but you know, like you gotta be realistic about this stuff."
They say that there's several missing people.
I've read quite a few articles on this.
They talk about missing people in the area due to the fog, but there's no names.
There's no dates.
There's nothing I can verify where they say, "This person went missing on April 12th,"
or even, "This person went missing in, you know, 1957."
There's nothing I can verify.
So it's just reports of missing people in the area.
Reports of bones being found in the woods is suspicious of their human bones.
However, bones are a pretty natural phenomenon, i.e., you rot.
You die, your body rots.
If there were Native American battlegrounds here, there would definitely be bones or fragments
of bones in the dirt and things like that.
Multiple people quoted the same thing about the first sighting was in 1605.
There's none of them attribute that fact to any other sight.
They're basically all referencing each other.
And then most of the accounts come from people who live in the area saying, "When I grew
up, I heard about the carnivorous cloud.
I heard about somebody."
You know, so very urban legend.
So I don't think it's true at all.
The actual theory that the mist itself is part of the healing properties of the cup,
I made that part up.
I made that part up because here's my thing.
Let's assume it's true for a second.
And I didn't make that part up to trick you.
I was just trying to weave it all in.
So here's my thing.
When I read it, I said, "Whoa, this is really interesting."
And every article I read repeated almost verbatim the same claim.
So I go, "Okay, there's really nothing behind this."
I was really looking for a name of a person who went missing.
All we have is the first sighting, an 11-year time period, and then stories that people
were told when they were kids.
But then I put back on my imagination cap.
I go, "It would be interesting if you had the power of immortality."
Okay, so in the animatrix, and I've talked about this before, in the movie The Second
Renaissance, there's this thing where when the humans built the robots to begin with,
they made them look like humans, which would make sense because you'd want them to be able
to move about in human spaces.
But once the AI, once the matrix basically was starting to be constructed and the AI
completely separated itself from humanity, it realized that human forms were actually
not the most efficient.
The insect form was.
So that's why all the robots you see in the matrix are like those squid things.
And it's really great because in that movie, you see the first great battle between man
and machine and its men versus humanoid machines and the men win.
But then the AI creates these insectoid machines that are far more efficient than the human
body with multiple limbs and different backup systems and stuff.
So if the head gets blown off, it has all these other redundant systems, and they just
swash on humanity.
If you had the power to be immortal, if you drank something mystical that made you immortal,
I don't think, again, we're in a speculative place here, but...
A human form isn't the best form to be immortal in.
It really isn't.
Like as much as I love being a human, if you were immortal, you'd be much better off being
something else.
Because unless you were unbreakable, like swords would break off you and stuff like that, this
guy obviously got, again, assuming this is real, got an arrow in his chest, the human
form is inefficient.
But mist or rain or water or smoke or anything like that, anything that has a physical body
is still limited to the physical realm.
If you became immortal, it would make sense if you had a choice, I guess, but it would
make sense for you to be cursed or gifted with a non-caporial form or incorporeal form.
So I like, I think my theory, because I think the whole thing is made up anyways, my theory
is that yes, he did drink from the cup, he did drink from the sacred water, he was killed,
but because he couldn't be killed only his physical body was destroyed, he did become
this carnivorous mist that floats through the forest and continues to devour.
Now, of course, the question of that is why was it only really seen between 1955 and 1966?
Well, I have two answers for that.
One, it may have moved on from that area, the pink mist now may be in other areas, other
states where people don't know to run from it, taking down hikers and campers and little
animals running through the woods.
Or going with my theory as well, it simply evolved to a less obvious form.
It still feeds, it's still lust for blood, now you just can't see it coming.
Right now though, we are going to talk about Gladiator Theater.
So not just sword and sandals, not just buff dudes with swords chopping each other up, crowd
going crazy, Gladiator Theater, which is different.
It was where they would basically put on productions in the arena.
You think, oh that's awesome, Romeo and Juliet?
Well kind of, except they both die horrible deaths, like they did in the original play.
But this one is more like live action saw movies.
So go ahead and pick a number between 1 and 8.
So it is a hot summer day in Rome.
The sun's beating down on you, you're dripping sweat, your pecs are just like, you got full
abs.
If you're a chick, pecs, you still got pecs, you're just boobs now, and then you got full
abs, you're just super fit.
But the sweating though isn't from the heat, it's because you're about to be led into the
Gladiator Arena.
All of these deaths were basically set up to be like plays.
Back in about 30 BC, a man is being led into the Gladiator Arena, and in the arena he sees
a giant wooden structure in the shape of Mount Etna.
Now if you don't know, Mount Etna is a volcano, and he's led up to the top of the wooden structure,
the crowd's going wild.
So you're kinda eager, you're like, yeah dude this is kinda cool.
This is the most famous I've ever been.
You get led up to the top of Mount Etna.
And at that point, the Emperor of Rome goes, if you picked number 4, this is you.
You're like, okay great, there's no volcano around here, obviously Hot Lava's not gonna
shoot out of this mountain.
The mountain basically does erupt, it just breaks apart.
But instead of Hot Lava shooting out, these are all real by the way.
You, if you pick number 4, you fall into the volcano, but instead of Hot Lava, it's just
a bunch of lions.
And they just rip you to pieces.
Just eat your legs off, totally chew you up.
So not only do you have a pretty bad bruise from falling about 20-30 feet, you fall on
hungry animals.
Which would be the worst combination.
Now there is Hot Lava, it's all your blood pouring out of the mountain.
First century AD.
You guys remember Hercules?
Hercules was a pretty cool guy.
He did all those things.
He was like fighting hydras and like diverting water and all that stuff.
And you notice as you're being led into the arena, you are dressed like Hercules.
And you're like, oh great, what are they gonna do?
Have me do a bunch of weightlifting?
Did they actually find like seven snakes in time together and I'm gonna chop their heads
off?
What's going on?
So you get led into the arena and it seems pretty normal, but there you see some wood
in the middle of it and you're like, oh that's kind of weird, what am I gonna do?
Like bench press this wood?
I can do that.
And then as you're getting closer to the wood, you remember a little story about Hercules.
Hercules was a demigod.
He was half man half god.
But when he ascended to godhood, they had to do something to him to make him fully a
god.
And that's when you see the emperor come out and go, if you picked number two, this is
your fate.
You walk out.
Well actually at this point you're getting dragged out because you start to see the guys
getting the tar ready and they're lighting it on fire and they basically just throw you
on the wood and set you on fire.
You burn alive.
And before you go, ah yeah, that's okay.
Burning alive is actually one of the worst ways you can go.
I actually heard this story once and I mean, I heard this story, it was on Mysterious Universe
actually.
This psychic was talking about reincarnation and she was saying that, I don't remember
all the details, but I remember the visual, that she was a witch you had burned during
the witch trials.
Mysterious Universe is a great show by the way, but.
And she said when she was set on fire, the first, again this is a past life regression
hypnotist so take it or leave it, but she said when she was set on fire, the stakes she
goes, the first thing she realized was how wet she was, not sexually.
But because, and I don't know how scientifically true this is, I don't want to really like
look up photos of it, but when you're set on fire as your skin melts away, you're still
alive, your veins open up and you're covered in your own blood and it's almost like your
blood is trying to put out the fire itself, so you actually feel super like wet and slick
as you're burning alive.
I don't know, I do know though that burning alive is one of the worst ways you can go,
so maybe you do get a little bit of comfort as your blood's trying to cool you down, I
don't know, it's gruesome either way, but that was you if you picked number two.
Now we're moving on to another first century disaster.
This one you notice you're dressed up like a guy named Mucus Scaevolia, now I'm sure
it's maybe it's Mucus Scaevolia or maybe it's nothing like I'm even pronouncing it,
everyone in the arena is scratching their head, they're like who's that, who's that guy?
This one if you pick this number, I think you're getting off pretty good.
In the arena you just see a little like pulpit thing, like a little, I have, what's wrong
with me, a little pillar on the top is a bowl, bowl's on fire.
Mucus Scaevolia was a dude who basically tried to kill an old Roman emperor way back
in the day and they caught him and this was kind of badass, he basically said, oh you
can catch me, but there's a bunch of other Greeks out there that are going to murder
you and let me show you, and he goes let me show you this, he sticks his hand in the fire
and just held it there for a while and he goes, like that's my dedication to killing
you, I can go through this pain, I'm going to use this hand to kill you someday or some
other Greek is going to.
So anyways, in this one all the dude had to do was go out and stick his hand in a fire
and if he could do that he was set free.
Or they killed him, we don't know about the historical evidence for that, but the emperor
is kind of like, oh it's kind of boring, but he does say if you picked number eight, you
just burned your hand, that's it and you're allowed to go, we'll allow you to leave.
So that's not too bad, I could put my hand, if my choice was burn my hand or get set on
fire or chop myself off, they may have made him put his hand in there for quite a long
time, I don't think they just let him like put it in, they might have held it in, but
even then dude, I would take the hand burning, so if you picked number eight, I think that's
probably the best one, you guys are all shutting off the podcast now, all the people here are
number eight are like I'm done.
The next one though we start to get a little ridiculous again, it's 80 AD and you notice
you are dressed up as Orpheus, the god or goddess, one of the two, I think it was a god, it doesn't
matter, you're dressed up as Orpheus and you're given a lyre, a little like harp thingy.
Now Orpheus's power was that he or she could play the lyre, they could play the lyre or
leer, what a man this is totally going off the rails, but anyways they could play this
instrument and they could soothe everything, they could soothe humans, make them just humans
just go oh you're totally awesome, they could even soothe rocks, rocks would be like rock
on and more importantly, music can soothe the savage beast, so you're let out into this
arena, you're surrounded by wild animals and you are told by the emperor, number seven,
if you play them a song and they don't eat you, you are free to go.
And before the emperor even gets done saying that, Achita rips your generals off.
This guy had no chance at all, no chance at all, these animals are constantly bred for
combat in the gladiator arena and you send them out there with a musical instrument to
sit down in front of them, he is beset by these creatures right off the bat, anyways
gets torn to pieces by these things, crowd goes wild and these guys are generally either
criminals or Christians, so you have a pretty good chance of whether or not you're just
a dude who was praying to the wrong god or you murdered somebody.
So ADAD, this one's pretty awesome, this one took some work, someone was really inventive
with this one, you are Deidolius, De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De-
Icarus' father, it's the dude who told his son, hey I'll make you these wings and you
can fly up to the sun, or no he didn't ask him to fly up to the sun, he made him the
wings and the dudes flew too high, the wings melted, it's weird how much like those sayings
come from old stuff, but he flew too high, his wings melted, he crashed the earth, so
this one you're dressed up as De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De-
this one you're dressed up as De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De- De-
And the emperor goes, if you chose number 3, this is your fate, or maybe not, maybe you'll
make it, and basically you were instructed to fly from one, they were really inventive,
you were instructed to fly from one end of the arena to the other, so you basically had
this harness and a rope and it was basically like a zipline.
So you're like, dooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
And you're like, I wonder what that for, are they going to start juggling while I'm flying
over them?
No.
The wings are pre-programmed to break right over the bears, you fall in horribly mauled
and eaten by hungry hungry bears.
I think if I had to choose between being eaten by a lion would be worse than being eaten
by a bear, because I imagine lions are any sort of wild cat, does that, playing with their
food type of nonsense?
Also don't they, no that's dogs that like grab food and shake it around until the next
snaps.
I wonder how, I think bears would probably just like step on you and then just eat you,
or eat you and step on you, I don't think it would be as bad, I think it would be much
quicker.
But anyways, this guy is falling in slow motion towards four hungry bears, and that's you,
if you picked number 3.
Next one, ADAD, still man they had a banner year this year, ADAD.
In this scenario you're actually a woman, because again these are all true events.
This woman, she notices that she is dressed up as Pasi-Fei.
Pasi-Fei.
Now Pasi-Fei is known for two things.
One, she placed a curse on a dude so every time he ejaculated snake scorpions and centipedes
would come out.
Which now no matter what that guy did, that is 100% an overreaction.
There is nothing you can do, nothing you can do that would deserve every time you ejaculate
a scorpion, a snake, or a centipede would come out.
Nothing.
But she's known for that, but more famously she's known for being the mother of the Minotaur.
So and then she is let out and there is a basically a cow costume out there for her
and now you're like oh I was hoping for the centipedes, this doesn't look good.
There's a cow costume and it's not like a onesie from Party City like fluffy cow costume,
it's basically a cow she has to climb into.
And as you hear a bull being released from the doors, the big gates behind you, you hear
the emperor say if you pick number six, I hope you have a high tolerance to pain.
And at that point the bull came out and had its way with the bull costume, unfortunately
you're in it and you die because that's what's going to happen.
There's no way out of that situation.
Second century, now we're a little bit more progressive, we've moved on from that horrible
thing, it's second century.
You're dressed up as Attis and you're like god damn it, why can't I have been Hercules,
why didn't I pick number two?
Why didn't I pick number two?
But you're Attis, also known as the castrated god.
So that one you were simply just let out into the arena and they cut your balls off in front
of everybody.
And, but this one you actually have company because they did this for a bunch of dudes
came out of the arena all at the same time and they got their balls chopped off one by
one.
So, just to make things fair, the emperor says if you chose number five, you're Attis
and you're at the end of the line so you gotta watch everyone else suffer.
That's you if you pick number five.
So finally though we have number one and now number one is an interesting story because
we actually have a journal of this person before they entered the arena.
There was a woman named Perpetua, she was caught for being a Christian and she was a
diehard literally eventually but she was ready to die for her religion and when they said
hey we want you to dress up as this mythological figure, it'll be awesome.
The crowd loves it.
She's like no, I'm Christian, I'm not gonna dress up like that.
And they go okay we'll just throw you out there nude and she's like okay fine, I mean
you're gonna throw me out there anyways but she is panicking about this whole thing.
And she's keeping a journal and the night before she's set to go in the arena she has
a dream where she comes out into the arena and there's an Egyptian warrior in front of
her.
Now she was told she was going to fight beasts in real life but when she enters the arena
she's relieved to see another person there because she can fight another person and she
sees them as an Egyptian which in so and it's interesting because in Christian culture
back then Egypt represented like darkness and satanic forces and stuff like that.
So she comes out in the arena, she sees this Egyptian gladiator come towards her.
In the dream then she becomes a man, it's kind of weird, and then she's surrounded by
young hot dudes who are all on her side.
A giant Jesus shows up in the dream dressed as a gladiator trainer and so Jesus shows
up and goes, giant Jesus shows up and goes okay this is how it's gonna go.
If the Egyptian wins he's gonna chop you up with his sword but perpetual if you win
I'm gonna give you this staff and how all these golden apples on it and he goes and
it was basically the staff of eternal life.
Super weird dream and I guess probably before you're about to die you probably do have some
vivid dreams just chock full of symbolism and she does dude she straight up matrixes
the Egyptian dude like she jumps on top of them starts beating them up throws them in
the ground beats them up some more and she wins and she wakes up and she goes I know
she's basically writing a journal is like I know I'm not going to die tomorrow I know
Jesus is with me I know that no matter what happens I will come out triumphant.
However, if you did pick number one you get gored to death by cows so she did die and
unfortunately she had to face the beasts so if you pick number one you do get gored to
death by cows but you have a kickast dream before that chock full of symbolism you had
a little bit of hope before going in there you didn't get castrated so that was good
so yes another interactive adventure I really like doing these but it's kind of hard to
find stories where multiple people die in different ways I mean we can only hope that
more this is tragic obviously this is absolutely tragic but you ever show often I'll come across
the store and I was like oh dude this is totally gonna be a choose your own adventure ones
that would actually be cool to do a full choose your own adventure podcast but there we go
one through eight which one did you pick which fate sealed you in but that's it for another
episode of Dead Rabbitio you know I know I normally in the or have been in these shows
with kind of like a nice ending like a good twist ending but this episode probably had
the most deaths possible on a show we've done I think more people have died named people
not like episodes that involve war but we've had just horrible horrible people die so let's
end on a happy note I can't think of anything dead rabbitio gmail.com is going to be your email
this was a depressing episode dead rabbitio gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also
hit us up at Facebook it wasn't that depressing but dead rabbitio gmail.com is going to be our
email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbitio twitter is @jasonocarpenter
dead rabbitio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast you don't have to listen to
it every day but I'm glad you listened to it today have a great one guys
so
(upbeat music)