From mysteries debunked to why the Titanic was sunk today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone, thanks for coming back for another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. This is episode 26. I'm very happy about that. I
Like I like just chugging along doing this thing. It's 100 degrees and
It's like 11 o'clock at night and that is just a crime against nature and
It shouldn't be this hot considering I am in the Pacific Northwest in the
Creepy tiny little town of Hood River, which I've talked about before the edge of darkness the last
Bastion of civilization on the edge of a
Black void that is nature. It's very weird. I didn't grow up in a very nature-oriented place. I kind of grew up in more
More more and I don't want to say industrialized but more developed areas
And most the areas I grew up with and had it was developed to a point
And then there was like undeveloped land that you know, eventually they're gonna put houses there because it was prime real estate
But at the time it just you all over neighborhoods just kind of ended into just like weed fields weed fields
But you know generally where I grew up. It was relatively flat areas
So it's weird for me one of the things that creeps me out about Hood River is you're surrounded well basically on one whole side by mountains and
So the other day I was walking to the store and it was probably like 10 o'clock at 9 o'clock at night
So the Sun, you know, it's the Sun's setting way later, but the Sun had set just enough
That there was only some light available from over the mountain range. So what I'm seeing is just these huge
Shadowed mounds and the distance and a little bit like a little line of light above them
I'm walking and I always have these thoughts. I walk everywhere and I love walking, but I always have these thoughts
What was this place like?
before men
Before mankind came here
What was it like?
before the native native population came over
What was it like before the settlers came over there was no lights
So nothing is just darkness and those people would look
Go what's on the other side of those mountains?
It's all mystery to them. We all have the maps nowadays. We know where everything's at everything's well-lit
We're surrounded by civilization even if you're in an area that is
Not as developed
You still know what's on the other side of those mountains
You can always
Google it
But there was a time when that wasn't the case and that always fascinates me
I imagine what the landscape would look like with no buildings no lights or anything like that
It's always terrifying to me because again, I like being around I like being in a civilized area
And when we talk about civilized areas, it's it's it's often easy to forget how much of the world
isn't
Isn't developed. There's just like just trees or deserts or ice wastelands
Even then we can have satellite view of what is in those areas
But when you're on the ground and you're walking through them, you may be even this time you may be the first person
Creating a path through that forest fascinating fascinating stuff to me
Now I'd said in the beginning about mysteries debunked. There was two mysteries
That I was looking at there
I have a little folder
That I kind of like as I'm going through the internet and I'm kind of like throwing stuff in this folder checking it out seeing what's on there
There's two mysteries on there that I was like, oh that sounds really cool. No, that was debunked
And then I found another one. I'm like, oh, whoa, this is right at my that's fake
And then we'll get to the Titanic one which is actually one of the conspiracy theories that I don't necessarily believe in
But I do talk to people about I always kind of it's one of those like
Baby's first conspiracy theories, you know, it's not one of the huge popular ones like 9/11 or Newtown and all that stuff
I kind of still like to do the obscure ones, but it's kind of one of those conspiracy theories
I shout throw out to people who are just kind of starting to show some interest in conspiracy theories
But first off so sticking with the wilderness thing. I found out about this place and it's called the Valley of the Headless Men
So I was like that's dope bookmark
I'll read that later because I never read stuff at the right time
But I do read it before I do this show. I did read it at least once kind of so
Mystery of the headless the headless the the Valley of the headless men is in Canada
One good thing to come out of Canada. I guess Brendan Fraser and Zac Efron came out of Canada. Did Zac Efron come out of Canada? I
Don't remember but anyways if he didn't then that's another strike against Canada
So the Valley of the Headless Men men. Yeah is a
Valley obviously in the Nahini Park Reserve
And the way that it got its name was that several bodies have been found there with their heads chopped off obviously and
There's always been
suspicions of who or what
Has been doing this
So to start it off and I'll just do a brief overview because I kind of gave a spoiler alert by saying that this story was debunked
These people actually did die. So first off there was two brothers who went there to find gold
They look they located a local tribe in the area who had these huge golden nuggets and they're like, oh, there must be gold here
So they went
Into deeper into the valley and they were looking for the gold eventually they went missing and
Then the next time they were found their heads were chopped off
So a few other prospectors had heard the legend of these guys going and they the stories of these guys finding this a massive
Amounts of gold they'd go in there and their heads would be chopped off their bodies were just found with no heads
This went on for probably about 30 years and they've never no one else has ever found the gold mine
There was a tribe of native people up there that it was their land
They just up and disappeared at one point
So the tribe was called the Naha tribe and they existed there and they would come out of the mountains to raid lowland settlements
And then they just mysteriously vanished according to all accounts
and
Then there were other tribes in the area and never were like that area is bad mojo don't go in there
It's really bad, but white settlers kept going in the area looking for gold and kept getting their heads chopped off
So I'm reading a couple different sources on this and I'm going from reddit to this source or that source the other thing and everyone's like
Yeah, these people are getting their heads chopped off. I'm like on a Sasquatch blog and they're like people are getting their heads removed and
All these bodies are being found with no heads and as I'm doing my research and it's not a huge conspiracy
But it's a conspiracy where I'm going from multiple blog to multiple blog and at first. I'm like, okay
This is a really creepy story. This is definitely something I want to talk about
But again, it's always more interesting. I think when reality intrudes into the fantasy
So on one of these blogs I can't one of these articles I came across they said
The two brothers who originally had went in to find the gold pieces. They were found tied to a tree and their heads were removed
Now this was the fourth or fifth article I had found
And it was the first time it acknowledged that the people weren't just found laying in the
brush
They were tied to a tree
So now it's not
this super mysterious
Ghost or paranormal force or
Gateway opening or Sasquatch
Bigfoot doesn't tie you to a tree
So they found these two dudes tied to a tree with their head chopped off and that's tragic. I'm not diminishing that makes it a little more reasonable
Then the other people who are also looking for the gold they just find them with their heads chopped off
This is going on for quite a while and what happens is eventually
The natives that are still in the outskirts of the area they start getting there. This is in December of
1931 so this is about 30 years after the original brothers got their heads chopped off after they were found tied to the tree and
So what happened was the natives in the area? They're putting their traps out for the game and
They would go to check them every once in a while and the tracks the traps would be broken and
Hung from trees now the natives aren't like oh, this must be the work of Bigfoot. They're like, uh, this must be that
Crazy guy who lives up in the hills and his name was the mad the mad trapper of Rat River is what he was called
Albert Johnson was his real name. But anyways, the natives weren't blaming this on any mystical force there because obviously Bigfoot's not gonna be like
He he he I have all this extra rope left over so I'm gonna tie their traps up on trees
They go to the Mounties and they say hey man
Someone's messing with our traps and we think it's this guy so the Mounties come out to this shack and the dudes like I'm not
Lanyuan Mounties are like dude let us in and he's like no
I'm not letting you in so then they leave to get a search warrant which is weird because I didn't think those existed back then and I
Really didn't think they existed in Canada
So Mounties show up with some extra people and the search warrant and they're like banging on the door
And there's a shootout and the Mountie one of the Mounties gets shot and they go and they recover and eventually they grab the guy
They are able to get into the cabin and take down the mad trapper of Rat River and when they catch him they find in his possession
gold teeth
Removed from the heads or mouths of local prospectors
The Mounties at that point said oh, he's the guy's been chopping everyone's head off
Case closed. Why did it take me four articles to find that?
That's the thing and I these articles tend to reference each other
You read this thing on Reddit about the mad trapper and it links me to this article
But it took me maybe 20 minutes to find this article and it was on a website called strange outdoors
It wasn't like this big debunking website, which sometimes I'll get led to those as well
But guys come on and see that's that I think it's one of the problems with ghost stories and paranormal
So I would go stories and conspiracy stories and stuff like that is you don't do your research
I'm a hobbyist at this stuff. I'm making no money doing this. I'm doing this for my fun and
Just to meet new friends to meet people like you and to talk to you about stuff
I'm not doing this for money and I found this article and you could say well, you know, you can't say case closed
You don't have any evidence true
But this is the most likely scenario that it wasn't Sasquatch that it wasn't some sort of demonic portal
It wasn't ball Barith before he took out XXX 10 Tatian. He was ripping the heads off of prospectors
This was most likely a fellow prospector
Who was stealing their gold and their gold teeth?
And even there were sightings of the two brothers
They people saw them with a third person none of that stuff was available in any of the articles I read guys
If you're doing this you got to do a little bit of research
Even if it ruins the story because to me it doesn't ruin the story makes it more interesting
It makes it more plausible because you can go aha mystery solved now
Let's look at the mysteries that we don't have an answer to and it makes you more credible too
I would love to just tell ghost stories all day long
But if I don't believe in them if I know that stuff is fake and I'm selling it to you, you know
That's to me. That's not fun. That's trickery now some of these websites didn't do their due diligence
And some of these websites that I read may have seen this article and said now I like the ghost
I like the ghost story better. Yeah, you know, it gives it a bad name
You got to be able to call like you see and that's one thing I liked about that show ghost hunters
They would walk into our house. They do an investigation be like your pipes are weakened
Everything is because your pipes are leaking and I don't know if they continue to do that
But in the first couple seasons every so often they'd come in our house and they're like, yeah that ghost
That's a car driving by
And it let it lent the show more credibility
There was another thing now. I've talked about this before
I'm a big fan of the idea of
Humanities been around longer than we think kind of hidden history type of things. I like those stories
All right, I don't believe aliens built the pyramids. It may have been done with techniques
That we don't have anymore
Or that we've forgotten the pyramids may be older than we think they are the sphinx the sphinx
Maybe older than we think it is. I've heard a lot of theories like that. I love that stuff
But again, you don't try to trick me
Makes it. Uh, so there's this thing called the wedge of iude a iud
and what it is
Is there was an archaeological dig in 1974 in romania in the town of iude
Is that how i pronounce it? I don't remember. Anyways
It's this there's two mastodontists
They're doing this archaeological dig and they find a mastodontist and they're like, oh score dude
I am getting laid tonight from all those cute archaeological chicks named dusty. They're all named dusty
And then they're digging and they're like, what they find another mastodontist and they're like, dude
This this is going to be dope. Let me brush something aside
It's a chunk of aluminum. So basically it looks like an aluminum
device
It's a big thick thing. Now the problem is is aluminum
If i'm saying that right
Then it wasn't really become a thing wasn't
synthesized or made or whatever the particular term is forged
until
Later in life. I think it was like the 1800s. So we're 1825
Metallic aluminum did not exist and reading that off of this website
I didn't just know that i'm not that smart obviously
They're like, here we go. What is this doing next to two mastodontists?
It's this this is proof
That people have been here before and they were saying that based on where it was at next to the mastodontists and things like that
That the wedge itself could be 11 000 years old minimum
Possibly millions of years old stories ranged everything from ancient humans hidden history stuff like that
To time travel to spacecrafts
And i'm like score. This is a great story. It's kind of hitting all of the stuff that I like
And I googled it
And the first article that popped up was on rational wiki, which is a skeptic website
Which again, I that's not a website that I normally have bookmarked
It seems it's kind of smarmy to me that every time I've read it
I've kind of been like they kind of act like they know everything
Because I don't think there's always an easy answer for everything. But anyways, so I pulled this up and they're like, oh
Here's an answer. It's the tooth of a tractor
What's that thing that digs? It's an excavation tool. It's the one with the
It's the one with the oh here it's an
Excavator bucket. So it's like, you know, the big I'm making the hand with the claw like you can actually see what I'm doing
But it's like the big claw that just whatever you'll see the picture, but it digs into the earth
Now I see that and it's like this is a tooth from an excavator bucket
And the part of me that wants to believe in the story. I'm like, no way. It can't be that easy and they're like, here's
Here's a picture of the tooth. Here's the picture of what they dug up
Here's an illustration showing how that tooth attaches to this excavator bucket. They're like it fell off
It fell off at some point
And which would make sense because you know, it's a dig
It's not like they just were walking across the street and they fell over two mastodon bones
Someone had to dig deep enough to realize there was something there and then the archaeologists are called in
And the material that is made that those excavator bucket teeth are made of oxidizes very quickly
So it looks old very quickly
Now here's the thing if it didn't look exactly like a tooth
I would say well, you know your structure that it looks exactly like the tooth. Don't lie to me, man
It's an interesting story. I just was looking at an article today
Saying that the new theory is is that humanity did not evolve in one location and spread across the planet
That we evolved in several locations on the planet. Boom. That's fascinating
That's a big article that's going around. I'll go ahead and put that in the links as well
So you can still have mysteries. You can still have this great stuff. Don't lie to me, man
Don't tell me that this tooth is from some sort of time traveling
You know mech where he's like had to punch a mastodon in the face to survive and then he's like warp out
And then he ends it back in the year 2400
This isn't a mystery bro. It took me five minutes to google that I can understand it was it probably was a mystery back in the
70s when they figured that out, but this story should not be on any website any mysterious website now
I know you're thinking jason you're getting riled up. It's just because it's 100 degrees and it's super hot
Maybe you might also be thinking jason are you still taking that pseudofit? Is that amping you up? Maybe
I am actually doing that. But so here's the thing. I want to end this on a conspiracy theory
That really hasn't been disproven and it's funny because as I was reading about this
It's a conspiracy theory I followed for a long time when I was reading the article about this they go
This theory's been disproven check the link here. It clicked on the link. It didn't disprove it
I think this one
It might be clocked up more to coincidence
but
As garak once said I believe in coincidences
Coincidences happen every day
But I don't trust coincidences
Oh man star trek deep space nine best television show best television show ever made I've watched it all the way through two times
And I think two and a half times. I love that show
But anyways, so we all know about the titanic whether you knew about the historical event or the movie
You know about it. It's the great big boat that got hit by an iceberg or hit an iceberg whatever
Whichever one is more grammatically correct. But anyways, so
Hit an iceberg it sank a bunch of people died and at the ending the girl threw the heart of the ocean
Was it the heart of the ocean? Yeah, heart of the ocean into the ocean
And then she becomes a ghost that itself is not a huge conspiracy theory
What is a huge conspiracy theory is why it sank now?
Of course people have said the boat was supposed to be unsinkable
And it hit an iceberg and it cut it open and I'm not really arguing with the technical sides of that
There were a few titanic
Conspiracy theories and they're all kind of fascinating the one that I wanted to start talking about was why it sank
Or who sank it is a better course of action
I'm not necessarily saying this is true conspiracy, but again, it's just kind of a fascinating story. So
JP Morgan was the owner of the white star line the boat line that the titanic sailed under
There was a still called sail if it didn't have any sails
anyways
So so what happened was at the time the titanic so it was like 1912 1910 1912
There's this debate over whether or not to start a federal reserve
So the united states would have a federal reserve bank that's still controversial to this day
It's not a so the federal reserve is actually not part of the federal government. It was it was
It existed because of an act of congress, but it's not a
It's a it's a private corporation basically
And if for the most part it can control it says interest rates
It has quote-unquote like control over our financial rules setting the interest rates a big one because it kind of depends
Kind of determines how people are loaning money and borrowing money and stuff like that
But it's not a government organization
The you know, we can appoint
You know ben Bernacky or alan greenspan and stuff like that, but it's more set up like a private corporation
So there are people against the establishment of a federal reserve
They didn't want they didn't want a federal head controlling money policy and this is
You know, like I said, we're going back to like 1910 1912 around this time period
Well and jp morgan was on this side of yes
We need to set up a federal reserve and there was three people who were against setting well
There's multiple people against setting up the federal reserve. These are some of the most powerful
It was benjamin guggenheim who you might recognize his name from guggenheim
fast food restaurants
There was issa strauss who is the inheritor of the levi strauss. I'm making that up
Benjamin guggenheim
Issa strauss and jacob aster and i know aster and guggenheim. I don't know strauss
I was making the levi joke up
But anyways, both of them according to this graphic that i'm looking at
Were worth a total of 11 billion dollars and that's probably in today's money
Maybe back then but anyways, they were adamantly opposed to the establishment of federal reserve
And all three of those men were on the titanic and all three of those men died the night it sank
So that's a fact
Those three men died during the sinking of the titanic and jp morgan owner of the white star line
Was for the federal reserve and they were against it
So the conspiracy is that the titanic was sunk to eliminate powerful opposition to the establishment of the federal reserve
Creepy if true
possible maybe
so
And that's a conspiracy theory that's been floating around for a long time
And it's one of those things that sometimes terrible events happen and they take on a life of their own
You know, we've seen stuff where you know the 9/11 was taken down because there was a bunch of gold in the basement of one of the
Buildings and someone wanted to steal it or a bunch of money went missing from the federal government
They wanted to hide that up so they destroyed all that stuff that fairly unlikely, but I could see that if
you were
I i'm a powerful man and I have three people who are equally as powerful
Maybe even more powerful trying to stop me and my side
From creating this federal reserve, which will benefit me endlessly
It'll benefit you endlessly too. So why don't you just get on our side and they're like no no no jp
We're not following your plans and that's all hop on this boat and take a trip and he sinks it
Now the couple I like that conspiracy theory. I think it's an interesting one some of the problems with it just to be fair one
If they were in such at such war with jp morgan, why would they ride his boat?
You know, why would they go on his boat? That's a question I have two
Bullets are cheaper than sinking a boat
And you could say well jason
If the whole boat sinks you can get them all three at once, but then it leads to my third question
What if they survived?
You know, what if they hopped on the life rafts right away?
What if there were enough life rafts? What if the rescue ship showed up early enough?
So on and so forth. So it's an interesting conspiracy theory
It's possible
I enjoy it. I enjoy that conspiracy theory and um, and it does fit the
idea of what a good conspiracy theory is and I guess when I keep saying a good conspiracy theory is I basically
I'm saying a conspiracy theory. You can't really disprove it involves time plus distance because it happened in the middle of the ocean a long time ago
it is a
Involved a group we don't trust which is billionaires and corporations things like that a little bit of the government
And it has very few people involved in it
You would just need well actually now that I think about it. It would basically
Someone on the boat would have had to steer it into the iceberg
I never mind that conspiracy theory is pretty ridiculous too now that I've actually put a little bit of thought into it
You would have had to have you would have had to
Know there was an iceberg in that area
Crash into it on purpose
And do enough damage for it to sink and I know there's also a conspiracy theory that it didn't even hit an iceberg
But at a certain point you kind of got to go
Yeah, and pterodactyls could have shown up and eaten everybody like at a certain point
You have to accept a certain amount of facts in any given story. So there we go. There's tonight's episode
I I guess I actually ended up disproving a conspiracy theory that I've talked about
I mean unless they really paid him off or paid off the the captain's family
Why would you steer your boat into a?
Into an iceberg for money to die in the cold
That yeah, that doesn't really work unless
No, I got nothing I got nothing
Well, that is it for tonight's episode. I started off with two debunked stories and pretty much ended with three
I really do like the titanic story if you have a
Answer for why someone would purposely drive a boat into an iceberg or go on a suicide mission
Because again, somebody has to make the boat crash and blow up
Let me know dead rabbit radio at gmail.com shoot me an email there
You can also hit me up on twitter at jason o carpenter our website is dead rabbit calm again everyone
Thanks for listening. I see you guys downloading. I got a fan in england cheerio mate
I don't know if you say mate over there, but I see you downloading my episodes
That makes me feel great
I hope you're having a good time listening to the show. I hope everyone's having a good time listening to the show
Hope you're having as good as the time as I am
Doing it. We're going to be looking at doing some stuff in the future with live streams and things like that
But for right now, I'm just happy to get a podcast out every day
That's like my news bulletin noise
As I was editing the episode and I'm looking back over my sources
There was something that I had read initially. I promise and I'd forgotten to say it originally
In considering how much I was lambasting people for not fully doing their research. I guess I'm the last one to talk
Nahini valley the valley of the headless men
myth busted or was it
In 1962
30 years after the event of the prospector having to shoot out with the Mounties and being arrested with the gold teeth taken from
the prospector's mouths
Alone pilot is flying his plane
Smoke billows out of the plane. I don't know smoke bill out of the plane. But anyways, so the plane crashes
into the valley
He survives
He's a good enough pilot. You can walk away from anything
He's downed though. He can't contact anyone, but he does have food
He has water
He has shelter
He's like i'm just gonna stay here
Until I get rescued that's the smart play right when you're a little kid you're taught if you get lost
Stay where you're at and your parents will find you
Don't do that if you're actually a kidnapped victim you have to get away, but
We're in a mall and no one's kidnapped you yet. Just stay there parents will find you
So he stays there and he's bored because he's in the middle of nowhere
Just like anyone who goes in the middle of nowhere is bored camping might be the most boring possible
I'm gonna I'm forget that forget that. He's bored. So what do you do when you're bored?
Keep a diary. You got nothing else to do. You have no television
So he begins writing about what's going on day to day just kind of keep himself
Keep himself going and if we see in his diary that planes are flying overhead and he's trying to signal them
Hey, I'm down here. I'm down here. They just keep flying
They don't see him
He keeps taking his diary, you know
gets dark
Snuggles up with a few slides. I don't know. I don't know what pilots like and then during the day
He's like throwing rocks at squirrels or whatever taking his diary way to get rescued now
He's actually only six miles from his destination of where he's supposed to go, but he didn't know in which direction
You know, maybe he's a little shook up from the plane crash. So again best thing to do is to just wait there
Six months later just on an accident his plane the wreckage of his plane is discovered
They find his camp. They find his diary which has 50 days of entries in it
The pilot
Was never found
Is a mystery back on the menu boys
We don't know we'll keep this one open on dead rabbit radio
[Music]