Is it possible for a ghost to be so powerful they can make you cease to exist?
Then we hop aboard a school bus to take a look at a bizarre experience of a seventh grader.
One day while riding home on the school bus they looked out the window and saw something
that defies explanation. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason
Carpenter, and I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got
a ton of stuff to cover, so we gotta get started right away. First off, walking into Dead Rabbit
Man is one of our legacy Patreon supporters. Everyone get on your feet and give a big round
of applause for SE. Woohoo! Yeah, come on in buddy. Walk on into Dead Rabbit Command,
do a little fancy spin. Cause you're a show off SE, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot.
This episode if you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand, I do. Just
help spread the word about this show that really, really, really helps out a lot. Now,
we have a ton of stuff to cover, but I do have to give a little bit of announcements.
First off, this is the end of season 19. This week is the end of season 19. After this,
I'm going to take a break until December 1st. However, I invite all of you guys to join
me on November 24th, that is a Thanksgiving November 24th at 12pm Pacific Standard Time
for the annual Dead Rabbit Radio Thanksgiving livestream. Meet us over on YouTube. This
is the reason why I stopped posting on YouTube, because they were getting ready to take the
channel down, because they hate the podcast, but I wanted to be able to keep doing these
livestreams and the YouTube shorts and all that stuff. And so I really would appreciate
if you guys came out here and spent, you know, with your family, spent it with us. Now I'm
putting it early enough in the day that I think most people could join us. And if not,
it really is just, you know, I know how lonely the holidays gets. So I thought it would be
really cool for us to hang out together. If you can't make it, that's totally fine.
But check us out on the YouTube channel. I'll put the link, the YouTube link in the show
notes November 24th, 2022. Cholpia Pacific Standard Time, Dead Rabbit Radio Thanksgiving
livestream special. If you guys can't be there, totally understand you'll be there in spirit.
Whether you want to or not, I'm going to reach through the astral world and suck your souls
into this livestream. Your relatives are like, Hey, why are you so quiet? Why are you just
standing around in the corner of the room? It's Thanksgiving. Come and have a seat. You
can't. Your soul belongs to me. S E. Let's go ahead. That's some threatening. I'm mildly
threatening actually. It's not more than mildly threatening. S E. Let's go ahead and toss
you the hair hang glider. We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command, jump off the highest
point and glide us all the way out to a shopping mall. I saw a movie the other day called Hex.
It was about a haunted, I don't even know how anyone would come up with this topic. It was
a movie about these parachuter people. What are they called? Skydivers. And they're like,
I'm probably should just get started with the other side. I'm actually not feeling that
well. But let's just prolong the episode a little bit. This is the last of the week.
I watched this movie recently about these haunted skydivers. They were, this is fantastic,
this is a fantastic plot. The movie wasn't very good, but it was about these skydivers
who they're like, they meet this new girl, they find this new skydiving girl. They're
like, you dive alone. And she's like, yeah, I've always dived alone since my dad died
skydiving or something like that. And they go, well, you know, I'd quit being such a
poor dad's dad. Why don't you come and join us as we go skydiving? Let's do this. And
so she goes skydiving with them and they said, you know what we should do now that we have
six people in our skydiving group, we should do the hex. People are like, Oh, no, not the
hex. And the hex is a, it's a sky, it's not real. I don't think so. I'm kind of scared.
It's it takes six people. It's a haunted skydiving maneuver. So they're like, dude, let's do the
hex. It'll be so cool. And people will be like, you can't do the hex. Every time someone
does the hex, they die. And not because it's so difficult because it's like magical, because
it's this magical cursed parachuting maneuver. And it's so funny. So they all go up in this
airplane. You can tell basically what the movie was. It was very well made. Like, like
cinematography was good. They had really good cameras and stuff like that. But you can tell
it was basically someone owned someone owned a skydiving school. And they said, Hey, let's
make a horror movie that takes place in broad daylight, 10,000 feet in the air. And so they
do the hex. And like one guy's in the middle, one guy's in the middle of this circle of
people. And they're falling. Then all of a sudden, he dematerializes. He just disappears
in front of them. And they're like, Randy, no, Randy, where'd you go? And they still
have to fall like another 9,000 feet, right? You see this guy simply ceased to exist in
front of you. And they all land. And then the movie I was like, what in the world? They're
like, where did Randy go? Where did Randy go? Did he pull a shoot early? No, he dematerialized.
You were looking right at him. He just disappeared. He stopped existing. They're like, maybe he
pulled a shoot. Well, then where is he? Well, maybe his shoot failed. And then they get
investigated by the police. And they're like, you got to find a friend, Randy, man, he's
missing. You must like parachuted away. He must have had one of those new dematerializing
parachutes that the predator sold them. They go to the police and the police are investigating
it. And they're like, you kids are crazy. You just can't disappear in the thin air literally
because the air is thin up there. And they're like, no, Randy's gone. And they're like, are
you sure about that? And then they see the helmet can footage of them parachuting down.
And there was only five people up there. So Randy never existed. Or something like that.
I'm not fully aware. That was when I kind of started checking out. I was like, I don't
know about this movie. And then the movie kept going on and on. And then spoiler alert in
case you're planning on watching hex, it turned out that there is so funny. I just need to
get started with the episode. But I want to tell someone about this movie. No one that
I know wants to hear me talk about hex. So I'm making you, it turns out that a parachute
person like a master skydiver made a deal with the devil. And the devil gave him a
cursed altometer. And the thing that tells how high you are, the devil gave him a cursed
altometer. And this device makes the old grizzled skydiving coach immortal. You can't die, which
would probably be pretty, probably be a pretty neat trick if you were skydiving all the time,
like not releasing your parachute at all. You're like, people are like, Oh my God, Joe,
you're gonna die. And then he hits the ground. There's like a puff of smoke from a roadrunner
cartoon. And then you get down there and he's like tea anybody. No, you just fell 30,000
feet and you didn't open your parachute. It'd be pretty, it would be a great skill for a
skydiver. It also be super suspicious. When you're like, I'm never done all this crazy
stuff. He's landing on his head intentionally. He's like, you're like, what? Let me see your
altometer. Is it cursed? And then it had something to do with the girl. Like the entire movie
took place in a comp... This was interesting. I never... I'm talking about it once I get
to the interesting part. I got bored. I was like, the whole movie took place like in three
minutes or something like that. It was kind of an occurrence at Al Creek Bridge. She was
trapped. She died in the plane crash. They didn't even get to do the hex. The plane crashed
or blew up or something like that. And I don't know. I lost interest somewhere in between
the guy dematerializing. And then at the ending, the bad guy had this cursed altometer and
the devil was driving the car. Not like a really cool CGI devil. Just a guy in a black
suit. They're driving around. They're doing donuts in the desert. Somewhere in between.
Somewhere in between. That was the final shot of the devil. It was like a favorite dream.
Maybe this movie doesn't exist. Maybe I'm Randy. The devil's driving... I just got to
get started with the episode. The devil's driving the car at the ending. And then about
20 minutes in is when that dude dematerializes. The whole movie, I guess, takes place in like
a three minute time period. The girl trying to solve the mystery as to where Randy went
and how to uncurse the hex. How to get rid of the cur... Whatever. Whatever. I'm just
talking about it. And now I realize it was interesting but it's kind of complicated to
talk about. Anyways, I saw that movie so thank you for... Thanks for letting me talk about
it. Nobody else wants to hear about that movie. I figured you might like it.
S.C. go ahead and land this... Dead Red Rapper finally getting started with the episode. S.C.
go ahead and land this hair hang glider in the parking lot of this shopping mall. We're
right outside a Sears department store. We're going to walk on into it. Now, we don't have
a location for this story. This is one of the stories where we don't have a location.
We don't have a time period. We don't even have the name of the person. The person posted
this anonymously. We're going to call him Sam. But if this story is true, this is a pretty
insane paranormal event. Sam, who uses the online name "Fordor II Seater." Sam used to
work at a mall photo studio. You know those places you used to go to to get your picture
taken before every single person had a phone in their pocket? You'd go in there and get
your photo taken. That's how it used to be back in the day. Sam used to work at one of
these places. When Sam is working there, he's told pretty early on that the place is haunted.
Sam says that this photo studio was set up... There was only really two main rooms to it.
You had these two rooms. You had about seven different backdrops. You would go in there
and be like, "Hey, you're going to go take a photo for your grandma. Let's make it look
like you're in Maui." Obviously, your grandma's a huge idiot. You can't tell the difference
between Maui and a backdrop at a mall photo center. You're pulling these backdrops down.
A lot of people go in here to take photos of their kids. You bring your kid in and there's
toys and stuff to animals that you can place around them. The baby's like, "Ah, click."
Then there you go. Send that to grandma. You're like, "What? I know the baby was in Maui."
That was about it. It was fairly small. You also had a room in the back where they developed
the film. Actually, I'm thinking about it. The story's probably pre-Mid 2000s. I'm going
to guess somewhere between the 90s and the 2000s is when the story takes place. They've
developed the photos in their ... I don't know if this story could take place yesterday
in Alabama, but you have the photos taken and developed there while you wait. Maybe
you could go get a churro and an orange julie and swing back by, but you could leave with
the photos that were taken. Basic place. These were around all the time when I was a kid
and a young adult.
Sam was told this place was haunted. Sam did realize it pretty quickly that, "Yeah, this
place is haunted." Very, very by-the-book paranormal activity. There was no missing
skydivers. It was just stuff ... I swear that I left this toy tiger in room A, but it's
weird. When I went to room B, the toy tiger was sitting in there. You'd have toys move
from room to room or ... that's weird. I remember we used the Maui backdrop for the last photo
in room A, but then when I came back later, there was a different backdrop set up. Interesting.
Now you could account that for the fact that people are constantly changing backdrops.
There's kids there. Stuff's going to move from room to room. It would be easy to dismiss
if you were a skeptic, but if you were working there and you knew you were the only one there
or it was just you and somebody else and they weren't in the room in that time period and
stuff was moving from room to room, it would also be easy to chalk up to paranormal activity.
This would be easy for both a skeptic and a believer in the paranormal to kind of get
an argument over, right? Because it's stuff that could easily happen with human interaction
and you not realizing it. A customer changing the backdrop, a kid carrying the toy from
one room to another, but if you believed in the paranormal, you could go and like, "No,
this stuff was happening when there was no one else in the building. No one else was
changing the stuff." But fairly basic. Fairly, fairly basic things. Also, again, this is
a staple of paranormal activity. Lights would turn on in rooms where there was nobody.
Malfunctioning lights. You could chalk it up to stuff like that. Very, very standard stuff.
Except for what I'm about to tell you. I actually was messaging four door two-seater
online. I've never seen anything like this. I couldn't think of anything like this. In
the realm of ghosts at least. Let's take a look at this. It's fascinating. 20 minutes
into the episode, let's get started. Sam and his manager were working at the photo studio
one day when a teenage girl walks in and she needs to get a passport photo taken. Pretty
basic stuff. You take a bunch of photos, select the best one, make five copies of it, hand
it to the customer. Good to go. So they do that. The girl comes in, they put her on a
stool, they have their basic backdrop, and 12 photographs are taken from about a few
feet away. Click, click, click. I'm not gonna do 12 times. Multiply that by 4. And then
it's time to develop them. Hey, young lady, why don't you go get a churro and an orange
Julius while we develop these pictures? So Sam and the manager go into the back room,
the dark room. Spooky is placed to be. Spooky is placed to be in a haunted photo studio.
They're in the dark room to develop these photographs. And all of a sudden Sam hears
his manager gasp. He turns to her and goes, "What? What's wrong?" And the manager hands
the negatives, the film negatives over to Sam. Photo one is a picture of this girl sitting
on a stool, the teenage girl, not like a spooky Annabelle girl. That's the first photo. Totally
normal. That's exactly what Sam had expected it to look like. Second photo looks the same.
Third photo looks the same. Variations in her facial expression, maybe her shoulders
are a little slump. This is why they take 12 of them, right? The first 7 photos are
of the young girl sitting on the stool. But Sam's continuing to look at these negatives
and photo 8, 9 and 10, the girl is gone. In the photograph is just the wooden stool. Photo
11, teenage girl sitting on a stool. Photo 12, teenage girl sitting on a stool. When Sam
posted this, he does address the possibility that it could be a malfunction in the camera,
but what would be the malfunction? What would be the malfunction? I could understand if
the photo was blurry or if a photo wasn't taken at all. Like obviously you need time
to get a new camera, but the photo is there, everything is there, but the girl. And then
you could say it was a glitch because the remaining photos didn't have the girl. But
there was 3 times that click happened where something was photographed. Well it's funny,
I was about to say that wasn't there, but that's almost a misnomer. When we talk about
ghostly photographs, normally what they are is someone takes a photograph of a hallway
and then when the film is developed or when you look at your phone on your screen, there's
something in the photo that wasn't there before. That's what common ghost photography
is. I can't think of a time, and maybe you guys can correct me, I can't think of a time
where a photograph was taken of something that was there that you could see with the
naked eye, that was a normal object. You're looking at a chair, an old antique chair at
a Goodwill and you want to send a photo to somebody, you take a picture of the chair,
but then when you look at the photograph, everything else, everything else in that Goodwill
is in the photograph except for the chair. And it's not that the chair is distorted,
it's not like there's something blurry that's been added to the photograph, what you're
seeing is something removed from the photograph that existed in reality. I can't think of
another time that that's happened. And again, let me clarify this too, I'm not talking about
a time where we have a story of somebody seeing a ghost walking down a hallway, taking a photograph
of the photograph not appearing correctly. I'm not talking about that. I'm talking about
you see your mom walking down the hallway, not a ghost mom, a real mom, and you take
a photograph of her and then when you look at the photograph later, it's just an empty
hallway. Because that's what this seems to be. When I was talking to Sam online, they
seemed to throw out the possibility that maybe the teenage girl was a ghost, maybe she was
a ghost all along. I've never seen anything like that. I've never seen something where
two witnesses, right, are seeing something with their own eyeballs that should be real.
Again, it's not like two people see a UFO in the sky and they take a photograph and you
can't see the UFO in the photograph. I'm not talking about, because we know that that's
already a bizarre event. This is just somebody walking in to get their photo taken and then
they cease to exist and then they come back. There's actually so many different layers
to this. It's not like they simply cease to be in them and they walked out. She had never
been there before because actually when I was talking to Sam about this online, one of
their theories was that she was a ghost or the ghost of the photo store, which I think
you could argue is possible. I didn't really go that direction because she showed back
up in the photographs and they also gave her the photographs and they gave her copies
of the photographs and she left. She left the story. She didn't dematerialize and the
photographs fall on the ground. She probably did go to Orange Julius. She probably did
get a delicious treat. I can't think of a time where someone's dematerialized in a photo
session. Now to be fair, we haven't covered a lot of photo sessions on this podcast or
even in my independent research, but what I think happened, what my theory is, is that
what was ever in that film studio was so powerful it could manipulate the technology at the
very least. It was so powerful that you could take a photo of something that exists, not
something imaginary, not something that could be a trick of the light because it happens
all the time in the world of paranormal. You think you see something walking down a hallway,
take a photograph, you look at the photograph, the hallway's empty. That's normal. This is
a situation of your mom walking down the hallway, you're taking a photograph, you look at the
camera, it's an empty hallway. Your mom doesn't jump, she's right in your face. Time for dinner!
That's what we're talking about. That's what we're talking about. Something real that
ceased to exist for a couple moments in time and then it started existing again. So fascinating.
I thought if it was my theory, again the story also could totally be made up, but my theory
is that the ghost at the very least manipulated the technology of the camera to make the person
cease to exist for three frames of film. And the reason why they would do that is almost
as a flex to do it to show that they had that ability. The manager also said she had never
seen anything like this before. She's never seen a glitch like this or even any haunting
activity like this. So it would have been an ability for the ghost to show how powerful
it was. That's theory one. Theory number two is actually far more disturbing and if it
is true, this would rank as one of the most powerful ghosts on record. Because what is
possible is as they were taking the photographs of this girl, the ghost literally made her
disappear. It wasn't that she was blinked out of reality in the photographs, it was that
the ghost made her blink out of reality in real life. Which would take a tremendous amount
of energy. At that point, we're not talking about a ghost, we're talking about alien powers
at that point. Aliens can dematerialize people and rematerialize people and things like that.
That's what we see in the lore. They can also materialize and dematerialize themselves.
But I can't think of a time. We do cover stories of people dematerializing. That's what a lot
of missing 411 is. It's a kid walking around a berry bush and then they never see him again.
Missing 411, although paranormal, never gets tied into the world of ghosts. There are pretty
firm power limits on the way we describe ghosts. The fact that a ghost could dematerialize and
then rematerialize somebody. You would almost need a haunted skydiving technique to do that.
Fascinating story. I wish I had more information like where to display it. I mean I'd say that,
but I'm sure this place is shut down by now. I don't think there's many mall photo studios
still in operation. What a fantastic ghost story though. I really hope it's true. It
could be creepy. It was posted pretty recently by someone who just talks about other stuff
online and they weren't just writing about the paranormal. But it's awesome ghost story
like that would be one. I would rather go to this place because that's such a powerful
ghost than go to the same old haunted insane asylum that everyone else goes to. I'm walking
through. I'm all possessed by an insane person. I'm all boring. Take me to the photo studio.
Fascinating ghost story. If it's true, it does transcend anything we know about ghosts.
She'd be looking at demonic at that point. Or alien. And I think again whatever it was,
it was flexing its power level. It wanted the people there to know how strong it truly
was. Why? Who knows. Sam didn't work there for long. It wasn't because they were too
scared to go back to work. They worked there for a couple weeks. I don't know what happened
after that. Again, I'd like to have more information about this, but that's all the information
we have so far. Terrifying story. If true, that is one of the most powerful ghosts I've
ever read about or came across. SE, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to those carbonar
copters. Everyone's trapped in your parachutes. SE, take us up and away where we leave behind
this mall photo studio. Take us all the way out to a bus stop. The year is truly beautiful.
The year is 2007. We're going to meet a 7th grader online. He goes by the name NateW9731.
We're just going to call you Nate. Nate is a 7th grader. And recently his family moved.
He says we didn't move out of the area. I still attended the same middle school that
I'd been going to. But we moved farther away from the school itself. So we're still in
the district. We're just farther away. So I had to start taking the bus to school. And
Nate explains that he's kind of a shy kid in general. And now that he's thrust onto
this bus, this school bus, he's already shy since he just started riding the school bus.
He doesn't have any friends on the bus. He hasn't made any friends. So it's kind of a
double whammy, right? He doesn't have any friends. He's too shy to make some. And he
says the bus in general was pretty rowdy. So that made him withdraw even more. Because
now he's completely out of his element. He doesn't know any of these people. And they're
a bunch of crazy people. So on this particular day back in 2007, he walks to the back of
the bus. He gets on. And it loads up with all these really noisy kids that he doesn't even
know. The bus leaves school. The bus has left school. And it's not far. It's not far from
school. Only about a mile, he estimates. The bus is only about a mile from school. And
it comes to a stoplight. This is a classic yellow school bus. So it sits really high.
So Nate sitting on the very back, he can look out and he can look into other people's cars.
And they're at this red light. The bus has stopped at this red light. And next to the
bus is an old 80s era Ford pickup truck. There's two guys sitting in the truck. And Nate says,
"If I had to guess, they look like father and son." One of them was in their 50s, early
60s. The other one seemed to be in his 30s. I'm looking into this truck, seeing these
two dudes sitting there. The driver, who's the older one, has both of his hands on the
steering wheel. He's staring straight ahead. The passenger is sitting there also staring
straight ahead, his hands in his lap. And there's just a weird look to their faces. Nate's looking
at these two guys. There's just something weird, something very emotionless about them.
They're just staring straight ahead. In between the two men, Nate sees a stack of what he
believed was folded blankets. It was a stack of folded blankets. Could have been towels,
could have been rags, could have been anything, but a stack of folded blankets between the
two men. And he goes, "The stack of the blankets, the fabric, was about as high as the men's
chest." So maybe about like two feet, you know, they're sitting down, probably about
like two feet high of these blankets neatly folded up. Nate's looking at these two men.
He's looking at the blankets. And his eyes just kind of scan down as he's looking into
this car. He's looking down this pile of blankets until he sees nestled in between the neatly
stacked blankets and the seat of the pickup truck is the severed head of a woman. Now,
Nate, even now, you know, this story happened in 2007, he's having a hard time coming to
terms with what he saw. Such a shock. But he 100% remembers looking down the blankets
and seeing this head. And he goes, "I knew it was a woman's head." He goes, "If anything,
it was a young woman." He goes, "I'm looking out the school bus window and I see the severed
woman's head and it is completely pale as if it's been drained of blood." But the worst
part about it, the part that he can't get out of his head, was the look on her face.
He said this woman's eyes were wide and her mouth was locked in a eternal scream. This
severed woman's head sitting underneath the pile of blankets. And Nate is so shocked by
what he's looking at, he actually begins to look around the bus. He has this crippling
shyness that won't let him yell out, "Guys, look, look!" He doesn't know anyone, there's
no one he can turn to, there's no one he can tap on the shoulder. And the kids are crazy
anyways, they're so rambunctious, the bus is full of noise right now. He's hoping another
kid sees it. A braver kid, a louder kid looks over and sees this woman's head. But no one
does. "Nate just sits there," he doesn't say a word. The light turns green, the bus
makes a left, the pickup truck continues on its journey. And to this day Nate questions
exactly what he saw. It's an interesting story, it's funny because Nate, when he posted this,
seemed to think that this could have been paranormal, which it very well could have
been. There are things that I've seen, personally seen, I'll try to find the episodes, put them
in the show notes, but there are things that I've seen that when you look at something
that isn't real, that doesn't make sense. And I'm not talking about like it's your
imagination or something like that, you're psychotic. I'm talking about when you see
any sort of ghostly activity that shouldn't be, your brain can create a false image to
cover up the impossible. So for example, let's say you came home, let's say you came home
and you have a kid and your kid was floating in air. That's impossible. That's impossible,
unless your kid's Casper, that's impossible. Your kid can't float in the air. So what would
happen, it doesn't happen all the time, but what could happen is you would come home and
you would see your kid floating in the air and you knew that would be impossible and
it's almost like a little bit of a glitch. You can't comprehend what you're looking
at, but what would happen is let's say maybe three or four years later you may go, hey
remember that time when Billy was balancing on three basketballs? And people are like,
what are you talking about? And they're like, no, I remember one day I came home and Billy
was balancing on three basketballs and it's completely impossible. That's that's equally
impossible. But it's more plausible than your kid floating. That type of stuff does happen.
So sometimes when we look at super bizarre memories that just don't make sense. We can
look at a paranormal answer for those things. So I can see where Nate's coming from where
he's saying that it's possible that what I saw was actually something paranormal that
shouldn't have existed and my brain was processing it in that way. His logic behind that was
there was no blood. There was no blood. I'm looking at the severed head, but there was
no blood in the car. It wasn't dripping out any sort of blood. If it was a real severed
head, there would have been blood. He also does to be fair, he does also bring up that
it could have been a prank that could have been a Halloween prop as well. It's possible.
Those are all definitely possible. I don't think this was a paranormal event, though.
It actually wouldn't make sense these series of events that would make this a true crime
tragedy for one when you decapitate somebody the head itself doesn't contain a ton of
blood. While your brain needs blood and your skin needs blood and all this stuff and you
need oxygen in your head, that's true. But it doesn't contain... I know it has a lot
of blood. It has a lot of blood as compared to maybe your fingers, but you could drain
a human head quicker than you could drain a human leg. It doesn't contain a lot of blood
to begin with. You actually, when you decapitate someone, you could drain the blood out of
a head fairly quickly. So the head not bleeding isn't a sign that it's paranormal, too. We
don't know the situation here, right? It looked like it was a young woman's head here. So
if you really were transporting a young woman's head, why would you transport it in that way,
in between the two people with the blankets stacked up on top of it? The blankets would
make sense to cover up the sight of the head for anyone who is driving by in a normal sized
car. You know, no one would think that the bus is elevated, that there's a chance that
you might come next to a school bus. Criminals aren't... they don't have a lot of foresight.
That's generally why they get caught. But that would make sense. They're gonna cover
it up. You go, "Why didn't they just put it in a box?" It's super interesting because
when we do look at criminals, they do... not all of them, right? There's a lot of monsters
out there, but most criminals were ordinary people up until the crime. They may have drug
problems, gambling problems, things like that, but for the most part, they're ordinary people
before the crime was committed. And you have all your normal superstitions and normal traditions
and beliefs. Just 'cause you've murdered someone doesn't... you don't go, "Well, I guess I'm
not Southern Baptist anymore." No, you're just Southern Baptist who murdered somebody.
I could see if this victim was somebody that they knew that they wouldn't want to throw
the head in a tackle box. It feels very disrespectful. It is an interesting quirk of crime, but you
will... you know, you bury bodies after crimes for two reasons. One, to hide the evidence,
to kill the two, also 'cause you don't want the body picked up by scavengers. You don't...
you knew this person. You knew this person. You guys hung out for years and years, and
then a drug deal went bad. He ripped off a bunch of money from you. You can't let that
stand. Otherwise, everyone will rip off money from you. So you do have to kill this guy,
but you don't want him eaten by the rats in the alleyway. So you could... I could see
that happening. I could see them not throwing her head in a tackle box and those eyes wide
staring into the darkness as it rumbles back and forth across the flatbed of the truck.
I could see them wanting to have some sense of grace, some sense of compassion for this
head. The number one reason why I think this is a real head, and again, the story could
totally be made up. This could be creepy, but the reason why out of all of this that
I think it was a real head was a detail that Nate said. Because while this detail isn't
impossible to make up, most people don't think of it this way. Most people don't think of
things like this. A violent death is a violent death. In the movies, people get shot, they
fall down, they die. People get hit in the back of the head with a baseball bat, they
fall down, they die. Or if it's the hero, he just goes "ouch." But in reality, killing
someone is extremely violent. You start off trying to strangle somebody and then three
and a half minutes later, the person is still alive, you grab the claw hammer. That's generally
how it happens. Unless you come with your own murder weapon, and even then, stuff can
go south, guns, jams, knives, break off. People go to houses with a steak knife that's used
to cut steak, and now they're trying to stab someone in the rib cage with it, it's not
going to work. I mean, it actually does work, but the chance of a malfunction goes up because
it's not designed for combat. It's not designed to go into a human.
Violent death is extremely violent. It's an extremely violent way to go. If you asked
the average person, "What would a severed head look like?" If you chopped a head off,
most people are just going to immediately think of something they had seen in the haunted
mansion down in Disneyland or something they had seen in a movie, or like a guillotine
type movie. It gets chopped off, it's a pretty clean cut. Head rolls around in the basket,
right? Draw a picture of a chopped off head. And that is pretty accurate. When you chop
a head off in combat, when you chop a head off while you're fighting someone, it's not
a clean line. But if you are doing it post-mortem, you can make it fairly clean. I've seen quite
a few severed heads in my life because my father used to own a crematory, and that was
my summer job. So when you find these bodies that have been chopped up, it's pretty even
cut. It's pretty even cut. I'm not saying you could put... I'm not saying that you could
put a bubble level on it and it'd be perfect, but a detail that most people would miss.
If you want... If I said show me the severed head of a murder victim, if I wanted to draw
a picture of that, if I wanted you to just describe a severed head of a murder victim
to me. One of the key details that I think a lot of people would leave out, and it's
a key detail that Nate said, it's something that he observed, this image has been with
him all these years, was that the woman's head was missing teeth. That is very common
in a violent crime, and it's not something that most people would associate. If I asked
you to picture a severed head, or to draw me a picture of a severed head, very few people
would draw that picture with teeth missing. But it is... I mean teeth get knocked out
in fights all the time. Teeth get knocked out in sports all the time. So when you're
trying to murder somebody, teeth will break. Teeth will break, teeth will shatter. If it's
a fight, if you're trying to strangle someone, again it takes a long period of time, it's
a very, very violent death. If you're trying to hold someone down, you go, "Well we're
just going to drown her in a bathtub." And as you're getting her head to go in there,
her jaw hits the rim of the bathtub, she's going to break teeth. It's super common for
a murder victim to not have all of their teeth in their face. It's not something you hear
about a lot, because we, most people see the depiction of violence that they see, they're
not seeing it on real life, and if they're not seeking it out in gore videos, they see
what they see in Hollywood. So the fact that the head was missing teeth makes me think he
saw a real severed woman's head. And these people, we don't know what happened, we don't
know who the woman was, we don't know where they went, we don't know if these people were
ever caught, we don't know if they were locals, there's so many questions about the story,
but I do believe that head was real. If the story's real, if these details that Nate wrote
are real, I think that was a real head. If it's creepypasta, it's creepypasta, I apologize
for wasting your time. But it's a terrifying story, it's such a terrifying story, because
in the end, you know, when we, if we suffer a violent death, I think the most we want
is to be remembered and to be abenged. It's just such a tragic story, right? You can imagine
this young woman in the last moments of her life not wanting to die, obviously, fighting
for her life, that's why she would have lost her teeth in the first place. And then as
she's dying, praying that she gets some justice, praying that these men don't get away with
killing her. But when that light turned green, and that little boy sat there on that bus
too shy to say anything, they did get away with it. We don't know for how long, they
could have been arrested, like I said, they could have been arrested the next day, they
could still be out there. This could have been a one off murder that was committed over
drugs or jealousy or something like that, or these guys could have been budding serial
killers we don't know. And I'm not blaming Nate, right? He's in seventh grade, he's a
shy kid, I'm not blaming Nate, but it's just kind of a sad story and a creepy one at the
same time. Who was the girl, why was she killed, who were the men, are they still out there?
We'll never have any answers to any of those questions. All we can hope is that whatever
happened, even though we don't know who that young girl is, there's someone out there
who does remember her. That she didn't live her entire life just to be forgotten. Just
to become a story posted on the internet. Just to become a screaming head tucked under
some blankets in an old Ford pickup.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also go to us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio. TikTok is @DeadRabberRadio. DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to
it today. Have a great week guys.
Bye.