What do blind people see when they dream? And then we visit one of the last
uncontacted tribes in the world. Are the inhabitants of North Sentinel Island
actually guarding alien artifacts? Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too.
It's actually still Thanksgiving for me because I recorded these the day before.
For you, future listener, it's no longer Thanksgiving. It's still Thanksgiving
for me and I have right here, because I'm celebrating Thanksgiving, a
strawberry-ta. Strawberry-ta. It is sparkling margarita in a can. I actually
have had this before. It's pretty good and before anyone says that it's a girl
drink, I'll have you know it is 8% alcohol. That makes it 16 proof. That's not a
girl drink. I also, this isn't a sponsorship or anything. I'm just
celebrating Thanksgiving and then after I recorded this I'm gonna eat some
Thanksgiving dinner, some instant potatoes, and some stovetop stuffing. And I
got these little turkey TV, they're not even TV dinners. They're like complete,
but it's like eats is all capitalized. So that's it. I like having a
laid-back Thanksgiving. My family's all over the place, so I like just kind of
chilling. And I'm chilling with you guys. I'm chilling with you guys, so that's
totally cool too. And I hope you guys had a great Thanksgiving and if you're in
parts of the world that don't celebrate Thanksgiving, I hope you had a great
Thursday. So we're gonna go ahead and talk about a couple different things here.
First story we're gonna talk about is something of particular interest to me
and I think it's something that people have thought about and that's do blind
people. What do blind people dream of? I said on an earlier episode people who
wear glasses all the time in their dreams do they wear glasses? I've wondered
about that. Like in the dream are you wearing glasses on your face and if
your glasses aren't on your face in your dream or your dreams blurry? I wear glasses
off and on. Like I starting to wear them more as I get older but generally only
wear them if I'm gonna be doing a lot of reading. Most of the time I don't have
my glasses on. But I was wondering about how the blind people, how the blind
people, what blind people dream. Now I will say this to start this off, this will
probably get a lot of listeners to just drop the show but I used to hook up with
this blind chick a couple years ago and she kind of explained it to me. So she
had this or has this degenerative "I" thing and started when she was like a
teenager where her field of vision gets smaller and smaller and smaller and
smaller. She may eventually end up being completely blind or it may just stop.
I used to know the name of it but it's this thing. So she was
explaining it to me one night and she said this was so bizarre. So she goes
"my field of vision is very limited but my mind is still processing the visual
input as if I still had a normal field of vision. So we're over at my apartment.
In my apartment, my apartment's messy as is and there was something on the floor
like a wrapper or I don't know candy bar something. Not a candy bar but there was
something on the floor." And she said "you see that on the floor?" She goes "what I'm
seeing right now is she goes "you're just seeing like a little green box sitting on
the floor and then the rest of it is just the wood paneling, the wood floor." She
goes "when I look at it, I see the green box sitting on the floor and I see that
green box replicated a hundred times in every direction because her brain is
saying, since it only has this little field of vision, her brain is assuming
that that obstacle is everywhere." She goes "but if I look a couple feet over
where there is no obstacle on the floor, I'll just see wood paneling go on forever
and ever." So her brain is trying to process the limited information
that it has and so that's why she kind of has to focus. That's why she can't
drive. That's why she kind of has to focus when she's navigating. She had
the walking stick and everything like that but you know you would
talk to her, you wouldn't know that she was legally blind but she had to be very
careful. And because it was degenerative, it wasn't like it happened
overnight. Her brain has learned to cope with this loss of vision. And I
will say this too, it was super bizarre. She was super nice and incredibly hot.
She did all this stuff that I don't want to go into because then
people could probably identify her better but she just lived the life
normally and did all this stuff and she was she's amazing woman but anyways she
doesn't listen to podcasts though so I hold that against her. The point is is
that the brain will try to figure out how to cope with any obstacle that comes
in its way. And that's where we get into the idea of dreaming because what
dream what scientists feel dreams are is it is a way to do practice runs
especially nightmares. Nightmares science believes is a way to do practice runs of
tragic and traumatic events so when these things really do happen you're
prepared for it mentally. It's a theory but I think it's actually pretty good
theory. Now of course we have dreams about dragons and nightmares about like
stuff that'll never happen but it's still your brain just basically putting
itself in a traumatic state to prepare itself for something traumatic happening.
In the future it's a safety mechanism basically. So this is where we're going
to get into what do blind people dream about. I know that was a bit of a lead-up
but I think it's important because we're going to get into how the what my
friend's experience was with her waking vision you'll see kind of start to play
out in the dreams as well. So Danish researchers did a study. It's a very
small study. There's only 50 people. They had 11 blind people who were blind
from birth. 14 people who became blind after the age of I think it was one and
then 25 non-blind people or seeing people. They did they had to take surveys on
their dreams. They had to ask questions like did you see was it in color? Did you
taste smell, feel pain? What emotions did you have? What type of themes did the
stories have? Seeing people had at least one visual dream. Now this was I think a
six-week survey. So within the six weeks seeing people on average had at least one
visual dream usually more but at least one. The blind from birth had none. No
visual dreams which is to be expected. They've never seen anything. People who
became blind the older they got since they'd become blind the less likely they
would see something because their their brain now is working being like oh
there's no visual stimuli coming in so we don't have to produce visual stimuli
in the dreams. What's interesting and also they had across the board across the
three groups they had the same they were able to identify themes in their
dreams but one of the weirdest things was that when it came for nightmares blind
people had over tripled the amount of nightmares of the seeing people. 25% of
the blind people said they had a nightmare versus 7% of the seeing people
who said they had a nightmare and and when they were looking at that they said
this is kind of showing that the brain is going through basically practice runs
for reality because the blind people their nightmares were things that they
worry about things that are major obstacles for people who are blind
things like getting lost. Falling in manholes was a very common nightmare in
this group. I've never once worried about falling in a manhole. I've thought about
climbing into them and seeing what was down there but I've never thought like
oh no what if I'm walking on the street and I fall in a manhole that's not a
problem that I face. Getting hit by a car was a common one because I have to
deal with that. Losing their guide dog so I mean these are real threats that blind
people face and so their brain is doing those practices so if that happens if
they're out walking and their dog runs away goes chases a squirrel or whatever
their brain will know how to deal with a situation that immediate panic will
start to be quelled because basically this has already happened to them a
hundred times in their sleep but even though this is first time it's ever
happened in real life. So and then there's this quote I thought this was an
interesting quote from this one study. It said when a blind man is asked if he
dreams the answer is an immediate yes but if we ask him if he sees anything in
the dream the answer is always doubtful because he does not know what it is to
see. Even if there were images and colors in his brain during the dream how could
he recognize them. There is therefore no direct way through the dream reports to
evaluate the presence of a visual activation in the dream of congenitally
blind subjects. So it's weird they may actually see in their dream but they
don't people who are blind from birth could never explain it. Their dreams
could be full of visual stimuli but it they wouldn't never be able to explain
it to somebody and I think the story is interesting. I find it absolutely
fascinating because that's almost how we try to talk about like cosmic level
things or there's there's so much stuff in the world that we don't have the
language to explain not only to ourselves but to other people. I find that
fascinating. I find everything with the human brain fascinating because it's
not just like oh I'm blind but everything else is normal like their their brain
still is processing all that information and the brain if if they're
just if just their eyes are blind their brain is still able to receive visual
stimuli it's just not getting there. So what's that part of the brain doing? Is
it creating its own? How would you define a color to someone who's never
seen the color red? I find all that stuff fascinating. It's all philosophical
arguments at a certain point but these people are living that philosophical
argument. Absolutely fascinating. The next story we're going to cover is an odd one.
It's one that I saw pop up a couple times on the conspiracy iceberg. I figured
there's nothing to it. There's no resources behind it. A lot of people
requested it and I said I'll look into it. It wasn't something I was too thrilled
about and then I looked into it and I was like okay there's something here. So the
conspiracy theory is that the sentinels, the sentinels are guarding alien
artifacts so to get into it I'm gonna have to give you some background to who
the sentinels are. There is an island off the coast of India, the Andaman islands
and there's multiple islands there and there's there's a lot of tribes there.
I think there's like four or five tribes there that are throwbacks. Now out of
most of those tribes there are trade and contact with the Indian government and
they're like yeah we know you guys are like way back. You guys are still using
spears and stuff like that but we want to have regular contact with you. When the
people in those islands are like yeah okay you know that's fine you know
it's a it's beneficial to both sides. One India gets to contact the people you
know and then the people on the islands get food and supplies and stuff from
India. However one of the islands, North Sentinel Island has a tribe on there
called the Sentinelese. They are completely for the most part uncontacted
by the modern world. They know we exist and we know they exist but there's been
no formal contact between the two. There's been attempts but there's been no
like shaking hands, sending ambassadors, stuff like that. India has said this
island's off limits. They don't want to talk to us. They're a fully functioning
basically prehistoric society. They don't want to talk to us. There have been
attempts where people have gone there and two of the so two of the elders from
the Sentinelese came and met the sailors. They ended up getting diseases, the
Sentinelese, because they're such a throwback. It's the same thing
that when the Europeans came to America and so the government of India was like
okay we can't be messing with these people. Like they're fully functioning
tribe. We're only gonna make things worse. And they have tribes like this.
Brazil has a couple of tribes like this. South America overall has a couple
tribes like this. But the government actually says don't go near them let
them be. There was a time where some sailors came to the island and they
gave them like pigs and some toys and things like that. The Sentinelese came
out, killed the pig and buried. They'd never seen a pig before. They didn't know
what it was. They've only really lived on this island. Killed the pig, basically
ran people off of spears. There have been times where the Sentinelese will come out
and they'll look like they're going to accept the explorers and then they
chase them off of spears. They shoot arrows at them. So they're a very very
like closed off tribe. They don't want to get to know people on the mainland. So
this guy just a couple days ago felt that he was in his heart to go
preach Christianity to the Sentinelese. You're not supposed to go there.
It's completely illegal to go there. He hired some fishermen, said let me take me
to the Sentinelese islands. I'll talk about Jesus. They killed him. They just
lit him up full of arrows. And India in response arrested the fishermen. Because
India has said that they've killed other there a couple years ago. There was a
fishing boat that the two fishermen fell asleep in their boat and it drifted
too close to North Sentinel Island. They lit him up. The Sentinelese fired much
arrows, killed him. India said we consider that island to be a sovereign
state. You invaded their border. They have the right to do that. We're not going
to interfere with that island. So India really has their back. Now let's go into
a little bit more history of the Sentinelese and then we're going to get
into the conspiracy theory because this all wraps up together. Sentinelese they
believe they're about 40,000 years old. Not the people on the island but I mean
the civilization somewhere around there. They believe they traveled from Africa to
the island. I don't know how but somehow they got from Africa to this island. I
guess if you have 40,000 years you can kind of do anything. We don't know how
many of them are on the island. Estimates have ranged over time anywhere from 40
to 500. So sometimes there's peaks in the population, sometimes there's valleys
but we don't know because we've never been there. We can fly drones overhead, we
can sit on the beach, not on their beach because they'll kill us, but you can sit
in a boat, look at them from a distance. They don't know how to write. They don't
even know how to make fire. What we can tell is they wait for lightning to
strike and they keep the fire going for as long as they can. Very very primitive
people. There's a little bit of relation between, like I said, there's other
tribes on the other islands in that area. There's a little bit of relation of the
language between the Sentinelese and one other tribe but it's still such a
far gap. They can't communicate with each other. So they're basically cut off
even from their closest neighbor. We know that they, anything that washes up on
the island they use, we've seen them with metal but they don't know how to do
metal working. So when we see them with metal we go, "Oh they must be getting
debris that washes up on the island, making these spearheads, making whatever."
Dude, and you're thinking, Jason, you're reading a Wikipedia article about
North Sentinel Island on board. No, because this gets really good. Trust me,
I'm just have to set this stuff up because we're gonna go back to this stuff.
The idea, that's the setup. The idea that the Sentinelese are guarding alien
artifacts. Let's take a look at that. Now, of course, the planet's been around for
billions of years. If there were ever aliens moving through the, so let's
assume the aliens are the aliens coming from other planets, not
interdimensional things like that for the sake of the story. Aliens coming through
the galaxy and things like that. Over the course of four billion years, it's
possible that artifacts and ships, I mean you have such a long period of time,
things are dropped off on our planet and actually there have been some scientists
that to look for proof of alien life, they're not looking up into the sky
because that's such a small window of time. They want to look at the Earth and
Mars and Venus for energy signatures that they believe would be coming from
alien craft. And they said, well we know Venus is basically a big old hot swamp,
not a literal swamp, like I used to believe. I said this in our earlier
episode when I was a kid, I was taught that Venus had lush rainforest jungles
full of dinosaurs. And that's why I was so cloudy and I believed that until I was
about 15 and I would quote that all the time to people and no one was ever like
"you're an idiot, that's not true." And I always wondered why whenever people talked
about looking for a life on other planets, I'm like why are you worried about
microbes on Mars? There's dinosaurs on Venus and I literally would tell people
that and they would never question it. But anyway so there's no jungles on Venus.
Any alien craft that crashed on Venus would have been liquefied by now, you
know, given the time period of millions of years. But if an alien ship or an
alien satellite or alien artifact was crashed or left behind on Mars or Earth,
we should be able to detect some sort of energy signature from it. And that's one
of the things with the idea of an alien artifact being left on North Sentinel
Island. If it was just a piece of metal that had like, you know, alien
graffiti on it, that's very interesting but it doesn't really help. It would be
like yeah okay, an alien ship crashed here. But what people are looking for when we
talk about alien artifacts isn't necessarily just a hunk of metal. It
would be something that would be incontrovertible proof of alien technology.
Is it alien technology? A piece of metal is a piece of metal. And you go oh an
alien must have crashed here but a power source or a weapon or something like
that is what we would really want to find. Something that would change, not just
change our view of the universe and say yes there is living stuff out here, here's
a picture of an alien like you know a Betty Boop alien on the side of a ship
or you know like how they used to paint the World War II bombers. That would
just be proof there's aliens. We would want some sort of artifact that would
give us free energy or teach us the secrets of the universe or something
like that. And if those things existed on this planet we should pick up the
energy signature. We haven't on North Sentinel Island. So you're thinking well
Jason okay then I guess you are saying there's no alien artifacts on North
Sentinel Island. Then I say don't interrupt me. Not done. And I'll go back to
this. A little bit of pushback on detecting for alien signatures. It's
possible that there would be alien signatures in our solar system. We just
don't have the technology to decipher what it is. We don't know what it is. If
they're not using nuclear or chemical or something like that they may be using
some sort of power source or artifact that's undetectable. So a little bit of
pushback on that. I'm not so sold on the idea that if an alien artifact was here
we would detect it but we're giving it our best shot trying to detect these
things. I don't think there's alien technology on North Sentinel Island. I
don't believe the Sentinelese are protecting alien technology. This is
what I think. And I have I have some interesting I don't want to say evidence
but I have some interesting facts to support this. Let's say I was an alien
and I wanted to put something hide something on Earth that nobody would
find. You could say you would could put it on a place that was going to be
guarded by a bunch of prehistoric people that wouldn't know what it was. So
that you won't have to worry about them dealing with it. However here's the thing.
You wouldn't necessarily know when you put it there that somebody else a more
powerful government wasn't just going to show up and take it. You could say I'm
gonna put it here and these people around it will never know what it is. But
there's a always a chance that somebody else will just go in. If this tribe was
located anywhere else in the world at any other point in time they would have
just been taken over. Like all the other indigenous people on the planet. It's
just because this isn't a super strategic area where you know all of this
stuff started really coming out like the 1800s where they're like I just kind of
leave them alone. But if it was a more strategic area and if it was in the 1400s
when these people were discovered and all this stuff going on they would have
just been taken over. Nowadays there's enough land enough resources and stuff
like that that they don't have to deal with this island that has enough to
natural. So if you were an alien race and you wanted to hide something yes. Hiding
it among an indigenous population who don't know what it is is a good idea.
But if they had done this with a Navajo, it was just the Navajo God-seem world who
would have found this huge reactor. If it landed there accidentally, if an alien
didn't purposely put it there, if it landed there accidentally then the same
thing. Eventually the chances of somebody sumlin across it and if it landed
there accidentally it could have landed anywhere, it could have landed in New York
City, it could have landed in North Sentinel Island. In New York City they
wouldn't have known what it was, in North Sentinel Island they wouldn't have, but
then they're not necessarily guarding it. It's just a piece of wreckage that's
there and they're there as well. But what if the alien knew that no one was going
to go there? The alien knew for a fact that for hundreds of years no one was
ever going to go there, that group of people were going to be left alone by
the government of India. They knew for a fact that was going to happen. You would
put it there because you'd have the best of both worlds. You'd have a group of
people who would have no idea what it was. They'd probably stay away from it if it
was too creepy and you knew no one would go to discover it. You would actually be
able to say we know eventually they're going to discover it in the year like
2100 or 2055 or whatever, but we're gonna place this here now and we know if for
the next 500 years no one's going to mess with it because of all these policies
with India and the way that people are structured and all that stuff. Now of
course this... okay we're coming to the end here. Of course they would have no
way of predicting if India was going to go there tomorrow, 400 years ago, or 300
years in the future. Aliens wouldn't know that, but time travelers would. They're
not guarding alien artifacts on North Sentinel Island. They're guarding a
time machine. Hear me out. And let me back up here. If this conspiracy is true,
I'm not saying that it's true, but let's assume that they are guarding something.
For the sake of the narrative, they're guarding a time machine because in the
future they would know for a fact how history would play out. They would know
that they would try to make contact with the tribe. The tribe wouldn't want it.
The government of India would step in and say nobody contact this tribe. People
from the future would know how even... and they would know for a fact in the year 2049
eventually someone does go to the island and that's when we move to time machine.
But for now we're gonna put it here. It's perfect location because it is
completely isolated. It's an island that you cannot get to. You will be arrested
if you go to and you survive. If you die, you die. But it's close enough to the
mainland that you can leave the island and get to the mainland. Sri Lanka, India,
wherever you want to go. It's possible that the people, the North Sentinelese,
were brought from the past by the time travelers, bring them from the past in
Africa and put them on the island. That's why the language doesn't match up.
They're there to guard the time machine. They said we're gonna go back to Africa.
We're gonna get this tribe of people. We're gonna put them on this island. We'll
take care of them. We'll give them the metal they need. Maybe make a lightning
strike every once in a while to give them fire. We'll watch over them because
they're going to protect this time machine that will give us access to come
and go as we please. Where we're completely concealed, we're close enough to
the mainland. And you go, okay Jason, interesting theory. But do you have any
proof? I'll say this. I have more proof of that theory than of alien artifacts. And
this is why. In 2004, the Indian Ocean earthquake, the Boxing Day earthquake,
massive earthquake, huge tsunami, hundreds of thousands of people killed.
Just devastated the coastlines of that area. North Sentinel Island, the
earthquake was so powerful it lifted it up three to seven feet in some areas.
Just completely crumpled the ground underneath it. Massive tsunami, hit
North Sentinel Island, hit the rest of the Andaman Islands. As the world was
starting to put everything back together after the tsunami, officials in India
said they're all dead. The Sentinelese are all dead. The other tribes on those
islands are all dead. That tsunami wiped out all the coastlines in this area.
Those islands had no chance. Let's get a helicopter and fly overhead and confirm
what we already know. Helicopter flies overhead. They see a villager come out,
shake his spear angrily at the helicopter. Helicopter goes, well at least
there's one of them. None of them died. None of them. As far as we can tell, they
just went on as normal. This massive tsunami and earthquake that devastated
the lives of millions of people and took the lives of hundreds of thousands of
people, didn't even scratch a population between 40 and 500. The official line is
that there, because they're such a primitive society, they're used to
being a tune to nature and they could tell the animals were acting weird. They
could tell the birds were acting weird and all this stuff. They found high
ground. The other tribes in the area also found high ground because they didn't
suffer massive casualties. So they knew it was coming in a way. They used their
nature-based instincts for being so close to the earth they knew something was
coming. I have another theory. They were warned from the future. Get to higher
ground. Their God spoke to them. And the time tribe, people from the future, not
only would they know that was going to happen, they would warn the people on
the other islands as well because it would look weird if only the sentinels
survived the tsunami and all the other tribes are wiped out. You just go to the
other tribes and say, "Hey, get to high ground. Make sure you're at high ground
before such and such time tomorrow. Disguise yourself as a villager." They
wouldn't know. Make it as some sort of miracle or maybe the leaders of the
other tribes are from the future. But for whatever reason, they were warned
whether it was their own natural instinct or a message from somebody who
knew what was going to happen. They suffered. As far as we can tell, no
casualties. Their society definitely continues. And its higher coastlines, like
I said, were destroyed. You can watch the YouTube footage of the tsunami and
imagine a prehistoric village surviving that. Is it possible that there is a
time machine on North Sentinel Island? When I started looking at the theory
that the sentinels were guarding alien artifacts, like I said, I figured there
wasn't anything there. But what I found is far more interesting than why I could
have thought of originally. I have no proof of any of this, just facts that can
be put together in any way because that's one of the problems with facts.
But I will say this, if I had a time machine, I would put it someplace that I
knew not only no one would ever go to, but the people there would have no idea
what it was. And North Sentinel Island is the perfect place in the modern world
for a time machine from the future.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabbitradio. Twitter is @jasonocarpenter.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You
don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm so glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend and I will see you again Monday.