When a man tries to become immortal, he finds out the price is too small to pay.
And then we continue Insanity Week here on Dead Rabbit Radio, which is oddly different
than the normal weeks, this week's even crazier.
Because today we're going to take a look at a man who believes that he's been abducted
by reptilians multiple times.
His mission?
Train them to be the best cops ever.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garbender and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having a lot of fun.
Insanity Week, that's the theme this week.
Bunch of crazy people.
I sent an intro more crazy than we normally covered.
If you can believe that, first off, coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now, we see
a mama bird flying in.
You didn't notice?
You didn't notice there's a little nest of baby birds on the floor?
The mama bird is throwing up our newest Patreon support.
Everyone is in fear that this time of saying their name.
It's Odie.
Everyone give a round of applause to Odie as Odie is falling into the mouths of several
hungry baby birds.
Sorry, Odie.
That's the only thing I can think of.
After Odie is digested and comes back to life and is now a normal sized person, Odie, you're
going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or if you're not regurgitated bird food, that is
fine too.
Just helps read the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
Odie, I'm going to go into Odie so mad.
I would sit there with her arms crossed like, "Listen man, I was trying really hard to come
up with something."
Odie, and that's when I came up with Odie.
Let's toss you the oars to the Dead Rabbit Robot.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed out to Indonesia for the rest of this episode.
Odie has a bunch of baby birds.
They've bonded to them.
But that's cool.
Now you got a bunch of little pets.
Maybe they'll come in handy later on.
We're rowing the boat.
We're headed out to Indonesia.
Splash.
Specifically, we're going to Pantai Celoton.
That's in Java, Indonesia.
The year is 1972 and we wash up on shore.
We get there just in time to see Hindra Hartonto come out of a cave.
He's walking out and he's like, "Ugh, stretching."
He probably should have found a taller cave to meditate in.
That one was kind of tight, but it all paid off.
And then he's holding in his hand these four figures.
He takes them to town.
There are these humanoids.
Little arms, little legs, scary-looking faces, long black hair.
He brings them to town.
People are like, "Dude, what are those things?
Are those dolls?"
And he's like, "What?
Okay, listen.
I know that they look like dolls."
Don't touch them.
I know they look like dolls and they look like if you touched them, they would feel like
dolls.
And basically, they're very doll-like, right?
But they're not dolls.
These are actually jenglots.
Everyone takes a step back.
But to you and me, I'm assuming you're not from Indonesia if you are.
Thank you.
I'm talking about your hometown.
But most people, jenglots, when I was doing this research on the story, I go, "Oh, it's
just the name that he named these things."
Jenglots actually in Javanese means vampire.
So even though it's just another word of a cryptid or a creature to 99% of the planet,
to the people of Java, they knew exactly what these things were.
They were little vampires.
But they never had seen them.
And they especially think they were going to be 9 inches tall, right?
Dracula's not really threatening if he's tiny.
But he goes, "Listen, I was meditating in this cave and I was able to manifest these
jenglots."
And they go, "Why do you call them vampires?"
And he goes, "Well, dummy.
I mean, why else would you call them vampires, you dolt?
I have to feed them blood."
And everyone takes another step back.
He goes, "But don't worry.
I only get my blood from verified sources."
The articles did not go into detail what he considered a verified source.
We do know that he fed them his own blood, but he also got his blood from verified sources
as well.
People who had blue checkmarks on Twitter, he said that he had to feed them human blood
every 35 days.
Now he puts them on display.
He charges money, of course, to see these things.
People walk up, look through the glass boxes, and you see these little guys.
And I'm reading about these jenglots.
I've actually wanted to cover these for a while, because what I read and what turned
out to be true is two totally different things, which happens in the world of the paranormal.
So I'm reading this, the original account I read, that these things were alive, they
moved around, and they drank blood.
And then as I did more research on these things, those things are true.
They drank blood.
But remember we did that story recently about the people who were pouring milk into the
mouths of statues of the Hindu statues, I think it was?
And I was like, oh, that's amazing.
Imagine if you could see a statue drink milk.
That'd be totally dope.
I would totally become a fan of statues right now.
I'm okay on them, whatever.
But if they drank milk, I'd buy some of them.
I'd be stealing David, and I have him in my bedroom.
Not my bedroom.
Forget I said that.
I'd be having him in the living room.
Be having him drink milk.
But my point is, is that they just stand there and they take the, it turned out the
statues weren't really drinking the milk.
They would just put the milk by the statues and they would spill it on the statues.
It was kind of a rip off.
This one too, they would take a plate of human blood and just set it by the jangleots.
They didn't actually go, thank you sir, and start like slurping it up.
Because my immediate thing was, here's the thing, at the end of the day, even though
I dismiss a lot of this stuff and I demuncle a lot of this stuff, I do want to believe it.
So when I found out that there was nine inch tall vampires, I started looking for videos
of them drinking blood.
I was like, surely there must have been someone who recorded this stuff.
Of course not.
Of course not, Jason.
Because they don't exist.
There's so much things in nine inch tall.
I actually tried looking on YouTube for a video of a nine inch tall vampire in 1972
drinking blood.
It doesn't exist.
So here's what it is.
They would take a plate of blood, set it next to the statue.
That spoiler alert was not really a vampire.
It turned out that, so let me tell the story, let me retract that spoiler alert.
What was going on?
You just charged them money for this in 1972?
By the time 1997 rolled around, a bunch of other psychics also started manifesting these
jangleots.
They would go, I went to a cave and I was meditating and look at these guys.
Oh no, you can't look at them unless you give me some money.
They started having all these psychics come forward and say that they were able to manifest
these little vampires.
And that's when, the ones in 1972 apparently are still around, but in 1997 it's late enough
that people could start doing what's called scientific tests on them.
And people have really said these things.
Up until the year 2006, they were doing DNA scans, X-rays on these, and it turned out shocker
that these things were fake.
They had nails, they could, through X-rays, tell nails we're connecting the arms to the
torso that the hair was actually from a human.
And it looked like they were all pulled from the same human.
Which wouldn't make sense, right?
You want to go like, I need 100 hairs for this doll.
I must contact 100 people.
The articles I read said a lot of them had been exposed, but since not everyone had actually
been tested, you couldn't say verifiably that every single jangleot was a fake.
True, I mean I guess you can't say that, but I think you can assume that if you test something
and 99% of them turned out to be fake, or even 90% of them turned out to be hoaxes,
you could assume the other 10% most likely are as well.
And if you couldn't test them, you would think, well they don't want me to test them, because
it's probably a hoax as well.
So despite the fact that I was typing into YouTube, 9-inch vampire drinking blood wasn't
finding any footage of these jangleots, there is still some interesting things to talk about.
And the lore of these things, when Hendra came out of the cave they were 9 inches tall, but
as time went on they were only 4 inches tall, and he explained that.
He explained that these creatures as they get older, they shrink.
And he also said these creatures, these jangleots, are actually thousands of years old.
So I don't know why they just shrink super slowly, and then in a couple years went from
9 inches to 4 inches, but the lore behind these things, other than them shrinking, is this.
He believes that he was able to manifest the energy of a white monkey, which is a real
monkey species, the spirit of the white monkeys, that's what these were.
Jangleots in general lore, outside of these little tiny statues, are, like I said, a vampire,
you can become a jangleot by abstaining from all sexual pleasure and meditating in a cave.
It's the search for immortality, it's keeping all that sexual energy for yourself actually
will make you immortal.
I would say this, if someone said Jason, if you never have sexual thoughts again, if
you never do anything sexual again, you can be immortal, I would take that, I would be
like okay.
But then if they go, oh, you're gonna be immortal but you shrink constantly, I wouldn't want
to do that, like if I was immortal and I was like 5 foot or 4 foot or even 3 foot I'd be
totally fine with that.
But if I was, there's some 2 foot tall listener and there's some kid being like oh man, no
if I was even, there's like, there's, one foot tall person is fine, but 9 inches, 9 inches,
I don't want to be the size of a fetus forever and you shrink.
That's the worst deal ever.
That's the worst, I'd rather be like one of those weirdos from Vampire the Masquerade
that hangs out in the sewer all the time, like the Nosferatu ones or the Malkavians
even, the super edgy, I hated Malkavians.
I used to do live action roleplay, I don't think I've ever revealed this before on the
show, I used to do live action roleplay, Vampire the Masquerade.
This was pre-internet, so we had no idea that edgy internet kids were a thing, we just
thought it was the edgy people in our town and you knew who they were, because they were
Malkavians and they were crazy and they were always in character.
I got knives and I'm dancing around, oh shut up, Malkavians, I just lost 3 Malkavian listeners.
It was basically Heath Ledger's The Joker, but that was their roleplaying class, it was
so, oh my god, but anyways, that was Ventrue of course.
How are you going to drink blood?
You don't even get to drink blood, they don't even take a YouTube video of me drinking
blood.
I just live super long and I keep shrinking and I look dried up and eventually I have
nails driven into my arms and my hair can be sent to DNA tests.
No dice, I'm not taking that trade off.
Odie, I look at Odie, there's some vultures circling overhead, he's like "get us out
of here, Odie, we're gonna- oh actually no, Odie, those vultures are still gonna circle
over you, I got one more thing to say about these jangleots, this is interesting.
He claimed they were the spirit of a white monkey.
The jangleots in normal lore are monks who go into caves who have not done anything sexual
and they become immortal.
Another side thing to this is that in Java they have a lot of UFO sightings, but like
in the Middle East they don't really talk about them.
It's just not something that's considered part of normal discourse.
We had an episode on that recently, how come we don't see a lot of UFO stuff coming out
of the Middle East?
It's not something in Java, but when they do talk about them, the aliens are only 3-9
inches tall.
So is it possible that some of these are fake to make money, but some of them, at least
one set of them, maybe the original set, are the mummified remains of crashed alien survivors?
That's another weird footnote in the story of the jangleots.
Odie, now we're going to touch the keys to the carbonicopter, fight those vultures off,
we're going to leave behind Java, we are headed out to New Orleans, Louisiana.
In New Orleans, let me back up before I even get three words into this.
This is what this guy is saying.
I don't know if this man is actually a police officer, so New Orleans Police Department,
please don't sue me and go "this guy never worked for us, quit saying fake stuff."
He says he did.
Your honor?
If a judge is listening to this podcast, just go "not guilty" and then I don't have
to worry about it.
In New Orleans, there's a man, not a man, a legend known as Matt R. He doesn't give us
a last name, we have his last initial, but we don't need a full last name to recognize
this man's bravery.
He claims to be a former New Orleans Police Department officer, more importantly than
that.
He's blowing the lid off of everything, dude.
If you have a lid on something right now, go look, it's gone.
He's blowing the lid off everything, especially the reptilian conspiracy.
He's been seeing them since the year 2005.
One day, he heard a tree smash in his neighbor's backyard.
From the same time he said he saw a bright light come from the sky now.
Not lightning, not lightning, mind you.
Bright light in the sky, tree explodes.
He knows what this is, it's not lightning.
It was a reptilian, because that's what reptilians are known for.
Remember, like Queen Elizabeth might be a reptilian, remember when she smashed all those
trees?
Because she's a reptilian, that's what reptilians do.
He runs out into the yard, he runs out into his neighbor's yard, he does this constantly
through this story, he's going into other people's property.
They're OPP.
He runs out there and he is trying to figure out where the reptilian's at.
That's what you would think, bright light in the sky, tree gets obliterated, reptilian.
He can't find them.
So then he starts doing this thing where he goes into the forest around his house.
I guess him and his neighbor live near the forest.
He goes into the forest and he says he spends hours a day asking the reptilian's questions.
This is what you want your law enforcement officer to be doing on their off time, right?
This is what you want them to be doing.
You don't want them to be like brushing up on like, you know, like how to discharge a
firearm safely or, you know, not even doing cost stuff, just reading a book.
He's standing in a forest with a notepad asking reptilian's questions and they're not answering
him.
The gall of them, right?
The gall of these imaginary beings in the forest not answering him.
Man, people today.
Let's see.
He knows that these are reptilians because his buddy's phone, not his phone, right?
He's asking the reptilian's questions and the reptilians get mad at him.
So his buddy starts sending him sexually explicit messages and he goes, I'm not doing this.
I actually didn't do this.
So Matt goes, Oh, must be the reptilians.
And I'm assuming the buddy goes, Yeah, I should have signed the reptilians.
He actually bought it that I didn't actually send those messages.
Of course not.
It must have been the reptilians.
So that's all you need, right?
Your buddy, your buddy confessing their love to you via text and then saying that it's
not them and must be reptilians.
But this, I'm dismissing him.
I don't know why I'm dismissing him.
He has proof.
He turns his face.
He turns his face to us and he looks and he goes, you see this wound?
You see this wound I have, Jason?
And it looks like he has just a thin scratch.
It looks like, you know how sometimes you're like, wake up, you'll have a scratch on your
face.
You're like, Jason, I never wake up scratch on my faces.
You might want to check out your house for Jangleots.
You guys have woken up with scratches on your faces.
He has a long thin scratch on his face.
He goes, you see this, you see this thing that Jason wakes up with all the time.
You probably should check for bed bugs.
You might be hitting his face in the middle of the night.
But no, this one, this hideous scar, don't look at me.
Don't look at me.
I'm hideous.
This thin cut you can barely see that'll heal.
That'll heal in the next six hours.
Was caused by a reptilian.
He tells us his story.
He goes, laugh all you want at my hideous deformity.
Don't look.
But I was thrown in a shipping container once.
We laughed at that.
That's actually kind of funny.
I don't know why the image of this guy just getting snatched off the street, thrown in
a shipping container.
He was thrown in a shipping container full of humans and reptilians and there was a door
in the shipping container and every show often it would open up and someone would be pulled
out of the shipping container.
He goes, I don't know how I knew.
It might have been the fact that everyone was violently trying to get away from the
door.
All I knew is I didn't want to go through that door.
So in the darkness he was just punching people and getting punched and he felt a reptilian
claw gouge into a skin.
One whole millimeter.
Razor talons that were evolved on another planet to fight for survival.
These seven foot tall reptilian creatures bred for war.
A single cut.
It's as deep as a paper cut.
He goes, I never got thrown outside that door.
I fought my way in that dark shipping container all that I could.
And he goes, this is the reason why.
He goes, I think this is why battle royale games are so popular nowadays.
It's preparing us.
It's preparing us homo sapiens to be thrown in shipping containers someday.
So interesting story, right?
Interesting story.
It would be terrifying to be thrown in a shipping container with a bunch of cuddly gerbils.
Let alone a bunch of humans and razor clawed reptilians.
How did he get out of the shipping container though?
It's a rhetorical question.
He never answers that.
We've talked about this in other stories.
These people who are exposing the truth that are exposing these government secrets, these
high level conspiracies, how are they able to tell us this stuff?
It's one thing when you have someone like Gary Webb, a real life journalist who exposed
that the CIA was complicit in the crack epidemic in Los Angeles to fund the war with the Contras
in South America, I think was Central America.
He was eventually ostracized from his profession as a journalist.
He was fired and he eventually quote unquote killed himself in Sacramento with two shots
to the back of the head with a handgun.
Now you actually can kill yourself with two shots to the back of the head with a handgun.
That does happen.
It happens more often than you would think.
There's been questions about did he kill himself because he had no money and that his career
was in the toilet?
He was a hero for telling the truth or was he assassinated by the CIA?
So we have stories like that where someone exposes a high level conspiracy and mysteriously
dies.
But this guy who arguably the fact that there are reptilians on the planet is a higher level
conspiracy than the CIA is selling crack cocaine.
Is flying all of this stuff over to LA.
How is this guy still alive?
And that's always the question I come to with this stuff because they could easily shut
this dude down.
Just don't open the container.
Just leave him in the shipping container.
Why did they let him out?
But he doesn't even reveal how he gets out of the shipping container.
Or does he?
Let's keep talking here for a second because that's what a podcast is.
It's me talking.
The reptilians have actually been experimenting on him.
They've actually made his eyes so sensitive to the light that he can't sleep with an alarm
clock in the room.
He says the light from the alarm clock is so bright he can't sleep his reptilian eyes.
Now there's no photos of his reptilian eyes.
He doesn't actually have like little slits.
This to show the mindset of a man like let's imagine you.
Let's imagine that you have been abducted by reptilians and your eyeballs have been
operated on.
And for whatever reason they let you exist.
They let you go home to take an out.
Your alarm clock is too bright.
Do you A. Buy an alarm clock that's less bright or buy an alarm clock that's like an analog
clock that doesn't have any lights.
Do you B. Turn the alarm clock so it's facing the wall so you don't see the light.
The alarm clock serves one purpose.
To have an alarm.
Or so it doesn't matter.
If you need to see the time you just turn and look at it and go oh it's 1103 and then
you turn it back.
Or do you or do you do what Matt did.
Those would have been the two most logical things.
Matt got up out of bed.
He can't sleep because the lights do bright.
He gets him out of bed.
He gets a blue Tupperware bowl or a blue Tupperware plate cuts it up and then glues it to the
alarm clock so he can't see the time.
Now if you're like I wonder what time it is you're all slowly peeling stuff it's all
glued together you're like oh it's blurt o'clock.
You can't even see anything.
That's the mindset that we're dealing with and what's so weird when I read stuff like
this is I'm reading it and thinking this guy's a lunatic.
There are other people reading it and being like that poor man if those reptilians would
just leave him alone he would have a working alarm clock and a blue Tupperware bowl but
he has neither now.
Who reads this and takes it seriously.
But what we're really talking about here is the reptilians relationship with the police
department.
So we're going back in time.
I jumped ahead to 2018 where he was throwing in the cargo container but let's jump back
to 2005 when he first started encountering these reptilians.
2005 was also the timing of a major event Hurricane Katrina.
Hurricane Katrina hits a couple thousand people died it was a horrible tragedy and then the
aftermath some people called them looters some people said they were just trying to survive
but the reptilians didn't care either way.
All that footage of police officers watching over people breaking into the local Winn Dixie
that was actually footage of people breaking into Winn Dixie but then they would cut to
a picture of a cop just standing there shaking his head that was a reptilian.
Did you guys know that?
No?
You didn't know that?
That was a fact?
You see Hurricane Katrina was actually the very first policing action of reptilians on
planet earth and Matt R. helped train them.
Like I said Matt R. at this time was a member of the New Orleans police department and he
said that what happened was apparently before Hurricane Katrina happened he was abducted
and put in an underground shopping mall.
It was more like a shopping mall set like he could tell that it wasn't a real shopping
mall it was almost like a testing ground and he realizes as he's there he's in his police
uniform there's a couple other people in police uniforms but he doesn't have any insignia
he doesn't have any badge or anything it's just a black uniform and he sees a bunch of
other civilians in there they're not wearing uniforms and then all of a sudden the walls
blow open that's how he knows they're underground the walls blow open and reptilians pouring
through these walls and they're carrying laser guns and they're shooting at the people.
The people are panicking they're running every which way and Matt and his fellow officers
are trying to maintain order but as these laser blasts are flying towards them there's
just utter panic and that's when Matt realizes something the reptilians aren't shooting the
people.
They're shooting around the people they're shooting like the signs they're shooting out
the windows they're shooting at potted plants it's like they're trying to herd the people
to go into a certain direction they don't want to kill them they just want them to move
and Matt realizes in this moment he goes this is probably where the legends of the fire
breathing dragon comes from because you're looking at the seven foot tall eight foot nine
foot tall reptilians and these heat rays are coming out he goes you couldn't actually see
like the red laser beam you could just see how the air would get wavy and then something
would explode or something would catch on fire.
He said eventually the reptilians all pushed them back to this big stage and him and his
fellow officers got up on the stage and the people were crowded down below it the reptilians
were cornering them in and then the exercise stopped as they're standing up there one of
these reptilians comes up on stage and walks right up to Matt and goes great job great job
in fact turns to the other police officers Matt R is the best cop among you in fact
I've served on planets I've met alien commanders all over the galaxy but Matt R I respect you
more than even my own commanders so Matt R at this moment realized that this was a training
exercise this is where he's kind of putting it together the reptilians were trying to figure
out a way to do crowd control on humans without injuring them he also realized that he was
part of that he was actually going to be training them to be better peace officers he was going
to train them to help protect humanity in their own weird reptilian way and after telling
this long story and after me reading this long story that he posted online I get to the
line of the very ending that's where my dream ends so now I'm rethinking whether or not
he was actually thrown in the shipping container was that a dream as well so basically he had
a dream he had a dream that reptilians the whole thing I'm not even going to take him
to fight him with retelling it and then he wakes up and at some point he notices he has
a pea sized lump on his penis and it goes away and then it comes back not all at once it's
not like blinking and out of existence one day but over time it's disappeared and reappeared
and in the article he's almost he's almost pleading he's written several articles for
this website called phantom and monsters in the article he's been like it's an article
right it's not a forum post it's not an ask me anything it's an article he's basically
like as he talks about the lump in his penis it's almost like he's asking is this okay
should I get this checked out I can't answer that first off yes yes you should but I'm
not I can't send you an email I'm not going to put in the comments dude get your penis
checked out that's the most important part if you have a pea sized lump in your penis
that comes and goes go to the doctor an earth doctor don't have a dream and have some reptilian
do you probably think it's a microchip honestly that's a big old microchip if it's the size
of a pea so what is it what's the end game with this what's the end game with this he
believes that this dream was real he says if he eats tuna or sardines or non processed
meat he doesn't have to cover up his alarm clock too late you can't really fix that
he believes that his buddy was also abducted because of his buddy goes to the Kroger supermarket
in the checkout lines his knee gets scanned because there's a microchip in his knee and
it shows up as a price was the price like leg of you like anyways he just has all these
weird anecdotes but we're really building up to this thing he believes that the reptilians
have one purpose coming to earth they want to be police officers they want to be that's
all that's all that's all they're in game and you go Jason that would make sense you
would need police officers like if you're gonna have a new global order you need a new global
police yes yeah the rational person we can have that conversation right if you wanted
to start a new global society earthbound or intergalactic you would need to have a global
police force you'd have to enforce the laws he says that these reptilians have one purpose
to stop looters when they look at all the combined violence throughout human history
all the wars all the sieges all the disasters everything they hate looters more than anything
because they look at the property damage there are billions on renticular nine are watching
us through their view screens and they're like oh no another window broken in Portland
send down the battle fleet that's their only goal is to stop looting here's a quote from
one of these articles they will not give warning before they strike no hovering ships why because
this would cause the exact type of panic looting that they are trying to prevent so basically
the reason why we'll never get disclosure with ships is because if you see an alien craft
overhead you're gonna want to break a window and they're here to save the windows so they
won't they'll just one day will turn around there'll be an alien standing there and he'll
just be you go to punch a window he'll be shaking his finger with that little claw you
don't want a paper cut on your face he believes that's their only goal not interbreeding with
humans not taking over the well they want to take over the planet they just want to save
the windows they don't want any looting whatsoever and this all came to a head when last summer
in the we had him in Portland and they also had him in Washington DC we started having
federal police officers not wearing any badges any name tags no identifying information and
they were scooping people off the streets and that's when Matt or started putting two and
two together that was the first strike force of the reptilians it's begun ladies and gentlemen
they're already here the training that he did in 2005 with the reptilians it's been put
into effect when you see those men and women with no badges their reptilians that's why
they don't have badges because he says this of a reptilian but no no what you're thinking
Jason I saw footage of those guys I saw photographs they weren't eight foot tall reptilians they
were normal sized humans okay just forget that part just forget that part he doesn't
explain that either but he says listen a reptilian if he came down from Cyrus nine comes down
in his battle fleet doesn't hover over a city because otherwise people start breaking windows
sneaks in through the back and then walks in gets a job at a police department is now
now standing eight foot tall reptilian but somehow he just looks like a normal guy he
wouldn't be able to wear a local police badge because imagine the horror imagine if he was
wearing a Portland police department badge on him and he goes to stop a looter and he
doesn't realize there's a difference in gravity between our planet and his planet and he picks
a looter and throws him like eight blocks eight city blocks smashing into some building
in downtown everyone's going to be like who who is the officer who was the officer who
broke the laws of gravity and it would turn out that it was this guy and then it would
be exposed and they wouldn't let him wear like a like a holographic reptilian space
badge because then everyone knows a reptilian so the only other thing you could do he specifically
states for liability reasons reptilians cannot wear local police badges again it's an alien
invasion I don't think they're worried about getting sued I don't think they're going to
be like dude our plan is going to go off without a hitch unless one person sues us and then
it's all over they can't wear the badges so all of these federal police officers that
we saw last summer were actually reptilians according to Matt Art though it's it's the
end now it's too late we can't fight against this it's the window industrial complex we
love windows as a society we put little windows on our eyes and call them glasses we drink
out of cups that we can look through and call them glasses we even have fairy tales about
shoes made of glass and then windows window the eyes are the window to the soul that's
the only thing I can think of with windows but we think about it we love comedies we
love like window washers like almost falling off to their deaths we love mirrors windows
are windows that didn't quite make the cut so they only are halfway well our world is
surrounded by glass and windows and we have skyscrapers with tons of these beautiful things
that we look out we see the sunrise and the sunset we've surrounded ourselves with the
only thing aliens care about protecting and it's too late to stop them now so the next
time you're driving down the road and you see that flashing red and blue lights behind
you don't stop don't hit the gas pedal like keep going bro keep going because for all
you know that car is going to pull up to you you're going to you're going to legally do
your duty as a citizen what you should do and you're going to pull over to the side
of the road and the cops going to pull over next to you and then he gets out and you're
like that's weird you look in your mirror and says his objects are closer than they
appear but you can only see the officers crotch coming towards you and you're like okay that's
super bizarre that's only something Jason would say and you turn and the officer is
eight feet tall and he has to lean down to look into your car with his reptilian eyes
you have to cover up you have to cover up your car stereo the lights do right he looks
at you and he goes he has that's why the cops wear those sunglasses to cover up their reptilian
eyes he goes do you know how fast you were going you're like what what you make that
last word weird cut and then he goes ah you want to give me lip and that's when you feel
reptilian claws reach and reach into your mouth and pull your lips off and he goes now I got
your lips apparently they're also from the leprechaun movies apparently they're also
a horror movie villain and he eats them and then you're laying in your car with no lips
and the reptilians calling in for backup more reptilian cops are going to show up and just
then you think that things couldn't get any worse you turn there's a little jangle on
sitting sit in your passenger seat and he's just sitting there and as you're bleeding
all over yourself the jangle lots just sitting next to you and you can feel him absorbing
your blood and then the blood was super realistic and it was coming out of your eyeballs I have
no other way to end this episode I have no other way to end this episode I'm sorry guys
I'm gonna tell you right now insanity week has pushed me to the verge just having to
delve into all this stuff just having to I feel like I'm breaking this might be the last
week of dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be your email address
you can also hit us up at facebook.com/where we did a radio gmail.com is going to be your
email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is our twitter
account dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true grand podcast you don't have
to listen to it every day I'm glad you listen to us today have a great one guys
you
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]