Today, we take a look at two terrifying households.
First off, we travel to France to meet a woman who swears that the only way to enter her
house is to walk on your hands.
And then we travel to South Dakota to meet a young man who's moving into his new apartment.
He quickly realizes that not only is he not alone in his new abode, this creature is not
alone.
This creature may have sinister implications for us all.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you have some cool plans for this weekend coming up.
First off, let's give a shout out to one of our legacy Patreon supporters coming into
Dead Rabbit Command right now is Devin.
Woohoo!
Come on in buddy, come on in.
Devin, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
Just help spread the word about the show that really, really helps out a lot.
I say it every episode, cause it's true.
You can really help the show grow.
Devin aka fellow content creator.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed all the way out to Old Timie, France.
As Devin is driving us out to Old Timie, France, we're headed back to the early 1900s.
I do want to say, next week is the last week of season 17.
So next week, we're gonna have five episodes and then I'm taking a two week break.
I'm not gonna do the bonus episodes this week.
I gotta start those up again.
I always talk about them.
But that's just ten more episodes of work and it's really hard to do the show.
It is a solo podcast.
I don't have anyone else helping me, except when you guys help me financially support
the show and get the word out.
I don't want to minimize that, but the production of the show is just me and I get burned out
and everything like that.
And I feel bad I even take two weeks off.
But I gotta take two weeks off every 50 episodes, that seems fair.
So there will be no bonus episodes.
It'll be two weeks of just Dead Silence on the Dead Rabbit Radio channel.
But we will be back for season 18.
And another 50 episodes of crazy, bizarre, macabre stories.
Like these ones.
These ones are really cool and I'm glad I was able to present these two as a pair.
Because I got an interesting hypothesis with this one.
So Devon's driving the old timey Jason Jalopy.
We're wearing old timey clothes.
We got on like the girdles and the big old petticoats and tiny little umbrellas.
We are walking around Roux de Montréal.
That's in the Saint Margarita district in Paris, France.
So we're walking around and we look dapper.
And we're going to court.
We're going to court.
We stole all these clothes from some old lady.
We're running down the street and we end up in court.
And as we're handcuffed sitting in the back of the courtroom, in walks Madame Burlody.
I'm almost for sure that's not a he-pronouncer name.
If my last name was Blody, I would definitely change it.
I don't care if my dad was very proud.
The Blodies helped build this country.
Madame Blody.
She's an elderly woman.
She walks into the local magistrates office.
I don't know if that's the same thing as the court, but anyways, just roll with it.
Just roll with it like you're a big bloaty old lady.
She walks into the local magistrates office and she says, "Listen, you need to help me,
sir.
I am just a simple old woman living at home with my son and my brother.
And it's fine.
Like everything's going good there, right?
But one thing that's super weird.
Every time I walk to my house, put the key in the door, click, click, clink, clink, clink,
and they open the door.
Eeeeeee.
She's making the sound effects to the magistrates.
Like, I know what a door.
I know what you're doing.
You're not doing some sort of audio podcast.
She opens the door.
Eeeee.
And then me, this old lady, I have to get down on my hands and knees, do a handstand,
and hand walk into my house.
And then I get back on my feet and I go about my business.
And the magistrate is looking at this lady and thinking, "She must be seeing me."
And she must be super limber if she can walk on her hands.
And he goes, "Wait, wait, wait.
So you're saying that they make you do that?
Your son and your brothers?"
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, maybe it wasn't that.
Well, no, dude, we clearly saw something.
I don't know, maybe we were just tired.
It's weird how the human mind doesn't want to believe in this stuff,
because it's creepy, right?
Our brains have governors built into them,
so we don't see everything that we see.
And the things we do see that we're not supposed to see,
we will discard them.
It's very, very interesting.
I've seen that happen to with friends of mine,
and it may have even happened to me.
I wouldn't know, obviously, right?
If my brain goes, "Ah, I was probably just made up,"
and then I stopped remembering it.
But yeah, it's super weird.
I've been on Ghost Hunts with people that were really good friends of mine,
and they would have seen something,
and I brought it up months or a year later,
and they're like, "Ah, they'll remember the event."
See, that's what's interesting.
They'll remember the event, but they'll remember it as,
"Oh, I think it was something different."
So now that they go, "Jason, what are you talking about?
Was that when you were doing all those binadrials?"
No, they remember the event, and they remember seeing the thing.
They just have a new--
I was just tired.
I just hallucinated the same thing you saw,
which really is unlikely.
The thing I love about this story is,
it's not just that there was a phantom in the house, right?
It's not just that there was the image of a man in a straight jacket
with a terrifying grin and crazy eyes.
Right? That enough is scary,
but the fact that the brother, when he walked in,
became the phantom.
He walked in and instantly felt compelled
to wrap his arms around his body,
walking to this little room,
and start acting like he's in a straight jacket.
Now, the other two people, Kevin and John,
were walking throughout the apartment for a period of time
before this creature, this spirit, made itself known,
but the younger brother immediately takes on the personality of the lunatic.
Now, he goes, "There's no history of the house."
He said there was a hospital nearby,
but he tried looking in the eye,
probably when he was trying to break his lease,
he was probably trying to prove that it was haunted or something like that.
He goes, "He couldn't find anything in the house
that would point to it being haunted
or being used as an insane asylum or something like that."
The implication is that little room was set up for a man in a straight jacket,
and now his spirit is free to roam.
Again, not only that,
it can actually not necessarily possess people,
but latch on to certain people,
and that person takes those traits.
Did it see the man?
Just felt acting a little crazy,
which makes you wonder,
what if it was the younger brother who moved into this place, right?
And he walks in there, and he sees that room,
and he goes, "Oh, I bet you this is where a crazy person would be,"
and he wraps his-- he's all by himself in this instance,
but he's pretending he's wrapped in a straight jacket for a bit in the room,
and he's like, "Haha, crazy, crazy times!"
Then he goes on and he's unpacking his stuff,
and this man is very vulnerable to this spirit,
and over time, it's not just,
"Oh, I bet you that room was used for a guy with a straight jacket."
This dark psychic energy is actually infusing this young man,
driving him crazy.
The other people had enough shielding, they could at least see it,
but this young man, when he walked in, he was instantly vulnerable to this thing.
And Mike and, like the story before, I mean, these are very obvious visualizations or actions from this.
The first story, having to walk in on your hands,
and this story seeing this ghost, and then someone being influenced instantly by the ghost.
I started to put together that hypothesis, like, these are obvious things,
but what about all the houses that we've lived in, all the apartments we've been in over the years, right?
Even just visiting someone else's apartment.
Who's to say, and we'll wrap the episode up like this,
with this very dark and dreary ending, how much of our personalities are us?
How many of our likes and dislikes are vices and addictions?
Are fears and hopes are actually us?
And how many are psychic residue from a place we visited once?
Or a home we grew up in?
Who are a young girl died in a pool back in the 70s,
and you moved into that house and you just didn't like swimming.
You just never really could explain it, and I'm not, you know, I'm a goat swimmer and all,
I just don't enjoy swimming.
Or you spend most of your life not being anti-cigarette,
but not really being interested in cigarettes either.
And then you're in your mid-20s and you're in a new town and you find yourself craving a cigarette.
You don't know, you figure, listen, I work in this new job, I'm in this new town, I'm super stressed,
and I saw the movie Joker and it made smoking look really cool,
so I knew it would impress some girls, so I went and I picked up some cigarettes,
and you know, I'm not addicted, I just smoke casually on the weekends.
But it's just all this other stuff going on in my life,
but it's actually psychic residue from your new place of residence.
It's interesting because this is actually a belief of Scientology,
that there are ingrams that are connected to you,
and we have to wipe those off of ourselves,
and part of being a Scientologist is building up, I'm gonna bastardize it,
I've had a few Scientology friends in my life and I'm just kind of putting it together piece by piece,
but it's something that you have to do this cleansing, you do like the E-meter thing,
and you relive the experience over and over again of this negative thing,
and you're kind of washing these ingrams off of you until you become clear,
I think it's the supposed to be the base level of humanity,
and then if you do it more you can ascend type of thing.
It kind of is aligned with that, but this leans more into just the paranormal thing.
Yesterday we talked about ghosts are everywhere, this one's kind of the same thing,
this psychic energy is everywhere, and how much of ourselves is actually ourselves.
One thing that I find very interesting, that my appetites are not my own.
When you fast, you very quickly realize that a lot of the stuff you love to eat
is actually the stuff your gut biome needs to fuel itself.
It's fascinating, your gut biome sends chemicals into your body saying,
"We need sugar, we need carbs, we need sugar, we need carbs,"
that's where those cravings come from, and if you can go, I think it's two or three days without consuming,
sugar or carbs, all of that gut biome dies off.
You'll actually be craving it even more because it's releasing more signals to your brain,
because they will die, it's basically an entire civilization in your stomach
that will die if you don't have at least a candy bar, or a donut.
Come on, just eat that donut, and you have to go three days basically,
and then all of that dies in your stomach, and your gut biome is now different,
and your taste buds are different, and what you want to eat is different,
until you start eating sugar and carbs again, and that gut biome starts to reappear,
and then the cravings start again.
Those aren't my cravings, those are cravings that are coming from within my stomach,
an alien life form that's made its home in me, but it's not me.
That's explained by science, we know that from science,
so the question is, when we look at the world of psychic energy,
how many of our phobias, or how many of our addictions, or how many of our attractions,
how many of our desires are actually natively ours,
and how many are things attaching themselves to us?
It's a tricky question because there is really no answer for it, right?
It just comes down to who are you as a person, what is yourself,
and you may think you know you, and you may be very introspective and know you,
but whatever could be inhabiting you could also be hiding very, very well.
I used extreme examples like picking up a smoking habit, or being afraid of water,
it could be far more simple than that, far more simple than that.
It doesn't have to be walking on your hands, it doesn't have to be being crazy in a house.
The world of the paranormal is so fascinating because there are so many roads we can walk down,
and a lot of those roads are spooky, very scary and unsettling roads,
and I think this is one of those.
I think this really kind of makes you buy into this hypothesis that who are you?
When you get angry, is it you, or is it some sort of rage energy that latched on to you many, many years ago?
You think you're in love with a person,
but you don't really understand why, it doesn't make sense to you why you love them so much?
Maybe you don't, but some energy, some thought form attached itself to you around the same time you met them.
Things just seemed to click, but were you really in control of those decisions?
I talked about on my episode Solar Plexus Clown Gliders,
how when I was in a courtroom in Sacramento, it was a college class I had to go to the courtroom,
I saw a King Cobra on the seat next to me.
It wasn't real, but I saw it, and I saw it uncoil and lunge at me.
And then for the next five years, I suffered from back pain, which led me to be prescribed 240 Vicod in a month.
And I always wondered, I always figured that that was some sort of psychic energy that someone had left in that courtroom,
and it had attached itself to me and caused this pain, it was physical pain, but it was caused by some sort of psychic entity,
and who knows where that is now, right?
Other than a few bumps and bruises due to being 45 years old, my back's fine, I didn't need to be on 240 Vicod in a month.
Back in 2003, that's where they were prescribing for a little bit of back pain,
and my life really started to slide.
How do you function on that much narcotics, right? It's a narcotic drug.
You know, I'm doing good, I'm doing great, there's a lot of people, right?
There's a lot of people who didn't get out of that.
There's a lot of people who got sucked deeper into that world of painkillers.
I consider myself very, very lucky.
Blessed, right? Blessed.
But I do believe that there are entities out there that can latch onto us,
and I do believe that it may not be the cause of all of our vices and all of our passions.
I do believe that these things are out there, I've talked about it before, I call them psychic landmines.
A thousand people could walk back and forth across one of these things, and it never do anything.
And a hundred people could walk by and get a weird feeling, right?
Something feels off in this area, they don't want to be here, it's creepy.
But maybe three or four people walk across that thing, and that landmine goes off.
That spirit, that demon, that archon, whatever you want to call it,
springs to life, latches on, and takes you for one hell of a ride.
The world of the paranormal is fascinating and terrifying.
Because it can go from being a spooky story to a life-changing event, like that.
And you never know what side you're going to be on.
Are you going to be the person just listening to the story on Dead Ravra Radio?
Or are you going to be the person whose life slowly descends into a living hell?
Simply because you moved into the wrong apartment.
[Music]
DeadRavraRadio.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRavraRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRavraRadio.
DeadRavraRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend, guys.
[Music]