An urban legend in the city of New York that was so real the police had to intervene.
And then we take a trip through a graveyard to see some of the creepiest, most odd headstones
possible. It's an interactive adventure so today you'll find out how you will die today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I think you guys probably
noticed by now last week and this week, last week we only did four episodes this week. We're
only going to do four episodes. That's just a byproduct of me being here with the family. I
don't have as much time to actually prep and record episodes so I apologize for that. So you'll get,
you got four episodes last week, you'll have four episodes this week but that's not going to be a
continuous thing starting the following week. We'll be back on regular schedule. Let's hop on
board the carpenter copter. We are headed to New York City, the big apple, home of Statue of Liberty.
I saw a documentary once, a bunch of goo when it never ran out of here. Okay so all aboard.
Dude, why don't we have a train? We should have a Dead Rabbit train. The Rabbit Railroad. Hop on
board the Rabbit Railroad. Choo choo. We're on the Rabbit Railroad. We're taking it across the
country. We are headed to New York City and this train, like most of our vehicles, have teleportation.
Wait no, then they don't need to be a vehicle. They have time travel ability so as we're on the
Rabbit Railroad, which has every seat is first class so you guys are eating well. The carpenter
copter just has like MREs. This time you actually like get fine dining. We're going through a time
portal and we're in the 1980s. We're in the late 1980s and we're in New York. Oh, aboard. Wait no,
no, everyone get off. How do they tell you to get off? How do they tell you to disembark? I guess
they just, the train's stopping at your destination but anyways we get off the train and we're walking
around New York City late 80s and we see a young kid walking through the streets. He just left his
high school in Brooklyn. He's walking through the streets of New York, backpack over his shoulder,
one shoulder because he's a cool kid. He's walking through the streets of New York and he keeps looking
over his shoulder. He's clutching his backpack super tight and we're like, well man this kid must be
super paranoid. He's looking around and we're like, hey kid, what's going on? What's going on? He's like,
don't you know? They're everywhere. He looks around, darts around. He's seen groups of kids just kind
of pass them by and every time a kid walks by him, he looks over. We're like, dude, what's going on? He's
like, the Decepticons. He says it in the near whisper. We barely hear him over the hustle and
bustle of the city. He's like, don't say it so loud idiot. And then we're like, you mean Decepticons as
in like the Transformers? And he's like, no, no, I'm not worried about fighter jets turning into
robots. That would be cool. I'm talking about the Decepticons. And at that point we realized during
the course of our conversation, we seem to be surrounded by about 15 to 20 teenagers and we
realize that even though they're not wearing any gang colors, they're not dressed like hoodlums,
they actually are dressed quite preppy. They have their eyes on what we have. Now I don't know what
I have on me. I guess I have the keys to the rabbit railroad. This kid has his backpack and I'm
assuming you at least have something. Whatever's to your right of where you're sitting right now
is the only weapon that you have available. I have an antique chair from my mom's desk. So that
magically appears and I'm swinging into these kids and he's like, no, no, no, those aren't the Decepticons.
Those aren't the Decepticons. Those are the Decepticons and we look and there's a bigger crowd of
kids that now there's a huge fight going on. So I've started a fight with a bunch of innocent kids.
The real Decepticons have showed up. You're bashing people with whatever you have. Hopefully
it's more than a hot pocket. Hopefully it's like a weapon. But that was this gang. Back in the late
80s, these three kids got together and they called themselves the Decepticons. The three original
members were Cyclonus, Rumble, and Megatron and those are actual characters from the cartoon.
And they said, this is the way this gang's going to work. We are Decepticons. We are not robots in
disguise. We are gangbangers in disguise. No gang colors whatsoever. We dress really preppy. We wear
like nice shirts, nice pants. We look like the average high school student and we rob people
blind. They also like grouped up to protect themselves from other people. But you had this
group, this gang that kind of defied expectations of what a late 1980s gang were. And the kids at
high schools, it started off in Brooklyn and it spread throughout the city of New York. And it
started off with just these three kids and then eventually they graduated, not literally from
high school. I don't know if they ever graduated from high school, but they graduated to more bigger
thefts where they would do mob thefts. About 10 to 20 people would surround you, beat you up, take
your stuff, and then disappear into the city. The police for a while thought it was an urban legend
because these kids were terrified. And their parents were like, my kids are telling me there's
this gang that nobody knows about that's beating people up. And the cops are like, that's not how
gangs operate. But as more and more reports came through, the police were like, this is a real gang.
And there's no way to track them. There's absolutely no way to track them. They're not,
you can't look down the street and see three dudes wearing all red and be like, oh, those are
bloods. Like you would just be walking through a department store and a guy would come up behind
you and hit you over the head. That was a Decepticon. The rumors got to the point where the Decepticons
were going to start laying sieges to high schools. They were going to attack high schools on a certain
day. And parents were going to the police and saying, you need to stop the Decepticons. And they're
like, okay, lady, I know how awesome the name sounds, but they do not have the ability to lay
siege to a school. Parents began pulling their kids out of school. It was this nightmare for the
schools and for the kids. It wasn't just a nightmare for the schools. And the thing was, you'd think
it's, it's funny because they don't identify themselves by color. You didn't want two groups
of Decepticons walking into each other. They may not even know they're in the same gang. That's how
deceptive that's how good their technique was. Two groups of three kids each walking down the
street and they're thinking about robbing each other. They don't know the other group is actually
in the same gang. So they developed a code. They developed a series of sayings or hand signs. We
don't know because it was one of the most valuable secrets in New York for a teenager in the 1980s
to know this code. Because that way, if you were approached by a Decepticon, you could say the right
thing or do the right thing. They would think you were in the group and they'd leave you alone.
So you would want that information. And everyone was like, thought they had a piece of the code or
knew a piece of the code, but the Decepticons weren't willing to share that information with any
outsiders at all. And they, they're wet when they use weapons. A lot of times they beat you up when
they use weapons. They use box cutters and hammers, which again, they're, which that'd be kind of hard
to pull off a preppy look with a hammer. But I guess if you had in your backpack in March 19th,
1989, the New York Times ran a profile on these guys saying this was a quote from the article.
It said, the police first became aware of the Decepticons in 1986. Sergeant Galea said the
gang has lasted longer than he expected, probably because of its catchy name. Other gangs with more
bulky titles have come and gone in the last three years. One group calling itself the Tonka
trucks lasted but a few months. I would love to roll with a gang called the Tonka trucks. And
then just watch them get annihilated and like, be like, I told you guys that told you guys that was
a dumb name. Call yourself the micro machines. Like, come on, like Decepticons is a catchy name.
They eventually died out in the 1990s. They're not around anymore. Or are they? Who knows.
So hats off to you Decepticons for having a cool name, having an entire city in fear of you.
And as well hats off to you because you probably stole my hat right off my head.
But let's hop on backboard. That was weird. Let's hop back on board the rabbit railroad. We are going
to a cemetery. That's cemetery fog being blown by cemetery wind. You know what? You can talk trash
all you want about the Transformer movies. There's so many awesome elements in it. You think that's
a, you think I'm going back to my old story but I'm not. And Transformers 4, Age of Extinction,
the military set up a group that their job was to hunt down Transformers and melt them and turn
them into Transformium. That part's dumb. But the name of the military group was Cemetery Wind.
And I was like, I remember watching the movie because when you start watching Transformers
movie, you think it's going to be good for the first 20 minutes. The third one was brilliant.
First one was okay. But whenever I watch a new Transformer movie, for the first 20 minutes,
I think it's going to be a masterpiece. And sometimes I'm right. So for the first 20 minutes
of Transformers 4, I was like, Cemetery Wind. Oh, that name's so badass. I want to get a jacket.
I want to get a cemetery wind military jacket. Not like join the military to get one for real.
I would actually if there was, we were hunting Transformers. But I wanted, I was like, can I
get like memorabilia, like cemetery wind patch and put it on my backpack or something? And then I
continued to watch the movie. I was like, oh my God. But cemetery wind is still a dope name for
like a paramilitary group. Anyways, that being said, Transformer episode is full of stuff.
This episode is full of Transformer stuff. I don't know why I keep saying stuff backwards.
We are going to the graveyard. We're going to the graveyard and we're going to take a look at some
crazy gravestones. Crazy gravestones. Seriously? Is that what you're doing this episode? Yes,
because these gravestones have some really interesting backstories to them. I'm not just
reading stuff like Papa farted and then he died. Like, yeah, I'm not doing that. And there are
gravestones out there like that. So I want you to pick a number between one and six. Pick a number
between one and six. And before we do that, I'm going to read you a gravestone. Well, while you're
doing that, I'm going to read you a gravestone that actually took out of the list because I just
thought it was too dark. So if you picked zero, this is you. There's a gravestone in Blairstown,
New Jersey that says this episode might be a little depressing. It might be a little depressing.
I found some interesting ones, but some of them are kind of depressing. This one says
Princess Doe missing from home dead among strangers remembered by all born question mark
found July 15th, 1982. So the story behind that one, I mean, imagine we're walking through this
graveyard. I guess I should have set this up first. Me and you are walking through this graveyard.
And once you pick the number that you win, you magically become that corpse like you travel back
in time and die the way that died. I didn't want to put someone through this one. This is tragic.
The story is they found the body of a girl in Blairstown, New Jersey with her head bashed in
thrown into a ravine. And she was between the ages of 14 and 18. She's never been identified.
They've never caught who did it. They just found a body of a young teenage girl.
She's just a heartbreaking tombstone missing from home dead among strangers remembered by all.
So I didn't want to do that when it'd be like, ha ha, you picked a 14 year old girl whose head
got bashed in. I thought that was a little tasteless. Some of these other ones, you might argue
are tasteless too. But let's continue our journey through the cemetery. We look down at a gravestone.
These are all real, by the way. These are all real. Look down at a gravestone. And it says,
we see a gravestone. We're very, very somber in the moment here. Baby monster. Baby monster is what
it says. Born October 23, 1888. Died February 3, 1989. Now, this is a real gravestone in Kent,
Washington. Now, the most likely scenario is that it was a baby who comes from a family with the
last name of monster. That's the working theory with this gravestone. Nobody knows. Because it's so
old. But there's a couple of questions about it. One, who has the last name monster? How did you
get that surname? Your ancestors were the ugliest people in Europe and they're like, ah, you're
the son of a monster. And he was born October 23, 1888. He died February 3, no wait, not 1989.
That would have made my 100 years old. I don't know if I said 1989 earlier, but I'm seeing it on
my notes now. I hope I didn't say that. He died February 3, 1889. So he lived, what is that,
five months. They never even named him. They just called him baby. So if you picked number four,
I turn and look and you're like, you're doing Benjamin Button style. You're shrinking down
into a little baby monster or a regular baby who just doesn't get named for five months.
I'm sorry. This episode, this one was a little dark too. So if you picked number four, you're
either a cool baby monster who lived from 1888 to 1989 stalking the wilderness,
or you're just a unnamed baby in a grave, one of the two. I'll let you choose. If you pick
number four, you're either a baby monster who lived 99 years, no, 101 years, or you're just a baby,
just a regular baby whose dad's name was monster. Okay. But assuming you didn't pick number four,
you're not shrunken into a little ball in the ground. I'm sorry, it's dark. We're moving on.
And even if you did pick number four, you can come along. So now we have a little baby monster
following us along. We come to another gravestone. Now this gravestone is from a graveyard at the
Ohio Asylum for the Insane. And you're like, great, I wish I had picked the baby monster.
There's two gravestones. There's two of these gravestones. They both say the exact same thing.
They're at the Ohio Asylum for the Insane's graveyard. And they have one word on them,
specimens. No one knows what they mean. No one know what people know what the word specimen means.
They can get a dictionary, but no one knows why they're on these gravestones. But if you pick number
one, you know, because you either turn into a bunch of body parts, because that's one of the
theories that they're basically gravestone. It's like caskets full of random body parts. So if you
pick number one, you either become a collection of nothing but arms and feet, no torso, no legs,
you're just a pile of body parts, medical specimens, or I'll give you an option to there's another
theory. There's another little creepy theory about this, that the Ohio Asylum for the Insane was
running experiments on the people there, hooking electrodes up to their brain. That's actually
not an experiment. That was actually a legitimate treatment back then. Anyways, they were like
making mutants in the asylum. They're trying to, they're trying to create the perfect insane person.
They're like having insane people bang each other and then having insane babies and then
raising them and then having them mate as well, creating the genetically perfect insane person
who has every, that's actually a pretty good idea for a movie. You have a guy who has every
possible insanity from like schizophrenia to like sexomnia, which is a real thing. It's where
you bang people in your sleep. You just have the most insane person ever. And then he gets out.
Don't, don't write that. I'm going to write that. Don't, don't steal my idea. So, but if you pick
number one, you're either a collection of body parts or you're the plot of my new movie and, and
interesting about this, why are there two of them? Do they have that? Whatever they were doing,
did that, they have that many of them? They needed two gravestones. Let's move on with this one. Now
we're going to go keep going through this graveyard. We got a pile of body parts following us.
We got a baby monster following us and we come to another gravestone and this one is very simple,
very simple gravestone. Doesn't say specimens. It says Sir Jeffrey Hudson, 1619 to 1682. And if you
picked five, you're this one. If you pick number five, you're this one. I want to tell you that
before so you can imagine if you picked five. I want you to understand the logic that you have
to go through to make this work. It's on a gravestone. Sir Jeffrey Hudson, 1619, 1682, a dwarf
presented in a pie to King Charles I. And I remember reading that. I go, "Isn't that how he
died? Was he a dwarf and baked into a pie and he died? Like, how was that on your tombstone?
Normally how you die is on your tombstone. What is this? Did King Charles eat a dwarf?
So I had to look this up. I don't look all these up, by the way. I'm not just reading these off.
So I had to research on all this stuff. Sir Jeffrey Hudson was also known as Lord Minimus,
which was Mad Max's most least threatening villain. Lord Minimus was 19... I see what's
weird is all this stuff is supposedly historically accurate because there is a ton of records kept
on this dude, but some of the measurements don't add up. Lord Minimus, at age 10, he was 19 inches tall,
which seems impossible. Seems absolutely impossible. The baby monster has given him the
run for his money. The baby monster could beat up Lord Minimus. Anyways, Jeffrey Hudson was this
little dude in the village and someone said, "You know what? You should go see the king." The king
loves to laugh at people with deformities. Jeffrey's like, "Yippee! Let's go!" And they
thought of an ideal way to present him to the king was to bring the king a pie. And they go,
"Here, your highness. Here's a pie." And the king's like, "That's kind of a letdown. Like, I thought
I was going to have some entertainment." And Jeffrey Hudson jumped out of the pie and goes, "Hi,
everybody. I'm Jeffrey Hudson. I don't have my name yet." He's waving everyone covered in blackberry.
He's covered in pie crust. And they didn't slay him as a demon right there. They actually thought
that was an awesome trick because it's a human the size of a pie. It's a 10-year-old boy the
size of a pie. The queen falls in love with him in the sense that she thinks he's the most fascinating
man in the world. This is before Doseki's. So she begins taking him every-- she took some everywhere
that she goes. And he would actually ride in the pocket of the-- they had this super tall porter
who would carry the bags and stuff like that. And Lord Minimus would ride in the pocket. So it was
like this total-- just basically a circus in your-- you'd go to see the king to discuss taxes
or something like that. There's basically a bunch of circus freaks living there. He ended up being
sent on missions. He became a diplomat. He was not an official diplomat. He's not signing treaties.
But he would travel around on the king's bequest. He ends up getting kidnapped by Dutch privateers.
They forced this boy-- he's not 10 at this point. He's like 16. But he's still only 19 inches tall.
They forced him to become a slave. And you're like, what-- what good is a 19-inch slave? Well,
they found good for him because they made him fight a turkey. They put him both in like a little
fight club cage match and he had to beat up a turkey. And he won. He ends up becoming a spy,
gets kidnapped again, and then gets involved in a plot to kill a king, not the king he liked,
another king. He goes to prison and died in an unmarked grave. Now, you go-- wait a second.
You said all this stuff about a grave. This is a memorial to him. It is a grave. But they don't
know where he was actually buried at. When he did die, he did reach the height of four feet. So he
was four feet tall when he died. And he died at the age 30. So he lived a good life. I mean, I never
fought a turkey. So if you pick number five, you did not get baked into a pie and get killed by the
king. You got baked into a pie and when you hopped out, your life changed. You became an adventurer.
Yes, you were a slave as part of the time. You did have to beat up a turkey. But you got involved
in a world of political intrigue and royal courts and all sorts of great stuff. But let's continue
our trip through the graveyard because now we are coming up to-- okay, I'm calling an audible real
quick. I'm calling an audible real quick. I was looking at one of them and I'm like, that's lame.
So we're not doing to the count of six anymore. You can only choose up to five. So I know that's
kind of late in the episode. But you can choose now. So if you chose six, if you chose number six,
now choose two or three. Because the number-- I had one that was dumb and I really considered not
to do it. But it's such a famous grave stone. I'm going to go over it real quick, but I don't want
to get too much into detail with it. In Salt Lake City, Utah, there's a tombstone because I know
people are going to email and say, hey, you missed out this one. It's really-- it's actually not
fascinating at all. In Salt Lake City, Utah, there's a grave stone that says Lily E. Gray,
June-- it has her date of birth, date of death. It says, "victim of the beast 666." Some people freak
out and they're like, oh no, was that Alistair Crowley? Was he in? Did he have something to do
with her death? I looked into it. She was 77 years old. She died of being 77 years old. She was married
to a man who hated the government, thought the US government was the beast, and that the Democrats,
the Democratic government, killed his wife. He was a convict who had these prepper things. He
believed the government was going to take over the world eventually and so on and so forth.
He had that put on her gravestone because he was a lunatic. Then her family hated him so much that
when he died, they buried him as far away as possible in the graveyard. That's that. That was
that one. A lot of people-- that's one's really famous because it seems mysterious, but when you
look into it, it was just some crackpot who believes the government is the beast, which is a very
common conspiracy theory, especially back then. So if you picked number six, that would have been
you, but we'll let you pick again. Pick two or three. I'm going to get something to drink real
quick. Okay, I'm back. I got my sparkling water here. I put on so much weight since I went on
vacation, but it'll all come off the bike within a week or two. Let's go ahead and move on. We're
going to move on to another gravestone here. Walk through the cemetery. Come across this big slab,
this big, big grave-- you know what a gravestone is. You come across one of those and it says
Geospenser. You're like, "Oh, that's interesting. Sounds like a sci-fi channel show." No, it doesn't.
It sounds like a Disney channel show. It doesn't even sound like that. Anyways, we look-- I'm like,
you're like, "Jason, just shut up. Just shut up and tell me how I'm going to die." I'm like,
okay, we're looking at this gravestone. It says Lost Life-- this one is grammatically weird,
and I'm wondering if they got paid if they hadn't got charged by the letter, because it took me a
while to make sense of it. Lost Life by Stab and Falling on Icaracer evading six young women.
Here, let me start over. Let me try reading it like an actual sentence rather than it appears on
the gravestone. Lost Life by Stab and Falling on Icaracer evading six young women trying to
give him birthday kisses and office metropolitan life building. Like, what? So much of this stuff
doesn't make sense. Icaracer, there's little soft spongy things that used to like dry Icaracer,
right? And he lost life by Stab. Anyways, someone was really cheap when they got this guy's gravestone.
True story, actually reported in the newspaper, people got arrested or one person got arrested
over this. The year is 1909. We're back in New York City. And if you pick two, you are young George
Spencer Millay. You pick number two, you're walking through is 1909 New York, you're like,
"Hey, everybody read all about it. The papers, the papers, bustling noises, it's fested with rats,
surly Irish. Might even be a member of the Dead Rabbit Gang." They're still around back then,
which would be pretty dope. But you right now are at work. Your name is George. You're 14 years old,
and you work at the Metropolitan Insurance Company. 14, by the way, worked in the accounting office.
1909, they had no laws against child labor. 14-year-old boy working in the accounting office.
He wasn't like cooking the books or nothing. He was helping with manual, well, erasing ink is
what he was doing. He was working like, he wasn't actually doing the calculations from what I can
understand. He got the job only four months earlier. And the girls who also worked there were like,
"Ooh, he's so cute. He's so, like, mannered, and he has, like, clear skin, and he's not covered in
boils, like the rest of these kids." I added the boils part. But anyways, they did say that he was
super hot, and he had really good manners, which is nerd. But anyways, so they all were like pining
for him. Now, he was about to turn 15, and the girls in the community, the girls in the building,
thought, "Wouldn't it be nice if they were like bobbing their hair? Wouldn't it be so nice if we
walked up to George and we kissed him once for each year that he's been alive, that he's existed
on this planet?" And the other girls were like, "Yes, that's a great idea, and I have a normal
sounding voice. I don't sound like a freak." And she's like, "What do you mean?" So all the girls
decided to chase down Georgie and kiss him at the end of a shift. Now, that would be one thing if
he was like, "Well, what?" It would be one thing if he was an adult, and he could prepare for it.
These girls, one of them was a 23-year-old woman. He was like, "Oh, I'm totally going to like tackle
this 15-year-old boy and kiss him. Ooh, that would be hot. It's so gross." But anyways, he's 14. He
just sees a bunch of girls coming at him. He doesn't do a crane kick. Like, he doesn't get in a defensive
position, but he doesn't know how to react. And they tackle him. Now, he had an ink eraser in his
pocket. An ink eraser back then was actually like a metal wedge-type tool with a sharp point that
they used to like scrape ink off stuff. And so when they were kissing him and they tackle him,
they hear him go, "I'm stabbed! I'm stabbed!" And they back up and blood is just shooting out of the
chest wound, and everyone totally freaks out. And they're like, "Hurry up! Someone invents a telephone
and then use it to call an ambulance and then invent an ambulance." But officially, they do get
an ambulance there. They send like telegraph or carrier pigeon. They had phones back then. I'm
just joking. But anyways, they get the kid in the ambulance and he dies. He doesn't make it to the
hospital. The 23-year-old woman gets arrested, not for like sexual predator stuff. She gets arrested
for murder, but as the police- because they just see a bunch of women descend on a young boy and
then blood shoot out of his chest. Once cops start an investigation, once some surly Irish cop on the
take from the dead rabbits who were paying them off, once they investigate the crime, they realize
it was an accident and she is found not guilty. Not guilty of murder. Guilty of being a pervo,
but not guilty of murder. The age thing, I mean, I think most of them were around his age. You just
have this weird 23-year-old woman also in this scene. But you get rid of her. Just assume that,
let's say, you're in your 20s. You're going to get kissed to death by six beautiful age-appropriate
women, but then become fatally stabbed because you put something in the wrong pocket. Not a
terrible way to go. Not a terrible way to go. I would much rather be a dwarf, would not want to
be a pile of feet, but let's go ahead and move on to our last one. Now I'm walking you over,
we're walking to these gravestones and I go, "You know if you pick number three, you're this one."
And they're like, "Well, actually I picked number six. You forced me to pick number three."
I'm like, "Silence. Silence. Come over to this gravestone. Come over to this gravestone."
It says, "In memory of Mary Jane McCoon, wife of James W. Forer, born about 1838,
we don't know, born about 1838, died 1855." And then there's more. Bitten, this one's pretty
self-explanatory. This gravestone has all the backstory you need. I did go research, but
it pretty much explains everything that happened. So if you pick number three, this is you.
Bing! You're out on a prairie all by yourself. A little shack. You're pregnant. You're like
eight months pregnant. You're like, "This is totally weird. I'm in all of a sudden,
I'm not there anymore. You are alone if you pick number three. You're standing out
outside of a farmhouse pregnant." Feeling really weird. And then you see a coyote walking through
the prairie. I think it snuck up on her. I don't think you looked right at it. And you see its
mouth is foaming. Now, the tombstone says, "Bitten by a rabid coyote, developed rabies,
became violent." So now you're beating up a bunch of people. You got your mouth is foaming. You go
into town. You're throwing people out of the saloon, kicking them. When they're down, you like
flatten their head and go, "Pfft!" They're like, "Stop that pregnant lady. She'll destroy us all!"
And the lawnmowers shooting at you, you're bulletproof. Throwing tables across the pool hall.
You're actually throwing not pool tables. I'm not giving you that much strength. You're just
throwing tables around a pool hall. Do they have pool back then? Anyways, the point is,
is that you become violent. You raise your fist to the moon as the towns people are chasing you
with torches. Let's go back to the actual epitaph. It says, "So dark. So dark." It says,
I'll read the whole thing because it made more sense in context. "Bitten by a rabid coyote,
developed rabies, became violent." We've already experienced that part. "Was smothered with feather
bed. When husband returned, she and her unborn child were dead and buried."
So the towns people did get you and you're like, "Oh, just rip your guts out."
And you do that. You're actually ripping people's guts out. They finally hit you over the head with
an anvil, drag you back. Actually, no, they don't need to do that. That would have killed you.
But at some point in the real story, you get tied down to your bed because you're so violent.
And when they were, when she was restrained to the bed, she basically like got buried in her own
blankets and suffocated because she was just thrashing about and she was pregnant. And the
dad was gone. Her husband was long gone. He was on a trip. He was on like a hunting trip or something
like that. And business trip, business trip. Maybe his business was hunting. I don't remember,
but anyways, the husband comes back and she'd been dead for months because they definitely didn't
have phones back then. He comes back and he's like, "Honey, I'm home. The house is completely trashed."
He's like, "What is going on? It looks like some violent activity took place here."
"Honey, I'm home." Okay, sorry. That, that's, that, it's getting dark. It's getting dark. The
point of the matter is if you pick number three, you are pregnant woman eaten by rabid coyote,
tore through a town. In reality, she just tore her house up. But I'll give you a little bit more.
Tore through town, villagers, the townspeople, I mean, had to fight you and then eventually
they tied you to a bed where you suffocated and you and your baby died. Sorry, I knew it was going
to be really, really dark. I tried to lighten the mood as much as I could, but I knew it was going
to be dark. So you know your fate. You know how you're going to die. I'm going to tell you guys
this right now. This is a little uplifting message from the end here. You, people don't have grave
stones anymore. They're super expensive. I plan on just getting cremated if my body just isn't
dumped in the middle of the forest. I don't care. Whatever. You, your life is your epitaph. How you
interact with other people is the legacy leave on the world. You don't need to have a witty saying
or a grave marker or anything like that. The legacy you leave, the way you interact with other people,
the way you help people is your epitaph. You will be remembered forever by your actions,
long after stone has been washed away by the elements. Go out there, do great things, interact
with people in a great way, be a great person, be positive. That is your legacy. Even if you're
been by rapid coyote, you can still go out there and say, I'm going to change the world. I'm going
to change the world around me in even little ways just by being extra nice, just by being
a good person. That is your legacy. And I know it's mine. I absolutely know it's mine.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabberradio. @deadrabberradio is our Twitter.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
[Music]
[MUSIC]