(laughing)
That last one sounds a little bit like Santa Claus
or should I say Satan Claus.
It's episode 666 of Dead Rabbit Radio.
Be prepared for this level,
this level of nonsense this episode.
Episode 666.
First off, we meet a woman who has one-on-one communication
with the devil.
Every time she makes breakfast.
And then, we travel to the depths of hell ourselves
to meet a man who promises us he can give us
all the gold in the world if we worship him.
Then, we stay in hell, 'cause it's episode 666,
to take a look at some of the most fearsome demons
that inhabit the bowels of the underworld.
And, it's an interactive adventure.
Today on the 666th episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
(upbeat music)
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode
of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carvin,
or I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Episode 666.
Can you believe it?
This show is now one of the episode-wise,
longest running paranormal podcasts in the world.
It's amazing.
You may say quantity over quality.
I wouldn't, I like the show, but you might say that.
But, 666 episodes, I think that's more episodes
than The Simpsons, really.
And guys, it would be impossible without you.
Thank you so much for listening.
We got another 1,000 episodes in the show.
But right now, we got this devilishly,
delightfully good episode, hopefully,
hopefully, of episode 666.
First off, we gotta give a shout out
to our newest Patreon supporter,
walking into Dead Rabbit Command dressed up as a sexy,
just as a sexy devil.
One of those costumes from the Halloween story.
It's Justin Mosier.
I wanna give a round of applause
as he's walking in, picking the tight costume
out of his butt.
Justin, you're gonna be at,
let's give him a better round of applause.
That was kind of lackluster.
He's really pulling off that outfit.
Justin Mosier, you're gonna be our captain,
our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon,
or if you don't have a sexy Satan costume,
and who doesn't, that's okay.
Just helps rid the word about the show
really, really helps out a lot.
Justin, go ahead and poke us,
poke us in the butt with your pitchfork,
and force us into the Jason Jalopy.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
It's all spooky.
I just shut the lights off.
That's all the decoration I did for this episode.
Click, you're just walking around in the dark.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed out to Small Town USA.
Justin is driving the Jason Jalopy.
We're listening to spooky sounds.
I got a CD of spooky sounds.
We're listening to the whole time.
I'm like, all right, this is my favorite track.
It's just a man screaming.
Notice Justin got a little turned on
by that song, I have to change the CD.
We are in a small town.
It's May 4th, 1984.
We're sitting in the kitchen of a woman named June O'Brien.
Now, before we get started,
I have a real problem with this story.
I really need your guys' help.
I'll probably be telling this,
and you guys will be like, what in the world?
He's doing this, but I'm so puzzled by this.
On May 4th, 1984, the Today Show
does a segment about supermarket tabloids.
And it's celebrity tabloids examined.
It is the name of the piece.
And it features June O'Brien,
and she has a haunted toaster.
And you guys may have seen the YouTube clip.
I'm gonna put all this in the show notes.
She goes, this toaster is possessed by the devil.
It's just a silver little toaster,
like the brave little toaster, but possessed by the devil.
She goes, this toaster is possessed by the devil.
Sometimes it'll say, I am the devil.
We don't get to hear that.
That's not actually on video,
but she does say that.
Sometimes she hears it.
What is on video is that she pulls a piece of toaster,
and she goes, look at what this rascally man did
to my toaster.
And it's all burnt, but then there's a part
that's not burnt that says Satan lives.
It's fake, right?
It's fake.
I'm asking you, I'm asking you as you're sitting
in her kitchen.
That's fake, right?
Then she puts a piece of toaster
to show the audience that this is real.
She puts a piece of toaster in the toaster.
She keeps trying to get it to go down.
It won't.
It's an average toaster from the 1980s.
And then flame shoots out of the toaster.
This is all on video, single take.
And she kind of jumps back.
And it's a good sized flame.
And so the interviewer goes,
why don't you get rid of the toaster?
It is possessed by the dark lord of hell.
It's ruining your toast as well.
And she goes, well, sometimes it makes really good toast.
So that's why she keeps the toaster.
And I'm watching that.
And I go, oh, this must have been
it's celebrity tabloids examined.
They were talking about national inquiring all this stuff.
I was starting to look around.
I was like, oh, you know, it's from 1984.
I'm sure they did like a 20 years later,
the hoax of the lady, how they pulled that hoax off.
Or this was debunked.
No, every single article you can find on this
or that I could find says that it was a real event.
Treats it as if it's real.
And I'm talking about like stuff from like the Huffington post
which has better things to write about
than this.
How was this real?
Am I missing something?
Does everyone know this is a hoax?
And that's why the articles are just like,
there's nobody's tome enough to think this is real.
We're not even gonna waste the paragraph
saying it was a hoax.
Is it real?
I'm seriously asking you guys.
Do you guys know something I don't?
That's what this episode has become on episode 666.
I'm just gonna start asking you questions
the rest of the series.
Here's the thing, there's no debunking on the episode itself.
There's no debunking in the future
when people are talking about it on the Huffington post
or Gawker or anything like that.
No one's like, yeah, everyone had a good laugh, but.
So you're going, Jason, maybe it is real.
Well, that same segment had a story about a man
who was walking.
He had like a vinquilitris dummy in a case
and he was walking across the frozen lake
and he fell into the lake.
He's about to die and then a little hand, little hand,
a little wooden hand reaching the water
and pulled him out and it was his howdy-duty doll.
So this is fake, right?
That's fake, like the possessed toaster.
That's in the realm of possibility for me.
Howdy-duty, one, how did he get out of the case?
You know what, I'm not actually gonna break it down
by like how can he lift up a man?
It is a doll that becomes animate.
None of it makes sense.
That's in the same segment.
So that's fake, right?
I'm asking you, that's fake, right?
And here's my other clue that this is fake.
The reporter for this segment was Richard Dominick.
I looked him up, I was about to go knock on his door
and be like, please tell me the toaster's fake.
Richard Dominick went on to become
the executive producer of the Jerry Springer show.
So I'm leaning towards the toast was fake
and the Howdy-duty was fake.
I just don't understand why no one else, am I that?
I don't wanna, what's the opposite of jaded?
Gullible, right?
Gullible, that I see this and go,
what is this real and no other article says that it's fake
because it's obviously fake.
It would be the same thing.
If every time you read a review of a Transformers movie,
they stopped in the middle of the review and they said,
okay, plot and cinematography aside,
this movie is fake, this is not a real movie.
Optimus Prime did not shoot Kelsey Grammer
with a giant blaster.
It did not happen.
And I'd be like, oh, I was wondering why no one
is freaked out, I was wondering why I saw
Kelsey Grammer on the news the next day.
I thought Optimus Prime shot him with that weapon
that was designed to punch holes through starships.
He just blasted a man.
Oh, okay, good thing I got to that.
Am I that daft?
Anyways, we will find out when I get your emails
and YouTube comments and you guys are like, yes,
it was obviously fake, dude.
Justin, let's go ahead and leave behind this woman's house.
We have some nice pieces of toast, some butter
and some jam, eating those up.
Call in the dead rabbit dirgeable.
We're going to take a one-way ticket.
Hopefully it's not a one-way ticket.
Hopefully we make it back.
Hop in the dead rabbit dirgeable.
Wait, that's super flammable.
Do we have a burrowing machine?
Justin, we're going to break out a new machine, I think.
Let's hop in the dead rabbit driller.
It's just the Jason Jalopy with the hand cranked drill.
I got to crank it the whole time.
Oh, my arms are getting sore.
You do it, you do it now.
I get like two feet into the soil
and now you're cranking it
and I got my feet kicked up on the dashboard.
The dead rabbit driller, Jason Jalopy
with just the hand drill on it.
We're leaving behind this woman's house.
We're drilling straight to hell.
(humming)
It is episode 666.
Now I was very adamant for a long time
that I wasn't going to do anything special for episode 666
and it wasn't for any reason.
It was because I can't even plan a Halloween episode.
I don't understand why you guys haven't figured that out yet.
I'll record a Halloween episode on Halloween
and it gets released on November 1st.
I'm really bad with this stuff
but everyone was clamoring for a 666 episode.
So I started trying to come up with ideas
that were quickly shot down by the people who love me
and surround me.
They're like, "Don't do that.
"Don't summon a demon.
"It's a terrible idea."
So this is plan B.
We're gonna talk about summoning a demon.
As I'm sitting in an haunted closet
where I'm gonna just simply talk about summoning a demon.
Justin, we've now breaking through the mantle of the earth,
the dead rabbit driller is driving around hell.
So let's talk about summoning demons.
It's something that I think everyone kind of goes through
a failure, Jason, I never did this.
Yeah, you did.
You're telling me you never watched like Buffy or Angel
or any like the craft or something like that.
Come on, tell me you never thought about like
how cool it would be.
You don't necessarily have to be a bad guy
but like you summon a demon and then it's like,
go beat up my bullies.
It's like, rip me their guts out.
It's eviscerating him.
You accidentally like summon a demon, the god of war.
And he's just like, killing some kid who like,
who like stalled your quarter one time,
rips his face off and makes him eat it.
We've all had not that fantasy
but we've all thought about like mastering the dark arts.
And again, maybe you don't wanna use it for evil.
Maybe you don't wanna use it to mutilate bullies.
You think wouldn't be cool to like use magic and,
you guys are shaking your head this whole time.
You're like, Jason, we've thought about this.
How to summon a demon and become insanely rich?
This is an article written by Clive Williams.
It's for a website called Exemplor.
And he talks about this demon named Maman.
He's the demon of greed and wealth.
So if you wanna become rich and successful,
it's probably the guy you're gonna talk to.
So in this article, he gives us a couple key points
we need to summon Maman.
First off, you wanna get an owl rope bracelet.
An owl rope bracelet is a bracelet made
from the skin of a Norwegian owl.
Now when I read that, I go, that's interesting.
This is a demon that's from Judeo-Christian lore,
which is mainly for the most part based around Israel,
the Middle East.
You told a dude in ancient times,
if you talk to some dude walking around
the wilderness of Israel,
you talk to a Sumerian or a Mesopotamian
who were actively messing with these old gods,
these old demons, worshiping them,
having civilization destroyed,
not learning their lesson, worshiping some other guy.
You told him, hey, if you wanna talk to this guy,
you need the skin of a Norwegian owl.
They'd look at you and go, what's Norwegian?
What's an owl?
I don't even think there's any owls in the Middle East.
It would be like telling us if you wanted
to complete a ritual, you'd have to go to Neptune.
And that's really the start of the complications
with this stuff.
I've looked into demonology.
I think, again, every paranormal researcher
goes through that phase.
They look into demonology.
They look into the rites of exorcism and things like that.
And when you dig deep enough,
you start to realize just kinda how ridiculous this stuff is.
'Cause Maman is, I'm not saying that when
God cast the demons from hell,
they all went to one location.
Like I'm sure a couple of them landed in Norway.
But it's bizarre to think like if this is legit
and this demon is from Judeo-Christian lore,
why, that is so far away.
That is so far away.
And you're telling me nobody summoned this dude
until the first explorer reached Norway.
He's just sitting in hell.
He's like, oh man, why did I have to have
the weirdo thing, right?
There's some other guys like, I can't be summoned
unless someone goes down to slip and slide three times.
So I'm screwed.
It's gonna take like 3,000 years before I show up.
Anyways, you need Al-Skin.
This other website, to verify that,
this other website talking about Maman,
this is, and we get into this.
This is really important.
Spelling errors are,
spelling errors are not things you wanna have
when you're trying to summon a demon.
There's this other website that said,
"You needed Al-Sink."
Like what?
What is that like?
Like they're, like, you know,
sometimes they're slang term for stuff.
Like you call it duck feathers down,
but it's just like feathers.
Like what's an Al-Sink?
Now imagine you were actually trying to summon Maman.
You're trying to summon the demon of wealth
and you're looking for an Al-Sink.
There's no such thing unless you actually,
there are actually sinks of Al's or videos
of a little baby Al's in Sinks, so that's cool.
That was the real treasure all along, Maman.
Have you seen a bunch of YouTube videos
of little Al's in Sinks?
You also need a Maman pendant that has his sigil in it.
So I Googled that and there were predictably
multiple versions of his sigil.
'Cause it's so funny because I wasn't actually
gonna summon Maman, but I started to think,
oh, that would actually be really interesting
if you could be walking down the street and you could go,
oh, that person, that person summoned Maman.
They're spinning around, they're vomiting everywhere.
But imagine you were at a cocktail party.
I've never been to a cocktail party now
that I think about it, ever been to a cocktail party.
I don't even know what makes a cocktail party
different than a normal party.
But I'll figure that out, I'm assuming they just drink
the whole time, but isn't that a normal party?
Anyways, if you're at a cocktail party,
fictional thing, it doesn't exist.
And you see them wearing a little pendant
and you could see the sigil and you'll go,
oh, that person, that person also has a bracelet
made out of Al's skin and probably an Al's sink at home.
But there's so many different versions of a sigil
that it was useless and one of them was pretty
a common symbol that I've seen around
on skateboards and stuff like that.
I don't think the 16 year old who smells like weed
is worshiping Maman.
Probably just thinks it's a cool logo.
But anyways, you get a Maman pendant,
but you really don't know which version is his.
But anyways, this article here by Clive Williams
has the incantation.
The incantations are hard to find
for these demon summoning things.
A lot of times they'll say, go to the lesser key of Solomon.
That's a book that really lists all the demons
or you have to go find some grimoire.
You have to do some, you have to pronounce the word
right first and then the great demons are like,
okay, now you can come in.
We didn't know what you're talking about before.
Here's this, I'm gonna read this to you.
You might think it's dangerous
'cause I'm reading it in the haunted closet,
but let me read this to you.
Evil, small lit, evil, small lit,
evil, small wick, evil, small wick,
yamroi, yajui, gog, l'arv, yamroi, yajui,
og, larv, yamroi, eb, es,
wit, syke, rof, yif.
The reason why I felt comfortable reading that
is because I translated it first.
And this is the thing.
When you're talking about demon summoning,
you gotta get stuff right.
This actually says, Clive Williams, Clive Williams,
Clive Williams, Clive Williams, May your writing go viral,
may your writing go viral, may you be blessed
with riches for life.
So it was a bit of a joke and when I read it
and once I cleverly deciphered it,
once I realized it was written backwards,
I started, I was trying to see if it was an example,
like he was like, but you do this in your own thing,
but no, no, he puts this out and I'm not faulting the guy,
like maybe he's just trying to take the piss out of
the kid on the skateboard who owes him money
for that weed he sold him, I don't know.
But there are people who are going to skin owls in Norway
and spin 1999 on some pendant and then read this backwards
and light a candle and stuff like that.
Yeah, it's just a waste of time.
It's not this segment, not this segment,
but it's funny because when you look at people
who believe in demonology, I'm sure not all of them,
but I'm sure there are some 12 year olds
who were suckered in by this and they wanted to have
enough money to take their girlfriend out
to a cocktail party, right?
To the cocktail party down the street.
So they did this incantation and obviously didn't work.
It's obviously a joke if you took more than five minutes
to read it backwards.
With the thing with demonology is there's so much information
and at the same time, so little information.
And people are, at the end of the day,
I think people who do try to summon demons,
it's because of two things.
One, they're seeking power, it's three things.
One of them is seeking personal power.
One of them is trying to prove that they exist,
some sort of validation.
And the other one is they're desperate.
They're desperate and that's the saddest one.
Like someone just trying to figure out,
like I wonder if demons exist and they do these rituals
and nothing happens then that just confirms
what they think, but there are people who are desperate
who they're backs to the wall,
they don't have enough money, things like that.
So let's go ahead and hop in the carbonar copter.
Justin is also canoodling up to the real devil.
He's like, "Hey, you think I can get a job here?"
No, Justin, you can't.
You're going up to heaven like the rest of us.
Justin, let's go ahead and hop in that carbonar copter.
We're leaving behind Maman.
And we are headed out to the lower depths of hell.
Get that heat shielding ready and go.
(imitates gunfire)
Guys, go ahead and pick a number between one and five.
Choose carefully, because this will be the demon you summon.
There's 72 demons listed in the lesser key of Solomon.
It's this book that was anonymously written.
It was on demonology.
It's from the mid 17th century.
Then about a hundred years later,
the infernal dictionary came out,
which kind of piggybacks on and adds to the lore
of these 72 demons.
A lot of these demons are like demons of war
and demons of lust.
There's a demon that can make women take their clothes off,
which is also known as only fans.
There's a lot of these demons out here,
but I found the five lamest demons.
I went through the entire list and I found the five demons
that if you summoned them,
you would wish you were on some sort of hellish battlefield
fighting for glory.
Nope, nope.
Pick your number between one and five
and get ready to summon a loser demon.
(mouse clicks)
We're in the lower depths of hell.
We're walking around.
There's a bunch of cubicles there.
There's a bunch of demons at a call center.
They're waiting to get summoned.
They're like, "Ding it, he hasn't got the Albracely yet.
"Muman is like pound in the table.
"He's stuck down here."
We see a demon sitting in the corner named Andrea Puss.
Andrea Puss.
Andrea Puss is sitting, I don't even know
if he wants to summon this dude.
He's just sitting there and he's like,
"Hey guys, hey guys, come here real quick, come here."
And we know it's not gonna be real quick.
He knows he's gonna talk our ears off
'cause he's been doing this for 10,000 years.
He's never been summoned before.
Andrea Puss is a giant peacock
that's just kind of sitting there being like pssps.
Come over here, look at my feathers,
aren't they beautiful?
They're all on fire.
They're all burnt and cinched.
We're like, "Yeah, Andrea Puss, they look great."
And he's like, "Yeah, he's pretty dope, right?"
We're like, "Yeah, dude, they're super feel so bad
for this guy."
He screams a lot.
He screams a lot, right?
That's kind of his thing.
He raises great noises.
So when he's summoned him,
immediately there's just this giant peacock screaming
in your summoning circle.
Ah!
So you got that to deal with.
So first off, they don't list this in the summoning spell,
but wear earplugs.
Secondly, we've summoned Andrea Puss.
It's this giant peacock.
This is what this is, this infernal demon.
One of the angels that turned against God
and was thrown down to hell, this is what they do.
They don't teach the art of war.
They don't convince people to fall in love.
They will teach you though.
They will teach you.
Some of you guys might like this.
I would think it would be super boring.
Astronomy.
You're like Jason.
I would have loved to learn astronomy
from a giant peacock.
That's the most amazing thing ever.
Well, maybe, but I mean, like,
you're just gonna sit out in the boonies,
look up the night sky and there's this peacock going,
that's the big dipper.
Jason, that's not astronomy.
That's like third grade stuff.
He'll teach me how to like quasars and black holes.
And I'm on a peak, I just jump on the peacocks back
and fly around.
Okay, fine.
If you picked number five,
there's a little saddle that appears.
If you pick number five,
you can attach it to the back of Andrea Puss
and you can fly him around and you can look at stars.
But also, he knows geometry.
He knows geometry.
So you're like, Jason, I love geometry
and astronomy go together.
Fine, whatever.
Maybe you, I'm all disappointed.
I'm all disappointed.
I'm like, dang it.
I thought this one was fun.
I do think it's funny.
Giant peacock.
I imagine him with a little like tweed jacket
with the elbows, with the leather elbows.
He's teaching geometry.
Anyways, he teaches you a string.
You're like Jason.
These really, the five you chose.
Listen, that was the weakest one.
That was the weakest one out of the five.
I didn't think it was hilarious, but don't worry.
Now, I'm just not gonna be,
I'm just not gonna be crapping on sciences the whole time.
'Cause a lot of times these demons do teach you stuff.
But for whatever reason,
this giant peacock will teach you astronomy and geometry.
To me, that's dumb just 'cause I could get a book.
But you're like, Jason, you can learn
from a giant peacock or you can learn it from a book.
I'll learn it from a book.
So number five is flying around the universe
with this, I wish that big number five,
I'm still all disappointed in that one.
The sound of my voice, I'm like, oh man, you're like,
dude, that's, he's on the back of,
you're trying to summon a demon right now.
You're on the back of a peacock flying through the universe
and you're totally poo pooing it, Jason.
What's going on?
Whatever.
We're walking through this call center.
You're looking back up at number five.
You're like, take me with you.
We're walking through this call center still.
And we see a guy standing in the corner
and he has his back to us and he's like,
we don't know what he's doing.
We don't want to know it's hell.
All bets are off.
He's actually standing in the corner
'cause he's super shy.
He's all gross.
He's a big old monster, even by health standards.
When a demon is described as a monster,
you know it's bad.
When there are other demons
like the body of a spider, the head of a frog
and this guy's described as a monster,
you know things are bad.
You know he's getting made fun of.
This monster is named Bifrons.
He actually has like a pretty big backing.
He actually controls six legions of demons.
Go do that.
They're going to do that.
Just don't have to look at them anymore.
They're like, fine.
Just station us far away from you.
He's like, oh, I just want friends.
I want six legions of friends.
So you meet Bifrons and it's this monster man.
He's a looks like sloth from the Goonies.
But on fire and horribly burned.
Ugh, he's standing there.
And he goes, if you chose number one,
come with me young person, come with me
and we will go into my layer.
So he opens a door and you walk in
and it's actually pretty nice house.
Bifrons keeps the place clean.
You walk in, you sit on this little couch
and he goes, yes, you have chosen to summon me
by picking number one.
So what I can do for you is I teach science.
I teach the science and the arts.
You're like, you look at the door, you see me.
You're like, Jason, these aren't bad.
It's good to learn.
It's good to learn stuff.
And I'm like, hold on, hold on.
'Cause some of these demon skills overlap.
He teaches science and art.
So you see like all this beautiful artwork around.
You see like an astrolabe.
You see a photo of number five
in a peacock flying through space.
Like that's weird.
How do they get that photo already?
He also teaches you all about gems and wood.
Showing you emeralds.
He goes, this is an emerald and this is how it's formed.
And this is wood and this is how seeds grow.
He's telling you all of this stuff.
Tells you about herbs.
He's sitting there.
He's like, I know the real KFC recipe
and I'll share it with you
'cause you chose number one.
You're like, this is amazing.
But then he goes, I'm going to show you my favorite trick
'cause other demons know all about herbs and stuff too.
That's not their specialty.
This is my specialty.
He snaps his fingers
and now you're in a graveyard that goes on for eternity.
Bifrons is gone.
You're just looking at it.
Tombstone after tombstone.
(laughs)
He goes, my biggest trick.
The real reason they call me a monster
isn't because of my hideous face
but because of what I'm capable of.
You see, I'm able to transfer the corpse
from one grave into the other.
You're like, what?
It's the dumbest power ever.
He goes, I know.
I know, that's why he just shows me for this list.
Sure, I can teach you about the arts and the sciences.
I could just do my little do-do-do-do-do
and you see where you're standing.
That was the body of a woman
but now it's the body of a young boy.
So gross.
And he goes, I know in this eternal graveyard,
that's my hobby.
That's what I love to do.
I just have to mix and match the bodies
but that grave over there is missing one
and then you find yourself in a casket
and then by from,
he went from zero to 60 real quick.
Number five,
number five is on a peacock.
Exploring the universe, you're getting buried.
You're getting buried alive by a monster.
He's throwing dirt on the top of the coffin.
You're pounding, you're pounding.
But Bifron doesn't care.
He goes, another corpse for me to teleport
from casket to casket.
That is what Bifron loves to do.
I mean Bifrons.
That is what Bifrons loves to do.
So I just lost one fifth of my listeners.
They're like, I'm never listening to this show again.
It's horrible.
That's horrible.
I got buried alive.
Well, your ghost is floating around
the rest of the episode.
So, you know, there's that.
You just gotta float around with little Casper legs
and eat slime or odd dogs.
We're continuing to walk through this call center
and we see a man.
He's actually picking up a lot of phones.
He's like, yep, Croc-L right here.
Oh, man, you calling for Croc-L?
You calling for Croc-L?
We noticed the phones aren't plugged in.
He's just trying to seem like an important person.
Everyone else is like, oh, Croc-L, that's so,
that's so sad.
He's pretending he's getting phone calls.
He's going ring ring.
He's making the sound effect.
Croc-L is sitting there.
He actually shows up as an angel.
So long white robes, wings, the sandals,
a little halo.
He is in hell.
So it's not a great disguise down here.
We weren't fooled, but Croc-L is actually an angel.
But he likes to speak in what's known as dark
and mysterious ways.
So I assume he always puts like a gravelly voice on
like Christian Bale in Dark Knight,
which I'm not going to do because I have to do
two more demons after this and I don't want
to ruin my throat.
But he's like, nevermind, I'm not going to do
what I'm going to try.
And he turns to us and he goes, well, well, well,
I'm busy on this phone right now.
I'm taking a call, but let me put them on hold
and I will talk to you young people.
Croc-L says, if you chose the number three,
crawl underneath my wing.
We're looking at you.
We're looking at you like, I don't want to go,
I don't want to go.
And he's like inviting you to underneath his wing.
It's all dirty.
It's all super dirty.
And you crawl under his wing if you chose number three
and he envelopes you.
And then you teleport away.
And now you're in a classroom.
You're in a classroom and it's just you sitting
at a desk, all the other desks are empty.
And Croc-L is standing there with a tweed jacket
and a little leather on his elbows.
Croc-L is known to teach geometry
as well as the other liberal sciences.
So you can actually get a pretty good degree
from this guy.
The Peacock, sure you can travel the universe,
but you're just going to learn one subject.
From Croc-L you can actually get like an associates degree.
It'll take a while, right?
It'll take a while, but liberal sciences plus geometry,
that'll be your math elective, you're good to go.
So at your graduation, you're there for two years,
you actually get your associates degree.
I've recorded two years worth of episodes,
you gotta catch up.
But you eventually do graduate from Croc-L University.
And on your graduation day, he goes,
"Now I'm going to show you what I'm really known for."
You're like, "Damn it, I know something bad's going to happen."
Crawl underneath my wing.
Crawl underneath my wing again.
You're like, "Oh man, that's where you've had
to sleep every night, that was your dorm room."
And you're all underneath his wings.
He takes you out into a beautiful lush field.
You just see rolling hills of green grass
and you're walking around and you're like,
"Oh, this is pretty dope, dude."
And he's like, "I know, I know, it is pretty dope.
It is my special power of all the demon powers.
This is what I'm most known for."
He goes, "Do you hear that?"
Splish, splash, splash, splash, splash, splash.
You're like, "I do it."
Sounds like it's water all around me.
And he goes, "I know, splish, splash, splish, splash.
My ability is helping people find water."
And you go, "That actually kind of makes sense
out of all the stuff you've talked about."
That makes sense, like in olden times,
you would want to find wells.
So calling on a demon who could actually help you
locate water, natural springs, things like that
would be super useful.
Sure, if you were trying to build the pyramids,
you might want to know geometry,
but if you're just trying to live your life,
Croquel is the dude.
And while he's helping you find water,
he can teach you a little bit about the humanities.
So you're walking around and you're like,
"Look, over there."
And it's a little body of water.
And he goes, "Mm-hmm."
And then you go, "Look, over there."
And he's like, "I know where all the water is at everywhere.
You don't have to keep telling me."
He's gonna, he spent two years with you at this point.
He's a little tired.
And he goes, "Go ahead and take a swim.
Go ahead and take all your clothes off.
And take a swim.
Little Croquel, watch a naked human swim around
in the water."
And you're like, "Uh..."
So you take your clothes off
and you're swimming around in the water
and Croquel's just standing there
standing there for an uncomfortable amount of time.
And then you notice the water's getting warmer.
You're like, "Oh..."
And then he realized that it keeps getting warmer
and warmer and you're like,
"Oh no, am I gonna get boiled alive by this guy?"
And he's getting warmer and warmer.
And then it stops getting warm
because he can make water warm.
He can't make it hot.
He can't make it boil, but he can make water warm.
So if you chose number three,
if you chose number three,
you got an associate's degree
and you found a nice warm bath.
You got to take a warm bath.
You didn't get to take one for two years.
But now you got a degree in one hand,
holding a diploma.
The rest of you is submerged in warm water.
No tricks.
That's actually it.
So this episode is a little inconsistent, I know.
But that would be lame.
If you went through the trouble of summoning a demon
and all they did was say, "Look, again,
if I was an old, timey dude,
that would be super useful.
But nowadays..."
Jason, I can't believe you gave such a gruesome ending.
I totally expected to get boiled alive
that other person got buried alive.
Ah, they'll get used to it.
Or the oxygen will run out, one of the two.
As we're walking through the call center,
we see a crocodile in there.
We're like, "That's weird, right?"
We didn't know if there was any animals in here.
Do animals have souls?
Or they go, "What did a crocodile do to go to hell?"
But then we see a little bit more of the crocodile.
And we see like it's two little legs,
and we see more of it.
And then we see an old man,
an old pale naked dude sitting on this crocodile.
And I turn.
I turn to you guys and go,
"If you picked number two,
"that's you, right?"
You're gonna, you know,
this naked old guy,
riding on the back of a crocodile.
We're looking at a gauri's.
He's sitting there on his crocodile, he's petting it.
He's like, "You wanna pet my crocodile?"
He says, "It's straddling it.
"You wanna pet my crocodile number two?"
And you walk, "Oh man."
So you're like petting it.
And the crocodile's actually pretty chill, dude.
It's just kind of like relaxing, you're scratching it.
Do crocodiles have ears?
You're scratching it behind the eyes.
It's like, "Oh yeah, that's the spot."
A gauri's has 31 legions of demons.
So a lot of people are listening to this old man
on the back of a crocodile.
You know you have to be pretty low-down with a total pole
if you get your orders from a naked old man.
You know that you're not doing too well.
People are like, "Who's your boss?"
Ah, dude, it's awesome.
It's this guy with like eight wings,
10 eyes, flames for vocal cords.
Who's your boss?
Old, naked man on a crocodile?
Oh man.
A gauri says, "Hop on the back of my crocodile, kid."
We're going on a little adventure and then he winks.
There's a little magical wink.
And (whooshing)
Crocodile's walking hella slow, dude.
Crocodiles are like, "What are the slow?"
How did you pick that as your motor transportation?
Crocodiles are super slow.
They can go 30 miles an hour.
So it like zips along for a bit
and then just starts going real slow again.
You're riding the back of this crocodile.
And a gauri takes you to a New York street.
The year is 1982.
There's a bunch of muggers on the street.
They're having a mugger convention.
They're mugging each other.
You just see random acts of violence
in the streets of New York.
It's loud.
It's smelly.
There's a crocodile walking down Times Square.
You're sitting on the back and super weird.
There's a naked man driving it.
No one's even paying attention.
The city is such a cesspool at this point.
And a gauri says, "You know why we're here, boy?"
He's calling you boy, which is making you super uncomfortable.
The fact that you're with this old man,
he keeps referring to how young you are.
He keeps referring to you that,
but he doesn't mean it that way.
He's unintentionally creepy.
He puts his hands on your knee.
He turns around and he says,
"You know why we're here, boy?
I have the ability to help find runaways."
You're like, "What?
That's kind of weird.
That's kind of a bizarre ability to have."
He's like, "Yeah, why didn't you get in line quick enough?"
I was running an alligator.
When they were giving out special powers,
I was the last in line.
I have the ability to find runaways.
So he sits there and he goes,
"Runaways, come back."
And then you see a couple people go, "Huh, what?"
They get out of their cardboard houses,
or one of them is about to step off the bus
and they look up and then they get back on the bus
and the guy who gets out of the cardboard house
walks out, picks up the phone, calls his mom,
"I'm coming back home, mom."
I just heard a crocodile yell,
"Runaways, come home."
The mom's like, "Billy, are you still doing drugs?"
Yes, I am, but I'm still coming home.
He has the ability to find runaways.
He also has the, that's fine, that's noble, right?
And again, I think that would make sense
in like a hunter-gatherer society
'cause if you ran away from that,
you're like, "Are you gonna go gather more stuff?"
Yeah, sure, and then you run off
and you're at like some arcade.
You invent an arcade here in the middle of the wilderness,
playing arcade.
In early societies, people would run away,
they would almost always die
and it would definitely impact the society.
So to have a demon that could actually hunt down runaways
or send them back home, that's pretty noble.
I could see people using that.
But then they also have the ability,
this is weird, it's not an opposite thing.
(laughs)
When I read this, I go, "What, it doesn't make sense.
"What's the opposite of a runaway to you?"
He has this power that if you're standing still,
he can make you run.
That's not the opposite of a runaway.
That doesn't make any sense.
What does he have that power?
Someone's checking, there was someone's walking down the street
and they stopped to check their watch
and then all of a sudden they're like in Toronto,
they're like, "What am I doing here?"
They ran all the way.
Doesn't make any sense.
Why would you have an opposite power?
The person who talked to you was strong to me.
He also didn't give you brain damage.
It was just the thing he did.
He didn't have to do an opposite.
Now if you picked number two,
you've been running for a couple days now,
you got great legs but you're like,
please let this torment end.
And every show often he goes,
"Runaways, come back."
And then you show back at his house,
that's you live with him now.
That's where he returned to.
And you'll talk for a bit.
And you have to constantly be moving.
If you stand still for just a moment,
you start running away.
But after this goes on for a millennium or two,
after he gets tired of dealing with this,
he's gonna teach you a new power,
the power he's most known for.
He says, "Come here, you look so good."
You're a young man, you've grown up so much.
Ooh, look at those legs.
Now it is creepy.
He goes, "Listen."
I've taught you about running.
You can't teach me about running away.
You made me run away.
He's like, "Okay, okay.
Now I'm gonna teach you my biggest power."
And then the earth begins to move under your feet.
(groaning)
You're pretending to be shocked.
You just want this to be over with.
You're like, "Oh, okay, this is so amazing."
He has the power to cause earthquakes.
Agarys has the power to actually destroy the land.
So because you've been such a noble servant of his,
such good entertainment, running everywhere,
he touches you and gives you the power to create earthquakes.
He has another power.
He has the power to teach you immoral expressions.
Technically he has the power to cause earthquakes as well.
But I can't think of anything funny to do with that.
So instead, we're gonna skip that superpower
that's actually functional in the real world.
Like you could fight crime,
but like burglars are trying to break into a bank
and you're like, "Not today."
You can't come with good catch lines.
You spent 2,000 years in hell.
But then you shake the world
and you destroy all of civilization
to stop two bank robbers.
They drop the coins.
You're like, "Another job done for number two."
You turn around and the world is flattened.
There's no building standing.
Hey, nevermind.
I check out something funny.
That's what happened.
If you picked number two,
you try to use your powers for good,
but you accidentally kill everyone,
stopping a bank robbery.
There you go.
That is if you pick number two.
We got one more left.
I'm not running out of steam.
I swear, it's just getting really hot in here.
Now it's just me and number four
walking through the Hellish Call Center
and there's a dark room off to the side.
If you pick number four,
you gotta open that dark door in hell
and walk through it.
Hello, hello, hello.
Is anyone here?
Here?
You don't hear anything,
but you can sense there's something in this room.
And you hear someone go,
"My name is Gamigen."
That's a real demon name.
It's not a D&D character that a 12-year-old came up with.
"I am Gamigen and I see that you're here to summon me."
You're like, "Yeah."
I'm the one who started this episode
and I was curious, so I kept finishing it
and I picked number four, so here we are.
What are you gonna do to me?
And he goes, "I am going to teach you
"the liberal sciences like that other dude."
That other dude, previous, but that warm bath thing.
That's lame, man.
I'm a gossip.
I'm the worst kind of gossip.
I gossip about people after they die.
I can actually tell you,
people who have died the sins they've committed.
You're like, "Well, yeah, I mean, I guess that'd be more
"useful if you told me what they were doing
"while they were alive.
"Can't really do anything about it after they're dead.
"If they're stealing from me,
"I kind of want to know about it while they're alive."
He goes, "Yeah, not the best trait,
"but it's way better than that warm bath thing."
And you're like, "Yeah, it is way better."
He goes, "I can also, if that didn't sell you on it,
"you want to know I can tell you about people who drowned.
(laughs)
"I can tell you, I can name every single person
"who's ever drowned in the history of the world."
Argy, Argalo, he starts naming him off
and he gets the D and you're like, "Oh my God,
"how much time has passed?
"I don't want to keep hearing people
"drawn in the ocean."
That's horrible, he's like, "No, no, no, drowned at sea."
I don't know the people who died in oceans
or tributaries or lakes,
only people who drowned in the sea.
You're like, "What?
"That's even more useless.
"He's like, "Yeah, yeah, I guess that's why
"they keep me in this little room."
But you see, unlike those other demons
who eventually leave, I'm sorry about your friend,
you got buried alive.
(laughs)
It was so grim compared to the rest of them.
They leave eventually.
I stick with you forever and ever and ever.
You'll never get rid of me.
Good old gammy-gin, friend to the end, that's my motto.
Also, I can name everyone who died in the sea,
that's also my motto, that's underneath the motto.
You're like, "Oh man."
And then you see gammy-gin.
He walks towards you.
It's a little pony.
Gammy-gin shows up as a pony
who will never leave your side.
He gives you a little saddle that's just for you.
He made it out of human flesh
of people who drowned in the sea.
You're like, "Ugh, gross, do I have to use this?"
He's like, "Yes."
And put this bit in my mouth.
This is feet out of the or bones of sinners.
You're like, "Ugh, gross."
But you get on top of gammy-gin, your friend to the end,
a little pony that you get to ride out of hell.
And for the rest of your life,
you're sitting now, you have to go back to your real college.
He's answering all the questions.
He's like, "Ugh, actually, no."
Emily Dinkinsen did not mean that in her poem.
I know I'm a talking pony from hell.
You actually, that is good.
So you get to have a friend to the end.
You get to have a pony right around whenever you,
like I said, account sheep at night.
He just names off the list of the dead who've died at sea.
And somehow you find that calming.
He's the best man at your wedding.
He's like helping you tie your bow.
He throws your bachelor party.
It's a bunch of demon babes show up.
This is an amazing thing.
Gammigan truly is your friend to the end.
On your deathbed, you're laying there.
You're like, "Gammigan, now that I'm super old and naked
"and I'm about to crawl on top of this crocodile,
"I want you to know that you truly were my friend.
"I never would have made it
"through all those liberal art classes
"if it wasn't for your jokes.
"And you constantly setting the teacher on fire.
"Oh, the days.
"And then you were always by my side.
"All that stuff, all those memories.
"This was a beautiful moment, Gammigan.
"And you're like petting his mane.
"And he's like trying to hold back a tear.
"The first tear that this demon has cried
"since he was thrust out of heaven.
"And Gammigan looks at you and goes,
"I love you, number four.
"You never learned your name.
"Throughout all of that,
"he never ever learned your name.
"He called you number four the whole time.
"But then he goes, I love you,
"but I want to remember you.
"I want to make sure that I never forget you.
"And you're like, no, Gammigan.
"No, please just let me die peacefully.
"He grabs you with his hooves.
"He grabs you with his ultra strong hooves.
"He drags you out of bed
"where you were about to die peacefully.
"He drags you across the country to a sea,
"a glimmering sea underneath the moon.
"And he holds you down with those little hooves.
"He holds your head underwater.
"And as you gurgle and gas for air,
"he goes, if you drown at sea, I'll never forget you.
"I'll never forget you.
"I'll never forget you."
So there you go.
(crickets chirping)
If you picked, who got buried alive?
I don't even remember who got buried alive now.
But if you picked number four,
I think it was the even ones that got shafted this episode.
If you picked number four,
or number, who did get buried alive?
I don't remember.
So if you picked number one,
number four, you did not have a good,
well, at least number four had a long life.
So there we go.
Episode 666 of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I hope there are 666 more episodes,
and further and further on.
Guys, I hope you had as much fun listening
to this episode as I had recording it.
I had an absolute ball,
but it is time for me to return to the crypt.
Also known as my recliner in the living room,
so I can watch episodes with practical jokers
and other YouTube videos.
(evil laughter)
(upbeat music)
(speaking in foreign language)