A string of arsons strike the city of Vancouver, British Columbia.
The target?
Mason lodges.
Are we going to talk about that?
I don't know.
This last episode of season 13 has been such a struggle.
I do have some stories though for you.
Maybe that one?
Maybe that one we'll see.
Are Nickelodeon theme songs haunted by angels?
And then some other stuff?
I don't know.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, and I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
I'd like to say we have a bunch of stuff to cover.
But I do have stuff in mind I want to talk about and it is related to the topic.
I'm not just going to start doing movie reviews.
But this is the end of season 13.
I'm physically beat.
I'm mentally beat.
But in good ways.
I think we're ending off season 13 really strong.
I can't say that in the straight face.
This episode might be a little wobbly.
Just like yesterday's episode, I have recorded a full episode for the season finale.
Wasn't good enough.
This one will be better.
The other one just didn't have any energy to it.
I wanted to pick some stories that I'm kind of excited about and are kind of more personal
type stories.
Not personal stories.
Personal observations.
Personal conspiracy theory type of things.
Which you guys do seem to like.
But before we get started on any of that, let's introduce our newest Patreon supporter.
Uh uh uh uh.
Duh duh duh duh duh duh.
This incomes our newest Patreon supporter, Wiz's Carb.
Everyone give a round of applause to Wiz's Carb.
He's dressed up like a boy band memories in a white suit.
Just like those boy bands in the 1990s.
Duh duh duh duh duh.
Now we all have white suits on.
We're all doing matching boy band moves.
Trust me.
This is better.
This is better than the last version, okay?
Last version was super boring.
Wiz's Carb.
You're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or if you don't know all the moves, we're gonna
spend a lot of time practicing.
Just help to get the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
We're gonna get into why Wiz's Carb is dressed up like a boy band member in a second.
Let's actually talk about this Mason's thing.
I was joking in the beginning.
I do want to talk about it, but we don't really have a lot of information to go off
of.
What happened was, actually before I'm totally getting ahead of myself, Wiz's Carb, let's
go ahead and hop into Jason Jalopy.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We were headed up to Vancouver, Canada.
It's a really bizarre story.
This just happened on March 30th, 2021 and anyone who knows anything about conspiracy
theories knows the number three is very powerful and I always poo poo that stuff.
But that doesn't mean that people who are into it find it very important.
Do you know what I mean?
I don't think there's any difference between committing an act on the 33rd day than there
is on the 7th day or the 12th day or anything like that.
But to someone who believes in it, it is very, very important for them to follow these numbers.
So 33-0, 2021, three Mason Lodges in Vancouver, Canada were set on fire within 90 minutes.
This wasn't an accident, it wasn't bad wiring and all three of them.
We know that for a fact because the suspect who has not been named has been arrested.
He was actually walking out of the third location with a gas can and an off-duty cop
is walking by and there's flames coming out of a building.
The cop is looking at the guy with the can walking away home in a jaunty tune and the
guy is looking at the building and the guy is in his car and the cop looks back at the
building and the guy is starting to drive away.
The cop actually does start wrestling the dude.
The dude gets away but the cop is like "Okay, I'll just do this" and he pulls out his phone
and he writes down the license plate and calls it in.
They arrest him.
They haven't revealed the name yet because in Canada apparently, this is a pretty good
law, you can't name someone until they've actually been arrested.
Actually, that's a terrible law.
What if someone is on the run from the cops?
They're like "There's a mass murderer and he might be buying a plane ticket to leave
the country and kill again in another country but we can't tell you who."
The airline's like "Oh, I'm sure there are.
I'm sure they can tell other cops.
I'm sure they can warn other cops."
They're like "Who should we be on lookout for?"
They're like "I can't tell."
But anyways, the media, they won't reveal to media.
But anyways, so he burned these things.
We know it's a 42 year old man.
That's all we know.
Here's my take on this.
The arsonist believed that the Masons were an evil group of people and he waited until
3030 to set all this stuff on fire.
There's also a question, because I mentioned it on a previous episode but I didn't actually
do the story about the, what was it, the 40 days blood ritual, the sacrifice, the mass
sacrifice days that are coming.
I researched a bunch of it and recorded it and then had a scrap and I don't really remember.
But anyways, they supposedly were in this time period, like the 40 days of the feast
of the beast.
That sounds like something, sounds like a special sale down at the local hometown buffet.
"All you can eat for $6.66.
Feast of the beast."
It could be related to that.
My take on it is this guy is an anti-masonic conspiracy theorist and he set it on fire.
However, I think we'll see conspiracy theories go around that the Masons set their own buildings
on fire because they committed some sort of blood sacrifice there and they had to cover
up the evidence.
Because you know, whenever you're committing a crime you do it in three separate locations.
But I think that'll be the conspiracy theory that grows out of this.
He probably would have kept burning them down if he hadn't been stopped.
I think it was the anti-masonic guy, but we'll see.
He could just be a crazy guy who had a thing against compasses and pyramids and was like
eyeballs and he decided to blow up any building that had that stuff in there.
Also linking to where we're going to see conspiracy theories come out of this.
I keep saying that, but it's so hard.
This is really interesting, but I went on a couple conspiracy boards and I didn't even
see them talking about this.
So who knows?
Everyone's so wrapped up in flat earth and the sky is fake and all this dumb stuff.
This stuff, people should be eating it up, but my theory again is that he's anti-masonic.
He's burning it down.
One of the lodges is completely burned to the ground.
You can't save it.
They have no sense of life support.
They have a little IV bag full of cement.
One of these masonic lodges just like a week or two ago, about five minutes away, a man
walked into a library and did a mass stabbing.
He murdered a woman and then stabbed six other people and then tried stabbing himself and
the cops caught him.
So just five minutes away from one of these lodges that burned down.
So I think you'll see conspiracy theory within conspiracy theory within conspiracy theory
in this.
Yeah, interesting story.
And I'm honestly surprised we don't see more.
As much as people seriously believing in conspiracy theories, I'm surprised we don't see more of
this type of stuff.
And we may in the future.
We really may in the future.
So remember that guy tried driving that train into the boat during the whole coronavirus
thing.
When the USS Comfort, when President Trump ordered that boat off the coast of LA to work
as like a makeshift hospital.
A guy was a captain of a train and he tried crashing the train into this military vessel
because he believed that it was all fake, that the coronavirus was fake.
Everything.
He was trying to expose the truth.
We had that other guy covered a long time ago who took an armored car and blocked the
Hoover Dam and held up a sign saying release the AIG report.
Which was supposed to be the...
Remember it's so funny because looking at these things they were so important to conspiracy
theory.
Do you guys even remember the AIG report?
Super early in President Trump's administration.
I covered it in like episode six or seven.
This guy blocked the Hoover Dam and put up a sign saying release the AIG report.
The AIG report was basically supposed to be whoever the Attorney General was back then.
I don't remember.
It was supposed to be the whole thing about arresting Hillary Clinton and Q and things
like that.
And he's, I think he got sentenced recently to like 10, 20 years in prison because it
was considered a terrorist act.
The train guy I haven't heard from.
But he's my personal buddy.
I'm like, "Hey Alan, what's up?
What's up train guy?"
It's not like I would personally hear from him.
It's why I shift from side to side, don't come looking for me FBI.
But yeah, those conspiracy theories were so important and people have acted on them.
This is Carbs.
Let's call in the dead rabbit dirgeable.
We are going to leave behind Vancouver.
We are headed out to Hollywood.
Dead rabbit dirgeable is taking the slow yet fun journey.
It's the last episode of the season.
So technically I should want to get there as soon as possible.
And as we're flying out there, here's a little, here's a little, why should come up a name
with this segment?
Jason's thoughts.
Jason just thinking.
How's that?
He's just thinking.
A long time ago I was at the Goodwill with my little brother and I said, "Hey, let's
have a contest.
Let's see who can find the saddest thing.
Let's see who can find the most sad thing."
Now I've done this before like Best Buy.
I'm not trying to find the saddest thing at Best Buy.
It's a tiny television.
No, at Best Buy I would have this game with Josh.
Josh Moore Meyer.
It's like, let's find the suckiest movie.
So we'd each have to find the worst movie and it'd be like this game.
Whoever picked the worst movie won.
It was fun.
But at Goodwill, at Goodwill, you can't find the best movie.
Let's find the saddest thing.
My little brother got a crutch because he goes, "This means someone's been injured.
The only time you have a crutch is when you've been injured."
I got a PlayStation 2 memory card.
I'm a little rough.
What?
What is that?
And I go, "On this card," and I'm holding my card right now, "On this card is unfinished
video games.
This card is literally full of people's achievements that were never finished.
Inside this card are hopes and dreams of beating levels, of saving the princess, of
ridding San Andreas, of corrupt police, and they will never ever be played again."
Now we argued over who actually picked the worst one.
But on my vacation, the reason why I was thinking about that, on my vacation I pulled my PS2
out of storage.
I keep talking about it and play video games for the next few weeks when I'm on vacation
from the show.
And yeah, I put this in and it had a couple games on there, Grand Theft Auto, that hasn't
been played, San Andreas of course, from 2009.
So yeah, it's weird.
I think it's true.
On these memory cards, we use them.
They're so important to us.
I don't even know what type of memory the new system uses.
Apparently I'm a grandpa.
But yeah, I just think it's interesting.
These memory cards are the digital version of the self storage locker.
That's always the thing.
Self storage is where dreams go to die.
I say it's where dreams go to be delayed.
But of course, some dreams do die off.
You buy the guitar, you never use it, you pluck around on it a bit, but then you don't
take it seriously and then it ends up in the self storage because you say you're going
to pick it up again someday.
Well, the memory card, I'm not saying to go play your PSDs today.
I am going to play some 2007 WWE vs.
Raw, this vacation.
I'm going to have a lot of fun with that and Ghost Rider and Jackass, the video game.
X-Men Origins Wolverine.
Never played that, but I have it.
But I like to say dreams delayed because like I was saying in the beginning, my 90 days
to a better you for me was lifting weights and I'm seeing those cuts in my, not my cuts
on my skin, I'm dropping the weights.
I'm starting to see my body to return to what it was when I was in my 20s.
I can look at my calves and see those little definition lines and I can look in my arms
and definitely my shoulders.
Everything's filling out.
So my Jason's just thinking was about how memory cards are full of dreams delayed and
possibly denied.
But don't let your dreams be denied.
It's okay to delay them.
But don't delay them too long.
And that was Jason's just thinking.
Let's go.
Wizis Khalifa is like, what is going on?
Wizis Khalifa land.
Wizis Khalifa.
You didn't know that?
He has now changed his name from Wiz Khalifa and he's now supporting the Patreon.
WizisCarbs.
I don't know how many times I've said Wiz Khalifa this episode.
Sorry, bro.
WizisCarbs.
Bring that dead rabbit dirgible down here in Hollywood.
Here's another.
This is a Jason's just thinking or this is a Jason's just stretching.
But I actually have wanted to talk about this for a while.
Longtime listeners of the show know that back in the mid-2000s, really for a long time,
like early 2000s, up until around 2011, up until I moved away from the area, I did a
lot of babysitting.
I lived with my grandma and they didn't have the energy to take care of all of their grandkids.
But I did.
So my boy Billy, I hung out with him, Logan and who are the other ones?
Logan and Billy and Chuck, I don't know who the other ones were.
Bobby maybe?
Maybe?
Billy and Logan were the ones that hung them and Austin, I hung out with him all the time
too.
Little dudes.
And when you're babysitting and I babysat some other people's kids too.
Jackie's kids, I babysat Jackie's kids and Kara's kids.
And when you're babysitting, you end up watching young people's shows.
So I watch a lot of Nickelodeon, I watch a lot of Disney Channel and there's some pretty
good stuff on there.
So I've been rewatching some of those shows on Netflix.
And usually it's before I'm going to bed because it's all, no matter what horrible news I've
been reading during the day or no matter what happened, I can always go and before I go
to bed, watch two or three episodes of Victorious, it's normally on the background or now Big
Time Rush is on Netflix.
It's like the number four show on Netflix.
And I just got done watching Big Time Rush when I started the show.
When I started Dead Rabbit Radio, I would talk about Big Time Rush from time to time.
It's good stuff.
I think it's quality show, it's funny, and it's also a good palette cleanser from reading
True Crime and reading all this depressing stuff all day long.
But I started to notice something in the theme songs.
But there's always been this long controversy that Nickelodeon is connected to Satanic stuff.
And it goes way far back.
And the most recent one that I saw connected to was, it was such an odd detail.
This part's not odd.
Nickelodeon was supporting the Black Lives Matter movement.
That's fine, right?
That's not the odd part.
But they would have this montage, and you can see it on YouTube.
I'll put it in the show notes.
There was this montage where it was like Nickelodeon believes Black Lives Matter, and then it said
like Black Culture Matters, and it had these other things.
And then one of them said Black Magic Matters.
And people were like Black Culture, Black Lives, totally understand.
Black Magic, there's only one.
I don't know the person.
And it's like these quick flashes too.
And I remember hearing it and not believing it.
So I looked it up and I was like, well, I mean, there it is.
Black Magic Matters.
Now they could be talking about like, you know, like the magic of the culture.
They could be talking about like the magic of, you know, the entire society.
But that's normally not what that term means.
Black Magic.
It normally has a negative connotation.
Even among magic users.
You have white magicians and gray magicians and like witches and wikens.
Black Magic is still, it has a negative connotation.
And it's not negative towards the black community, but it's definitely, it has that connotation.
And that is just the newest thing.
I was seeing stuff about Luminati.
There's like an Illuminati logo, you know, like the triangle with the eye in it, going
way back into Nickelodeon's past.
And then some of the choices they've used for the show.
I remember a long time ago when I was more believing in conspiracy theories.
And I say that, doesn't mean I don't believe in them anymore.
But I used to be really, really like into them.
Like believed them.
I remember once there was an episode of Icarly where she fights Victoria Justice.
Who's not a superhero if you're unfamiliar with that name.
It's not a superhero.
It's an actual woman.
Icarly was fighting Victoria Justice.
And it was this whole boxing match or kickboxing match or something like that.
I haven't seen the episode in years.
For no reason at all.
Let me look it up here real quick.
I didn't plan on going on this ramp, but let me look this up here.
So in the episode I fight Shelby Marks.
What was it?
Damn it.
I gotta look it back.
I fight Shelby Marks is the name of this episode.
For whatever reason, Icarly has to fight Shelby Marks who is a kickboxer played by Victoria
Justice.
This is the Nickelodeon show.
Fine, whatever, whatever.
But for no reason at all.
They never acknowledge it in the show.
Shelby Marks's logo is like a bull's head.
And it's a picture of like a bull.
They never at it.
Her name's not Shelby the bull marks.
They never reference it on her workout or on her fighting outfit is a picture.
It's a red circle with a bull.
It's snout appears to be bloody and it has horns.
And you could even argue it's not a bull.
It looks.
If you're a conspiracy theorist, it looks out of place.
It looks satanic.
And on her gloves are red stars.
Which when held in a certain way look like upside down pentagrams.
A reach?
Definitely.
But I remember I was watching the show back when I was more in a conspiracy theory and
that peaked my interest.
I go, why is she wearing that horned?
Why she like they never mentioned it in the show.
She's just wearing a picture of a bull with like a red snout and these horns.
And you know like is it mo-lock or something like that.
And then she has the gloves with the red stars on them.
Which again when her hands are held in a certain fashion blah blah blah.
It doesn't mean anything.
I thought it was weird.
I thought it was a weird detail to add.
So Nickelodeon has been tied a lot into Illuminati theory.
Brainwashing the youth.
Stuff like that.
Kind of standard Illuminati conspiracy theory.
So I'm watching the shows and watching Victorious and the theme song.
This is banned from YouTube week so I can actually sing these theme songs.
You don't have to listen to them.
Let me sing you a bit of this song here.
This is the Victorious theme song.
So Victoria Justice ended up getting her own television show called Victorious.
It's about a group.
It's like fame.
It's like a new version of fame.
It's about a group of kids.
They're Hollywood high and their classes are singing and acting and dancing and they're
all trying to become successful artists.
It's actually a pretty funny show.
I always rate stuff on how funny is it compared to network television.
Like 2 and a half men or Big Bang Theory or stuff like that.
And it's not as funny as say Arrested Development or Modern Family but it's light years funnier
than Big Bang Theory or 2 and a half men.
So they're actually pretty well put together.
But anyways.
Take a look at these lyrics for the show Victorious.
I can't play you the song because I'm not willing to take that copyright risk.
But you don't have to be afraid to put your dream in action.
You're never going to get to the song.
It's better than that.
But here deal.
You're going to have to roll with this.
You don't have to be afraid to put your dream in action.
You're never going to fade.
You'll be the main attraction.
Not a fantasy.
Just remember me.
When it turns out right.
Cause you know that if you live in your imagination tomorrow you'll be everybody's fascination.
It's an interesting lyric.
It's an interesting lyric and very uplifting right?
The song is called Make It Shine.
It's about...
Well it's interesting because the song is about like making it.
Making off not really knowing where they're at but eventually they make it shine.
But let's look at these lines again.
We're not going to sing them.
Remember the show ran for three seasons.
It ran much longer on repeats.
It was in constant rotation.
Now it's on endless rotation on Netflix.
You don't have to be afraid to put your dream in action.
That's a great line.
You're never going to fade.
You'll be the main attraction.
Not a fantasy.
Just remember me.
When it turns out right.
What we're seeing in that line is the law of attraction.
What we're seeing in that line is the science of getting rich.
Which is the book I talk about all the time.
This song is really talking about the secret.
Cause you know if you live in your imagination tomorrow you'll be everybody's fascination.
By visualizing it you can have it.
So this is what I find so fascinating about this.
The conspiracy theory that Nickelodeon is run by the Illuminati.
But this song is very uplifting.
And not only is this song uplifting it actually I believe in the science of getting rich.
I believe you have to work hard and you have to visualize it.
The strength gains I've made in my body.
I give 60% to physically lifting more than I was lifting two weeks previous.
And 40% to visualizing myself getting stronger constantly.
You gotta do both.
This song is actually giving young people the secrets.
It's not just about hard work.
It's not just about imagination.
You have to do both.
You have to put the dream in action.
And you have to live in your imagination.
And what's super weird about this.
What's super weird about this.
Is basically this song could be considered a spell.
It's a very very positive song.
And you're listening to it on repeat as the show's playing over and over again.
The cast of the show, Victorious, you have Victoria Justice who was the star.
You have Elizabeth Giles or Gillies.
She went on to be in the remake of Dallas.
She left the show and ended up doing the remake of Dallas.
Victoria Justice has had done a few projects here and there.
But the big star to come out of Victorious is one of the biggest stars in the world.
Ariana Grande.
Ariana Grande is on the level of like a Madonna at this point.
She is a global superstar.
There are still people who would be like, "Who's Cardi B?"
Everyone knows who Ariana Grande is.
Whether or not you like her music, she's put out hit after hit.
She's on like album number seven.
Like she's just been, and she releases, sometimes she'll release like two albums in a year.
She's like a monster.
I covered her on an episode.
She's really into the paranormal.
She's really into supernatural.
She'd probably love this show.
But what's so fascinating about this is you have, and when she was doing the show she
was 15 years old.
She's a side character.
Not a fantasy.
Just remember me when it turns out right.
That is the theme song for the show.
Throughout the opening credits they're showing Victoria Justice walking to school.
They're showing the cute boy number one waving his hand.
They show cute boy number two with his marionette puppet.
Not a fantasy.
Just remember me when it turns out right.
Ariana Grande appears on screen.
Like right when they show her picture we're getting that line.
It's not a fantasy.
It wasn't a fantasy.
It was putting your imagination and combining it with your dream.
Put it into action.
Is it possible that this song is a spell?
Out of all seven characters on that show, the other most popular guy was the teacher,
was the voice of Plankton from SpongeBob.
Which I think they just grabbed him from that set and took him to this one.
What if you had crafted a song that was a good spell?
A positive spell?
And it plays over and over and over again every time that episode is aired.
Every time they're in the editing bay.
Every time they are assembling this episode and it's sitting on these DVDs to be shipped
off to the studio to actually be aired and they're constantly going through this and
it's always playing that line and always showing Ariana Grande's picture.
And she's the biggest star of the show by multitudes.
Like not even close.
There's a lot of talent on that show but Ariana Grande outshines them all.
Is the song a spell?
So did the people who even wrote that song knew they were crafting a spell?
And are there more songs out there like that?
I don't think so.
To both of those.
I think this was a fluke.
I think a lot of magic could be flukes.
But it's interesting nonetheless and it's interesting because it comes out of a place
that is very very closely associated with Illuminati, with darkness.
The conspiracy theorist hate Nickelodeon.
Absolutely hate it.
Now even when I was a conspiracy theorist I knew funny.
Like I think the jokes are funny.
Plus I was with a bunch of kids.
I can't watch like Homicide Live on the street right?
Or I couldn't even watch 2 and a half men.
I was watching this stuff.
It's funny.
But yeah, you wonder how many other spells are out there?
Sitting on albums.
Just a fluke.
An accident.
The songwriter didn't know they were actually crafting something that powerful.
Just sitting out there.
Waiting to be discovered.
So Wiz's Khalifa.
Dammit!
So Wiz's Carves.
Let's go ahead and leave.
What if it is really Wiz Khalifa?
He's enjoying the show.
Wiz's Carves.
Go ahead and call in the Carbentercopter.
We are leaving behind Hollywood Hills.
We are going to travel out to Finland.
But first, do you like board games?
And murder?
Dun dun dun.
Then the dark comedic thriller Murder Berry.
Murder Berry Win.
Burry, you know like Digging a Hole.
Is for you.
I point right at you.
Critically acclaimed on the festival circuit.
And winner of the best feature at Phoenix Fear Con.
Murder Berry Win.
Winners on three aspiring board game designers who have to dispose of a body.
With few options available, they turn to their game for guidance.
The premise of their game?
How to murder someone and get rid of the body.
Pre-order now and you'll receive the original deck of cards as featured in the film for
free.
Details at MurderBerryWin.com.
Wiz's Carves as you're flying us out.
This is why I was laughing during the promo read.
It's a good movie.
Check it out.
But Wiz's Carves as you're flying us out to Finland, you start to notice that my voice
starts to change.
It starts to sound like this next story we're going into.
I recorded for a different episode.
For a different episode.
But that's just the altitude.
That's just because we're so high up in the carbonicopter.
It's going to sound like I had recorded it for another episode, but the rest of the episode
wasn't that great.
So I clipped out that ending and moved to this ending because I can't figure out a way
to end this episode without singing more songs.
But it's just the altitude, bro.
It's all in your mind.
So Wiz's Carves and there might actually be jokes.
There may be jokes that don't make sense because they're called back to earlier in this Phantom
episode, but it's just your imagination, man.
It's season 13 and you're just imagining stuff.
That's the end.
But so there we go.
This is my eyes do the ultimate shift from side to side.
And hopefully my voice quality doesn't change that much.
Wiz's Carves.
Let's call in that world famous carbonicopter.
We are headed out to Finland.
Specifically we're headed out to Cryola.
It's in Jarvanapaa in Finland.
It's November 1991.
It's 9pm.
There's a 29 year old woman.
Let's name her Margaret.
And she's just watching television.
She's just sitting in her chair checking out the old boob tube.
New episode of Perfect Strangers is on.
That bulky.
He's so funny.
No one ever said.
I actually liked that show when I was a kid.
She's sitting there in the chair and then all of a sudden.
She starts to take a breath.
A circular wind starts to wrap her up.
And she feels the wind kind of started her feet and wrap around her body all the way
up to the top of her head.
She tries to stand up but she can't.
Her mouth opens up.
I don't think she made that noise.
I don't think she was mumra coming out of the crypt.
Her head is forced up.
She's sitting in her chair completely paralyzed.
Mouth wide open.
Looking up now.
She's forced to see something in front of her.
There is a what she describes as a holographic picture.
And on that picture is a foot and a half tall alien just laying on a bed staring at her.
Her eyes wide open.
Her mouth a gape.
She's staring at this image.
This creature is laying there with one hand casually under its jaw.
And its feet are kicking back and forth a little nervously.
This creature doesn't seem to be prepared for what is going to happen next.
She said the only thing she could think of is how angry she was.
Margaret was overwhelmed with anger.
This goes on for 10 minutes.
She's completely paralyzed and she's staring at this foot and a half tall creature just
lounging there.
Staring back at her.
Then the image of this creature is replaced with a star map and then it slowly fades away
and the creature is laying on the bed once again kicking its legs nervously.
At this point the anger has become terror.
She feels like they have now projected a map of where they are going to take her.
And she can't speak.
She can't move.
She's beginning to just think how terrified she is and she's trying to send a message.
I don't want to go.
I want to stay here.
Don't take me anywhere.
And this creature stops kicking its legs and then sits up on the bed.
This massive white tube appears.
She can see it out of the corner of her eye.
It's actually right outside her house.
And she's staring at this alien.
She's sitting on this couch and then he starts to fade away.
And then starts to fade back in.
He's sitting on the couch.
Starts to fade away.
Fades back into view.
And then right where she could see the outline of the alien.
He faded away but it's been replaced by the shape of the alien.
But now just fuzzy lines in the outline of the creature she just saw.
The encounter ends.
She can move again.
The white tube outside of her house disappears.
And she realizes something almost immediately.
She's been sitting in that chair for 10 minutes looking at this thing, looking at her.
She did not see its hands, its feet, or its face.
She couldn't make out none of those details.
She saw the legs kicking.
She saw it looking at her.
But when she tried to recall details about the face, how many fingers it had, what its
feet looked like, her only answer is, "I didn't see them."
She saw them, but she couldn't remember them.
I got this story from ThinkAboutItDocs.com and they actually got it from Mervi Vertanen,
who I believe is a UFOologist in Finland.
This story was originally going to be on my David Lynch episode because talk about a
lynchian encounter.
This story is bizarre, just for the visuals.
And just for the idea of the alien does nothing.
I used to kick it with this girl named Kate in Sacramento and she always said the scariest
thing to her is looking out into her backyard and seeing a man in the backyard.
And I go and then, like, he tries to get in and she goes, "No.
If he tries to get in, then I know what to do.
If he tries to do anything towards me, I can do it."
The man in the backyard is what's terrifying to me.
Not knowing is terrifying to me.
That's what this alien story represents.
This creature just stared.
It's in a very, very long for an alien encounter as well.
Ten minutes?
I mean, that's just boring, right?
You get bored after a while, but ten minutes is a long time for an alien encounter unless
you're getting taken onto the ship.
But this story is so surreal.
It's so bizarre.
That you would almost want, like Kate was saying, the man in the backyard is creepy.
You'd almost want to wake up and have an alien encounter at all.
It's much better to wake up late at night and you see the gray alien poking its head out
of your closet.
And then you get terrified.
And the next thing you know, you're facedown on some bed on a starcraft.
I mean, again, I'm saying if you had to choose.
Because at least that makes sense.
Or you wake up and there's a dark shadow standing at the end of your hallway.
And then, you know, that's creepy.
But then you're getting chased by it.
And the next thing you know, you're facedown on a metal bed on a starcraft.
Because those make sense.
And if you are being chased by something, if the gray is in your closet, you could beat
it up, you could lock it in, you could make it record a podcast, you do all these things.
But this is just so surreal.
The way that it appears and the way that it disappears, the whole interaction with it
defies logic.
It's like an abstract interpretation of an alien encounter.
You can't fight back against something that you don't understand.
And we understand biology.
We understand gray aliens.
You can grab their little tiny legs and you can spin them around and hit their heads on
everything.
You can punch them.
You can fight reptilians.
Probably lose.
But I mean, you could go toe to toe.
You could ride an insectoid.
You can turn them in.
Put a little saddle on them.
Whee!
You can do all this crazy stuff.
But how would you fight against this?
I mean, she just willed herself into not going.
But even in the end, like she's staring at something for 10 minutes and she can't "see"
its face?
That is more terrifying to me than scout crafts and aliens taking slaves and hybrids and
all that stuff.
An abstraction of those stories is far more terrifying because there's just no rhyme or
reason to it.
The real terror out there isn't the gray alien standing in the foot of your bed.
Or the shadow man that you see crawling underneath your car in that dark parking lot.
Or the movement out of the corner of your eye right when you flick off the light switch
to go to sleep.
The real true terror is the stuff that's so incomprehensible our mind can't even process
it.
That we could look at something for 10 minutes and then be asked a mundane detail what did
it look like and you go "I don't know."
Because if something can bend your mind that much then what hope do we have?
We can fight physical wars, military might versus starships.
But this, this abstraction, there's no defense against it.
All you can do is hope and pray you never encounter it.
Or if you do, you never remember it.
Because by glimpsing madness like this, you are almost guaranteed to go mad yourself.
DeadRabbitRadio at gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
In the season 13 I'm going to go play so many video games.
You don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Thank you guys so much for supporting the show.
I'll be back in two weeks.
Don't you worry about that with all sorts of new stories.
My legs are cramped.
I'm ready to go guys.
Peace.
Love ya.
Drop the bomb.
Peace.
Love you guys.
Have a great one.
I said drop the bomb.
I'm dead of that out.
Otherwise we're going to get it.
Federal government after me.
Do not.
I repeat, do not drop the bomb.
Have a great one guys.
Have a great one.