A debate rages online.
Is there really a cannibal in Iowa?
And then we travel back in time to meet a man
who is so adamant he has proof that Bigfoot exists.
He turns to an unlikely ally.
The Federal Bureau of Investigation today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have an awesome weekend.
So our first story we're going to 4chan.
So sit down you're like Jason and brother not no sit down.
We're going to 4chan because this is where we have
a bizarre exchange going on right now.
A man jumped on 4chan today and he said guys you won't believe what happened.
I had a conversation with a cannibal from Waterloo, Iowa.
This is the conversation this guy logs into a meagle right.
What allows you to talk to random people you put in what you're interested in.
Other people put what they're interested in.
It just lets you chat to random people.
This guy supposedly gets a conversation here's some screenshots.
Well you can't see screenshots I'm going to read them to you.
Gets his conversation this how it starts off.
Our intrepid young conspiracy paranormal researcher whoever he is 4chan poster.
Doesn't matter we'll call him Gary.
Gary is sitting there and this is the first message he gets hit up on Omegle.
Just out of the blue very first sentence.
Hello that's very polite I'm glad that the stranger's saying hello.
Hello would you like to be fattened up and eaten by a cannibal family?
Now this that's bizarre obviously.
This is actually the second conversation that Gary has with a cannibal.
In one day Gary came to 4chan he goes guys you won't believe it but
I talked to a cannibal earlier and he told me all sorts of stuff that he belongs to this
cannibal family in Iowa.
He wants to eat me he wants to see if I can eat fattened up but I don't have
screenshots or any proof whatsoever and I'll never find the guy again.
But here's his kick which is another message now.
And people immediately go whatever dude you got someone burned you in a drug deal.
They sold you like mushrooms off a pizza and told you that they would get you high
and you've been eating them all day long and nothing's happening.
You're just trying to get someone in trouble and then he goes wait no no no no no no.
Hours later I found him again on the massive website on the massive messaging app known
as Omegle against all odds I found him again and that was the screenshot I just read you.
So not only did he find a cannibal twice in one day but the cannibal has no intro.
Imagine you are just hanging out on Omegle.
Now he put in that he is interested in death which is a very broad subject.
Maybe you like the Sandman comic.
Maybe you enjoy Death's Head the other comic but with head at the end of it.
Or maybe you enjoy dying but there's a far cry between I enjoy death and hello would you
like to be fattened up and eaten by a cannibal family.
First thing the dude says.
Gary says perhaps.
Now that would ring if I was a cannibal and I was just hitting people up randomly
saying hey yo you want to get fattened up and I can eat you.
You're going to expect people to go the first thing they're going to go is what wait what
huh what but if someone goes perhaps I'm going to assume they're a fed at least the city cop.
And then the cannibal responds don't worry it'll be quick and painless end terrible grammar.
You would have figured that cannibals because they're eating all those brains would be a little
bit smarter and then Gary responds really what's the process and then it just kind of goes on from
there. The cannibal goes what's your height and weight and the Gary says six this is a lie.
Six feet point two five point two five inches so you're five foot eleven like I don't understand
why people are sensitive about their height but I've never heard anyone describe themselves as
six feet point two five inches. Is he trying to say he's six foot two or is he a quarter of an
inch is he's just a quarter of an inch over six feet and a hundred and seventy four pounds and
you can hear the cannibal like salivating delicious and then the cannibal says so you'd be fattened
up we got to fatten you up and the guys like it's my fetish for being eaten and then they go on and
on basically at this point that's the story now people now that he's provided this quote unquote
proof with these screenshots people are like oh no it's true and they start looking into the kick
they find a name associated with the kick start finding people in Waterloo Iowa whose name is
close to that name it's not the same but close enough and becomes this web of investigation now
I here's the thing I think it's a lark because the guy tells a story of this is what the cannibal
said to me that's what he says in the very first post on the thread people don't believe him and
then he randomly finds the guy again and it's the same conversation it's the same conversation
when's the last time you had the same conversation in four hours like four hours apart you meet someone
you have a conversation and then four hours later you have the exact same conversation it's going to
ring some alarm bells you're going to be suspicious yourself you're like wait a second then I just
have this conversation secondly that's a pretty bold way to start off just talking to someone hey
you want to get eaten I think that the I think the screenshots are photoshopped and there was some
allegations in the 4chan thread itself that these are fake this isn't what a screenshot would look
like on omegle other people are like no no no because it's on the mobile app I don't know I've
never used omegle I don't know what it's going to look like but what's interesting is people then
started finding these people in Waterloo Iowa who have a similar name and going like isn't this
suspicious isn't this suspicious isn't this suspicious to be fair and I'm not going to say the
name because I'm not trying to dox the guy because I think it actually is a lark I don't know if it's
a lark this is interesting either the OP is larpine or he got incredibly lucky and found the guy twice
and was able to take screenshots and that guy is larpine making it all up or they're both larpine
it's him and his buddy doing something who knows or it's a real cannibal or it's a real cannibal
because one of the people in the 4chan thread said if you go to the Iowa missing people website
it has some bizarre statistics if you look at the city of Waterloo 11 people have gone missing
in Waterloo this year alone from ages 12 to 17 that's what this this post says what's interesting
and I'm continuing this quote what's interesting is those 11 people are all from this year while
other missing person reports are more than 20 years old I kind of looked into that there's a lot of
info there's really like 20 pages of missing people men and women and he could be that could
be part of the lark that could be accurate I really didn't check I mean like I looked into it and
there's a lot of missing people what it's the OP made it sound like the dude wanted to eat dudes so
there are 11 people but are they all dudes that would be the thing are these 11 people fat too
missing persons don't normally say man was excessively chubby the man had sweet tasting sweet
sweet delicious meat it's usually not included in missing persons things so the reason why I wanted
to cover this was because 4chan has a history of doing this and we've actually covered this before
the mysterious daycare center actually I think that started on Reddit but the mysterious daycare
center we did a couple episodes back this daycare center is there it looks creepy and then people
start bombarding them with phone calls and sending pizzas to the door knocking on the door because
they thought it was some sort of child trafficking thing Hillary Clinton was eating babies there
is all sorts of weirdness then recently there's been a thing about snack food like there's a snack
food company this was actually a request to it from max f on youtube max f mentioned this
there was a thing recently on youtube a company called stone creek stony creek they make little
bags of food that you buy at the gas station and some guy bought some and they were super disgusting
it was like pumpkin seeds he said they tasted like chemicals he hold on guys I know you guys are
getting ready to type in the comments let me finish this he eats the pumpkin seeds they taste
like chemicals he goes to complain to the company he writes him a letter or tries to call a number
on the back of the package and no one answers the phone it turns out that this company has like a
bunch of empty it turns out this company apparently has like five different mailing addresses and a
bunch of different phone numbers and it's like four people work there and it's a multi-million
dollar company and the ex paranormal board lost their head over this trying to figure out like is
this some sort of conspiracy is it money laundering human trafficking always it's always human trafficking
it can never just be like drug deals but it's all there's always human trafficking behind every
conspiracy hillary clinton's waiting there with a bib the picture of a baby on it people are trying
to call up stony creek stony creeks basically starts complaining i'm getting harassed this is
ridiculous then it turned and it was weird too because then the conspiracy kind of ended
because it turns out the original poster who started the stony creek thing never ate pumpkin
seeds he ate gummy bears and people are like what and i was like this is ridiculous i knew from the
beginning on that one that 99 probability that this company my guess was this with stony creek was
that the packaging was older and so some of the packaging had different contact information on it
because when you make candy for a gas station you're pumping it full it's you're eating candy from
the carter administration basically when you're buying stuff at a gas station it's super old
so you're buying stuff from say 2005 and then other stuff from 2017 maybe it's not the carter
administration but that was my first guess the second guess was that they just had different
distributors they're not shipping pistachios all the way from washington dc that i figured it was
just something like that so but you can sometimes you it's for sometimes the most mundane conspiracy
totally gets blown up you have a creepy looking daycare center therefore human trafficking you
have disgusting pumpkin seeds or gummy bears therefore human trafficking or money laundering
or whatever it was this is going to be the same thing this this iowa cannibal thing most likely
will just continue to grow and grow and grow and grow it'll keep getting pushed out there now
i don't think the i don't think the conversation actually happened i don't think any other people
involved are cannibals but i think it's a good look at how these things grow it could completely
die off i didn't think the stony creek candy thing was going to go anywhere and it lasted for like a
week multiple threads as people try to unravel the mystery of disgusting gas station food it's
gas station food it's going to be disgusting and i would argue that you could you could conti
you know what here's an actually interesting thing the i eat these beef jerky sticks these
jalapeno beef jerky sticks made by tilamook the packaging says it's three grams of carbohydrates
three grams of dietary fiber so basically makes it a net zero for keto and i thought that's not
accurate and i know that the nutritional value things on food there's you can lie on them
you can lie on them you the FDA gives you some wiggle room so i thought this is weird this can't
be right so i went to tilamook's website they listed the nutritional value on the website for
the jalapeno things three grams of carbohydrates zero dietary fiber huge difference if you're on
keto that's a massive difference so i emailed them and i said hey there's a difference here now
i'm thinking in my mind they're lying with the stuff on the shelf because that's where people are
going to grab them and they know that people are looking at that stuff nowadays i think it's some
sort of conspiracy i think you're trying to rip us off i ended up getting an email like two weeks
later so at that point like enough time had gone by is like that's where they haven't gotten back
to me they're a company i'm emailing them stuff i started thinking did my email go through it wasn't
a huge deal but i was curious i ended up getting an email about two weeks later and they're like oh
thank you so much for pointing that out to us the website is actually outdated it is three grams
of dietary fiber so thank you for pointing that out to us they didn't send me anything for you so
whatever tilamook you suck but my point is is that in those two weeks had i posted that onto a say
like a nutrition form or something like that i really could have blown their spot up and been
like guys look if we're getting lied to by this company i could have gone to some keto reddit or
something like that like they're they're messing with us they're it's really easy to get a conspiracy
theory rolling because people are naturally suspicious and whenever you have a sexy conspiracy
like i get human trafficking cannibalism they're not sexy but they're intriguing people like to hear
about that stuff so if some random dude you've never met before tells you he has no proof shows
the and you go well that i don't believe you shows up four hours later with proof of a totally
different but same conversation you shouldn't believe that you should be very very leery about
anything that comes out of that and when they start naming people and saying i think it might be this
person here you should be more suspicious and what's funny is that people kept saying contact the
police dude if you have this conversation you know what city it's in contact waterloo police some guy
looked up the police department of waterloo police and goes here's the link just call them
wouldn't call them the original poster wouldn't call them people are like dude maybe like we
should figure out like this is super sketchy like look at this information look at this article i
found on this guy with a similar name and that's it other people be like just call the police
just call the police nobody would do it everyone wants to talk about the conspiracy theory no one
wants to call the police now i don't i would call the police if i actually thought there was any
truth to this but i don't i think it's a lark i think it's an entertaining lark and then i think
it's great for a friday episode of dead rabbit radio interesting story and an interesting insight
to how this stuff is created let's go ahead of though and move on to our next topic so we're
going to say goodbye to iowa we're saying goodbye to waterloo waving goodbye to our new non cannibalistic
friends they're like hey see you later jason oh by the way keto's dangerous don't that's not a good
diet for you you should just eat what you want i'm like huh and they're like and come back and visit
us soon after Easter when you eat all that candy we're like that's cool they invited us back after
Easter and you're right i shouldn't be on keto and you're you're super suspicious you're like no
dude stay on that diet you're looking good i'm like nah man let's go eat some cake so we stop at
the cake store and we're eating a bunch of cake and there's people from iowa just with their hands
on the window licking the glass and we leave we leave iowa behind but we'll visit them again in
Easter we're headed up to the dowels in Oregon that's where i'm at not the dowels the it's so funny
when i first moved up here i asked someone i go hey so uh what's the dowels like and they're like
don't go to the dowels the kids they're smoked duct tape they're all idiots they don't even
let you buy duct tape if you're under the age of 18 in the dowels and i go what that has to be in
urban legend and so every time i met someone not that's okay that's a bit of an exaggeration i'm
not like nice to meet you ma'am so do the kids in the dowels smoked duct tape but i would meet people
and we'd be talking for a while and i'd be like hey have you ever heard that about kids in the
dowels smoking duct tape and some people would be like yeah yeah i've heard of that and other people
would kind of laugh off and say yeah i heard that but it was like an urban legend but it's real
popular in hood river that kids in the dowels smoked duct tape and you have to be over 18
to buy duct tape in the dowels i eventually ended up running into somebody from the dowels
after a couple months of being up here i said hey dude is it uh is it true that you can't buy
duct tape and the person's like that's not i'm so tired of that that's doofur so i guess farther
out east there's a town that's supposedly dumber than the dowels called doofur which to be fair
that's a pretty dumb name for a town and they're the ones who smoke duct tape it's not the dowels
but it's funny we basically just have these different towns and each one the farther east
you go the dumber you get anyways we're not talking about smoking duct tape i imagine you
know i imagine if you smoke duct tape you actually would get some sort of high simply
because you're inhaling a chemical and or you're cutting off blood flow to your brain by trying
to like suck on something i don't know don't try it kids i think you have a better chance
find them in cannibal in iowa than you do get in high up duct tape but we're going to the dowels
and in the dowels i've heard about this for a long time too since i've been up here there used to be
a mobile home that was the bigfoot information center and exhibition it was this guy had parked
this mobile home in the dowels his name was peter c burn and his little bigfoot museum
and apparently at one point bigfoot walked through the dowels so bigfoot's really big up here like
if you walk around hood river you're going to see a ton of bigfoot related merchandise you're not
actually going to see a ton of bigfoot but you're going to see like shirts and mugs and hats and all
sorts of stuff now and statues there's quite a lot of bigfoot statues around town it's kind of cool
for like to being into cryptids and stuff like that it's kind of cool little area but back in 1976
the year i was born peter burn had the bigfoot information center and exhibition or bice i just
realized is the acronym for that this guy had been hunting bigfoot that was his thing he was a
bigfoot hunter which you know i don't want to crib a joke but listening to the parapod is one of my
favorite podcasts of all time highly recommend you guys listen to it the guy on that show the
skeptic on that show goes if you hunted foxes your entire life but never caught a fox could you call
yourself a fox hunter that's kind of i know that's kind of a flippant way to describe bigfoot hunters
but i think there's probably another way to describe them researchers or investigators but
yeah can you call yourself a hunter if you've never actually caught one anyways peter burn i'm not
trying to burn him uh peter burn found some bigfoot hair picks it up look at it found it little
little little hairs little follicles and there's a piece of skin attached to it too now it's 1976
when i was growing up and i've talked about this before on the show bigfoot people not actual bigfoot
people bigfoot researchers ufo oligists paranormal people they were basically like you had to join
a mailing club or you could have a magazine maybe if there was enough people in your area you can
meet up and talk about it but there were no there was no internet i was born in 1976 that wasn't
around until the late 90s if you were into this stuff you either knew someone in town who was
into it as well maybe three or four people or you mailed letters back and forth you were part of
some correspondence club so everyone felt fairly isolated i think nowadays you have way more communication
between people double edged sword though because now you can combine your efforts and be like let's
really look at all the evidence we have on bigfoot or you can combine your efforts and possibly
end up harassing some innocent people in Iowa but in 1976 this guy has this hair and he goes hmm
you know i've been studying bigfoot for a long time i found evidence before but i think this is
conclusive i don't really have anywhere to turn to though and again that was another thing back
then like nowadays every show opting you'll get some research scientists you'll get like neil degrasse
thyssen talk about like alternate realities or you have people who grew up on more sci-fi stuff
enter the sciences and they have a bit of more open mind back then people who are running the
colleges running the scientific organizations they were like no this is all goofy i'm not going to
ruin my name by talking about bigfoot so if you had a bigfoot hair sample there wasn't really a lab
you could send it off to there was no national group that had the ability to do dna testing or
anything like that so he has this sample of hair and he turns to the federal bureau of investigation
he sends the fbi a letter and he's detailing listen i found this fur it has a little bit of
skin attached to it now i know this is going to sound crazy but i believe it's bigfoot and he puts
in the letter and he puts in the letter here's a quote please understand that our research here
is serious this is a serious question that needs answering and the fbi doesn't respond which is what
you would expect so peter writes another letter basically please pretty please with the cherry
on top draws a little picture of a sunday a little scented sticker attaches that that says you're doing
a great job you scratch it and it smells like federal building it's a little fbi sticker
on the fbi the second time they're like oh they're so cute they actually say secondly yes and it's the
fur send us the fur we'll take care of it so on the fbi side there's a guy named jay cochran jr
the assistant director of the fbi scientific and technical division or std which i'm sure he was
reminded of all the time hey jay you're still working in the std division he's a single tier
i'm the assistant director you can't make fun of me like that they put a sign on his back
just says got std he's like oh that's not even a reference yet that commercial hasn't come out
so anyways he's sitting there crying in his laboratory and he gets this second letter
and he scratches the sticker and smells like linoleum and chlorox and he goes yes we'll take
care of this he actually writes back and says yes send us the sample and he tells his team
normally we're set up to help local crime units however we have in the past helped with scientific
research museums have sent us stuff laboratories have sent us stuff so we will actually help this
guy out because why not and i've mentioned this in another episode too it's really easy for us to
look at federal agents and police officers and stuff like that as the other as this separate thing
from society but people in those groups love to watch science fiction shows they read spooky books
they play magic the gathering and doom whatever game they're on at this point they're just like
you and me they have a different job and sometimes that job involves you know knocking you over the
head with the billy club but really at the core there's still people so i'm sure that there were
people at this laboratory who were familiar with the legend of bigfoot back then they had read
these books they had heard about in the news and they were curious as well so when the fbi gets the
skin sample and then peter hears nothing back from them at all never ever gets an answer from them
and we're at that point where we've talked about this before as well i don't mean to keep doing
callbacks but there's always that story of the smithsonian like someone finds proof of a giant
skeleton and the smithsonian shows up and they're like what giant skeleton as a giant truck is
driving away with a giant tarp on it they're like i don't know what you're talking about so there's
always that like you send off information and you hear tons of UFO stories like that as well
people take photographs of alien ships or they find a broken component and they send it off to
the government and the government's like what are you talking about what what component and you never
send anything to us so a lot of people in the meantime for 20 years thought that's what happened
that a they sent the equipment off and that was it they just never tell peter what they find
or if they find anything peter sends off the skin sample with the hair on it
he never finds anything out now you could say that it might have been lost in the mail it could be
that they found it and it wasn't worth anything it could be that they found it and it proved bigfoot
existed and as a national security issue they refuse to let people know what was going on
possible too right so 42 years pass peter is still alive still alive today sends it off never
hears back and i'm sure that was always going in his head i had proof that bigfoot was real
senator the fbi never got a letter back heartbroken 2019 2019 though fbi's been opening up their files
and they open up a file that they have it was no longer top secret about their bigfoot investigation
about this skin sample
it was deer they the fbi said it was most likely from the deer family is the terminology they used
so that was it right sends off the sample fbi probably investigated it right away saw that it
was deer family but still it was a classified investigation they didn't respond to him because
something like bigfoot would be a national security threat something that could walk around
america completely undetected could teleport in and out leaves giant footprints you would never
be able to fix the road destroying everything wet concrete is safe nowhere in the united states
national security threat so it was classified at the time but now that it's been declassified comes
out that it was related to the deer family there's two takeaways for this first off we're going to
look at an article written by hannah chin this was for the williamette week newspaper it was
written last year about this story and we're going to take a look at this man named peter bern turned
94 in 2019 94 years old he says quote i'm still in it but in a much milder way so to speak he says
nowadays he goes actually the technology makes everything so much easier he goes him and his
team they put up trail cams where they know that bigfoot has been spotted have them all over the
place pick up deer they pick up mountain lions they're seeing all sorts of stuff elk but no bigfoot
here this is a little heartbreaking quote you have this 94 year old man sitting there talking
to this reporter he says quote i would love to see a bigfoot i've never seen one i've seen
footprints that's all i'm still hopeful i mean think about it he's been researching since before
i was born for this one particular creature is looking all over for it i never found anything
more than footprints probably spent 42 years holding on to hope that he had actually found proof
that the fbi thought was too dangerous to get out so they kept it but now he's being told it's just
deer family which he accepted that belief you know what are they why would the fbi lie to me
it's probably true but don't feel bad and it's funny because when i read that i actually kind of
felt bad for him i was like oh peter you're just kind of hanging out elderly man looking for something
that may not exist dude spent my lifetime looking for something that may not exist however i did
look more into this dude he's had an awesome life dude he's been a himalayas looking for the yeti
there he has a personal website it has all these amazing adventures he's gone on to in world war
two he was working for the navy and there was a plane crash and him and his buddy jumped in a boat
and like saved five people pulled him out of a burning aircraft great man great man he may be
looking for something that doesn't exist but it's definitely not a life wasted he's done
crazier adventures and done more than i've ever done and he's still having fun whether or not
he finds bigfoot he has a crew of people they're out looking for something he has a purpose in
his life and he's like i said he's had some great adventures already so when i read the
article originally it's like that's i can just imagine this old decrepit man sitting on his porch
waiting to find you know like a leprechaun for all intents and purposes and then i read more about
him and he's actually pretty dope dude and then i came away with another thing though the FBI is
in the laboratory and they're testing that fur looking at it under a microscope or spinning
around in a spinny thing or whatever csi device they had back in 1976 they had it just like a
light bright they in the shape of a double helix and they're like holding it up against it
and they go well that's part of the deer family and we know bigfoot if it exists has to be related
to humans or apes right that's the common idea so just put it in a vault somewhere or probably
just threw it away if it was just deer related they went on with their business and then i thought
about something how many times do they find bigfoot fur supposed bigfoot fur there's like
footprints around and they find fur and they send it off to lab and it gets brought back as deer
fur a lot of times it's deer fur sometimes it's dog fur but a lot of times it's like deer fur
why do we assume that bigfoot is a descendant of an ape or a man
just because it walks on two feet who's not to say that bigfoot isn't related to the simians
but to one other species a deer perhaps now i know what you're thinking jason that's brilliant
and i know i know isn't it just because he looks like a big old monkey doesn't mean he is a monkey
he's he's related to a monkey because you think about it i think humans look more like gorillas
we walk more like gorillas but we're more related to the chimpanzee so even in that sector of the
simians like we don't you very rarely see like tiny little people walking around they're normally
like big old dudes i mean maybe not gorilla big but and you're like jason that's brilliant too
that one that arguments a little weaker but hear me out what's to say that a deer couldn't evolve
to walk on both feet now i know what you're thinking because i just realized this as i was
saying this that yes bigfoot's have hands with like five fingers and feet and i know you guys
probably think in this couple minutes ago i just i just realized this and a deer has hooves right
but but give me a second to think about that one what what if the reason why it has hooves
is because ooh think about it this way
it has hooves i actually don't know why animals have hooves
over fingers and toes but if let's say that a million years ago dude okay yes yes okay that's
a weakness in the argument and sure the antlers the antlers in the snout but but what i'm saying is
that think about it a kangaroo looks like a deer the head if you just saw the head of a kangaroo
and the head of a deer lying on the line on the ground you would go i can't tell the difference
or you would be able to tell the difference because you're an outdoorsman but i wouldn't
if i saw a chopped off kangaroo head no not even chopped off if there i'm not going to get gruesome
with this if there was like a board with two holes in it you're like this is more weird this is your
weird living room there was a board with two holes in it and one had a deer head like there was a
live deer under there and then the other one had a kangaroo head would you be able to tell the
difference now you might you might be able to however they're not the same family so just
because they look alike doesn't mean they're related crocodiles and alligators they're different
and they look exactly alike to me i get a mix up all the time so is it possible
think about oh here's a good one here's a good one you're like jason this is this is totally
gone off the rails snakes have no legs and lizards have legs but they're both related
because they're both reptiles so a deer can have hooves and then a different kind of deer
that walks on feet because it's walking on two feet evolved feet and hands because it doesn't
need hooves so kangaroos have hands and toes so they have the same head but different bodies so
who's to say that a bigfoot is not related to the deer family but it just has different
different appendages and a different face and a different height and totally acts differently
than any deer possible and doesn't have antlers but everything's different every every possible
thing is different except the fur except the fur right so my my point is i think i think it's
a couple different takeaways here one you realize i know nothing about biological science or nature
and i can't tell the difference between a deer and a kangaroo secondly that's all true secondly i
think you've realized that i had an idea and then once i started to process it out loud i realized
the hoof dilemma the hoof dilemma is a new rule for dead rabbit radio that's where once you state
something out loud you realize that there's a flaw in it but you won't give up your argument i will
still say this stubbornly say this who's to say that bigfoot is related to apes or humans who's
to say if you grab the patch of bigfoot hair you sent it to a lab and it wouldn't come back what was
supposed to come back a gorilla or human it wouldn't come back it can't come back we don't know what
it is because it has to be something everything on this planet is related to something if you found
a new fruit on a tree and you sent it to a laboratory they're not going to say this is nothing
they're going to say it's related to an orange it has to be related to something if it's from this
no see now we're back on track it has to be related to something nothing comes out of nowhere so
it's not that maybe let me correct that it's not that bigfoot is a deer it's that the closest thing
to its fur is a deer maybe bigfoot's are naked and the fur we see is deer fur that would have been
an easier argument to make five minutes ago that is possible bunch of naked people running through
the woods that have never been discovered wearing deer fur so don't let that be proof that bigfoot
doesn't exist you should when they tell you that that's really deer fur you should say ah just more
proof of my giant naked humans wearing deer fur or actually bigfoot theory be like peter and never
stop searching for the truth dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also
hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but i'm
glad you listened to it today have a great weekend guys