Has the internet uncovered the path towards summoning your own jinn?
And then we take a look at a man whose father told him many stories growing up of being abducted by aliens and
Having a religious experience with them. Is there any truth to these stories? Is it possible that all aliens?
worship the same God today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a ton of stuff to cover. It's day two of Alien Disclosure Week
Yes, we're here called the UFO Disclosure Week. It doesn't matter stuff is getting disclosed one way or the other first off
Let's give a shout out to our newest patreon supporter Nate
Nate thank you so much for supporting the show. You are going to be our captain this episode
I may refer to you as Nate dog. Hopefully you're fine with that. Hopefully you know who it is
It's definitely a compliment from me because I love Nate dog rest in peace
If you can't support the patreon that's fine too. Just help get the word out about the show
That really really helps out a lot and I actually want to highlight this I have a Google alerts set up for Dead Rabbit Radio
But it only pops up once a week
because otherwise it goes off all day long because
Every time I put out a podcast it goes to all these different websites and things like that
So a lot of times I don't see time stuff that pops up on time
So Nate as you stand there dutifully with your arms and a wet your side or something
I don't know crossed you just kind of standing there waiting for your turn to drive one of vehicles
Let me read this post I found it pops up on my Google alert too late, but I want to read this post
I found on the export. It's a titled dead rabbit radio. I did not write this
I did not write this but somebody did and I wanted to address this a dead rabbit radio and here's what it said
I miss it bros. I can't wait till Monday if you're here Jason. Hey friend
I am thankful for your show and it makes me happy life has been hard lately, but dead rabbit radio is real good
I'm not saying that because it's complimentary towards me
I wouldn't be reading it if it was insulting, but there was a there's a key point in that and I get this in emails all
The time I actually got a similar comment from a YouTube username
34.qg7 just today
That they're having trouble with their life that life is hard
That things haven't been going well for them that they're lonely or sad or whatever and guys
It makes me feel so good to know that I can help you out in that way
Because we're all we
One like being into ghosts and stuff like that like sometimes you can find like ghost buddies
physical corporeal beings other humans that are into ghost or paranormal or Bigfoot and stuff like that
But a lot of times it's pretty solitary right a lot of times. It's maybe an internet community and things like that
So I'm glad that I can kind of be
Be out there be out there in this audio realm
To be your friend to be your your buddy your your
You know what I mean like that made me I get so many emails or people are telling me
That the show makes them happy and that to me is the biggest compliment
That really to me is the biggest compliment for the show. So whoever you are anonymous person
It's back the show is back. It's not going away anytime soon and to everyone who's ever emailed me
Saying that they're not doing good that they've been having a bad week or a bad month or bad year or whatever it is
I'm glad that I can be a little bit of
making it better
Making it better
So I just wanted to acknowledge that because I get that comment a lot and I'm glad I can kind of
Do my little part to make your day at least for maybe half hour a little bit more fun a little bit more fun
You're not alone. You're not alone. There's millions of people out there just like you you just haven't met them yet
But you will you'll be really good friends when you do
Nate let's fire up at Jason Jalopy
We are driving down to Los Angeles this I mean I got a ton of stuff to cover today
We're driving down you found breathless. We're driving down to Los Angeles right now. So as we're driving LA
Let me give you a little bit of this in two or ten different things at once right now
I'm all feeling that reports and you're looking for UFOs and like giving you a hug so you don't feel so sad and Nate's like
Where's my hug? We're going to LA at September 7th, 1973
And we're gonna go see the Johnny Carson show at the Tonight Show is what it is
So it was the Tonight Show starring Johnny Carson
I'm old enough that I actually watched it when it was on the air not this episode not that old
But I remember watching it in the 80s yesterday
I talked on the episode saying that for a long time talking about aliens talking about UFOs
It was you were ridiculed for it
Nowadays you can have your own web group or you can actually have your own YouTube channel and and even if you're not doing that
Even if you're an officer speaking in front of Congress or something like that. It's not as jokingly
Courage as it used to be and I want to play this clip as an example for this
What I'm about to play you it's Muhammad Ali famous boxer Muhammad Ali
He's on the Tonight Show and he's acting a little kind of reserved and Johnny Carson kind of picks up on it
So he asks him like, you know, what's going on? That's what kind of the lead-up is to this clip
Quite reserved tonight. I've been studying UFOs. Did you know there are UFOs out here flying around?
This would be the place for him Southern California
I'm seriously sighted a bunch over Georgia. I've seen him at night
They have real photos of him and the government and the people just completely seem like don't talk about it
But mr. Harold Salkin of Washington DC is head of the National UFO
Bureau
brought me moving films
I actually have moving pictures of little saucers of gray steel objects coming into pictures that people took and I'm just surprised
They don't know that talk more about it something they can another great insight into the fight game
I read that but did you read the thing last night on the news? No, it's on physicists said there's two things to address there
It appears that that was the first thing really Muhammad Ali is saying in that clip other than like hey
He starts talking about this UFO thing and he's kind of like this is what I wanted to talk about
Sitting next to him is the heavyweight champion Ken Norton
they're doing publicity for their upcoming heavyweight fight rematch and
Ken Norton's just kind of sitting there shocked the whole time the whole clip is about three minutes long and I had the links in the show
Not to recommend listening to that but that laughter
That laughter even what you have Muhammad Ali
World famous boxer
Saying yeah, you know, this is something I want to talk about I want to talk about you talk about UFOs and that laughter and you can
Tell half of it is nervous laughter because they don't know the audience doesn't know how to react to it
But the other half is laughing at him. That's really what it used to be like for the UFO community
You don't get their reaction much anymore. You can have post Malone who I'm pretty sure is haunting my apartment at this point
I'll do that story tomorrow's episode because I'm still doing some research on that
But you can have post Malone and I think it's also picking the audiences back then you had a general talk show
You went on there and then after that after Muhammad Ali gets off you'd have like a dancing cat
It was just kind of a general talk show nowadays post Malone can go on
H3H3 or Joe Rogan and they'll talk about UFOs and one there's no audience there
You don't get that instant reaction
But two I think one people are more open to it and you can pick your audiences when you talk about it
That's what it used to be like though and that takes guts
Now it probably caught him a little off guard when they first started laughing but like I said the clip goes on for three minutes
He just keeps talking about and Johnny Carson kind of he's a little dismissive at the beginning
But then he actually goes oh, you know
I read this article saying that it may be satellites falling and stuff like that
There's like this back and forth between them as far as that goes, but it was
Completely hostile you had a hostile audience when you talked about this stuff back then this was in 1973
September 7th 1973 as opposed to today
So it really took guts to talk about this stuff when a heavyweight boxer is getting
Laughed at and mocked on national television
Imagine someone who just saw UFO and they're in their small town and they're like hey
I think I saw something weird last night. I don't know what it was
Imagine that reaction, but it's your peers and you're in your small town diner
So that's what that was like Nate. Let's leave behind LA Muhammad Ali's like no no
Take me take me to a future where people will believe me. We're like no, sorry, dude
You got you got fights to win or lose. I don't really know his record
But I don't know if he won that fight, but he was were speeding away. He's like do I win?
Do I win this fight? I don't know. We're not sports people at least I'm not we're driving away Nate. Let's go to
Spooky bedroom. I don't know. Maybe it's your bedroom. That's spooky. I'm pretty sure my bedroom is haunted by post Malone
Even though he's still alive something weird is going on. We're elite. We're not going to my bedroom
That's tomorrow's episode. Let's just go to your bedroom, but it's super spooky like you've put up like crepe paper and
It's like black and red and you've lit some candles
That's what your bedroom normally looks like and we are going to look at a
Ritual I found this on Reddit. I found this on Reddit
It is supposedly so I always like to say that because I want to give credit to the person who brings it to my attention
This was from a user named bill feiny. So we're sitting in your bedroom. Thank you bill whoever you are
We're sitting in your spooky spooky bedroom
And we're going to look at something that he supposedly found from a book called the miraculous aspects of things
Existing supposedly according to this reddit post. This is a book that was written by Zachariah L.
Cosweeney in the
1200s so long long time ago if you don't have a calendar if you don't have a calendar in front of you just take my word for it
The 1200s is farther back than the
2020s apparently this is a text that actually shows you how to summon a gin
Now gin, you know one of the biggest things I see in the party
I can't say it's the biggest thing I see but it pops up a lot in paranormal world. The one thing that pops up a lot is
How do I get wishes?
It's funny because you think about it. That is the
Wanting to have a wish fulfilled and wanting to be able to go back in time and change things
It's like an it's like a basic human need
It's so weird to think that you know if you I think I talked about this like on episode 40 of this podcast
If you went back to like old timey England like the 1400s
And they're like using sickles and stuff to like chop hay up and like pet and sheep
Do instead of using the sickles on the sheep. You know, they're like, oh, you know, what would be totally awesome
I heard back in the the thousands things were way cooler people are dressing all in retro thousand clothes
They're like, I don't know. I don't know what clothes they wore in the 1400s
But you know what I mean like people always look backwards with like sepia colored glasses or they didn't have glass glasses
Wasn't invented back then so they just looked back and go, you know what?
I'm sure I wish I lived in the times of the Arthurian legends. That's what they were thinking
They're like back when knights actually fought for good instead of like beating up peasants and nostalgia is a thing
I'm sure you could even go back to like the bee season. They're like, ah, I don't know
Maybe maybe there's a limit because you have to have some sort of record of the past
You're gonna be sitting in your hovel in
Grease and you're like, ah, dude things were way better back
I'm guessing cuz things suck so bad now. I'm just guessing anytime before now is better
But anyway, so time travel wish fulfillment very very basic human needs
So that is a very lengthy introduction to this. I said I have a lot to cover and I'm seeming to ramble more than often
Here's this. Here's your instructions. Get a pen and paper. You write this down
before sunrise
But but but before you start writing stuff down realize you will be summoning a gin if you follow these instructions
So maybe not spooky spooky bedroom. You got a I'll give you a single light
So you can write stuff down or you can use your cell phone because you don't live in the PCs
Before sunrise you have to practice solitude and quiet and then at night
So this is like the day before so it takes a couple days preparation
So you wake up one morning you practice solitude and quiet and then that night you pray and praise God
So this might not work for atheists although I
Would be kind of weird when atheists are trying to summon a gin and expect it to happen
They're like, I don't believe in anything except this thing. I heard on a podcast before sunrise
I'm sure do atheists believe in ghosts actually not that I think about it. I know do they?
Like I guess like they probably believe in Bigfoot
That's for that's another episode. That's that's another episode
I could see an atheist believe in an aliens
But I don't get an atheist believe because at what point you're like, ooh that ghost
That's real, but then it's if it becomes like a wraith or a demon you're like
It's ghosts ghosts all the way down like I don't I don't know actually that's a good question
But the question that will be answered on a later episode has nothing to do with this one except
Except you'll be summoning a gin and to do this you have to praise God. So that's why that comes up
Could you praise God if you could you fake it fake it till you make it fake it till you make a gin
Before sunrise you practice solitude and quiet and then that night you pray and praise God the next day
You're gonna fast, but before you fast you're gonna fast from Sun up to Sun down
But you're gonna wake them in the morning. So you got to wake up before the Sun comes up
You have to only eat unsalted food
No planters peanuts for you. You can eat this stuff is inedible. This stuff is inedible
I'm about to list by the way, so I mean if you want to summon a gin your first wish should be make unsalted foods taste good in the future
You can only eat barley. I don't know where you're getting that at
I have no idea where you buy just straight barley, but you can eat barley
You can eat unsalted olives. Those are disgusting even if they are salted dried grapes
That's like a raisin right dates. I've never had one of those and
My food review it's it's oddly become that you can eat barley unsalted olives dried grapes dates or
Fruits and vegetables they should just say fruits and vegetables right because no one's gonna go out and buy
You don't have to eat barley by the way
You don't have to go raid a horse farm or like guys. What are those things called the stalls the horse place?
Thing you know what I mean. You've seen movies or been around real horses the place with all the boxes and the horse heads are popping out of it
Whatever
You don't need to go there for this ritual
But if you wanted to steal barley go to a horse farm
But anyway, so you just eat fruits and vegetables really and then but here's the thing put down that honey because that's what you're going for
It's not a fruit or vegetable. You can't eat anything that has an animal origin including honey
So no meat no eggs no milk and then whatever else comes out of a cow or chicken or an owl
Don't eat it and then you fast first from sun up to sundown
And then when you break the fast you have to go back to eating the barley you have to go back to eating unsalted stuff or again
Just fruits and vegetables
That's when the sun's going down now before nightfall comes
So you have that time period of dusk and then night falls coming you need to start
Summoning the gin now you have to read this phrase out now. I am
Going to be a total chicken. I'm not gonna read this phrase out on I've debated this and I know you guys were waiting with baited breath
Is he going to actually summon a gin during this podcast?
So this message is apparently written in a combination of Arabic and a gin dialect
I'm like, okay, but when I ran it through a translator and there's no Google translator for gin
There's no Google translator for like leprechaun or anything like that
But when I ran it through the translator it didn't even pick up any of the Arabic words. So I was like
I'm not really don't really feel comfortable, but
You can check it out online. You can check it out online. It's not super long
I don't even feel comfortable reading the first word
Because again first off post Malone's already haunting my apartment and then two maybe he's haunting my apartment because I've been reading this in my head
It's probably I don't know it probably take you 30 seconds to say it if that but you have to say it one
Thousand times so it's nightfall now
And you've already done all this preparation and you repeat this phrase over and over and over again
1000 times out loud and there you go
After the thousandth time this is interesting because this is something that's easily testable. I
Listener be aware as far as actually doing this ritual because again, it may work
You may want to summon a gin it may summon something else
But or it may have a psychological component to it as well
We'll get into that but it's something that's easily testable like once you get it down
After the thousandth time the gin will appear in front of you in human form
And if that happens if you're standing there and you see a human that previously did not exist appear in front of you
Don't panic it says do not panic if you've summoned something from the other realm
You are instructed to crawl into bed and go to sleep
You got to immediately go to sleep. I don't know if you have to immediately like I don't know if you have to
Immediately go to sleep that might be putting a little pressure on you
But you have to at least like try to go to sleep can't be on your phone
Can't be playing your Nintendo switch while you're sleeping the gin will wake you up. Hey, dude
Hey, dude wake up wake up you do you summon me dude?
You said that a thousand times don't you want me to be here?
Why are you speaking so rude and then you wake up and then you will create a contract with this gin during this conversation?
I don't know how casual the conversation. Hey, how was your day?
Were you doing anything before I summoned you into this realm?
You know stuff like that it could just be straight to business
But eventually you do come up with this contract and here we get this quote
The gin will be bound to a lifelong servitude which includes fulfilling realistic wishes and
Forming the human about the questions that he sets to the gin
Unquote so there you go. I think it's funny because there is that caveat saying well the wishes have to be realistic
Like you can't wish to be
King of ours or something like that like it has to be something like I wish this donut had only a hundred calories and the
Gin's like Duke
He got sit in one fourth and gives you you're like, huh? They have to be realistic wishes, but that's still an interesting thing
I would just be fascinating that a human appeared in my bedroom not saying that humans don't appear in my bedroom
They don't magically my bedroom, but humans do walk around in my bedroom from time to time
But that would be weird right if someone just magically appeared in front of you that would be proof enough
But the fact that he will stay stick with you forever. He'll answer questions that you set upon him
So you're like who is
Who's who's that man walking on the street and Jin's like
And he reads his ID in his pocket. He's like, oh, that's Jimmy Smith the actor
He's that's where what's he doing in my hometown and Jin's like
He's looking for a job
So I don't know
That would actually be kind of cool because I would be pestering him with questions all the time
In the middle of night. He's trying to sleep. I'm like, hey, Jin. Jin wake up. Hey, dude
I was wondering what do you call place where horses are at?
He's like, oh, please. Let me break my contract. I'll make you president of Mars
I'll break all my laws just to get out of this. So anyways, that's how you can summon a Jin
I'm wondering if you could record it record that saying and go
And then hit play and let the recording play out a thousand times
It would be weird then what if it doesn't work?
You're like, I'll go to sleep but like your mp3 player
It's sitting there and it's like just sitting there like the cameras closing on the MP3 player and
Then the Jin appears in the MP3 player and he's like I'm you're at your command and like the music is allowed to make wishes
It's a little black mirror episode for you guys
That one's free, but anyways apparently if you doesn't work
I'd be shocked if it did obviously, but I'm not gonna try it if it doesn't work
They say just keep doing it just keep doing it over and over again
It'll eventually work and what's interesting is in the reddit comments
So one of the first ones that popped up was from a guy named
Ibnami this guy says
Don't do this don't do this at all for a psychological reason if you repeat anything
1,000 times in a row it's gonna mess with your head like that is really how
I'm not saying like chanting chanting is supposed to take you to another like realm another like supposed to elevate the spirit
But he's like don't do this chanting if you channel just random stuff and just repeated that phrase a thousand times
It's gonna mess with your head. Don't do it. This is not saying don't do it because the Jin might show
Don't do it because you might actually cause psychological damage to yourself. That is probably true
It probably has some sort of tulpa effect
But who knows maybe this guy is onto something not this guy not this killjoy the original guy
Maybe you can do this and summon a Jin and get realistic wishes, but again, that's a that's a bit of a
That's a bit of a small print thing going on there because you could be like I wish and the
No matter what the Jin's I can't do it before you before even finish it
Nope, he's just eating all your potato chips all your unsalted olives. You're like, oh man. I really wanted those
It's going to garbage. Yeah, because they're disgusting. He's eating barley
So let's go ahead and get Nate in the seat of the carboner copter now
What I did was I promised you on yesterday's episode to talk about
This guy whose dad was abducted by aliens not only did I promise it on yesterday's episode
I promised it on this episode as well in the intro, but Nate let's get in that carboner copter
I don't know if we have enough time for that
Honestly, I don't know if we have enough time for that technically the the story with
Ufo disclosure
I don't think I have time to really do this story justice and I don't want to have another long episode because I want to make sure you guys
You know, I don't want to waste your guys's time
Let me not saying the show's waste of time, but you know what I mean?
Like I like having a set amount of time. Hold on a second here
Let me find a shorter story to end this on a shorter good story. Don't worry. I'm not just going to throw throw mud of the wall
Okay, here we go
Nate you've been doing circles in the carboner copter been in a holding pattern
We are now leaving behind your creepy bedroom. You can redecorate it when we come back. We are headed out to Kokomo, Indiana
It's January
1999 I got this from that website one of my favorite investigative websites think about it docs.com
It's January 1999
Helicopters coming over Kokomo, Indiana. It's late at night
It's late at night
It's late at night and two women are driving
Down a dark country road in a little area north of Kokomo, Indiana
We don't have their real names, but we'll call them June and
Monica June and Monica June is driving the car and those are their real names. It's just a shot on the dark
June's driving the car Monica's on the passenger seat. Yeah
Car is driving on the road this area that they're in if you're familiar with Kokomo, Indiana
If you're familiar with that area, you may actually know the stretch of road
Apparently on both sides of the road
There's these big bushes these big bushes that kind of line the road and they're about 10 feet tall
Monica and June are just having a good old conversation driving on the road
Monica falls silent for a moment and then a moment longer
And then a little longer and June looks over and she sees her friend's face
contorted in fear
Not just a slight grimace. It's not just a
It's a look of pure agony
Seeing something that fills her with
mortal fear
Monica points out into the darkness as the cars continuing down the road and just then
The car engine shuts off
The car is now just coasting down the road the headlights dim
Lining each side of the road are these bushes these 10 foot tall bushes and Monica is pointing out
Towards the bushes, but not at the bushes
above the bushes
June sees it too. What she's seeing is
peeking over the bush are people
She said the heads seemed larger and the shoulders seemed disproportionately big
but all of these
Creatures these beans these shadow people were all over 10 feet tall big enough that she could see the head in the shoulder
So 12 feet tall 13 feet tall and they're just staring as the cars coasting down the street
engines completely shut off June almost reflexively
You're gonna think it's natural geography, right trick of the light something like that June swivels her head to
Her side of the car looks out. She sees the beans on her side of the car as well looking down at them
Now at this point June turns to Monica who Monica is still just barely holding it together
June turns to Monica and she says the one thing that if you are a passenger in a car
You hope no one ever says in a situation like this because you are helpless
You are stuck to the desires of the driver June says quote
They want to communicate. I am stopping
But before June can actually hit the brakes because she believes that whatever this encounter is they want to just talk to them
Monica flips out Monica absolutely flips out on this. She's having a completely different reaction to this
June is getting the sense that they want to talk to us and
Monica in an almost animalistic fight. It's basically you have that response. You have like a fight response than a I don't know
Communicate with us response. That should be the fourth one fight flight freeze or just talk it out
Monica though is straight fight complex. She's really not even communicative at this point
She just becomes violently hysterical is the quote that's used and while June is now trying to call Monica down
The car is just continuing to coast and these things are standing on both sides of the road for a length of around 50 feet
And then at that point
June looks up and she doesn't see them any further
Than the 50 feet that the car coasted once they pass by where these shadow beans were on both sides of the road
the engine
Starts up again lights turn back on
car drives home
That story ends with this passage here quote one of the women who I'm assuming is the passenger
I don't think the driver would be like well golly. I wanted to stop the car
But now that I think about it here's this quote one of the women locked herself up in her room for two days
And we're not talked to anyone after the incident. So again, I'm just assuming that's the passenger. That's an interesting story one
It's terrifying
Because it has all these it has all the combinations. It's at night. You're in the middle of nowhere
You have an unknown
Element and in this one you have multiple unknown elements. They're basically surrounding the car the car is dead
And you have a fight between the two people in the car not a physical fight
But you have the passenger who noticed them first and was just instilled with fear
Freaking out when the driver says well, they want to just want to talk to us
Let's stop
Now we don't know what the intentions of these creatures are
We don't know if these were shadow people. We don't know if these were malevolent. They're a bunch of out-of-work gins
We don't know but I think if in my case, I wouldn't stop the car
Especially if I was surrounded if I saw one of them, maybe
But if I saw a bunch of them both sides of the road, I wouldn't stop the car
This story is interesting because what would have happened if Monica wasn't there
That car could have passed silently by all those subjects. June was just looking in front of the road
Maybe she experiences a little bit of car trouble, but even the car trouble didn't come till Monica had already pointed them out
Maybe her car would seem to the gas pedal wasn't really working for that point in time and it keeps going
Maybe the fear actually now that I say that maybe the fear is what gave them enough power to shut the car down in the first
But June could have just driven right by him
June's car could have broke down and she's out there trying to figure out what's going on. It's 1999 not everyone has a cell phone
It's nighttime. She's hoping someone else is gonna drive by to help and while she's trying to figure out what's wrong with her car
Why the engine just died there are these dark shadows just staring down at her
Silently watching her and waiting
It's also possible that she was driving out
Like this episode are you glad I found this one people who are listening to this episode at night driving down the road and
They're experiencing car trouble. It's also possible that she would have stopped so let's play it where she's driving on the road
She sees the figures the car does die
But she's coasting and she goes they just want to communicate
She gets out of her car and then just disappears
I have to assume some sort of malevolent force with this because there's very few guardian angels that will
Check up your car to talk to you right that was always my biggest complaint about that twilight book
There's a lot of them
But was that Edward the romantic star at one point doesn't want Bella you guys didn't expect this
You guys didn't expect this on today's episode Edward doesn't want Bella to go meet the werewolf guy
Whatever his name was Sean or Sam or something like that
Edward doesn't want Bella to go meet that dude Sean the werewolf whatever his name was so Edward
Breaks into her car and rips out the starter engine to her car and says I told you stay away from Sean
She's like pretty sure that's not his name
He's like doesn't matter stay away from them because you're not getting this starter engine back and I'm never reading that and I thought I
Know guys like that. I know guys that would
Human strength they're not like er, but I know guys that if they could have they would have ripped starter engines out of their
Girlfriend's cars or girls they're interested in but she ended up with them anyways though
It's horrible horrible moral of the story, but and then the werewolf ends up with her baby
It's the whole the book is so all the books are weird didn't finish the last one, but it did three of them
my point is is that
Good things good guys don't normally damage your car or even temporarily
It's so good that that gin that I summon was throwing down spike strips on the road doesn't happen
You could say guardian angel makes it so your gas pedal doesn't work just right and then a car goes by it because you were
decelerated fine
But to actually like kill your engine and have you glide down this dark road as you're surrounded by ghosts or demons or whatever
They were aliens who knows seems odd. It's almost like when you read the story
I'm sure there's a group of people who go oh dude if Monica was in the car June could have had a
Close encounter like June could have experienced the paranormal
But I think a more rational person me would say good job Monica good job because you probably saved her from
A fate worse than death. Ooh, here's one. Here's one. So to wrap this episode up this chaotic episode
You're driving down the road late at night
And then that story happens to you
I'm gonna repeat the whole thing
But you're driving down the road late at night your car dies and you've always been a little bit interested in the paranormal
You've summoned gins you read the Twilight series and now you are in the middle of nowhere
With these giant beans of shadow and darkness
It has to be the the silhouette would have had to be so pitch black to be noticeable at night
I've seen things like that. I've seen shadow people like that. It's like watching it. It's really hard to describe
It's like it's like darker than black
Very it's like an true absence of light. I've done a couple episodes on those guys
My personal experiences, but so to be able to see those things against the night sky that have to be
physically and possibly dark
Machine good, but you get out of your car. You've always wanted an encounter like this you get out of your car
You just want to communicate you yell out into the darkness. I know you just want to communicate. That's why I've stopped
Please please tell me what you want me to know
But you never get to tell that message
The next day your car is still on the side of the road police car shows up tow truck shows up
Family and friends wonder what happens to you
Nobody can ever really figure it out
then on another night
Another car is driving down that same stretch of road and that night a keen observer
May notice
There's an extra
Giant shadow standing on the side of the road
looking for another victim
Dead rabbit radio a gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
This is more of a episode will actually be what I planned. It'll be the dad's story. It's a really good story. Have a great one guys
*Music*