What would you do if your best friend asked you to write him a letter?
A letter which could change his life.
And then we travel to Santiago, Chile, to meet a young man who's riding his bike home one
afternoon.
When a car slams into him and he flies off of his bicycle, he thinks this is the end.
But as he suddenly realizes his soul is leaving his physical form, he has no idea of the adventure.
He's about to go on TODAY on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too and we'll do a little dance in each area.
It's nice that you're dancing Jason, but maybe focus on the audio quality.
We have a lot of stuff to cover so first off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command, give it
up for longtime supporters of the show, Nick and Helena Buston.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Come on in!
Nick and Helena Buston into Dead Rabbit Radio.
They are longtime supporters of the show.
They always stop by for the live episodes we do on Sundays and they sent me a birthday
present.
They sent me a birthday present because my birthday is next Tuesday.
If you're listening to this episode in time, October 4th is my birthday and they sent me
a present off of my Amazon wish list.
They sent me the book Humanoid Encounters, the others amongst us.
Woo!
Spooky title and timely.
It's a meme.
This is actually as much as I'm making fun of the book.
I love this book.
This is by Albert Rosales.
We've covered a lot of stuff from his Humanoid Encounters books over the years.
What I like about it is not just UFO stuff.
It's not just like, "Oh, I saw a light in the sky."
Well, thanks for telling me that.
That doesn't edify my life in any sort of way.
This is all humanoids and it's for the time period, 1900 to 1929.
So a lot of old school stuff.
I'm imagining there's going to be a bunch of fairies and there's going to be a ton of
fairy sightings, all this stuff.
It's like, "Whoa, dude, this is super awesome."
Then I get to the end and they're like, "And they are only nine.
It's just tall."
I'm like, "Oh, dang it, man!"
Nick and Helena, thank you so much for giving me this book for my birthday.
You guys are going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't swear to Patreon, if you guys can't buy me birthday presents, that's
fine too.
Just helps spread the word about the show that really, really, really helps out a lot.
Now Nick and Helena, I'm going to toss the keys up into the air.
You guys fight over who actually can grab them first.
Let's hop into Jason Jalopy.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Take us on out to Florida.
As we're driving out to Florida, we're going to stop off first at North Carolina, specifically
Winston Salem, North Carolina.
On June 28, 2022 in Winston Salem, at a Target store, there was a confrontation.
There was four people involved in this.
You had a guy walking through the store and he was confronted by three other dudes.
You know, words were exchanged.
The guy, he fell.
He was, "I'm a danger, man.
I'm a danger from my life."
He starts slapping at the three dudes.
It's like one on three.
Three dudes keep coming.
This is in the store, by the way.
This is like by the toothbrush aisle.
The dudes are like, "Oh no, I'm so scared."
He pulled the gun out and he shot one of these three dudes.
Then they took the gun from him.
They did a little like, "Ah, give me the gun."
They took it from the dude and the three guys took off running.
You're like, "Man, how scary would that be?"
You're just walking through Target and then three dudes confront you and you're like, "Oh,
dude, I better start shooting."
Now, you totally get that right.
Three on one.
You can fear for your life.
What happened?
And that was pretty much the tone of a lot of articles covering this crime.
But let's look at what really happened.
We'll see which side you pick now, you pervert.
You thought that the guy being assaulted was the victim?
Oh, you're sick.
Oh, quit listening to my podcast.
That is the way a lot of news articles report to this story.
What happened?
There's a group called "Dads Against Predators" and it was these three dudes who lure...
I have a hard time saying that word, so it's gonna make it sound like I have some head
injury/french accent.
They would lure men generally.
Every show I've done they catch a woman, but I don't know if this group did, but these
types of groups.
Anyways, "Dads Against Predators."
They go online and they pretend to be underage girls and then they say, "Hey, you wanna meet
up?"
And the dude's like, "Oh yeah, dude, I'm told scummo dude, I'll totally do that."
And then when they meet up, generally at Walmart, I watch a lot of these channels on YouTube.
I'll be sitting there eating dinner and they'll be like, "What?
I'm not a pervert.
Let me show you these chat logs."
What it is is they lure them to a public place and videotape them and go, "You're a child
predator, you're so sick, you're a big ol' gross dude."
And videotape them and they post it on YouTube for me to watch while I'm eating chili beans.
That was this group, "Dads Against Predators."
And there's a ton of these groups out there.
There's dozens at least that are active.
"Dads Against Predators" were talking to a 25-year-old man and they got him to come to
this target and when they confronted him, he slapped the...because they were filming
him.
They're like, "What's up, pervert?
What's up?
You're here to meet this little girl?"
He slapped the camera, slapped the camera phone, out of the guy's hand, a scuffle broke
out and so then this dude pulled the gun out and shot the guy.
He's referred to, the 25-year-old guy's referred to as the victim multiple times even by the
police and I'm like, "Yeah, okay."
He did get roughed up by three dudes.
He was the first guy to slap.
He's also a dude trying to meet up with a little girl.
Right?
Like it's so weird to read these articles and yes, I guess you might...actually he didn't
...he didn't get shot.
The only thing he did was get harassed and then he hit somebody and they started beating
him up and then he shot somebody and he's the victim.
This is...and you know what's so funny?
So you can find a lot of articles about this and we're missing some key details.
We don't know how old the fake girl was.
Usually it's a teenager, generally it's not like "I'm six" type of thing.
Normally it's like between the ages of 12 and 16.
That's the ones that I mostly see online.
The girls don't actually exist, but we don't know how old the girl was, right?
Which is weird.
The news article...I have a couple articles in the show notes.
You'll start to see the first ones are like, "Dad is against predators.
We're luring this dude."
I'm assuming the news reporter could pronounce the word correctly.
So then you'll see other articles where it's like, have her through the article, they set
it up and they're like, "Yeah, this guy, this poor guy was at Target and he got jumped."
And then have her through the article, they're like, "Yeah, the people who jumped him were
from a group called Dad's Against Predators."
So they'll build it up like, "Look at this poor guy.
This could happen to you, right?
The reporter is a big pervert too.
He's like, "This could happen to any of us."
And everyone else is like, "No, it would only happen...I mean sure, I guess anyone could
beat up at a Target, but this guy specifically got roughed up."
Oh, and they were like...articles would be like, "We don't know if they're gonna charge
them in with robbery for stealing that gun."
You're like, "What are you talking about?"
This dude was here to meet up with a kid, right?
Now, listen, I understand.
There are people who go, "These people aren't legal professionals.
The group's called Dad's Against Predators or Creep Catchers.
There's a group called Creep Catchers.
They're not legal professionals.
They're not law enforcement.
Nothing like that."
I totally get that.
And they say, "Well, they can falsely accuse people of doing things."
Yeah, they could.
Like, I could totally see that ruining somebody's life, right?
They can say that they're actually endangering active police investigations into these pedophiles.
I don't believe that.
Because I don't think that the police are...obviously, these YouTube...I mean, it is catch after
catch after catch.
If you're gonna have a YouTube channel with 140 videos and you're just in your hometown,
the police are not doing anything about this.
And that's what all of these groups say.
They're like, "We're doing this, one, because we really love that Chris Hansen show to
catch a predator, but two, like, obviously if we can catch these many people, then law
enforcement is...what active investigations am I interfering with?
You're not doing it.
I shouldn't be catching anybody.
I shouldn't be catching anybody."
Now, when I watch these channels, I prefer to watch the ones.
And it's boring, and I'm not saying that I watch the first five minutes.
Sometimes I'll skip past it.
But you need to post the chat logs.
Because otherwise, I'm taking you at your word that this guy is as creepy as you say.
There are some channels where this dude will just walk up to an Arby's restaurant and be
like, "Hey, bro, you're a pedophile."
And they'll be like, "What?"
And they're like, "You were trying to meet up with this 14-year-old girl, and he's like,
"What?
Oh, no, I wasn't.
I was just trying to be friends with her and stuff."
Which is still gross, right?
It's still gross.
It's still gross, but I'm thinking, like, if they're the chat...some of them will show
screen shots of the chat log so you can see how gross they are.
I would be taking you at your word when you go, "You're trying to meet up with this girl
and she said this and you were being all perverted and stuff like that."
There's a lot of groups like Perverted Justice that will put all of the chat logs online
so you can see how gross they are.
I don't want to get all the details.
You can even blur out the grossest stuff.
But show me you've done some investigations.
But anyways, you have a bunch of these groups and they're actually starting to get taken
down.
Like, I actually was looking forward this video because they post this stuff up.
This group called Dads Against Predators were putting on their YouTube channel.
The video of them and the target, I couldn't find it.
Apparently they took their...this is always a bad, bad thing.
They took their spiciest videos and put them behind a Patreon paywall.
So join our Patreon and then you get access to all this additional content and apparently
it looks like Patreon shut them down.
So all that content's gone.
They didn't back it up.
It's all gone.
Their YouTube channel is no longer any of this stuff.
They have a podcast where they sit on a couch and talk about...I don't know if this is all
they talk about.
It looks like they have guests and stuff like that.
They're bringing on pedophiles.
They're like, "Yes, meet me at my house.
Come and talk to my two big brothers."
I don't know.
I don't know what they're talking about.
All of their catches.
I couldn't find them on YouTube anymore.
Creepcatchers.ca was so big they had their own theme song.
It's dope.
You want to talk about a battle rap.
You want to talk about a diss.
Their theme song is amazing.
I might play a little snippet for you depending on how much I want to go through the fight
of copyright violations and stuff like that.
But it's a good song.
I mean it's all about catching creeps.
Creepcatchers.
So you want to mess around with little girls?
Well we'll expose you to the world.
Creepcatchers.ca.
Another community.
Memorandum every day.
Your skin is up now walking free on the street.
So put them online for everybody to see.
Hope you recognize where everyone you ever did meet.
Hope it make you lose your job and all the love from your family.
Hope it make you get addicted so you live on the street.
Begging for change to go get something to eat.
Then you feel it's helpless as that child would be.
What you gonna get a lick it up and then advance with the D-9 sex with a drugged up
routine.
Casually.
Fuck no.
Socialy cash straight, humiliated since we can't depend on the law.
They giving drug dealers more time than the pedophiles.
Nobody has to be brave.
People ask for money.
They ask for money.
He has this stuff on his computer apparently and he was trading it online and at one point
he traded it with an FBI agent.
They scooped him up.
And I'm sitting here at this Twin Peaks restaurant and I'm talking to my friend and he's telling
me this whole story and I'm just like, I mean you just have more questions every time another
piece of this story is revealed like what in the world?
What in the world?
I remember one of the questions I asked was, was he always like this?
Do you think he was always a child predator?
Do you think he was always into this stuff?
And Jerry kind of looked at me and kind of took a deep breath inside and he goes, he
says, I just think he got into some really degenerate stuff, which is possible, right?
There's two types of people who look at child pornography.
There's people who are child molesters and that's the type of pornography they prefer.
And then there are people who go down this pornography rabbit hole where they just can't
get off unless this stuff gets more and more degenerate.
It's a crime either way.
It doesn't matter if you're robbing the bank to buy meth or to pay for your grandpa's funeral.
It's still a crime.
It doesn't matter if you're a child molesting freak or someone who's watched so much porn
and becomes so degenerate you're watching it, but you're like, I would never actually
do it.
That's not the point.
You're watching what you're watching is a criminal act.
And I always have to take the time out to say this.
I know a lot of people when they go, oh, child porn, what was it?
Some 16 year old girl is pretending to be 18.
That's not what this type of stuff is.
I was always under that impression too that oh, it's some 15 year old girl who looks older.
Right?
It's like someone who looks like she's 18.
No, this stuff is like nine and under.
Generally, that's the type of stuff that's being viewed.
I don't know exactly what this dude had, what Kamal had on his computer, but it was enough
for the feds to bash down his door and take a minute, gunpoint.
And I remember I'm sitting there.
It wasn't, obviously wasn't the best meal anymore, right?
It's like, now the food can take a while to get here.
It's probably not going to taste that grand.
Because my buddy Jerry was grappling with this, all of this still.
If I remember correctly, it started all like in January, February of this year and now
we're in July and we're sitting here and he's still talking about it with the same pauses
and the same emotional tug of war inside of him that I'm sure he was going through in
February, March in April.
I mean, you know, he's still coming to his best friend, got caught with these images
on his computer.
And it's interesting because there's two other ways to look at this.
One is we're old men.
Kamal is 50 years old.
I don't know his last name, I can't pronounce it.
And federally, when you commit a federal crime when you're in possession of child porn, it's
five years mandatory minimum per image.
So I don't know if he had a hundred images.
I don't know if he had 10.
But unless you have a good lawyer that can really wrap it up and do a plea deal.
And sometimes that happens, right?
He's looking at a minimum of five years minimum.
If he can get all of these combined into one crime.
But see the thing is too is that's for possession.
He also traded it.
Apparently he was passing this stuff around.
So it's another crime, right?
I said earlier this season I go when you're a 20 year old man, right?
When I was 20 years old stomping all over Sacramento getting fist fights.
It was like I was a kid in a candy store fighting over candy.
Whatever.
10 years in prison, whatever.
I'm 20.
I'll be out when I'm 30.
Like that's kind of your attitude, right?
First of all, if you don't think you're ever going to get caught.
But secondly, you think, yeah, I beat someone up and sure you don't really do 10 years unless
it's like second degree manslaughter or something like that.
But they beat someone up.
I spend a couple of weeks in jail, year, whatever.
It's really bad to couple of years in prison.
It doesn't matter.
I'm going to get out.
I'll be fine.
When you're 50, the idea of spending five years in prison, there's no way, right?
You're not institutionalized.
You didn't go in and out of juvie as a child and then in and out of prison when in your
20s you're totally living a civilian lifestyle.
Now you're in prison for five years.
And here's the thing.
Will he get five years?
Let's say he got, let's say he had five images on him, which I think would be the minimum
for the FBI to kick down your door.
Five to 25 years is the sentence you're looking at.
And here's the thing.
So he's not in jail right now.
He gets sentenced on my birthday.
October 4th is when he's going to find out how long he's going to have to spend in prison.
And it's funny because Kamal committed this crime, right?
He did commit this crime.
I feel bad for Jerry because he didn't commit this crime.
And Jerry has to watch his best friend go to prison.
He understands why he has to go to prison.
And I've been thinking as I'm looking forward to my birthday like I do every year, Kamal
will find out on my birthday how long he will spend in prison.
And this is where the letter comes in.
Kamal's dad called up Jerry over the summer and said, "I need you to write a letter to
the court telling them what a good man Kamal is."
They have those letters that you write that you were able to present to the judge and
say, "Listen, these are all the letters from community leaders.
These are letters from members of the church.
These are letters from friends and families and employers showing that my client is not
just these crimes."
Dad called up Jerry and said, "I need you to write one of these letters for Kamal."
I asked Jerry, "I go, did you write the letter?"
And he goes, "I don't know if I'm going to."
And he's struggling with this decision.
I don't know if I'm going to.
Do I write that letter?
What he did was inexcusable.
It's his best friend.
It's his best friend and his best friend's dad is calling him up and saying, "Can you
write my son your best friend?
Can you just write a letter saying that he's a good person because you've had experiences
with him for over two decades?"
But the crime is so awful.
If he had gotten into a bar fight and smashed a bottle over somebody's head and sliced their
face up and they lost vision in one of their eyes, you'd write the letter.
He's a good guy.
He has an out drinking problem, right?
These are all the other experiences I had with them.
He was driving down the road, drunk, slams into a Subaru in front of him, killing kids
sitting in the backseat on their way home from soccer practice.
He'd write the letter.
Horrible accident.
Horrible, horrible accident.
There's no way that he can give back the life that he took, but I've known him for over
20 years.
He's more than just that.
But when someone has a collection of images on their computer that they've obviously been
hoarding, collecting, and giving back out, trading, right?
Distributing.
How do you write that letter?
It's fascinating.
It's fascinating when we think about that.
If it was someone who snapped and killed people, if it was someone who was drinking or on drugs
and killed people, if it was someone who robbed a bank and killed people, I keep using that
as an example, you would write the letter.
This crime is so gross.
Do you write the letter?
It's so fascinating because I hung out with Jerry a couple of times on my vacation.
Sometimes we would talk about this, and sometimes we wouldn't, right?
It was so fascinating because, so Kamal's father is in his 70s.
Imagine being 70 years old and everything going pretty according to plan, and then you
find out your son just got arrested for, I mean, it's the people on the sidelines that
I feel bad for.
Kamal did what he did, and he needs to pay for that.
And here's the thing, Jerry knew the stakes.
Jerry knew the stakes.
He thought about this a lot.
There's a big difference when you're 50 between five years and 20 years.
But I don't really, I understand it as a period of time.
This is the difference between me and Jerry.
This is the difference between somebody who has a family and somebody who, I have a family,
I don't have my own family, I don't have children and stuff like that.
When we're talking about the sentencing that's coming up, he said, "It's the difference five
and 20 years," right?
This time period.
To me, if five years in prison would suck, 20 years in prison would suck, you'd be getting
out when you're 70.
He saw it as a different way.
He goes, "It's the difference between whether or not you can attend your father's funeral."
I go, "Oh my God, that's true."
See, I'm not a family man.
I'm thinking of it that way.
Jerry is, see?
And to him, that was the big thing.
Kamal's dad is going to die in a very short time period, right?
It's not a threat.
It's not a threat, but if Kamal gets 20 years, then he'll never see his parents again.
When you go into a federal system, when you get arrested as a federal crime, they can
ship you anywhere in the United States.
But even if his parents do come to the prison that he's at and they get to visit him, he'll
never be able to hug him again.
He'll never get another kiss from his mother.
He'll never stand at the site of his father's death bed, holding his hand.
I didn't even think about that.
It didn't even occur to me.
And you may, in fact, if he got 20 years, never even be able to visit his father's grave
one day.
He dies in prison himself.
And that's a weighty decision, right?
Because Jerry's thinking, "Should I write this letter?"
Could be the difference between whether or not Kamal gets to go to his father's funeral.
I remember it was shortly before I left to end my vacation when I came back up here.
I was hanging out with Jerry.
I think I hung out with Jerry a total of four times, right?
We would go over to his house and stuff like that.
I asked him, "We're getting close to the end."
I go, "Did you write the letter?"
And I told him too.
I said, "Before I asked him."
Because again, I needed to know on a narrative level, right?
Because I already had established, I go, "I have to tell the story on the podcast."
So as my vacation was winding down, I asked him, "Did you write the letter?"
He couldn't even look me in the eyes.
And I looked down and he goes, "Nah."
Nah.
I don't think it would have done any good anyways.
And at this point, I'd actually done research on these types of letters.
I don't remember them, but they're called off the top of my head, but these letters
of reference or whatever it is.
Personal character, character letters, character witness letters.
And I go, "They actually can do some good.
They actually can help the judge see the defendant in a different light."
And he just kind of goes, "I didn't write it."
And so we wait.
We wait until October 4th.
On my birthday, Jerry's best friend is going to find out how long he's going to spend
in federal prison.
And that's a whole other psychological battle going on, right?
I was thinking, I was going, "Listen, if I'm out and I'm free, and I know on October 4th
I'm going to walk into a room surrounded by armed guards and someone is going to tell
me how I'm going to spend the rest of my life, whether it is five years in a federal prison,
20 years in a federal prison, 50 years in a federal prison."
Do you enter that room?
Because he pled guilty.
He has the files on him, all of that stuff.
Do you walk into that room knowing you're not walking back out for a minimum of five
years?
Do you go on the run?
They paid the bail, right?
That money would be gone.
You go for a run and hope they never find you.
Do you spend the life as a fugitive?
Do you just kill yourself?
Do you just end it there?
The unknown, the...
I can't imagine being in that situation, right?
I cannot imagine being in that situation, right?
I was with my buddy Billy when he was in court, right?
My cousin Billy, when he went to court.
I sat there in the courtroom and they gave him 17 to life for murdering that guy.
He stabbed the guy to death with a stake.
I've only stabbed him once, but it just went right in his heart and he just killed the guy.
Over... they were having some sort of disagreement.
I mean, that was rough, right?
But again, you're like...
He murdered someone.
That totally sucks.
Whenever you have the L at the end of a sentence, he may never get out.
But at that point, he was already arrested.
He couldn't pay bail.
He was on trial for murder, so he didn't have any choice but to walk into that room.
But if you had a choice, if you're out free and you know, on October 4th, you're going
to walk into a room with armed guards and a judge is going to tell you how long you are
going to spend in prison.
There is no zero years.
Do you walk into that room?
Fascinating story, right?
It ends next week.
Well, ends in a way.
The sentencing will happen.
Kamal will find out how long he's spending in the federal prison system.
For a completely avoidable crime.
For something he did to himself.
There's so many moral questions involved.
I haven't even touched on how the parents must feel about this whole thing, right?
Imagine being in your 70s and getting that phone call from jail, your son.
It's insane, right?
It's insane.
And it happened.
I've learned about this this summer.
We've been recording all these episodes since I came back, right?
And I've been wanting to tell this story because it's such a close-up view of a true crime
story.
You know, I'm standing on the outside, I'm looking in, but I'm looking at one of my
really, really good friends struggling over simply putting pen to paper.
Because how do you defend this?
Can you even defend the man?
Can you even separate the man from the charges and something like this?
So fascinating.
I'm lucky I did not have to make any decisions like that.
I'm very, very lucky that I didn't have to spend the past couple months thinking about
whether or not I would write a letter to defend someone against such heinous acts.
Because your first thing, you know, a lot of people listening to this would be like,
"No, of course I want to write a letter."
That's disgusting.
But I've never been placed in that situation and I hope that I never am.
I'd be shocked, obviously, if I was.
Just like Jerry was shocked, but...
So just a fascinating story.
And yeah, on the day that I'm sitting there eating my cookie dough ice cream cake from
Dairy Queen, opening up my presence, he's going to be walking into a room full of armed
guards and finding out how his life is going to end.
While I am celebrating my birthday, Kamal is going to be finding out if he can attend
his father's funeral.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great day guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]