It's missing persons week once again here on Dead Rabbit Radio.
A whole week of the craziest stories and you go, "Jason, I know the ending to each one.
They're still missing.
Uh-huh!"
Well, maybe some of them are, but the other ones, who knows?
Maybe we found them.
It's that crazy of a week.
First off, we travel to Helena, Montana to look at a story straight out of the pages
of missing 411.
A young girl vanishes in the middle of the woods, but this story has a creepy perverted
twist.
You're like, "Jason, I don't want to hear that."
And then we take a look at the saga of 4 different men who vanished in plain sight.
One of them was leaving a party.
One of them went out to get a bucket of water.
And then the other one was doing something else and he also vanished.
And then there was another guy, I think two.
The point is that today's episode, this whole week is vanishing week, but today I'm missing
people's week, but today it's all missing people.
And it's super spooky and I hope you enjoy it.
And this intro has gone off the rails, so let's start the show today on Dead Rabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had a great weekend.
I hope you guys had lots of fun.
And you guys heard the intro.
It's missing people's week.
I found all these crazy stories.
I didn't set out to do this, but I found all these crazy stories of people not only mysteriously
vanishing, but people mysteriously being found, which is not something that we often get.
Sometimes they are found, but it's not very mysterious.
They're like, "Oh, I was kidnapped and put in a basement for the longest time."
I have stories about people who just magically reappeared.
It's amazing.
We have so many cool stories this week.
But speaking of magically appearing in our lives, let's go ahead and give a round of
applause to our newest Patreon supporter.
Give it up for Goose Motion.
Everyone clap your hands.
Goose Motion waddles on into Dead Rabbit Command, shaking his little feathers.
Goose Motion, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Really helps out a lot.
Now, Goose Motion, we're going to put a little hat on your goose head.
We're going to pick you up and put you in the Jason Jalopy.
You are going to drive us all the way out to Helena, Montana.
This first story, it's a little rough.
It's a little rough, but the second story is very whimsical.
Now I could have told them in a different order.
I could have told them in an order that you could listen to the whimsical stuff and go,
"That was a fun episode, a fun Monday episode, Jason."
I just skipped the second story.
I did consider that.
But I figured, no, I'm going to do it this way.
And hopefully, hopefully you know where your fast forward button is.
I want to give a shout out to Pingo One.
Pingo One is the one who brought this story to my attention, so thank you very much.
I hadn't seen this before.
Their post.
It's June 25th, 1983.
And we're in the Elkhorn Mountains.
That's in the Helena National Forest near Helena, Montana.
It's 4 p.m.
Sunbeams shining down from the sky.
Look how fast I can run.
No, I can run faster.
These kids are playing a game.
Apparently they're having a race.
And it's just a fun family picnic.
Everyone's just hanging out, laughing, debating who has the fastest children.
And at this picnic is Nyline K. Marshall.
She's a four-year-old girl.
She's kind of waddling behind these other kids.
They're down by Moppen Creek.
And they can go, "Oh, look at these berries, man.
I can eat more of these berries than you can.
It's a very, very competitive family.
Om nom nom nom."
And at one point they see little Nyline kind of waddling behind them, the way a four-year-old
walks.
And they're just playing around.
And as these cases often happen, not much time goes by.
And they turn around.
And Nyline is no longer on the trail.
And then the search begins, right?
They contact the authorities.
Police come out.
The FBI gets involved at a certain time.
Friends and family and volunteers from their church are all combing the area looking for
Nyline.
I can't find her anywhere.
She has vanished.
In this type of situation, you're praying for the best that she reappears.
Magically, mysteriously, or not, you just want her to show back up.
And then the worst-case scenario is that she fell off a cliff, was eaten by a bobcat, fell
into a mineshaft.
But that's not really the worst-case scenario.
We like to think that's the worst-case scenario, but it's not.
Because we all know the worst-case scenario is that somebody abducted her.
On November 27, 1985, so two years later, the national missing and unidentified person
system receives a phone call from a man who says that he has Nyline.
And she's still alive.
January 1986, type-written letters begin to be sent to law enforcement agencies.
This letter says that I have Nyline.
Now the full context of the letters have never been released.
We have excerpts, and we'll get to those in a second, but they don't want to release
the whole thing because there's information they know only the kidnapper would know.
What we do know from these letters is that they came from Wisconsin and more phone calls
began to be made from pay phones in Wisconsin.
So the police are flooding the area around here.
We're talking to Madison, Wisconsin, Edgerton, Wisconsin to try to find Nyline.
There's a sighting of a girl that matches her description in Janesville, Wisconsin, but
they were never able to verify that that was Nyline.
In 1990, there was a guy watching Unsolved Mysteries, one of the best shows ever made.
And he goes, he's watching it, and he's eating his Cheerios, and he goes, "Whoa, wait, wait,
what?
I know Nyline.
Not know Nyline when she was four.
I went to school with her, like in elementary school."
So he calls up the hotline they have on Unsolved Mysteries, and he goes, "I'm pretty sure
I know this girl.
I'm pretty sure I went to school with this kidnapped girl Nyline."
Now it's really interesting, Unsolved Mysteries, they get tons of tips, tons of phone calls.
You gotta sort through all of them.
And a lot of them are fake, but you do have to sort through all of them.
And this is one where the police probably got this tip, I mean, seven years after the kidnapping.
Do you really expect this to be true?
I'm sure they're getting all sorts of calls from psychics, and people will be like, "Oh,
I saw her.
She was with Elvis and Big Fun, like crank calls and all sorts of things."
But the police go and they investigate this.
I believe this was in the Pacific Northwest.
They go out to investigate this sighting of Nyline from like elementary school.
They go out and they start knocking on doors and they found a missing girl.
Not Nyline, oddly enough.
They found a girl named Monica Benilla.
She'd been kidnapped by her non-custodial father eight years ago, even before Nyline
went missing.
Looked like Nyline.
Acted weird, acted like you would expect a kidnapped kid to act.
I don't know how kidnapped kids act, but I'm sure there's something a little off about
them.
I don't know if you're a kidnapped kid.
I'm sorry if I discriminated against you.
But my point is, is that so that did solve that mystery.
They have now been reunited.
The mother and the daughter.
In 1997, New Orleans, there's a nurse watching reruns of Unsolved Mysteries.
The greatest show ever made.
She calls police.
Now you know that they've been getting phone calls this whole time.
And it's good.
How many just false leads?
Good hearted people, but false leads.
This nurse tells this story.
One day she's working at a hospital and a woman named Helena comes in.
She's with an unidentified older man and she comes in to give birth.
And it is typical hospital policy to ask simple questions like, "Who are you?
Can I see some ID?
What are your medical records?
Is there anything we didn't need to know about?"
And the couple gets kind of weird.
They get kind of cagey.
And they leave.
This woman's trying to give birth.
And they leave the hospital and that nurse thought about that story and thought it was
so weird.
And then she goes, "Wait a second."
Nyleen was kidnapped from Helena Mountains.
That maybe it's a connection.
She's using that as a fake name.
She calls the tip line of through unsolved mysteries.
And they pass it to the FBI.
The police are like, "Oh man, we're so tired of falling off these leads."
The FBI looks into this one.
They track down this pregnant woman.
Very, very good at their job, the FBI.
They track down this pregnant woman that this nurse met a single time.
They track her down.
There they go.
So, listen, someone thinks that you're a missing girl named Nyleen.
She goes, "No, no, no.
My name is Helena.
But my mom's name was Nyleen."
I think.
She goes, "I don't remember my mom's name."
FBI just, at this point you think they're having to interrupt.
What do you mean?
You're named after the mountains where a girl named Nyleen disappeared.
You happen to know someone named Nyleen you think.
You don't know your mom's name?
FBI agents don't even know how to process this.
What are the chances that this girl even knows someone named Nyleen?
Let alone now she's saying she doesn't know her mom's name.
So they are like, "Let's just get a blood test so we can end this whole thing."
So they take some of Helena's blood.
And then they get some blood from Nyleen's father.
She is not Nyleen.
What's interesting about this is that you would prefer to test the mother's blood because
the fact of the matter is Nyleen, women cheat, men cheat, right?
That just happens.
It's unfortunate but it happens.
But there's always a chance that he was not the real father of Nyleen.
That she had an affair or something like that.
You always want to test the mother's blood just to be sure.
And I'm sure the FBI agents even knew that.
So you would want to test the mother's blood.
Why can't they test the mother's blood?
She was murdered in Mexico in 1995.
Such a bizarre story.
And when I looked, I was immediately intrigued about that.
Oh, we haven't even gotten to the letter yet.
We haven't even gotten to the letter yet.
I want to go into that in a second.
But at the end of the story, when you read about this, it always says the mother was
murdered in Mexico in 1995 and I'm like, "What?
And there's no details on that.
There's no details on that.
Was it just a random murder?
Was it a hit?
Was she involved in some sort of cartel activity?
Who knows?
We don't know.
But I would say I'm sure that law enforcement always would prefer to test the blood or the
DNA of the mother.
Because then you could totally rule it out.
It's possible that that wasn't, that Nyleen was never his daughter.
I'm not saying that that's the case.
This woman may not have been Nyleen, but it's very weird that she doesn't know her mother's
name.
She thinks it was Nyleen.
It's a very, very weird story all around.
And we haven't even gotten to the letter yet.
So at this point, we're in the year 2021, we still don't know where she's at.
She's still missing.
And the reason why, I mean, obviously there's two things going on.
The FBI wants to find missing kids.
One wants to find missing kids.
But this letter that they received made things far more alarming.
I'm sure there are people who kidnap kids.
There was that movie I watched a long time ago called Slender Man or Tall Man with Jessica
Beale.
And the whole part of the movie was rich people.
They send this tall guy out who's dressed like Slender Man to break into poor people's
houses to steal their pretty young children and take them to rich people's houses.
And you're like, ew, gross.
And then they just taught them manners and had them become young debutants of society.
It's like, what?
It was nothing sexual.
They just wanted attractive kids to carry on their attractive lifestyle and raise them
right.
And then there was, sorry spoiler alert, you're like watching it right now, you're like,
dang it Jason!
That was the premise.
It was nothing sexual.
They just wanted to give them a better life.
And that's still creepy, right?
Because you're still kidnapping people.
But it's better than what that, that, that, that, that, that fictional account is better
than what I'm about to tell you in real life.
So here we go.
Here's this letter.
He keeps calling her K. Here's the first part of the letter.
I picked K up on the road in the Elkhorn Park area between Helena and Boulder.
She was crying and frightened.
And as I held her, she was shaking.
And I decided that I would keep her and love her.
I took her home with me.
I have a nice investment income and I can work at home, so I care for her myself all
the time.
I teach her at home and she likes to go with me when I travel.
Her hair is short and curly now and she's really grown.
She's about 45 inches and around 50 pounds.
She has all four of her permanent upper and two of her lower incisors at this time.
She takes a bath and brushes her teeth every day.
She eats well.
Her favorite meal is pizza and cherry.
Okay, I'm gonna assume for whatever reason they edited out cherry Coke.
Maybe they didn't want to do an advertisement for this creepo.
The Coke company is like, "Uh-uh, uh-uh, we don't want to be associated with this."
It's her favorite meal is not pizza and cherries.
Because that's disgusting.
We kidnapped his pretty gross too, right?
I'm like telling that kid like gross.
Ew, you like pizza and cherries?
She's like, "Please help me."
No, the cherry is also capitalized, so I think they cut out Coke.
I think the FBI was like, "No, we have a big sponsorship deal with them."
They provide us with free sodas so we can never mention Coke.
Coca-Cola products, right?
None of it in ransom letters.
This is the second part of the excerpt.
Coca-Cola, I'm just joking.
I'm gonna go on more about Coca-Cola.
Here's the letter excerpt.
I have to get a laugh sin now because this is gross and it starts off rough.
I give her medicine from the bathroom every morning.
It is actually a spoonful of my semen.
It doesn't affect her physically.
I have never molested her in any other way.
She is a sweet little girl and it is because of how much I've grown to love her that I
realize how much her family must miss her.
But she has adjusted and seems happy.
She trusts me and she isn't afraid.
We play a lot and she laughs when we clown around.
She smiles and acts coy when I tease her.
She giggles when we snuggle and hugs me sometimes for no apparent reason.
I love her and I have her.
I just can't let her go.
Did you imagine getting that letter about your kid?
It's horrifying.
Horrifying.
I don't know this girl and it's gross.
It's hard to even read at a certain point.
Absolutely insane and she's never been found.
She's never ever been found.
Horrifying story about a young girl who went missing and what a terrifying way to start
off missing persons week.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
I have no real segue from that.
It's just creepy.
But I will say this and we're running out of time but I do want to say this real quick.
It is amazing how this story saved another girl.
And even the family said, listen we were hopeful that it was Nyleen.
But the fact that another family was reunited means so much to us.
Really really means so much to us.
So that's an interesting side note on that one.
Okay, we have more missing people coverage to talk about so let's see how we can squeeze
all of this missing goodness in.
Goose motion, I'm going to go ahead and touch the keys to the carbonicopter.
We are leaving behind Helena Montana.
We are headed all the way out to an insane asylum.
Pick a one.
Pick any one of them.
Goose motion.
Any insane asylum.
You're like, I don't even call them that anymore.
Yeah, well I'm a boomer.
And we still call them insane asylums where I come from.
I don't have time to tell the other missing story that I talked about.
The super interesting one that I said.
You're going to have to listen to this horrible story about this kid before you get to.
But this story is also equally fascinating and more importantly takes less time to talk
about.
This story is recommended to me by Weiselhorn on the Patreon Discord so thank you very much
Weiselhorn or Vizelhorn maybe.
But thank you so much for sending this my way.
We're headed to this insane asylum because what he turned me on to was a shared delusion.
Because he was talking about, you recently did an episode where reality is basically
consensus.
It was like in the past week or two.
I don't remember what the episode was.
Reality is consensus and what happens if a lot of people agree on something that's not
true.
If a majority of people agree on something that's not true, does reality shift?
It's kind of where we were at the last week on this show.
When he sent this to me, there actually is, this is so fascinating to me, there is a thing
known as folly adieu.
Which means delusion, a folly of two and then it goes on.
They have folly infamilie which is family.
Family believes something crazy.
And then the folly aprecio which is madness of several.
They should call it madness of many.
That would be a dope like heavy metal album.
Madness of many.
They're not trying to name heavy metal albums, they're trying to cure psychotic diseases.
Trying to help people but they should make them sound cooler.
And it's funny because he sent me this and I'm looking at this and at the same time I
was reading an article from the BBC called The Moment QAnon.
There goes my YouTube channel.
Getting banned again.
The moment QAnon took the person I love most.
I read that article and I often go to the subreddit called QAnon Casualties and what
they do, it might be the funniest subreddit on Reddit right now.
QAnon Casualties is this subreddit where people, I gotta read you some of these headlines.
These are absolutely hilarious.
QAnon Casualties is a subreddit where people talk about their friends and family who have
started following QAnon beliefs and they're like "I don't know what's going on."
And it's hilarious.
It's so funny.
I would love to know these people.
All of these interactions sound so fascinating and they're complaining about them.
I would love to one day just walk into a dinner party and there's two people sitting there
like an aunt and a nephew and the nephew is just trying to eat steak and the aunt is going
on about the craziest conspiracy theories and the nephew is like "I've had enough.
I would just sit there and soak all that energy in and it would be hilarious."
Let me read you some of these QAnon Casualties headlines here.
"My QMom, so a mom who believes in Q, thinks I support cannibalism.
That would be hilarious.
I would love if I was talking to my mom and she goes "Can we watch something else?"
And she goes "Jayson, the only reason why you want to watch something else is because
you're a cannibal."
I was like "What?
What?
No, I'm not a cannibal.
It would be hilarious."
Here's another one.
"This would be fantastic.
Why are these people complaining?"
"My dad told me that he's going to be a cannibalist."
"I'm not a cannibalist.
I'm not a cannibalist.
I would love this.
I love my dad, but my dad would be 50% cooler if he believed this.
My dad told me he can now detect me via Bluetooth.
He can now detect me via Bluetooth on his phone since I was vaccinated because the vaccine
has 5G particles or something in it.
So I read this one and this kid says "I'm walking around my dad's house."
And when he goes on his phone via Bluetooth, it's whatever this dude walks into the room.
Dude, this is amazing.
Why would it use to be the best thing I could do?
Whenever this dude walks into the room, his dad's phone shows a new set of wireless headphones.
He has to convince his dad every day he's not a set of headphones.
Tell me that's not the best sitcom ever.
Why are you complaining?
Dad, I told you once, I told you twice I am not headphones.
He's trying to log in.
He starts singing Bruno Mars.
He's like "Oh no."
Oh, it's hilarious.
This one person goes on about their 84 years.
These are all in one day.
I didn't even look at the time.
Just look at the newest posts.
These are all posted within the past day.
One of them is their grandma started buying survival gear.
She has a little mirror for signaling in the outdoors.
Hilarious.
I wish my dad thought I was a pair of headphones.
And it goes on and on and on for them.
So let's bring that back to the mannists of many things here and we'll wrap this up like
that.
This is basically how it goes.
If you believe that your son is a pair of headphones, that is insane.
And it is insane.
I think we can all agree that if you think that your son is injected with 5G particles,
that is nuts.
But the idea of a shared delusion, which was what Q would be classified as, a shared delusional
disorder, it is spread.
It is something that you would not have otherwise if you had not listened to this leader, who
would be Q in this case, and generally happens in times of social anxiety and social isolation.
So stress and social isolation, which we've seen a huge explosion of conspiracy theorists
in the past 18 months because of the COVID lockdowns.
You're stressed.
You don't have any other peer groups you can really talk to.
You're on the internet all the time.
The last time we had an explosion this big was back, I would say, 9/11.
It's not a pun of the building blown up.
I mean conspiracy theory explosion.
So we have this shared delusional disorder.
Here's the caveat, though, and this is actually written into the definition of shared delusional
disorder.
It is only insane if most people don't agree with it.
It has nothing to do with whether or not the belief itself is nuts.
It has to do with the amount of people who believe in the insane belief.
Because if you think about it, most of the things we believe in don't make sense.
They really don't.
And I mean, sure, we believe that if you hit a gas pedal on a car, the car goes faster.
There are certain things that do make sense, but I'm talking about life after death.
I'm talking about religious principles.
Follow these rules, and you will go to paradise.
Don't follow these rules, and you will go to eternal damnation.
But it's my rule.
My religion's rules, not your religion's rules.
Those ones are all messed up.
Mine are the right ones.
When you step back from it, it doesn't make much sense.
They may be good rules for us to follow through life, but we're making a lot of assumptions
about heaven and hell and things like this and what happens in the afterlife.
If there is even an afterlife, ghosts and Bermuda Triangles and all this stuff, all the fun
stuff, right?
All the fun, meaningful stuff.
If less people believed in it, it would get you locked up.
That's 100% true.
If less people believed in your religion or believed in your paranormal beliefs, people
would out and out call you and say, "People do think people who hunt ghosts and are into
all that stuff are nutty to begin with."
And think about the sea change we've seen just recently.
In my lifetime, people who believed in UFOs, they were writing books for a very particular
audience and everyone else thought people who believed in UFOs were nuts.
And now you can't read the newspaper without a week going by and they're doing articles
on UFOs.
Now you would start to be considered insane if you didn't believe aliens exist.
People would be like, "Really?
You think in the whole universe there's not any aliens?"
And you'd be like, "Well, the idea is still weird, but more people are starting to believe
in the existence of UFOs, so therefore you're starting to become a weirdo."
If you don't, you'll hear people go, "Well, sure, I believe in UFOs, there's unidentified
objects, I just don't think they're...".
You have to start to introduce all of these side notes.
Whereas before, people would be like, "What?
No, little green men, you're nuts.
You should need to stop reading comic books, you big old weirdo."
Just in my lifetime, we've seen that shift.
It's only insane if not everyone believes in it.
This is the actual caveat they have written into this.
It cannot be something "ordinarily accepted by other members of the person's culture
or subculture".
It doesn't have to be global, just in your subculture.
Think about this, in rural China, I don't know if they still do this, but in rural China
at a time, they bound women's feet.
They wanted the girls to have petite feet.
And that was considered normal.
If I did that to my daughters in America, they'd lock me up.
They'd call it child abuse.
They'd lock me up.
It's interesting though, I don't have daughters, thankfully, but I could send my daughters
to ballet class and they could damage their feet all they wanted.
They could damage their feet till kingdom come.
That's fine.
And the ballet community is acceptable to be in foot pain.
Terrible foot pain.
Bizarre.
It's only insane if not everyone believes in it.
And it doesn't have to be a worldwide thing in your subculture.
So the people who make the rules deciding what's insane have carved out an exception for themselves
and for most of society and said that other group's insane.
At what point do we get to when people go, "Oh, the world is ruled by reptilians."
When a mass amount of people do.
It's growing.
It is growing.
More people believe that now than honestly I ever thought would.
I mean, it's blowing up.
So what happens when more people believe that reptilian shapeshifters rule the planet?
What happens when the world changes so radically that most people believe in something you
know is false?
You know it.
You've watched it slowly take over society.
You know it's not true.
You start to question your own belief and go, "Maybe they're right.
How could I be so wrong?
How could I be so wrong?"
Do you say, "You know what?
It's just easier to go along with the belief."
I know it's fake, but I'm just going to pretend that it's not.
If anyone asks me about it, I'll agree with it.
But I know it's not real.
Or do you continue to stand and fight?
But see now you're the lunatic.
Now you're the person who doesn't believe in the consensus.
Reality is consensus.
And I meant that on a metaphysical level, but it is also a very social level.
If everyone agrees with something and you don't, you are out of order.
You are chaos.
And when you stand against order, you pay the price.
Even if the chaos was order, chaos was the truth just a few years ago.
Reality is consensus.
But that doesn't always mean it has to make sense.
It's not.
[MUSIC]