When a young woman leaves the safety of her village to go gather some firewood, she has
no idea she's about to come under attack from an unthinkable enemy.
And then we travel to Hollywood to take a look at the very well-known conspiracy theory
that to make it in the entertainment industry you have to be a Satan-worshipping Illuminati
member.
But, is this conspiracy doing more harm than good?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover but I do have to say this first just a quick reminder we
have today's episode and then tomorrow's episode.
We're gonna have two weeks of classic episodes and the show will not return until the end
of August.
I think it's like, I have to look at my calendar, I think it's August 30th, September 1st or
something like that.
I have to take a physical vacation.
My first vacation was just because you get burned out on the show after doing 50 episodes.
Now I have to go to another city, do a bunch of stuff there.
So I have recorded 20 episodes, the last 20 episodes or the last 18 episodes you've
listened to.
I recorded in the span of 7 days.
It's been insane.
And if I get these last two episodes done tonight, I'm gonna give myself tomorrow off.
I'm not gonna do anything Dead Rabbit related.
I'm just gonna play a video.
It's dude because here's the thing, I want these episodes for you right?
I love doing this stuff.
I wasn't gonna leave you guys in the lurch so 20 episodes in 7 days.
I will have a microphone down there with me in case there's any breaking news.
Speaking of breaking news, there's been no news about the Georgia guide stones blowing
up.
And I called that.
I said we're never gonna find out who this was.
I hope I'm wrong.
But have you noticed that?
There's been no investigation.
Okay, we'll look back up there.
I'm sure there's investigation, but we don't know what's going on.
Georgia guide stones.
It's been a couple weeks now.
But I will have a microphone down there just in case.
And I'll still be doing the TikToks for the YouTube.
Those true crime TikToks that I love.
I bust out 5 of those in 30 minutes.
So that's nothing.
But anyways, anyways I'm super exhausted.
And once I'm done recording this one, and I got one more to do.
And then officially, well I only take a day off and then I'm gonna do tons and tons of
editing and all that stuff.
So thank you guys for being with me on this journey.
I couldn't do it without you.
And someone I definitely couldn't do it without is one of our legacy Patreon supporters.
A longtime supporter of the show coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now.
Everyone give it up for Land Canyon Lifter.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in buddy.
It sounded a little lewd.
Come on in, he's lifting all those Land Canyon's.
Land Canyon Lifter.
You're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That really, really helps out a lot now.
Land Canyon, let's go ahead and get you behind the pedals of the bunny bicycle.
Everyone else hop on the handlebars.
He is going to take us out of Dead Rabbit Command and pedal us all the way down to Ukraine.
I'm still trying to figure out the sound effect for the bike that sounded like what the Wicked
Witch's bike sounded like when she's flying around in the tornado.
I want to give a quick shout out to someone known as Soul Drifter.
They, there's a website called Alien Expans and this person named Soul Drifter compiled
all these really cool articles and thank you so much.
I wouldn't have come across this otherwise.
We're going to Ukraine.
This is back in the year 1945.
So this is where you're just starting to have the Soviet Union control this country.
This takes place in February, March of 1945.
Specifically, where in the Zakhar-Potaya region, that's past the Carpathian Mountains, take
a left and you will find this little village.
I don't know if it's still there.
Don't plan your vacation to go out there.
First off, I want to be visiting the Ukraine right now anyways, but don't go out there
going, "Oh, wait, he told me to make a left.
He said this village was still..."
Also after this story, you're not going to want to go visit this village.
There's lots of reasons why you shouldn't go out there.
There's a village near the river Uz in Ukraine and there we're going to meet a young villager.
Her name is Maryyaka.
Mary for short.
She's sitting in the village and she's like, "Wow, things sure are nice here.
Soviet tanks are everywhere."
She's like, "I hope this turns out well.
I hope there's not some massive famine or anything like that."
And she goes out and she goes to collect firewood.
And later, just an hour or two later apparently, later that morning, she comes running out
of the nearby forest, screaming at the top of her lungs, "Help!
Help me!
Help me!"
And of course, this is super alarming.
People in the village, they hear a young woman screaming, everyone turns and looks
and they see Maryyaka running out of the forest.
She runs into town and her clothes are shredded.
Her clothes are just like tatters, rags on her body.
She's bleeding.
She's covered in bruises.
And she collapse when she reaches the town.
She just falls to the ground and people are gathered around her, "Mary, Mary, are you okay?
What happened?
White ape?
White ape?"
She would cry out.
They're like, "What is she saying?
White ape?
What does that even mean?
White ape?"
And they're like, "Okay, we got to get her.
Let's get her off the ground.
Let's get her somewhere.
Let's see if we can stabilize her."
And maybe someone keep an eye out for a white ape.
People are going over in that forest.
What happened to this woman?
She's so terrified her entire body is convulsing as they're trying to move her.
She's just freaking out on the ground.
And then she completely goes into shock.
At this point, you don't just have the people who gathered around her originally as she
was running out.
They're like, "Go get her relatives.
Go get her family.
What is going on?"
At this point, you're starting to have other people from town, gum over there.
Her relatives arrive.
And she just keeps saying, "White ape, white ape, white ape."
Over and over and over.
And she's screaming.
And they call in this local healer woman.
Not a registered doctor, but a medicine woman, basically.
I don't know what the actual Eastern European term would be for that.
But I don't think they called them witches in 1945, but a medicine woman.
They bring her out and they get her to take a look at poor Mary.
And she goes, "I don't know what to do for her."
She's obviously been assaulted.
We can all see that.
Your clothes ripped off.
She's bloody and she bruised.
But I mean, I don't know what white ape means either.
I don't actually know.
But the medicine woman, although she's not able to render any first aid, I think I'm
sure they put pantages on her wounds.
I don't think they just stood around and watched her bleed.
But the medicine woman's presence actually does calm Mary down enough that she begins
to explain what happened.
Mary said, "I went into the forest to get some firewood.
And out of nowhere, this white ape appeared.
And it grabbed me.
And it raped me.
And I was standing around and I was like, 'Oh my, what in the world is going on?'"
Now there was no other sightings of this white ape creature.
And they believed Mary's story because she had obviously been attacked.
Like she was covered in bruises.
She had all these injuries.
They believed her story, but there was no sightings of a white ape before this.
And there was definitely no sightings of a white ape after this.
People would have been looking for this thing.
And two months after this incident, Mary died.
Now according to the report, they're not necessarily saying that she died of her wounds.
I think that's kind of implied.
But it just lists that she died two months after this event.
It could be the shock of the whole thing.
It could have been the wounds.
But there's no story like she went off back into the woods and she was never seen again
or that the white ape came back to finish off Mary.
We don't know how she died.
However, there is a clear connection between the phenomenon in the forest and another event.
After Mary had passed away, people started seeing these strange sparkling orbs flying
around a certain part of the area.
Where the medicine woman lived, every so often people would see white orbs flying over that
area.
People were like, "What?
That's not normal.
We know she's maybe a witch."
But I've never seen orbs over there.
And this phenomenon happened a couple times.
And then a few days after this phenomenon first appeared of these white orbs floating
in the sky over the healer's home, the healer's house was attacked by some unknown force.
There was no witnesses other than the medicine woman, but her doors had been ripped off of
the house and the elderly woman was found strangled to death inside her home.
This event became pretty well known to the point that the local militia and the secret
police came to the village to investigate what was going on.
We're hearing reports of a rape from a monster in the woods and then we're hearing reports
of some sort of unidentified aerial phenomenon above a witch's house.
I mean, is this clear?
What's going on here?
And because this was a newly conquered region, you had a brand new government, right?
You had the Soviet Union.
Who knew what these guys were up to?
People in the village didn't trust them.
Rightfully so, right?
They didn't trust these outsiders.
They didn't know who they were.
Even the local militia was seen as working for the Soviets already.
They'd already bought into the system.
So the people in the village didn't reveal any of this information.
They just said, "I don't know what you're talking about."
So there was no official answer to either of these events.
The assault, the sexual assault of Mary, or the death of the healer, or Mary's death
as well was her death just, you know, circumstance or did have something to do with the attack.
We don't know.
There was no official government investigation into this.
We know about this story from an author named Andrew Zabava.
Andrew Zabava, he is someone who wrote of a lot of UFO events in Ukraine and he claims
that some of them had happened to him himself.
He's a UFO experiencer and he's covered that.
He's not a super well-known name in UFOology, but he is well-known for that region.
He does seem to have a lot of stories on that.
Interesting story, you know, we look at these creatures, these cryptids, and I think there's
a base thing like you can see them in the woods walking by or they attack you, right?
They're like stealing your beef jerky and stuff like that, punching you through, and
rocks into your cabin.
There's not a, you know, basically it's either one of two extremes.
It's either active assault, throwing rocks at you, chasing you with a big old stick,
kidnapping you, we covered that story, to just a sighting in the woods, maybe some lame
old Bigfoot telepathy telling you to be better to nature, stuff like that.
I'm actually surprised whether or not you consider these stories to be made up.
I'm surprised we don't get more stories like this.
I'm not saying that I want more cryptid stories where they're raping people.
I'm not saying that that's something.
I actually do have another one.
We'll save it for a future episode or maybe never even talk about it.
It's pretty much the same setup but in a different region.
I didn't want to do them both in the same episode, but I mean, think about it though,
out of all the Bigfoot or cryptid encounters, we've just covered on this show, let alone
all the thousands, tens of thousands out there around the world.
Sexual assault is super rare, right?
We do have a lot of stories of like sirens in South America.
They have a lot of cryptids that are trying to seduce young men, but then in the middle
of sex they become ugly and kill the men and eat their hearts out and stuff like that.
Having this type of story, right, where the creature actually rapes a woman, those are
fairly rare, which is good, right?
But I'm actually surprised they're not more common.
Again, I'm glad they're not more common, but it kind of makes you think one or two things.
The phenomenon is real if a Bigfoot is a biological creature and it is humanoid and it's stronger
than a human, it can disappear, it can pretty much do whatever it wants, then you would
imagine these stories would be more common, right?
Because it's basically nature's supervillain, Bigfoot.
You can't catch it, you can't track it, and whenever it has a base desire to procreate
or just get off, you could imagine attacking somebody like that.
It's a biological thing, you would imagine that it would happen more often.
Again, I just, we're very clear, I'm glad this is rare.
I'm just curious to why.
And then if it's a spiritual phenomenon, it's some sort of metaphysical entity, then yeah,
sure, you know, they don't have any sort of biological desire, they don't have any sort
of needs to satiate.
But if it was metaphysical, then you would imagine there would be zero.
And I have two, I have this one and that and another one.
But then we even have stories like demons raping people and stuff like that.
So it's an interesting phenomenon.
Why aren't there more of them?
I mean, maybe it's because we live in a kind universe and it doesn't want to constantly
have this stuff happening to us.
And really, you know, obviously I think it's implied that the, with the orbs flying over
the healer's house, it kind of makes that connection between the Bigfoot, the white ape creature
being part of the UFO phenomenon, which is a very popular theory growing a popularity.
And actually when I said I got this from Soul Drifter, remember I said the website was alien
expanse as Soul Drifter was getting stories together that were Bigfoot and UFO connected,
connected, right?
So we have this story, we have this horrible thing happening.
I mentioned I had another version of this.
I don't again want to talk about it.
I don't want to keep talking about this subject.
That one is interesting.
We'll cover that in a future episode because in that case, the woman, pretty much same
setup, she was attacked by this Bigfoot type creature.
But according to the report, she became pregnant because of that event.
But we will talk about that in a future episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
Right now, let's go ahead and have Landcanny and Lifter take us away in the Carboner Coventry.
We are going to head all the way out to Hollywood.
This is a story I talked about earlier on this week.
I talked about the aliens.
If aliens came down and they could prove to you that they were sincere and on your side,
no wishmaster trick double crossing thing.
If an alien came down and said, "I'm here to help you kill the evil people on the planet."
And their definition of the evil people was the same as your definition of the evil people.
Would you work with the aliens to kill the evil people?
And you knew for a fact this wasn't a double cross.
You knew for a fact this wasn't Project Bluebeam or anything like that.
Demons in disguise or anything.
I thought experiment.
I'm waiting here to hear your guys' comments.
I recorded that episode about three hours ago.
That episode will be released in three weeks.
I'm very, very eager to see what you guys have to say about that.
This is kind of the same thing.
This is another little question because I don't know if it's a question so much as...
Well, I guess that's the same thing as a question.
I was going to say I'm eager to hear what you guys have to say.
This one's a little bit different.
Listen, everyone knows of a very popular conspiracy theory.
It's so common that to make it in Hollywood, you have to be a member of the Illuminati,
the secret society, Satan worshiping group at best.
And then at worst, they're also adrenochrome drinking, child molesting, horrible people.
To make it in Hollywood, you have to be a member of a satanic Illuminati secret society.
That's the only way you become famous.
This is a very, very popular conspiracy theory.
It deals with things that conspiracy theories grow on a lot.
The other, right?
You see yourself and then you see these so-called elites.
What's Chris Pratt have that I don't have?
Satan worshipers.
What's he saying, worshipper?
And it's interesting, my conspiracy theory, I believe that a lot of the Marvel superhero
actors do steroids.
I think it's pretty obvious.
I guess I shouldn't name out just Marvel.
I think a lot of the superhero movie people do steroids.
I don't care, I'm not for all drug legalization, but I don't see why people shouldn't be able
to do steroids.
This episode is not getting monetized by YouTube.
If you're not in any sort of competitive event, if you're not actually doing something
like playing baseball or in the Olympics, if people can get Botox put into their face,
why can't you do steroids?
It's cosmetic.
It doesn't make you any stronger.
It makes you look stronger.
Who cares?
Has side effects?
Everything has side effects.