Do you have what it takes to be a master detective?
And then we meet an old man who's out camping by himself.
He thinks he's going to have a relaxing evening.
Instead he stumbles onto the answer that explains everything.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
You know I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are getting ready for the weekend.
It should be a lot of fun.
You know who's a lot of fun?
Our newest Patreon supporter, Chaz.
Everyone give a round of applause for Chaz.
He's floating down.
He's like has a bunch of balloons.
Super spooky, super slow.
He's penny wise, he's now supporting the show.
Chaz has been listening to the show for two years.
That's an OG listener.
Really, really appreciate it and appreciate the support through the Patreon.
You're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode, but you're gonna have to get rid
of the clown makeup and let the balloons go because it's too freaky.
If you can't support the Patreon but you do want some balloons, forget the balloons.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That really, really helps out a lot.
So Chaz, we're gonna start this story off.
Actually, let me back up for a second.
Chaz, I'm gonna throw you the keys to the Jason Jalopy, but before we get started, I had
a little omission yesterday.
Yesterday's episode I said I woke up from a nap.
Not a map.
I was about to say map.
I woke up from a nap.
I've been battling insomnia for the past week or two and I left out a crucial piece
of information about the NBA Jam story, that being who I got the story from.
Now, it wasn't sent to me, but I learned about it watching a video from a YouTuber named
Oddheader.
It's an amazing channel and I totally, I felt really, really bad that I didn't get
to put that in there.
It's an amazing channel that covers video game mysteries.
It's really, really cool stuff.
I got two or three more stories that I'm gonna cover that I learned about from his
channel and I'll give him proper credit at that time, but it's a really good channel
for you're into video games and you're into spooky stuff.
Easter eggs, creepy game endings that no one was ever supposed to find, haunted video game
machines.
It's a really good channel.
So sorry about that Oddheader that I left you out.
I definitely did not know of this NBA.
I don't believe I knew of this NBA story until I saw his video, so I apologize for that.
Okay, are you ready Chaz?
He's putting back on his clown makeup.
No, no, no.
I'm not.
[music]