What would it take for you to drive down three-legged lady road?
And then we travel back to the Renaissance to take a look at the story of when a very famous philosopher comes face-to-face
with ascended alien masters today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys are having lots of fun
staying warm or cold depending on what environment you're in. It's freezing up here. Before we get started
Let's go ahead and welcome in one of our Thanksgiving livestream
Donators coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now. Give it up for Alison's Wake. Woo! Come on in. Yeah, Alison's been waiting a long time for you
That's not that that's actually true. Alison's Wake when they made the donation. They said please don't put me on any gross episodes
So it's taking a while. It's taking a while. This episode should not be disgusting
I'm sorry you pervo out there who was hoping it was another one of my disgusting episodes
There's not many but I think for the people who don't like them one is too many
But Alison's Wake you're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you guys can't support the show financially
I totally get it trust me. Just help spread the word about the show. Tell your friends. Tell your family
We got flyers you can print out in the show notes post them up around town
Anything you can do to get the word out really really helps out a lot really does
Alison I want to go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider
We're gonna glide out of Dead Rabbit Command for our first story. We're headed all the way out to Mississippi
Before we get started I want to say this real quickly. I'm currently recording this episode. I'm freezing
I got my neighbors televisions blaring really loud and other neighbors working on the car out in the garage
You know, they're good people. I really like my neighbors, but the reason why I'm telling you guys that
excuses for the poor audio quality
I'm telling you I know a lot of you guys are like me a lot of you guys have projects that you want to do the time will
Never be a hundred percent right for you to get started on that project start it start it now
Start it now. It really really will change your life
This show has changed my life and I things weren't perfect when I started it
I had three jobs. I worked seven days a week and now I was able to quit two of my jobs because of the money
I make from this podcast so I mean you just get started when you can and like tonight
I could wait till tomorrow or whatever to record this episode put it off
No, I can't right. I got to do it now. I've learned to just do it now
So sorry for sometimes poor audio quality, but guys it will never be perfect start your project now
If you're waiting for the right time, you'll never get started
The little PSA I get to write this episode office attacks deduction now that he said that now I'm joking
I really do mean that Allison glide us on down here into Mississippi specifically. We're headed to a road Nash Road
Which is outside of Columbus, Mississippi. This is a like a rural road
I mean it's paved and everything like that. It's not made for goats and covered wagons
It's a regular road, but it's kind of in the middle of nowhere. There's lots of trees everywhere. It looks like a pleasant drive
during the day, but
We're here obviously for here in a paranormal true crime of conspiracy by the guys. It's not a pleasant road all the time
This road is Nash Road legally that is how the government recognizes it, but locals call it by a different name
three
Legged Lady Road
That might be that would be the most descriptive term for this legend
It's interesting. This is one of those urban legends that crosses over into a possible haunting. What's true?
What's not we're gonna take a look at all this stuff three legged lady road though leaves very little to the imagination
It involves a three legged lady
But which three legged lady is the question?
There's more than one there's more than one for this phantom on this road so apparently according to locals
I'm sure they get into very loud arguments at the local tavern over this some people say this place is called three legged lady road
because of the story of Rose a
Long time ago. There was a young beautiful girl named Rose and she lived in the area
She had two legs. She had two legs at this point and she's just growing up and experiencing all the wonders of
Columbus, Mississippi all the great sights and sounds of this place
But unfortunately, there is a group of Satan worshipers also in Columbus, Mississippi
So a group of Satan worshipers are living in Columbus, Mississippi
It doesn't say exactly where they live
I wonder if they just rented out a townhouse and all of them were like roomies together
But whether we don't know what they're living arrangements for but we know what their deading
arrangements were because they like to kill people the Satan worshipers grabbed Rose and they wanted to use her for a
Satanic ceremony so they took her out to Nash Road and
During the ceremony they chopped her up
well, what happens is
Roses mom realizes Rose isn't home and she starts to worry about her and she's like oh
Just being a worry wart, but I hope all of her limbs are still attached
So she begins to kind of drive around looking for Rose and apparently law enforcement gets involved at some point
this becomes a missing persons case and
Whether or not the Satan worshipers have infiltrated the local police department, you notice that all the cops also live in the same townhouse
We don't know we don't know the specifics of that really what we know is that Rose had no luck in finding
Her daughter until one day she was driving down Nash Road and she found
Her daughter's leg sitting on the side of the road
not very
Worshippers if they can't clean up after themselves
Apparently she found her daughter's leg and that was the only piece of her daughter that she found
And I don't know again like if the cops were corrupt or people didn't believe her
I mean it's one thing to say my daughter's missing them for the police to go
Ah, she probably just ran away
It's another thing to show up at the police department with your daughter's severed leg and be like
This is my daughter's leg and them to be like oh, maybe she ran away. Maybe she hopped away
We don't know and then not investigating it, but apparently
Rose was executed by Saint-Worshippers. She was chopped up mom finds the leg into this day
If you drive down three-legged lady road you may see a grieving mother carrying her daughter's severed leg
walking through the darkness saw being silently
Hoping that someday she can finally find the rest of her daughter and save her soul from Satan's grasp
That's a pretty good story right urban legend goes. That's a pretty good urban legend. However
Is it this is where you become a philosopher if a woman with two legs carries a leg
Would you ever call her three-legged lady?
Or would you call her nor normal grieving mother with the severed leg of her daughter road?
So there's actually another version of this that is more grammatically correct
Apparently in this area there is the action to say apparently this is true
You can do Google Earth. I'll have a link of the show notes. You can check it out
You can drive down this road with the with the camera van or whatever it is if you look at Google Earth at this location
It does show that this used to be a church like it's actually marked as a church, but when you go to Street View
It's just rubble
So I think Google Earth might need to update their descriptions there
But it is no one at it was no one as a church at one point now
It's so creepy because I'm sure this place is fairly popular with you know kids and teenagers stuff like that
There's a yellow
Lawn chair just sitting there in the middle of nowhere, right? This is really down this forested street
Road highway, whatever you want to call it road road is what it's legally called
But you'll see the ruins of a church and there's like a yellow plastic chair sitting there with somebody set up maybe
Three-legged lady will find out so three-legged lady. This is the more grammatically correct version of the story
What happened was
Before this church became rubble. Let's go back in time where the church was actually a church
There was a woman and her husband who lived in the area
You have a lot of farms in this area and this story
I think is supposed to be implied to take place sometime in the like 1950s or something like that. You have this woman
We're gonna call her Margaret
Margaret is married to Sam and they are deeply in love Margaret every day
Just loves waking up next to Sam and being like what a beautiful morning. I got both
I got both my legs just checking and Sam is such a hard-working guy so handsome. I love this guy and her love for him was so deep
that
It could complicate things in the future right sometimes someone can love you too much that you think hmm if I ever cheat on this person
Dozens of people may die
But Sam doesn't get that get that little recognition in his noggin because he does cheat on her and apparently he cheats on her a lot
She puts up with it for a while, but he's constantly playing the field literally because they're all farmers and
One time she actually just has enough of it
She can't she can no longer bear the love of her life
sleeping with other women
so
she kills him and
After she kills him she decides that I always want a piece of you with me
So she could have taken an ear right made a necklace like some sort of psychotic soldier
She could have made a nice charm bracelet out of his teeth
You know maybe taking off his nose and kept it in a little music box
But since this is called three-legged lady road, you know, she didn't take any of those suggestions
She actually chopped off his leg and
Then in a feat of engineering that no one explains in this story. She was able to sew
His leg onto her
Hence she truly is a three-legged lady. She's walking around on two legs and then sticking off of her left hip is the rotting
Leg rotting man's leg. I don't even know like she'd be super unbalanced
Maybe she'd be like a weevil wobble
Maybe as she starts to tip over that left leg would kind of help her probably not
It's probably super disgusting very smelly and I'm sure she immediately got an infection
I'm glad I'm talking about this story scientifically as if this is possible in any way she ever formed
So now Margaret has murdered her husband and is walking around with a quickly decaying leg
So into her and people in town start to get kind of suspicious
they start to think hey, it's weird no one's seen Sam lately and
Then it's weird that his wife has an extra leg
Maybe we should put two and two together and some people did at the local church
The aforementioned ruins when it was a real church the people there started to really start to think something was up again
Because guys missing woman has a new leg. It smells like rotting flesh and she's very coy about the whole thing
She's go what this oh, no, I was born with this. I had this the whole time Mandela effect
What the world's Mandela effect? Who's Mandela? Anyways
The church people say you know what Margaret? We're gonna turn you in we actually think you murdered your husband
You weren't born with the third leg
We're actually going to turn you in the church people all decided to turn her in but first
Let's go church
This was all on a Sunday morning
They converged on her house and they said we're gonna turn you in and then the church bell started ringing
And they're like oh, we'll do it after church
So all of the people who are accusing her happened to go to this church and
As she watched them go into the building she goes aha the perfect plan as everyone who knows my crime is in that building
I'm gonna barricade the door shut and I'm gonna burn the church down
And she did the pretty easy plan right she seems to be batting a thousand at this point
She burns the church down and everybody dies all of them die
So that's kind of the end of that story
There's no part where like the police surround the house and they're like come out with your legs up
And she's like you'll never take me alive covers
She's like shooting at him and stuff like that or you know just regular legal stuff like her getting arrested in standing trial
And they're like we're gonna have to take that leg off as evidence and she's like no I was born with this
It's a Mandela effect than the judges like what so to this day
Some people say as you're driving down three-legged lady road
You may see a literal three-legged lady just walking down the street her body is normal and then a rotting
Male leg strapped not even strapped stitched into her. She's walking down the street now
I'm gonna ask you a couple questions here real quick. What's more terrifying really?
Driving on the road and seeing a woman walking carrying a leg
You're like just the only terrifying before you even say the other one or
Seeing a three-legged lady walk down the road now you could be born with three legs
And it could be a like a birth defect so that's not necessarily creepy
You're not gonna be like and run away from someone
But if they had three legs because one of them was the leg of a murder victim, right?
So that's that's that's not a birth defect. That is a mental defect
The fact that you thought you could get away with it. What would be who would you want living as your roommate is a better thing?
Because if I say driving on the road, you're just gonna hit the gas pedal and get out of there
You are renting out your apartment and there's two people if you choose neither one then both of them live with you
One is a grieving mother who's constantly carrying around her daughter's severed leg
And so like she's like it's your turn to do dishes and she's like setting the leg setting the leg in the sink
And she's watching the dishes and putting them in the water with this severed leg
And you're like, uh or your roommate is a homicidal woman with three legs
And it's like this big hairy muscular man leg and she's like sitting on the couch next to you all the time
She's trying to play footsie with you and toes and skin are falling off. Which one's worse?
Which one's what? I don't have the answer. I don't know which one would be worse
I think they'd both be equally terrifying if I had to choose between the two actually I think I would choose the mom
Right because at least then you can maybe you can maybe hide the leg when she's at work
You could probably send her a psychiatrist and get her some mental help, but the woman with the three legs
She's a killer. So I think that's kind of
It was kind of a waste of time for me to even pose that question
Everyone's like Jason if you're asking me who would I rather be with a grieving mother or
Homicidal maniac. I'm choosing the grieving mother. Anyways, I love this story
It's so weird and specific like a lot of times we have crybaby bridge and that's where you can hear the sound of children
Crying underneath the bridge. There is a crybaby bridge in almost every country like it's so common because surprise surprise
When water is running over rocks in the middle of the night it can make weird noises
It oh, it's so specific
It makes me feel like there is a ghost here that has three legs whether or not she's carrying one or it's attached to her
It's such a specific road like we've covered roads
Maybe it's like Clifton Road and that's the official name of the road and that's
That's what the name of the ghost hunters call it too
But that's where you can drive down that road and you'll see like a phantom hitchhiker
We actually covered one recently about a phantom hitchhiker. It wasn't even called phantom hitchhiker road
It was just called the road. They didn't even have a name for it. This one is so specific
Three-legged lady road. That's the term that local superstitious people ghost hunters use
So why would you have such a specific name if you hadn't seen that phantom there?
Because a lot of I figured originally it was an urban legend set up because there's a burnt-down church
And then a big brother was like well, you know why that church was burned down. No
Well, let me tell you this totally creepy story that's gonna disturb and ruin your childhood
But this is so specific. It's weird all of the urban legends revolve around a one
I just told you two of them. There's other origin stories, but
Revolve around a woman with three legs. What if it's an urban legend did someone come up with the name first and then
Backwrite the urban legend was there an actual phantom scene there at some point that was
Distorted in some way and looked like it had three legs
So it slowly got the name three-legged lady road
Is there any historical truth to any of these stories?
Out of all of them
I think the most realistic one is the mom carrying the severed leg of her daughter, right?
And it could have not even been a satanic worshiping thing
It could have been like a car accident or something like that just this horrible real-life tragedy that became an urban legend
Who knows super mysterious? I mean, I guess you can go find out when your new roommate comes knocking
I'm here to check out the new bedroom as they're walking in with a severed leg
Allison's wake let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonar copter. We are leaving behind
This listeners apartment now, but it smells like decaying flesh. We are headed all the way out too
As we're headed out there
I want to do a really quick dead rabbit recommends for this movie that I absolutely love and I could go on and on talking about it
But I'm not going to because I got to keep it quick. I saw this movie just recently
It's directed by a guy who does like asylum films. He used to do like playboy videos
This movie is neither of those things. This is actually one of the most clever movies. I've seen in a long time
It's called the man from earth and it's directed by Richard Schneckman. It's a
Dialogue movie you may call it a you may call it a drama
I'm a big action guy like explosions. I like sci-fi like horror and this movie is
sci-fi I guess but it takes place in a cabin not a cabin in the woods
Not like a spooky it like a cabin that people are living in and the setup is this this college professor is
Leaving he's decided to quit his job as a college professor
He'd been working there for the past couple years and he's gonna move on and he invites a bunch of his friends over
For actually he doesn't invite him over they crash
They show up at his house because they're like hey, we heard you were leaving and you didn't tell us why?
And the guy his name is John. He says well, you know, I don't normally tell anyone this but
I'm 50,000 years old and
The movie is this brilliant
Set piece this brilliant play of words between him
Trying to convince them that he is 50,000 years old
But he doesn't really even care if they believe him and them constantly asking him questions
And it's laid out so perfectly. I'm a big action movie fan and the conversations were like fight scenes
Like you would feel the like a particular conversation start to culminate and then it would hit the climax
And then you would have that denoment and then someone else would ask a different question and you would feel the dialogue
Beautifully written film beautifully acted film
It's so weird. It's such an interesting film dead rabbit recommends the man from earth. They made a sequel. I haven't seen it yet
I heard it's not very good
But the man from earth is definitely like one of the best movies I've seen this year hands down the man from earth dead rabbit recommends
the man from earth I
Like how Allison's wake I just realized this has not to be on a gross episode and I just spent what 15 20 minutes talking about
Severed legs rotting slowly, but Allison's wake. Let's go ahead and land this carboner copter here
We are currently in Milan, Italy. It's August 13th 1491
This is actually a really good segue from that the man from earth movie recommendation because this is kind of the same
But apparently this is a true story
It was a summer evening in Milan, Italy on August 13th 1491 and
Fosio Cardano is sitting at his home now Fosio
was a philosopher a mathematician he was a professor and
He studied the occult
So if anyone was going to meet
aliens
This is the guy. I'm not discounting everyone else who's had an alien story, but they always say like
We should have brought a poet up to space like all these technicians have gone up there all of these highly trained
Astronauts have gone up there, but if you could take a poet who can actually express in such beautiful language
What it's like to leave the planet like we should have brought a poet an old saying
Fosio is that guy which
For sure and pronounce it his name wrong walk a walk a walk a
Fosio is there. He was a personal friend of Leonardo DiCaprio not him. He was a personal friend
Totally different story that does involve time travel
He was a personal friend of Leonardo da Vinci. So this guy ran with a good crew, right?
He wasn't a slacker on August 13th though. He was just chilling at his home
He had a long day of philosophizing and he goes I think I'll stay at home tonight and
Suddenly in his house. He realizes he's no longer alone
Seven men just appear they just appear out of thin air
He described him as majestic men
these figures
Inspired awe and him almost immediately
He said they were wearing bright colored flowing robes with sandals very very functional
Actually now that I think about it
How come they weren't wearing like sneakers and stuff because nowadays if you saw an alien they'd be wearing
Do I know they don't wear sneakers anyways?
You see any reptilian coming after you and he's wearing Air Jordans
But you know what I mean like that's interesting. They're dressed in the clothes of the time
I never even thought of this as I was putting these notes together anyways. They're wearing bright flowing robes
They're wearing sandals and they have on Greek tiaras, which I don't know if that's different than normal tiaras
I tried looking that up and just got a hundred photos of regular tiaras
They had black hair
They all had matching black hair and he described them each of them as just being very beautiful
Beans wherever they'd come from. They were quite the lookers
He says they all appear to be 30 to 40 years old
There's no
Word saying that they're aliens and they have giant eyes or they look like frogmen or anything like that
These guys definitely appear to be human and
They've appeared in front of Fazio
So let the questions begin
This is one of those stories where the human is just asking questions of these alien beings and we're getting these pretty interesting answers
He asked, you know, who are you guys? He's picking up his cane. He's about to beat these seven guys
He broke into his house
He asked who who are you guys who are you guys and they said that they are men composed of air?
Whatever that means
He's asking questions and they're answering them a lot of their answers are weird
Right, I guess I never expected me to show up and be like oh, I'm from Michigan
But you know he asked who they are and he goes we're men composed of air
We are just like you in the sense that we are born and we die
We do have finite lifespans, but we live to be up to 300 years old
Like we can live much longer than the normal human
That kind of started this
Conversation they're having
Fazio says we spoke of philosophy. We spoke of life after death
Like where does this journey take us?
and they
Were very very specific about the transient nature of man's existence on earth
This is just a moment in time for you. There is life after death
But this physical point between a beginning and yet another beginning
This is just a little way stop
An interesting thing that these aliens told Fazio is that
Nothing singular to a human survives death
So all of your quirks your personality everything that makes you you
dies
you survive
But all of the things that are only part of you
dies with your physical body
Fascinating right like fascinating is this true and this is true because these beautiful men are telling Fazio this back in the 1400s
Does it mean more than any philosopher?
Before or sense or science or religion or anything like that who knows but in this in the in this story
That's just a really really fascinating concept like who I am Jason Carpenter with all my passions and all my faults
Die with me but the soul of me continues on forward because I like my passions and I like my quirks and I even like
My faults I try to work on them
But you know even the stuff that I've done that I've messed up doing are part of my experience
So very very fascinating thing and and Fazio says they talked for three hours this company where I'm not gonna read you three hours of questions
Unfortunately, we don't have three hours of questions now the thing about it
I would have loved to read you a three hour long conversation between a human and an alien and I'd love to listen to that as well, but
They talked for three hours and this is this is one of the most interesting concepts
That I've come across lately. I love this thing. It's both frightening and
enlightening
Fazio asks what is the nature of the universe?
These are big questions we covered a story about a farmer who got fed pancakes by an alien
Which I'm sure they were pretty funny alien pancakes
But when you drop a philosopher who studied the occult and who is an introspective and extra
perspective person
Gonna have better questions right then can I eat your pancakes?
Fazio asks what is the origin of the universe and for the first time in three hours?
these seven aliens
disagree
Apparently most of them were of the belief that God created the universe
I always find it fascinating when aliens talk about religion
Most of the aliens say well the origin of the universe is that God created the universe, but two of the aliens disagree
And one of the aliens the tallest of the aliens says that's not true
God
Well, it's kind of true, right, but not quite true
This is dope. This is so awesome. He said God creates the universe
constantly
Like what does that mean he goes
Every minute
God creates the universe every minute every moment
God is creating the universe and you're going so he's making it bigger is it is expanding? No
the
Universe basically blinks out of existence every single moment and God
reignites that flame
It's this constant rebooting of a computer in a way and
That's how we perceive time and movement and things changing
Moment-to-moment God creates the universe from the beginning to the end of that moment
And then the new moment starts and he recreates the universe from the beginning to this new moment
It is a constant work
being built brick by brick
but each moment the wall is cleared and
The entire wall must be built once more with another brick added to it and
if at any moment
God hesitates
God stops God blinks
Reality ceases to exist forever
What an interesting way to think of reality
Let me source this story real quick
I got this from Albert Rosales humanoid sightings report, which is a resource we go to a lot
He got it from Jacques Valet's passport to Magonia, which is one of the key books in UFO literature
especially when it talks about the
Paranormal or extra dimensional origin of alien life Jacques Valet is kind of the
the
The progenitor of that theory really he's definitely made it more popular if he didn't
Created himself. I'm more of a Jacques Valet style believing in aliens than thinking they're coming from Alpha Centauri
I think there's a lot more evidence to say that they're extra dimensional or
Like that right
But I'm not completely soured on the alien coming from other planet anything so but to source that there this is stories coming from some pretty legit sources
Fascinating I mean I know I again
I don't think I'm gonna do the story anymore justice if I just drone on and on to be honest
I did just do ten minutes of just rambling and I edited it all out, but I just love this story
I wanted to share the story with you. I mean
Incredibly disturbed by it. You're like, oh great Jason now something else
I got to worry about God burping one day and then all of us just disappearing because he forgot to recreate it
I find it absolutely fascinating. It's
The the idea of a trained philosopher sitting down and talking to aliens. I really wish we had more of this conversation
But we don't I guess I guess we got the best we could this famous philosopher sitting down with aliens
And actually now to think about it. I wonder if this happens more often. I wonder if more aliens visit
People who can ask these questions, but we don't hear the stories. I just found this story
Right, maybe there are a lot more stories out there of these great minds sitting down with greater minds from another world and having these
Conversations about life about the nature of things and maybe we haven't uncovered them
Maybe those stories have never been told maybe those philosophers heard truths that they didn't think humanity was ready for
Maybe sometimes it is better to keep the deep truths of the universe hidden and
Feed the rest of us space pancakes
Maybe that's all the truth we can actually digest
Dead rabbit radio a gmail.com is gonna be our email address
You can also set us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio tiktok is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you listen to it today
I
[MUSIC PLAYING]