A mysterious waterfall in England may actually give us clues to finally answering the question,
is magic real?
Now we meet an old man whose peaceful retirement has been interrupted by invisible phantoms
who live in his attic, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having not a great day, but I hope you guys are having
a great day.
I've actually been lying to you the past two episodes and I said I was having a good day.
I was hoping I could get rid of it, my back is killing me.
I'm having some really bad back pain, back spasm, and it's so bad I've been having a
heating pad on it for so long I burned my back with the heating pad.
Oh, oh so anyways, yeah sorry for lying to you for the past two days, you know trying
to be chipper for you guys, but I'm in a lot of pain, I've got my muscle relaxers, and
a bunch of Tylenol and Ibuprofen, I'm just trying to do my thing.
The only reason I say that is that if I do appear certified, I've been able to be normal
Jason the past two episodes, but I'm a little more surly this episode, you'll understand
why and if you're a new listener, sorry to drop all that stuff on you, but someone who
I never drop on people, you like this subway?
Someone who's always a stand up kind of guy, everyone give it up for our newest Patreon
supporter, walking into Dead Rabbit Command, it's Grant Bonnet, whoo, giving him a big round
of applause, he's walking in, and he brought a massage table with you, oh perfect, I'm
gonna lay down on this massage table, we're gonna do the entire episode at Dead Rabbit
Command.
No, Grant, I'm gonna ultashi the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible, we're leaving behind
Dead Rabbit Command, we're headed all the way out to Jolly Old England.
Grant, so hopefully you can fly us out on this Dead Rabbit Durgible, we're headed out to
Narsboro, that's in North Yorkshire, England, and over in this area there's the River Nid,
and we're walking down this trail, there's a bear trying to eat one, and by this area,
there's this unique feature, it's basically like a little waterfall, so the water, I don't
have to describe what a waterfall is, what this place is, is it's known as the Petrifying
Well, it's a waterfall, I don't know why they don't call it the Petrifying Waterfall, but
anyways, I'm not British, maybe it makes sense, there's a translation error between British
English and real English.
So you have this waterfall and people would be bathing in it, but at a certain point,
people figured out something else, so imagine every week you go there and you're like getting
all this water on you, you're like, oh yeah, I feel just like so hard, I can't move my
arms anymore, but that means it's working.
And while you're there you go, oh and I forgot, Lil' Lass Alice gave me this teddy bear and
she said, take it with you, take it with you to the healing pond, my teddy bear has horrible
back pain, and oh, I'll just leave the teddy bear here.
When he comes back next week, the teddy bear is turning a stone, and this well, this waterfall
actually does turn things to stone, this is very well known, I'm not making this up,
this is not a muscle relaxer induced hallucination, what this is, once they discovered this, people
stopped using it as a healing point, but the water is so heavy with minerals that if you
leave something underneath this waterfall, it will become encrusted in a stone like casing.
Remember like that chocolate stuff that you put on your ice cream and it, hard shell ice
cream, hot chocolate, chocolate, please don't record an episode when you're here, please
don't record an episode when you're this sick, go rest.
So you papaled, okay so let me try to explain this, this is totally real, the minerals come
off of the waterfall and they infuse like say a bicycle, which is an actual example,
someone brought their bicycle there, the bicycle now has a rocky exterior, so now you have
a rock covered bicycle, you could also take teddy bears there, and now even I know this
isn't making any sense, you can take teddy bears there, most people take teddy bears
to this fountain, to this waterfall and you let the water drip all over the teddy bear
and then the teddy bear turns the stone, and people like to use teddy bears because,
let me back up here, okay so what happens is, oh my god, if this is your first episode,
this is your first episode, I promise they're all not like this, go back and listen to yesterday's
episode for my remaining listeners, imagine Kentucky Fried Chicken, right, you have a
chicken and you dip it in flour and 11 herbs and spices and then you put it into the fryer
and when you pull it out, it's still chicken with crust, the fried crust is on top of it,
but once you eat the crust, the chicken inside remains chicken, so it's the same thing with
this, it's a bicycle that gets 11 herbs and spices, 11 minerals pouring all over it and
it creates this rocky exterior to it, now if you smash the rocky exterior, the bike is
still there, the reason why people like to take teddy bears there, because they're porous,
so both the inside and the outside, it basically becomes a statue instead of a teddy bear,
this is what I think is so interesting about this, magic is real, 100% magic is real, this
is magical, but you go Jason, no we actually know how this works, it's the minerals, it's
very very high mineral content water, it's like rolling over limestone, it's basically,
when I say that it turns into stone, you can turn a teddy bear into a statue in about 2-3
months, it's the same technique how stalactites appear, how it's just those minerals growing,
growing, growing and then you've got a big spike right over your head, it's the same
thing, it does it very quickly, this is magic and you go no no no Jason, that's not magical
because we know how to do that, that's science, that's science, but this was magical for hundreds
and hundreds and hundreds of years, people considered this place magical, first they
bathed in it and then once they realized it, then it turned things to stone, they stopped
bathing in it, and it just started throwing teddy bears in the water, top hats and stuff
like that, this is magic, this is magic right, you go no Jason, this is science, this is
actually the definition of science, we know what causes it, it's a highly mineralized
water, we know how it works, we can measure it, we can steady it, we can replicate it,
but magic is, I believe that magic exists and magic is just things that science hasn't
been able to figure out yet, the reason why I wanted to tell this story is because I do
believe that magic exists and I believe that the only thing that separates like the world
of the paranormal, I use that word all the time because it's a defining word but I believe
that the paranormal is normal, we just can't explain it scientifically yet, we can't explain
ghost scientifically or demon scientifically or telekinesis, remote viewing, I believe
that someday we will be able to, personally I could care less whether or not other people
believe in it, I'm never trying to prove this stuff but if back, let's say a hundred years
ago someone tried telling you that they had access to all the written works of civilization
at the touch of a button, in the palm of their hand if someone told you "I have access to
all of the great writings" and a lot of lousy writings as well and not only that but I can
instantly communicate with almost anyone on the planet, wherever they're at, you'd call
that person a sorcerer but we all can do that right now, we have access to the internet,
it's magical, it's magical and it's so interesting because what happens is we create something
magical and have a scientific reason behind it and go "but this isn't magic, this is
electrons moving around, this is cables put down that's able to send your voice across
the planet, the planet!"
It's not magical, that ghost that's magical, this isn't magical, we have science to prove
this and like the petrifying waterfall, the scientific answer was always there, it was
always there but until we learned to measure it, we called it magic and the second we were
able to measure "oh this is how we measure the minerals and water" we go "oh but that's
not magic, this is science but that other thing over there, that haunted bridge, now
that's magic!"
I honestly think that the paranormal is normal and it is so weird how much magical things
we do, I walk to the bank, I don't even walk to the bank, I walk to a robot built into
a wall and say "I want 80 dollars and money appears" that's magical, up until 1980s that
was insane, you wouldn't ever think that would be possible, I could get money out of
a brick, I get money out of a piece of plastic put inside a brick wall and if you went back
500 years they'd be like "that's absolutely impossible, what you're talking about is black
magic" I find stories like this super interesting, I do think that someday we'll look back and
we'll be like "oh yeah ghosts, no we're totally able to communicate with the afterlife, it's
normal, we know exactly how this happens because when you die you're actually this frequency
and you're kind of floating around and we just never knew the right frequency to tune
into but now we've built these devices, of course you can talk to people after the dead,
I think that's just going to continue to happen, the paranormal is actually normal, we just
don't have the tools to measure it yet and the second we do come up with some, when telepathy,
if telepathy ever becomes a big thing they'll be like "oh yeah of course telepathy, duh,
we just didn't know how to work it, we didn't know how to tune into the brain frequencies"
we build devices that can look at your bones while your skin's still on them, oh that's
not magical Jason, that's x-rays bouncing around your body, that's what will happen,
the answer to faster than light travel, the answer to the law of attraction when we figure
this stuff out as a society, as a civilization will go "I can't believe it took them so
long to figure this out" for 500 years they didn't know what was going on with this well
and then they figured it out that it has this minerals in the water, that's how it'll be
with a lot of paranormal phenomenon, okay, Grant, I feel so sorry for Grant, Grant's
in this weird ass episode, Grant let's go ahead and touch the keys of the carbonic
copter, we are leaving behind this petrifying waterfall in England, we're headed all the
way out to an old man's house, as we're flying out there I wanted to do a really quick dead
rabbit recommend real quick, I saw this movie the other day called The Revenant, now not
that Leonardo DiCaprio one where the bear rapes him, The Revenant is the story, this
is one of those movies that you put in and you watch and you have no idea how it's going
to end, at all, and I would say that every time there was an act change from act one
to two and then two to three, those were shocking, I had no, when I put the movie in, I didn't
even know what the movie was about, I do this all the time, I watch movies I have no idea
what they're about, this movie is about a Revenant, a ghoul, basically this guy dies
in the middle east, he's like in Afghanistan or something, he dies and when his body is
shipped back to the United States, he comes back to life and he is a ghoul, a vampire,
a zombie, he actually has won a bunch of awards for best vampire movie and best zombie movie
because it's really hard to classify it and it is a movie about this guy who comes back
and he's in the United States and he needs to drink human blood to survive and it's
a comedy and as the movie progresses, it's actually a pretty funny comedy but as the
movie progresses, it stops being funny and gets super dark and I have to say it's probably
one of the most realistic vampire movies that I've seen because what's so fascinating about
it is when he realizes he doesn't know what he is and eventually they have that part where
they learn the rules like this is what a Revenant is, this is how a Revenant survives, this is
how you kill a Revenant and none of the rules are right, none of them, they're told all
this stuff and none of it's right and I thought that's actually how it would be, you would
go to what you saw in movies and read in books but who's to say any of that's accurate, a
lot of times in movies or shows like Buffy the Vampire Slayer or Sinister, the rules
are correct because in this universe this creature existed but in this movie, it's
in the real world, there's no such thing as a Revenant in the real world so they're going
off of myths and fables and movies they saw and none of the rules are right so that was
a really cool detail as the movie was going on and then when the movie ended I watched
the final scene and I had no clue this is how the movie was going to end, it's one of those
movies that's such a fun journey and even the plot changes throughout the movie I go
I guess we're watching this kind of movie now, really really good movie and the fact
that it's called the Revenant probably makes it really hard to find but I'll put the trailer
in the show notes, if you're looking for a cool horror or comedy I mean that's one way
you could classify it but it actually moves through different genres throughout the film,
the Revenant directed by Cary Pryor, really really good movie, Dead Rabbit recommends
the Revenant.
Grant go ahead and keep flying this carbonic helicopter, we're flying over this neighborhood
and you see that little house there, let's land, let's land a couple houses away because
we don't want to scare this dude.
I want to give a shout out to the bro magnan, that was the person who posted this story
originally or brought it to my attention, I never heard of this story, this is a really
really good one so thanks for putting that out there.
So we're at this house and inside lives an elderly man, he's disabled, he's living on
a fixed income, he's just trying to make ends meet, he's reaching the end of his life and
that's really the time you want to be the most comfortable, when you're a kid you run
out and you go on adventures, when you're middle age like myself your back goes out
and you're stuck at home and then when you're elderly you just kind of want things to end
peacefully and maybe not even for a while but just for things to work out.
I hope you can tell him the sound of my voice this story is a little depressing.
This elderly man, he's been leaving these reviews for amazon products that he's buying,
he goes by the online handle of Samina, we're just going to call him Sam and he has these
reviews and all of this is going to be in the show notes, you can look at him, he has
these reviews, he's written about all these products, he's written around 22 reviews in
total, pretty normal stuff, he reviewed a skillet that he bought, it could cook up to 12 eggs,
that's a lot I'm glad that he's Gaston, he has to eat 12 eggs every morning, he's a huge
fan of the movie The Pelican Brief, huge fan of the movie The Pelican Brief, I don't know
why I said that twice, just for a fact because he's probably the only fan of that movie,
my grandma was a huge fan of Primal Fear, my grandma, whenever Richard Geer would appear
in anything, she would basically stop what we were watching and tell us about how good
Primal Fear was, she loved that movie, but anyways on April 14th, 2021 though he left
the review that's been getting a lot of attention, he left it for a product called Evernary Glass
Break Alarms, it says anti-theft alarm obviously can also tell if your glass is broken because
they fall on the ground, you're like oh they're not supposed to be there, someone must have
broken in sight, they're these very very loud alarms of like 126 decibels, they come in a
three pack, so if you've ever wanted to deafen people in three rooms this is the way to go,
and Sam leaves a review for these alarms and he said he's placed them on five of his windows,
now again it's a three pack so I'm wondering either he's really bad at math or he's bought
15 of these and put three on each window and you're thinking why wouldn't Eldie, I mean
obviously you know you should have an alarm system in your house, it's probably a good
idea, but do you need 15 of them, 15 of them, so he's buying a lot of these things and he
explains why, he leaves a review, he really likes these alarms, he gave them I think five
stars, he goes I've tried a lot of alarms in my life, but these are the best, these are
the best alarms, the other alarms I bought they would get thrown at me, they didn't go
off, they didn't go off as they were flying through the air, but these alarms no one's
thrown at me yet, you're like wait, wait, if someone's throwing an alarm at you they're
already in your house, so when do you just see the guy dressed up in the ski mask and
he's like I didn't bring a hammer, I didn't bring a weapon with me, but good thing these
alarms are aerodynamic, how is this guy even breaking into the first place and throwing
these alarms at you, well Sam answers it's the guys, come on, you know the guys, they
also took my curtain rod once, I was walking around my house and they took a curtain rod
out of the window and they smashed me in the head with it, those guys did that, they're
like what in the world are you talking about, he says listen man this might sound crazy
because the police don't believe me, no one believes me, but you'll believe me, I can
tell, I can tell from that confused look on your face that you'll believe me, they're
in my attic, they're living up in that crawl space up in my house and every night, every
day really it seems like I don't even get to enjoy my life here in this house, they
crawl out of the attic and they steal things from me, it's weird what they steal I understand
it's really weird, like I have money and you'd think why don't they steal my money, what
they steal is the little things, they'll steal food which of course people in the attic
have to eat too, I get it, but they steal food, they steal my shoes, clothes, dog collars,
what are they gonna do, they got a dog up there, see they're doing it just to drive
me insane, but I'm not insane, I'm not insane, but I come home and I notice that these things
are missing, I don't even know why I say come home, sometimes I go into one room and when
I come back to my living room my drink is gone, so now I have to go to the fridge to
get a new drink because the people in the attic stole the drink and I'm thinking I gotta
keep them from walking around in my house so these ever-nary alarms are the best, they
can't climb in and out of the windows anymore, I know from that look on your face you're
wondering are people really invisible, well I guess I shouldn't say they're invisible
as much as you can't see them, you're like isn't that the same thing, no no no no no
no see, what happens is they have this clever thing where they will set off an alarm on
the opposite side of my house and I will go to check out that alarm because I figured
I finally caught one of these dudes and as I'm walking through the house to get to that
alarm and shut off that alarm by the time I return to the room I was previously in something
is gone, I can tell what it is right away for some reason they also like to steal one
of a kind personalized items to myself, so it doesn't, they're not just stealing for
function they're just stealing to steal and the cops don't believe me, I keep calling
a place and they don't believe me, they think I'm crazy, they think I'm a crazy old man,
they won't even come over to my pelican brief viewing party anymore, now I don't understand
why they're doing this to me, I live in a high crime, I live in an area where there are a
lot of drug deals around, I think maybe my house is being used as some drug dealers headquarters
but I have no proof of that, I don't believe that insane theory what do I look like a madman
but it's just something I can't think because here's the other thing, they're using advanced
technology against me, they're using advanced technology against me, one I have fire alarms
in my house as everyone should and my fire alarms have wifi built into them and they
are using the wifi in the fire alarms to affect other things in my house and I can't disconnect
the fire alarms because then I could die in a fire so I just have to deal with it but
I have to buy things that don't have any other internet activity like I have to disconnect
my wifi before I go to bed from my computer because otherwise it will be sneaking around
on my computer, they'll be erasing all of my high scores but it's not just that level
of technology that they use, sometimes let's say their alarm trick doesn't fool me, let's
say that the alarm goes off on the other side of the house and I say I'm not leaving, I'm
gonna let that alarm play all night long, neighbors be damned, I'm not leaving the room, then
they get mad, not throwing alarms at me mad, no, I'll start to see the stars, I'll be standing
there in my living room and a million twinkling stars will appear, they'll flood my vision,
they're so bright, I can barely see and then the wavy lines, my vision becomes bright and
sparkling, the waves crash over my retinas, I can't make sense of anything, the whole
world becomes a blur and they still grab something right out of the room I'm in, they blind me
and sneak in, if I avoid the alarm trap, if I stay in the room they use advanced technology
against my brain to blind me so they can run into the room and grab what they want and
sometimes they'll just create holograms in front of me, things that can't exist I see
in my house and the police call me crazy, I'm not crazy, there is someone in the attic,
so why would they use such advanced technology against me, I know this isn't stuff you can
buy on Amazon, why, I'm just an old man, I'm just an old disabled man, I don't have anything,
I really don't have anything, why are they using this technology against me, why are
they using this advanced borderline magical technology against me, I'm not crazy, I know
all of this stuff that I put into this Amazon review which makes me sound like a lunatic
but I'm not, he goes listen I know I'm not crazy because my dogs react to it too, but
I can't say they're all bad, I guess they are all bad because they're blinding me and
stealing my stuff but listen I'm on a fixed income, I can't afford to buy stuff and I
remember I went to the store and I bought my dog a new dog collar and they took it and
I remember I was walking around the house, I don't have any money, I'm pleading to them,
please give me the dog collar back, I cannot go down to buy another one of these, just
please, you can have the food, you can have the shoes, just give me the dog collar back
and sure enough one day I walk into a room in my house and there's a bag sitting there
and I open up the bag and inside that bag is the dog collar and it was not in a room
when I bought that dog collar I never took it into that room, I left it in the living
room let's say and it ended up in the bedroom, I never took it into the bedroom, please,
members of Amazon reviews, please, realize I'm not insane, there's no other rational
explanation for any of this, nobody believes me, my dogs sensitive, unfortunately dogs
aren't good witnesses in court, the police don't believe me, nobody believes me and this
is completely affecting my well-being, I'm an old man and I'm losing weight rapidly,
I can't sleep, I can't eat, one because I'm so worried, two because they keep stealing
my food and I don't want to go out and buy more food and then bring it in, put it in
the fridge and then just to take it anyways, it's not that I just don't want to buy food,
I don't want to buy anything because they take it but these alarms, these evanery glass
break alarms seem to be stopping them at least from coming in through my windows, I like
these alarms, five stars, here's a quote from the end of his review, quote, I don't
know what to do, anyone has any suggestions please share them with me, my window alarms
work great if their signal frequency isn't disrupted, they are very sensitive and loud,
I highly recommend them for an intruder who doesn't set up camp in your home, best wishes
for all, every detail that I read that was from that review, this review is like 3-4
paragraphs long, it's huge and Sam lays out the story I just told you, holograms getting
blinded by these guys, the alarms making them run from room to room, all of this stuff disappearing,
insane, and the stuff falling on him, the people are thrown, this is one of those stories,
obviously we're a paranormal podcast so we could easily go down the route, there is a
poltergeist in his house, there is some sort of interdimensional mob boss living in his
house, he's like in this reality I fight spider-man, but over here I just annoy an old man in his
attic, which is all well and good, those are all fun, but this dude I think is suffering
from some serious mental illness, it's so fascinating isn't it, that when we're reading
the story his memory could be so shot that he's bringing this stuff home, misplacing
it and then he assumes the people in the attic are doing that, and then he becomes so nervous
and so worried about what are they going to steal today that he then is not clearly thinking
and he's forgetting stuff even more because he's stressed about something else, there's
also the possibility that his memory could be so shot that he's like oh they're not
going to steal this, I better hide this and he hides it and then he forgets that he hid
it, and I'm not even talking about dementia or Alzheimer's, like he's just so worked
up, he's buzzing on such a high frequency that he's stealing his own stuff, you know
that's one possibility, the other possibility is he does have some sort of mental illness,
I'm not a psychiatrist, I will go ahead and diagnose this guy, he probably does have some
sort of mental illness at this point, but it's so fascinating to me how the human brain
works and how it doesn't work, because all of us lose stuff, all of us lose stuff from
time to time, but this guy's losing his food, I've never misplaced food before, and how
scary that would be, right, like how scary that would be to be elderly, not just elderly,
you're going to live a fulfilling life, but to be elderly and alone in this house and
think that this phenomenon is happening, he's not even talking about ghosts, right, he's
not talking about some sort of paranormal phenomenon, he actually believes that people
are in his attic and he doesn't specifically say, I was reading from pretty much my notes
from his Amazon review, he doesn't specifically say, but what I think the implication is,
is they don't live in his attic all the time, like that's a base that they sneak in and
out of his house, that's why he has the alarms on the windows to keep them from sneaking
back in once they've left, I think that's kind of the implication there, but he doesn't
actually say that, and that would, that's still insane, right, that's still so bizarre
to think that, but, so it's not like a haunted house is kind of what I'm getting at, like
most people go, oh no, my house is only haunted at night during the day, the ghost roams the
neighborhood and haunts the local 7-Eleven, like the house itself is haunted, he's not
looking at this as a haunting or some sort of interdimensional or aliens or anything
like this, he thinks it's biological humans that are using his house and have accessed
all this technology and they're tormenting him, it's like gangstalking home edition,
right, this is basically the home version, the board game of the gangstalking world,
where they're actually in his house and he's there, but how terrifying would that be to
suffer from this type of mental distress, and you're calling the police and you know
the police dread seeing that phone number pop up, they're like, oh no this guy again,
because I'm sure he's a kindly old man, right, I'm sure when that officer picks up the phone,
and he's talking to this guy on the one hand, the officer is reminded of their own grandpa,
right, their own uncle who was elderly and lived alone, oh yeah, they gotta be nice to
the old guy, they know what it's like, we're gonna be old someday, and at the same time
they know he's off his rocker, so you have to balance those two things, you just can't
keep sending patrol units out there because they remind you of Paw Paw, there's bunch
of gangland shootings across the street and they're like, well we wanted to go cheer this
dude up, it's scary, but in his world, see, the police just don't care, nobody believes
him, he's reviewing a product on Amazon talking about how much he loves these alarms, and
he's like, can anyone help me?
Not knowing that you can't respond to stuff on Amazon, and he probably was checking the
review a couple times waiting to see someone with some advice and no one was ever able
to reach out to him.
Well I guess nobody really cares, old man, old crazy man.
Time to watch the Pelican Brief again.
It's weird too because when you look at all the reviews they're all so normal, like I
almost was expecting this to be an ARG when I first saw it, or just like an obvious proof
of like just a long term schizophrenia, no, all of the reviews are normal except for this
one.
Which makes it even sadder, right?
So this guy isn't like completely insane, he may never be completely insane, this may
be the limit of it, but whatever this mental distress is, it's driving him nuts, it's
driving him to an early grave, he can't eat, he can't sleep, because he thinks invisible
people or people he can't see, real people, are doing these things to him.
And then the thing about them giving back the dog collar, what a weird detail, right?
If this stuff just constantly kept disappearing, then you could say well he must be losing
it or never bought it in the first place and his memory is just not right, but the fact
that they brought it back, and again you could say no he put it in the bag and took it in
another room and forgot about it and all that stuff, but the way he tells it, he loses the
dog, or the dog collar is stolen, he asks for it back and then it appears in another
room he wasn't in in the bag, like if that part is true, that does make you start to
think is there a biological or paranormal answer for this.
This is one of those stories where the creepier answer is not the paranormal answer, right?
I mean if it was a ghost doing all this stuff he could get an exorcist, he could move, he
could do this, he could do that, he could take care of it, right?
But if it's a man in mental distress and he doesn't have anyone to take care of him or
anyone to tell him hey you need to get this, you need to go see a professional, that's
way sadder, it's a lot harder to fix.
I hope this is a ghost story, I really really do hope this is a ghost story, because otherwise
it's the story of an old man dying in his house, but not just dying in his house, he's
dying and he's worried, he's dying and he's fearful, he's dying and he is so alone in
the world.
In his world the only place he could tell this story was in the review section on Amazon.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address, you can also hit us up at facebook.com
to get our latest news.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast, you don't have to
listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
[Music]
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]