A rapper is shot dead and within hours the conspiracy theories already start.
And then we take a look at the story of Jerry Williams, a man who went missing for 18 years
and his mother's quest to find the killer.
And then we take a look at the Pombaro, a small, disgusting, gremlin type creature kind
of like a gnome that place tricks on people, moves their car keys, knocks over potted plants.
If this one has an especially sinister side, it's also a serial rapist today on Dead Rabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We're gonna just jump right in on this because we got a lot of stuff to cover today.
Nipsey Hussle, rapper, shot dead in the street along with three of his associates.
Now I had never heard of Nipsey Hussle.
I actually may refer to him several times as Nipsey Russell because I'm a little more
familiar with him.
That's who he got his name after.
Nipsey Russell was a comedian on game shows when I was growing up and Nipsey Hussle is
a rapper, but I'll constantly confuse their names.
I'm constantly talking about Nipsey Hussle, I think one of the times, it's getting confused
and it's getting confused.
He got shot down in the street.
That happened on Sunday within hours, within hours.
Let me read you the headline of this article that popped up maybe like 5 hours after he
died.
All these numbers are part of the headline by the way.
3-3-4-6-4-7-5-8-6-2-6-7-7-4-1-1-8-1-3-7-1-8-7-2-2-8.
The author of Nipsey Hussle, March 31, 2019 at his store, that's in quotes for some reason,
at his store, plus Nipsey Russell, Lauren London, and Dr. Sebi.
This website is chock full of numerical codes showing that Nipsey Hussle was sacrificed
by the Illuminati.
Yes, the world controlling organization that controls everything from the World Bank to
the militaries all around the world, the global elite, they are responsible for shooting down
a 33 year old black man at his place of business.
They said, you know what, we've already talked to Kissinger today, let's see Soros, we'll
see him tomorrow, what else do we have on the docket?
Oh yeah, let's kill this rapper who has one album out.
Ah, that's perfect.
Why are we doing it?
Well, he's 33 years old and today is March 31st and if you add up 3 and the 3 of the
March and the other Illuminati members, like yeah, dude, we know our own code, you don't
have to explain it, I was just wondering.
I'm like, well, yes.
So the Illuminati goes out and kills this man and others outside of his store, quote
unquote store, according to this guy, probably it was assuming it was a drug front or something
like that.
Within hours, this conspiracy theory popped up.
Even when the chauffeur started, I did a couple episodes on XXX Tentation and it's
funny because you can kind of see, it took place over three or four episodes and you
can see how the conspiracy theory started to grow from him getting shot and it was tragic
to him possibly having a beef with Drake and then to Bald Barath, Archduke, Demon of Hell,
going down there and killing him with some other gangbangers or something like that.
It was absolutely bizarre.
But it took a couple days.
This one within hours, this website breaks down the date that he was killed, the age
he was killed, the numerical value of his last tweet, which was having strong enemies
as a blessing.
If you add all the letters up, it says 187, which is the murder code in California.
It even ties in the release date of his girlfriend's first movie.
If you break that down numerically, it equals a demon number.
The proof is overwhelming and by the word proof, I mean nonsense.
The nonsense is absolutely overwhelming.
Within hours, shocking to me.
Super bizarre.
I mean, it's a massive page of just numbers.
To that to them is just proof that he was sacrificed by the world controlling Illuminati.
When they're not busy eating babies or shape shifting into reptilians, they're walking around
Crenshaw, murdering people on March 31st.
You know how many people were 33 years old yesterday on March 31st?
A lot.
A huge amount.
Just one third of them got killed or one thirty third of the 33 year old population got killed
on March 31st.
I'm not buying it.
But these people are and what sucks is that this page is going to be up forever and that's
fine.
I don't want to say that sucks.
It's free speech.
But you know what I mean?
Like this information is up forever.
People who just want to find out a little bit about Nipsey Hussle are going to go to this
page.
9 out of 10 people are going to dismiss it or won't be able to make heads or tails of
it but one out of ten people are going to look at it and say "Hmm, maybe he was killed
by Henry Kissinger."
Hmm.
So.
But anyways, whatever.
I have no other way to end that segment other than just I'm flabbergasted that it even exists
this closely to his death.
Let's go ahead and move on to our first story.
That story just kind of fell in my lap.
I didn't plan to do it but I was like I gotta cover this weirdness.
Let's go ahead and move on to our first story.
In Tallahassee, Florida sits a gravestone and an elderly woman is staring at it from
her car.
She had it erected just a few days ago but she still visits it.
The gravestone sits there in a peaceful graveyard, simply says "Rest in peace Jerry Michael
Mike Williams.
Loving father, loving son, loving brother."
On October 16th, 1969, murdered December 16th, 2000, buried September 6th, 2018.
When reporters asked her why did you put the word "murdered" on the gravestone, she had
a simple answer.
She said "In a hundred years from now, when somebody is in the cemetery, it might make
them go back and look and wonder what happened to him.
I just feel really sad that my son didn't get to live his life."
The story of Jerry Williams is kind of an odd story and it almost sets itself up for
a lot of twists and turns but it really starts off with the disappearance of Jerry Williams.
Jerry Williams on December 16th went out to go duck hunting.
He gets on his boat, this is down in Tallahassee, Florida so he gets on his boat, has a shotgun,
goes out early one morning, never comes back.
It's the normal thing, people start reporting him missing, his wife reports him missing, his
mom reports him missing, they can't find him.
They do know that he went duck hunting so when law enforcement goes out and finds his
boat empty, they fear the worst.
Now, what they figure happened is that he had his waders on, not like little butlers
clinging onto him but he had those rubber pants that were kind of heavy and he fell
off the boat and then he was eaten by alligators.
His wife Denise was obviously upset about this, they'd been married for quite a few
years, the mother is inconsolable.
She can't believe that this happened but the cops say it was an accident.
Six months later they do find his waders butlering around in the swamp.
Okay, I know this is a bad joke but I have to make this lay hard in some way.
They find his waders and they find his jacket like his vest with his ID in it so that point,
six months later the cops do declare him legally dead.
They go, alligators must have eaten him, horrible accident.
But mom doesn't think it's an accident.
She writes letters to the governor of Florida every single day.
2600 letters in total.
Now it's funny because when you write, a lot of people don't know this, when you write
a government official, you go on a watch list for the most part.
I've had friends who've worked in government and they've told me don't ever write a letter
to your senator, don't ever write a letter to your governor.
I'm like why not?
And they go, because they put you on a watch list.
It's not a permanent watch list but if you write a letter saying the rent's too high
or I'm not getting enough money for my corn feed, they will take your letter and they'll
read it, their staffers read it generally and then they'll put it in a file and then
that way they can go oh yeah that guy he's been writing us all these letters, they can
go directly to your file and go this guy is kind of harassing us.
So don't do that.
But anyway I know democracy we're supposed to be able to do that but I guess write him
and tell him you're doing a great job but be friendly.
But anyways, I don't write letters to my government officials but what are you going to do?
It's a grieving mother.
I mean she probably was on a watch list but 2600 letters to the governor over this span
of time saying please open the investigation.
Now what and she would stand on street corners with a big sign saying who killed my son,
where's my son, just tragic man, tragic, the mom just couldn't deal with it.
Rightfully so.
So that happened in 2000 when he went missing.
There were certain cops who were like I don't think that is what happened to him, I think
something else happened to him but there was no evidence.
In 2004, four years later, I don't know how they came across this information but I imagine
a cop was taking his kids to the zoo, went to the alligator exhibit and the zookeeper
said alligators actually don't eat during the winter.
They stay low in the water, they do all they're eating when it's warmer and when it gets
super cold they stay at the bottom of the water where it's not freezing for them.
And the cop's like eating his popcorn standing next to his kid being like uh oh.
That's not good.
He goes back to the precinct, hey guys you won't believe what I learned at the zoo and
he still has like a giraffe balloon and he's still like wearing his shirt that it's like
his picture is face imposed on a monkey.
They're like dude why are you in here with that uniform?
He's like stop it, stop it.
Hey let me tie my balloon down so it doesn't fly away.
Alligators do not eat during winter months.
There was no way that Jerry fell off that boat and was eaten by an alligator because
it was in December.
And the other investigators are like is that caramel?
Is that caramel popcorn?
Can I have some?
He's like yeah yeah take the popcorn but what do you think about my theory and they go
that's actually quite fascinating.
So the cops decide to reopen the investigation but the problem is four years have passed
and they treated the original disappearance as an accident so they didn't secure a crime
scene or anything like that.
Now we're going to fast forward to the year 2016.
So 16 years after the disappearance.
Denise Williams ended up remarrying a man named Brian Winchester and they were actually
friends with Jerry.
Like Jerry and Denise were married and then Brian and his wife were married and they'd
go on double dates together.
But after Jerry disappeared, Brian ended up leaving his wife for irreconcilable differences
and Denise and Brian started dating and eventually got married but in 2016 the marriage started
to fall apart.
She wanted a divorce.
She said he was a sex addict and she couldn't deal with it anymore which is probably why
he got divorced to his first wife.
Denise gets the divorce and one day she's driving to work and she sees something for
a quick second in the back of her seat she turns and Brian Winchester jumps out of the
back seat like the boogeyman puts a gun to her head and says drive to this location.
Now she does the smart thing.
She drives the opposite direction and parks outside of a grocery store.
So now there's a bunch of witnesses around and he starts freaking out and he goes please
don't leave me, please don't leave me.
I'm going to kill myself and all this stuff and she's saying don't kill yourself.
Like that's not smart.
Just give me the gun.
You know we obviously I'm not going to get back together with you because you're threatening
me.
I don't think she said that but I think that's what was going through her mind.
Eventually she talks him down from killing her and killing himself and then oddly enough
she drives him back to his car so he could go home and creepy this part was creepy he's
like thank you thank you Denise I'm so sorry I'm just going to get out of your car now
I never meant to hurt you and as he's getting out of the back of her car she sees him grab
two plastic sheets, bleach and a tool.
So he was basically about to murder and dispose of her and he's like you're not going to
call the cops right I don't want to go to jail man I'm so sorry and she's like of course
not Brian despite all we've been through you're still my husband at one point until I got
you being a sex addict and he's like thank you and it's not an addiction it's just like
I can stop anytime I want and she's driving off.
So she immediately goes to the police and says yo let me bust the flow for you no she
goes so no she walks into the police department and she sees like a deflated animal balloon
on the ground and she goes my ex-husband just put a gun on my head trying to kill me and
then kill himself so they arrest him and he gets charged with kidnapping and attempted
murder and all this stuff and gets sentenced to 20 years and at this point the cops are
thinking okay we have a widow of a man who went missing she remarries one of his really
really good friends since high school and he threatened to murder her so maybe he has
something to do with disappearance.
Brian Winchester sold life insurance and before Jerry went missing he sold a bunch of life
insurance that was not necessarily under Denise's name or it was hidden that she had recently
purchased this life insurance on her husband totally $1.75 million and the police were
like if we had known that back then she would have been a suspect but she wasn't because
we didn't know that it was hidden well and the person who sold it to her was now in prison
for kidnapping so they go to him and they're like listen we're pretty sure you have something
to do with the murder of Jerry Williams and Brian Winchester goes yeah yeah I killed him
but but big asterix there Denise ordered me to he tells this tale is absolutely tragic
that him and Denise had been having an affair for years and they decided first to kill both
of their husbands and wives on a boat accident and he's like I don't want to kill the mother
of my children also that'd be really suspicious if two people died and two people lived and
then they ended up getting married but anyways he said you know what I remember once I went
hunting with your husband and during the affair and he fell into some quicksand and I stood
there for a second and thought I could just let him drown no one will ever know and I'll
get to be with his wife my girlfriend but something took over and I pulled him out of
the quicksand and so Denise goes that's perfect why don't we stage a hunting accident we'll
leave it up to God if he survives it's because God willed him to survive and if he doesn't
then we can be together so no one else knew this but Denise but on that duck hunting trip
it was Brian Winchester and Jerry Williams in that boat and after is really like five
in the morning it was super dark after Jerry had put on his waiters which Brian was like
hey you should put on your waiters it was weird situation the guys like really he's
like yeah put him on you look so snazzy in him Jerry put him on he puts him on Brian
and then pushes him into the water but he doesn't drown even with the weighted pants down he
bobs back up to the surface somehow and swims to a big tree stump sitting in the middle
of the lake and at that point Brian Winchester is looking at him and he circles his boat
around gets closer to him and shoots him in the face with a shotgun now he hauls the body
up and buries it buries it nine feet deep goes home cleans up goes to Christmas party
so they had the murder of Jerry Williams solved but now the police had to go after the wife
Denise what is absolutely bizarre though that whole story is heartbreaking you can imagine
the young man clean clean on to the log and seen his best friend circle the boat after
knowing that he got pushed into the water seeing the boat getting closer and closer to you
the shotgun aimed at you and all that stuff but anyways all that being said in 2018 Denise
was also arrested for the murder of her husband and she was sentenced to life in prison with
absolutely no physical evidence none she never confessed they had a couple recordings where
she would say stuff like what do you know what's going on but see Brian said the reason
why I kidnapped her and wanted to kill her because I was afraid she was going to turn
me into the police because we are getting a divorce but what he ends up doing is turning
her into the police after he got a 20 year sentence it's possible that she had nothing
to do with it at all he gets 20 years for kidnapping her and he makes the whole story
up it's possible but the police say now she has something to do with it life in prison
no physical evidence the word of someone who's already facing 20 years who you broke their
heart now do I think Denise is guilty yeah probably and I think she's guilty because
if she didn't know about it at the beginning what you probably did but let's say she didn't
she definitely knew about it when she got the $1.75 million coming in like obviously she
had bought I think that's really what they hung their hat on the prosecution that she
had bought this life insurance and stuff like that but crazy story and that poor mom for
a decade and a half trying to convince the rest of the city that her son was murdered
and they finally find him in a bog they was actually so well preserved some of his clothes
were still on his body she never gave up she kept fighting for the truth about her son
and in the end that she has the truth etched on his gravestone he was murdered he was murdered
and his life was ended very short you know it's funny this episode is actually kind of
depressing this next story we are going to beautiful where does this take place oh yes
we are going to beautiful parts of Argentina and southern Brazil but all of Paraguay you
know that region that you always see in the brochures this story is actually a request
from Nicholas via email so we are traveling through all of Paraguay southern part of Brazil
and parts of Argentina very odd tour that we are on because we are just like walking
through parts of Brazil and they are like no no no now we got to go all through Paraguay
this little creature is known to inhabit all those areas we are on tour we are walking
with our tour guide and we are like he is like look at these beautiful Brazil nut trees
and we are like are we in Paraguay at this point I think we are in Brazil they are in
Brazil nut are we in parts of Argentina and the guys like dude just pay attention to the
beautiful stuff around us quit worrying about the geography but at a certain point he goes
you know I am a little parched we need to go get some lemonade so we all go to this
house this house in the middle of nowhere which is already creepy enough but we are
in the house and you feel like something is watching you the whole time you turn you
look you see like a little shadow run by you think oh it's just a cat walking upright
he kind of brushed it off even though you still hear the hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe
because you can feel like something is watching you and what is watching you is known as a
palm barrow they are also go by the name Pyroggy which means hairy feet or Karai Pyhair which
means Lord of the night or man of the night and Night Man from it's always sitting in
Philadelphia popped in my head and then I realized what they are describing is basically
Danny DeVito okay before I read this first description I love you to death Danny DeVito
but this is what the palm barrel looks like he is short and ugly short arms hairy hands
and feet and the feet are so hairy it actually gives him like a stealth movement like his
hairs are actually like dampening the noise so it's not just like hairy feet on the front
hairy souls which seems incredibly uncomfortable imagine having a million little pebbles in
your shoes but you don't have shoes and they are attached to your body he lives in forest
he lives in abandoned homes sometimes he lives in your home sometimes he is hanging out where
you live sometimes he is tired of living all by himself he wants to go into a home with
a family these things are very very well known in parts of Argentina Southern Brazil and
all of Paraguay very well known to this day they are still considered they are basically
on the equivalent of a big foot type creature where everyone knows about them everyone has
like a legend and some people have encounters with them there is YouTube videos about these
little ghoulish creatures walking around Nicholas had heard growing up that they lived in potted
plants inside your house so again it's an the big foot at least you're like well as
long as I don't go to the Pacific Northwest I don't have a problem imagine if big foot
was your roommate like and you can't get rid of him he's just like hanging out in your
house obviously you'd be able to go like a big foot as he's knocking stuff over but
the palm barrel is actually like a gremlin where even if you caught him he would just
snicker and run away wreck stuff in your house steals your car keys knocks over your plants
kicks your cat does whatever and then he'll go out to your farm and start killing your
animals like strangling chickens ripping the udders off of cows that's kind of gruesome
but he's just like messing with your livelihood so what they oh oh and he also has a special
target he goes after kids who slingshot birds people who little kids are shooting pebbles
at birds he totally hates them now the palm barrel before he shows up he has a couple
quirks he'll whistle he'll whistle and it sounds exactly like a bird and then he'll
make his appearance so just kind of walk into the scene there's a YouTube video of a bunch
of adult men sitting around and then a palm barrel shows up I'd have seen the video years
ago it's really kind of creepy it could be fake most likely is but it's still creepy
but before he shows up you hear the whistle he whistles because he's talking to birds
and that's why he hates kids who go after birds with slingshots he also has an affinity
for rum honey and cigars which again reminds me Danny DeVito if he's messing with your
livestock or if he's running around your house tipping over tables and stuff like that basically
poltergeist activity but this one is real you just give him some you leave out some rum
and some cigars on your windowsill and he'll actually won't go in your house he's already
in there you're kind of SOL but you can still give him this stuff and eventually if you
give him enough rum and cigars he will become he'll like you so much he'll become a guardian
of your property protecting it not only from other palm barrows but just bad actors in
general smoking that cigar drinking that rum I don't know if I would want to protect her
who was sloshed all the time from all the rum but better than nothing it's better than him
attacking you to this day a lot of farms will still leave out glasses of rum and a cigar
on their windowsill superstition possibly but they still do it because they go I want the
Pombero to be my friend if you ever want a free drink go to parts of Argentina Southern
Brazil and all the Paraguay and just walk on a farm I doubt anything bad will happen
to you you'll get a free shot of rum if not a free shot of buckshot in the brain for trespassing
so that would be that right you got this little gremlin type character gremlin-esque creatures
are all known all over the world sometimes they're poltergeist sometimes they're just
little guys messing with the planes of World War two fire pilots whatever that would be
it normally would just be a normal little cryptid this one though has a special ability
that I actually think ranks it in some of the most dangerous cryptids out there he's
a serial rapist which is not normal I mean you can have go like sex with ghosts and stuff
like that sometimes you hear about that or you can have suck you by but this one actually
not only can rape women doesn't want anything to do with men because he has children I can't
think of I really can't think of another cryptid that breeds with humans they may have cryptids
like a succubus who has sex with a man and then has like demon babies but this one the
ponderos has sex with you and you have a ponderos and it can do it by one of two ways one it
can just touch the woman's belly you just touch a woman's belly and she gives birth
not immediately not like she's like and then a baby pop sound but he can impregnate a woman
by touching her belly or he tricks them to have sex with him or even brainwashes them
to have sex with him so he has all of these magical powers right he can appear as I think
even though he's tricking him and brainwashing them they're still banging a three foot tall
little monster man I don't think it ever shows up and is like hello I'm Brad Pitt haha just
tricking you I'm a goblin I think he's being like hey come in this abandoned barn like
a rapist I don't think he's like a shape shifting into a good looking dude he's basically like
no it's safe you can walk across the ice in this lake and then she falls in and she
gets half frozen and you know he's crazy he's a rapist he's a horrible little monster man
and then you give birth to a ponderos and the thing is is you give birth to a baby and
it's ugly or and or Harry other people in the region go really you got tricked by the
ponderos and they assume the ugly baby is a monster now I that's super bizarre to me
I don't understand like a let's say you have a baby and it's super hairy and everyone in
the town is like oh man got a ponderos baby what happens when that kid grows up and it's
like six feet tall do they think he's just the giant ponderos but do they just go oh
no I guess he wasn't a ponderos we just called him a monster for the first five years of
his life and then he got taller than three feet or even when he's an adult do they say
he's like mom mom who's my father and she just points to the jungle and go he's out there
you'll find him in parts of Argentina Southern Brazil and all of Paraguay and he's like
ah it's only happens to single women though if you're married or dating you don't have
to worry about the Ponderos getting you so again you know all of these stories generally
come out of morality plays all of these cryptids the old versions of cryptids one don't shoot
rocks at birds or the Ponderos gonna get you to don't be single ladies forget Beyonce song
or a Ponderos will get you and three I don't know what the third one is I don't know what
the morality tale is for the farmers but anyway so that's the that's really how these legends
grow is the Ponderos real who knows I mean whether or not he's real I think is the less
interesting question because we can ask that about every cryptid I think there's a more
interesting spin on this the idea that a cryptid can breed with a human successfully for centuries
is fascinating to me absolutely fascinating the children that the women of course is most
likely not true but again let's put on our imagination caps here the children that are
born from these women are and all appearances human other than the fact that they're ugly
and hairy but we would have to really go back to the days of old like the Old Testament
when the angels were apparently interbreeding with the women on earth and giving birth to
the heroes of renown that was one of the reasons why the world was flooded according to the
Bible between the Old Testament and the stories of Ponderos today how many other cryptids have
successfully impregnated and really successfully infiltrated the human species how many monsters
or goblins or wraiths have had intercourse with women giving birth to not just a little
monster baby but a new branch on the human evolutionary tree it would be odd to think
that every genius every person who has unbelievable physical strength or speed all these people
that we look at as normal humans and go how can they do that how is that possible that
he can do that I can never do that what if all of them can trace their family line back
to a foggy night in a barn somewhere or an attic or a graveyard or some cryptid unknown
to us brainwashed a young woman and inserted their seed into the line of humanity ridiculous
I know but we do live in a ridiculous world but you know what every day doing the show
I don't always find proof of monsters but I always do find proof that this world is
far far weirder than I ever could have imagined dead rabbitio at gmail.com is going to be
our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio Twitter is @jasonocarpenter
dead rabbitio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to
listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys
you
(upbeat music)