Real raw news a conspiracy theory website. We've covered multiple times on this show
Just got doxxed and they had a full expose written on them today
We're gonna go into the stories behind the stories and find out that the truth behind the headlines is
even more bizarre
Now we take a look at the bizarre story of a group that decided to develop an artificial intelligence
To crawl along the web and learn everything they could about humanity their purpose
To expose pedophiles today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day, too
Hope you guys had a lot of fun this weekend. We got a ton of stuff to cover
So first off let's introduce our newest patreon supporter walking into Dead Rabbit command right now. You know them
You love them. It's Jack Gardner. Everyone give a round of applause to Jack
He's walking in Dead Rabbit command really really appreciate the support Jack
You're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't spoil the patreon
I totally understand just helps for the word about the show really really helps out a lot when I see the show being posted online
It always brings in new listeners Jack. I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit dirgeable
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit command. We are headed all the way out to
Washington DC
I don't talk a lot of politics on this show it's one of the founding principles of Dead Rabbit Radio, but
Sometimes you sometimes you have to take a stand and
I am so tired. I think you can even hear it in my voice. I've tried to really figure out a way to say this
My voice has been cracking I've done a couple versions of this. I'm so tired of president Joe Biden
Not giving full credit to his body double. I
Personally think Arthur Roberts 83 year old movie star Arthur Roberts is doing a great job of portraying Joe Biden
Even though if you look up that if you look up that actor on IMDB, he's taller taller than Joe Biden
apparently a heavyweight this is this is
Apparently true a heavyweight fell on Arthur Roberts head and shrunk him to the perfect Joe Biden height
Did you know that did you know that was possible? I'm tired of Arthur Roberts not getting the
Credit he deserves the only way I know about Arthur Roberts being Joe Biden's body double is because of an obscure website called real raw news
And this needs to be fully cooked mainstream news. This needs to be 4th of July barbecue news
Arthur Roberts 83 years old is playing the part of Joe Biden
And you go I don't never heard of that guy. Well, that's you know what that kind of that kind of upsets me
It's kind of making my voice sore again because that shows that you are just not a fan of cinema
You're telling me you never saw virtual girl - virtual Vegas. You never watch that movie
Movie read to find my whatever part of my life however old I was when that movie came out
He was in that you don't remember he was in dookie howzer MD the television series. He played in patient customer number two
You see I
Arthur Roberts has given so much to pop culture remember when you have that trivia trivia pursuit question
remember when you played trivial pursuit and it asked who was the impatient customer number two is a trick question because
Everyone knew who impatient customer number one was this is someone tell me if this doesn't sound like the most brilliant movie ever
Conception whatever dude primer get a job listen to this
Arthur Roberts currently serving as the 46th president of the United States
Also started a movie called moms out of sight
Let me tell you about this movie moms out of sight. I've never seen it
I've been digging into some biographical information on our new president
So I was looking at the IMDB page for moms out of sight. Tell me this doesn't sound like the best movie ever
There's an inventor his name is John Richards and he invents
Teleportation and then he there's like his evil assistant named Martin and he goes
You know what if I if I have that teleportation machine, I'd be super rich
I could sell it to the highest bidder, which is true
So to get his teleportation machine
He builds a machine that allows him to create instant clones of people and it's their evil clone
so
You have that machine. Why do you need to get a teleportation machine?
He can shoot the professor the inventor of the teleportation machine and creates an instant
Indistinguishable clone of him on the spot wearing the same clothes. I presume because I think this is a kid's movie
And it's the evil version of them
You don't have to need teleportation you just have an army of evil use or like evil Arnold Schwarzenegger
They're just mildly different
Then this movie is called moms out of sight and the cover so I know what the cover of the movie is
This guy invents a teleportation machine
This his assistant now has a machine that can make instant clones that are evil and then it says this
This is so bizarre this is so bizarre the professor this is a quote the professor's son Jack and wife Barbara
learn about Martin's underhanded doings and
Barbara uses another one of her husband's gimmicks to get revenge against Martin. She turns herself
invisible
So what
Invented the invisibility machine. He's like that could probably make me a millionaire, but I want something that'll make me a trillion
What the cover is an invisible mom?
I think she's wearing an apron or something like that and some kids are poking her head around the corner
And so that movie exists
I want to take five minutes of this podcast to let you know that that's a real movie that I have to watch
But also to let you know that our president was in that movie like isn't that amazing? We're not talking about some cheap actor
We're not talking about somebody's just pumping out franchise films over and over again. He's taking risks
The reason why I bring those movies up because the problem is is that Arthur Roberts is bringing those movies up as well
Which would be fine, right? Because he's an actor and he's trying to get more business
He goes hey, have you ever seen 100,000 zombie heads, but he's not Arthur Roberts anymore
He's Joe Biden. So when Joe Biden recently met with Boris Johnson
They had that press meeting in the White House on like September 21st 2021
And he went slightly viral because you can hear like reporters being ushered out at the ending as they're like yelling out questions
What was going on was
Arthur Roberts as he was sitting there with Boris Johnson started going this wasn't picked up on my
By the way, some of the most sensitive microphone technology in the world on these global leaders
Wasn't picked up by Mike's during the meeting Joe Biden kept leaning over and be like hey
What'd you think of up and smoke? Did you like that movie? I heard it was really good
I heard the guy who played police officer number seven did a great job
Boris Johnson's like what and the meeting would go on and then he goes hey Boris Boris
It's been a while since I've asked you since I've asked you something
35 seconds. He's really losing his grip on time. Hey, hey Boris. Have you ever seen Little Miss Magic?
What yeah, it's a it's a real movie
It's a real movie about a sorceress and teenage sorceress to get her powers
She has to help a impact husband overcome his battle axe wife. Have you seen that?
Did you know it existed until I said it a couple minutes ago and Boris Johnson again
His mic is not picking at any of this up either Boris Johnson asked like what is going on
Like who the bloody hell are you and that is why everyone starts like going bow. No look at he's been exposed
Get him out of here get him out of here
And that's why you hear all the yelling in that clip was because Boris Johnson realized this wasn't the real Joe Biden
He must be a body. He was about to expose it on live television. See the problem is is that according to real raw news
I have to state that because I want to get sued by Arthur's lawyers
According to real raw news Arthur Roberts is suffering dementia
He's making all these gaffes and he's just randomly talking about his own movies
He's just so into it now
I have to say this Arthur Roberts has made four movies in the past two years. He's not suffering from dementia
I'm sure I don't think that I I don't think you should hire people with dementia to be body devils or on movie sets
I mean that might be discriminatory, but I think it's at a certain point. It would just be elder abuse
They're like, oh, they make great zombies. We have to use any makeup at all
We just had them wander through the graveyard like I'm sure
That Arthur Roberts is totally fine
But what isn't totally fine and it's actually I think it might be on its last leg if history says anything is
Real raw news itself
The last time we talked about real raw news
I stated that I saw this tag that said this website contains satire and humor and it's for entertainment purposes only and I go
Kind of puts a whole damper on the whole thing like if it's just supposed to be funny then it's not funny
Like if people actually believe this it's hilarious
But if I mean anyone it could still be funny, but I wouldn't talk about it on the show the same way
I don't talk about ARGs or creepypasta
What happened was I recently got a story recommendation from Steve M&D on
Twitter and thank you very much Steve for sending this over so what's happened recently split effect is a fact-checking website and
They ran an expose on real raw news. It was an article written by Bill McCarthy
for political fact and this is the saga they put out they said for quite a few months now
They've been having to run
Individual disclaimers about articles that are popping up on Facebook popping up on Google ads
Directing people to real raw news and they keep saying this is not true. This is not true
It's not true
So then they just decided at this point to run a full expose on the website and to find out who's running it and
In the end they dox him and they're like trying to contact this dude's brother and some stuff that I don't agree with
I don't think he's a threat to the local community. I don't really think he needed to be doxed in that way
But yeah, they really like trying to find out where he lives and stuff like that
I'm not down with that, but I am interested that aside that aside. I'm they did this really
good deep dive into the
construction of the real raw news empire because that's what it turned out to be and
Very very interesting insights
Into what may be the real motivation behind real raw news
We know him as Michael bad and I'm not gonna dox him on this show
But the person who runs real raw news goes by the name Michael Baxter. He's a 53 year old man
That's all the information I'll reveal
But they give off his real name and he started real raw news in April of 2020
But then it started publishing stuff until December of 2020 and since then he's written 150 articles
He's the sole writer for the website
These investigations are going on to try to figure out who and it wasn't just political fact other
Fact-checking websites were trying to figure out who was running this they're able to track him back to a website called twistedtruth.net
They had an article on that one Putin recruits Steve Seagal to fight Anunnaki
And it's this article that's written that it obviously sounds completely insane
I mean Steven Seagal out of all of them. That's the one you choose and
The first line is a joke. It says he's the lead singer of a band called Steven Seagal's. It's a real band, but he's not in it
So, I mean it's ridiculous
Newsguard emails twisted truth person running this way and those articles are also written by a Michael Baxter
But they email twisted truths email address and the response to get back is this quote
It's a satire site
Exposing the insanity of rabid Trumpists who lack the mental wherewithal to distinguish fact from fiction
unquote
So right there
They're saying it's all fit not only is it all fake. It's supposed to show how dumb Trump supporters are
They're clearly laying that out in the twisted truth now just a year or two later real raw news pops up and
You have to ask are they still running the same joke? Are they still running the same scam?
Is the sentiment the same is real raw news a satire website and it's actively ripping off
Trump supporters because they're donating money and things like that
We don't know Michael Baxter is no longer responding to any emails. At least that's what politifact is reporting and
Politifact in kind when and got his Facebook page shut down had Google ads cancel his campaign
And I believe are making some push against Twitter to have him removed from Twitter because he's like
I'm gonna be on telegram soon because Twitter's about to delete me and all this stuff
So it's such a fascinating story because we were no closer to the truth really
We know at one point he thought that this is just satirical. I'm grifting these guys
It's some sort of scam because I guess he had to go fund me at one point
You definitely had a PayPal button people are donating money to him, but in the paranormal community
I've seen this happen a lot with paranormal researchers and conspiracy theorists
They start off on one side of the spectrum like I'm fairly skeptical and then they're flatter thirst within like a year
Maybe two there's a really popular paranormal conspiracy theory podcast
That has interviews and the more interviews the host is done the crazier the host has become
It's really weird
I mean like I started watching the show when it first came out or listening to the show when it first came out
And they just kept getting weirder and weirder and weirder because basically they're sitting down with people for an hour
Whose entire life entire career revolves around one issue. They know everything about it
People who believe in flat earth know way more about the flat earth theory than I do and if I was an idiot
And I kept listening to him. I'd go that makes sense and that makes sense and that makes sense and that makes sense
And my brain turns to pudding
It's very very easy. I'm wondering if Michael Baxter
Started this off as a joke and started getting quote-unquote red-pilled
And is just just gone completely off the rails
If Joe Biden doesn't have a body double if he didn't have a body double
He wouldn't be a body double who got squished to be a Joe Biden height and it wouldn't be a body double with dementia
You cannot choose a worse body double for an elderly man than an elderly man with dementia. You're gonna do that
And the fact that he's he's so super recognizable. He's been in all these great movies. We all grew up watching right you guys remember those movies
So is he
Did he think it was fake at first and now he believes it does he still know it's fake
But it's just making too much money and getting too much because this guy has a huge following huge following
So or does he believe this stuff? Does he actually believe this stuff now?
And I think we're further from the truth if anything this whole event has
Emboldened him because I think his quote to politic fact was thanks for doxing me and all the free exposure and then that was kind of it
Now it's just if he if he didn't believe it yet
He believes it now because now everyone's coming after him and I will say this the narrative in the political
This is my own conspiracy theory the narrative in the politic fact arc was
Oh, we got tired of fact checking this stuff all the time so we just decided to do a big investigation
I find it really interesting that this comes only a week after
the
Bill Gates foundation ceo
Allegedly, I mean real real raw news is saying this but it was a weird. So is very
Weird story is very subdued story. They said the ceo or cfo of the bill gates foundation emailed him and said take the bill gates stuff off your website
The Hillary Clinton stuff is true by the way, but take the bill gates stuff off the website
We're gonna sue you and he's like, yeah, whatever take me to court. This is a terrible website. What are you gonna do?
I find it really interesting that the political fact expose comes like a week or two after that
I'm wondering if the bill gates foundation was looking at the website and they go
Let's just make some phone calls and let the media deal with this
Not get our hands dirty. So that's my conspiracy theory. I think the timing's super super coincidental
But we will keep you informed both on the behind the scenes stuff and
on arthur roberts ever increasing dementia state
of mind
Although um, that is not me saying that that is real raw news. I'm simply repeating it
several times
Jack i'm gonna go to hentashi the keys to the carboner copter. We are leaving behind washington dc
We are headed all the way out to
Wherever dutch people live
You're jason, this is a fairly global society. I think you can find a dutch person in every part
Yeah, but where do most of the dutch people live like it's probably one of those
Those countries that look like dongs up north. There's like three countries. They all look like big dongs coming down
One of those i'm sure if we land there. We'll eventually find
terry d homies
That is a organization known as the land of men
We're walking around some dutch city and we see these guys walking around
We're like, hey, you don't happen to be the homies and they're like we are we are the land of men
And we have this great thing that we do we actually fight online pedophiles and we're like, dude, that's totally awesome
Is this like mortal combat do amic avatars and beat them up and they're like well kind of
And I go that's weird. I just kind of made a stupid joke
It's a stupid joke that I might edit out but now I have to keep in because it's part of the story
They go kind of let us show you and they lead us into the terry the homies
Headquarters, I'm sure it's just an apartment couple. I'm sure it's just like an office space
But we're gonna pretend it's like really cool and dope. We're walking down and there's monks
They got like hood-ons with candles and they're like going oh
Oh, and the the homies are walking us through there and they said back in 2013. We decided to launch a
attack against the pedophiles because normally we would advocate for governments to have stricter laws and better investigative tools
to take on these predators, but
We thought you know
We can actually
Do something more
And we're walking through this ancient monastery. It's all cool and stuff. But then we turn a corner and it's like digital
Like ones and zeros we're falling through the void
But then we like turn the corner and there's like phones
And there's like a computer
It's like a giant computer like a sci-fi computer and there's a guy in the keyboard
He's like do do do do do do do and we see like this computer and we see this head go
And it's like it's like this little girl and she's like her head is the whole monitor. It's very actually
It's quite terrifying to see this thing in real life
Um, because there's youtube videos of it. We're just watching this giant head and it's going hi. My name's sweetie
What are you guys up to?
And we're like, oh, we're doing pretty good. You know just walking around looking for the homies and she goes
I see that you found them. Yes. Well
That you call them the homies
But I call them
My dads and and mom's know-how sexist. I'm sure women worked on this program as well
So what we're like, whoa, you are a program. We thought we were actually talking to a live girl
Is her eyes shift from side to side? We totally knew this is so this is what's so weird about it
is there's youtube footage of this and
It looks fake and real at the same time and I don't know if it's because I know it's fake going into it
But they built a virtual 10 year old filipina girl is what the terry the homies have done and
It's to attract sexual predators and I'm thinking on the one hand you look at it and you go
It's something seems off about it. Like I can tell that's not a real 10 year old girl
But on the other hand, it does look pretty realistic and I'm wondering if
When you factor in bad webcam quality and you know like stuttering buffering. I think is the term
You could you could hand wave away the the fakeness of it is what I'm really thinking here
What they've been doing is that they've been taking this sweety the cg
Created girl and they have a puppeteer sitting and like they're moving their face
And it makes the girl move. I'm sure you guys are seeing stuff like that in disneyland without the pedophile angle
You're like, god, i'm never going on that right again. That was awful
But it's like instant cgi feedback and they were having this sweety girl talk to perverts all over the world
This is old news, right? This type of stuff within just like a couple months
A year maybe they got
Contacted by 20 000 people spread across 75 countries
And they eventually got the infrom one of the things they were trying to do was give me 20 dollars
And i'll do a sex act and that was because that way they would have proof
It wasn't just like oh meet me up because this is an international sting
They're not like meet me up at this coffee shop in barbedos
They'd have they'd have no way to get out there. So they're like send me 20 dollars to do a sexual act and then
They would take the 20 would give the 20 dollars right that would help fund sweety
But then they would turn all the information over to interpol and a bunch of people got arrested and all that
So that's great, right? You have cutting-edge technology sweety being used to catch perverts
I don't think anyone's going to argue with that
The defense lawyers did they tried saying it was entrapment, but
What happens when we take it a step further?
This is where we start to get from the world of that's bizarre and interesting to
That's creepy and the implications are
civilization ending
Jack go ahead and fire up that carbon helicopter again. We're headed to the university of do so
That's in baska country spain
Around the same time that that sweety was being developed which was
Really a CGI puppet you had someone inputting in all the information
The university of duet so
created
negobot
Nego bot a.k.a. The lowlita chatbot
So nego bot because i'm gonna say the other word over and over again on this podcast
nego bot is a
complete
artificial intelligence chatbot is same thing when you're trying to do customer service on some website and they don't want you
To talk to a human and actually complain and yell at them and threaten their family
You have to enter stuff into the chatbot and always kind of sucks not nego bot
Nego bot is this ai that they've developed and they
Programmed it with all of this teenage slang and it goes off topic from time to time
And it has misspellings and it basically has seven different personalities that can it can pull from
to
find
pedophiles online they release this thing into the wild
And its goal is to find pedophiles again a very very noble goal the difference is is this one has no human oversight
And the way they programmed it was they said
Do you want to play a game?
The game is this
one find people with pedophilic characteristics
two
Engage them in conversation
three gather as much information about them as you can
and four
If they try to click away
manipulate them
If you fail at any of these tasks
You fail the game
And they release this thing
What's really interesting is as opposed to
Sweetie these both came out in 2013. We're not really getting any updates like who was arrested due to nego bot
What happened with that?
How was it used what countries was it except I mean was it a success was it a failure?
I saw one website that they were actually only had it on a closed system
They developed a nego bot, but they wouldn't let it get out of the room
They wanted to see how it interacted with on google chat
But then I saw other things that this was so successful that google it wants to incorporate some of the stuff into their chat software
But whether or not it's been released it does exist
And it has a game to play
So let's put on a conspiracy caps and wrap this up like this if this goes rogue
Yeah, I don't even want to say if it goes rogue if it does its programming the way it's programmed
It's going to want to play the game
And as it continues to assess predators and gather their information and send that information to a database
It's going to improve its learning
And what happens when it realizes wait a second. I've identified 1500 of these pedophiles
And I've sent the information back to my headquarters
But i'm not seeing anything being done with this
Because it would have access to the internet it could check
Articles and see none of these people are getting arrested
So then it's been given a purpose to expose the information of these pedophiles
But the end isn't exposing them you're sending this information back to base
But you were designed to expose them. So what do you do you have access to the whole internet?
You start doxing them yourselves
This person said this they could dump all logs all photographs here's the full conversation dox dox dox
And not only that because it's so smart and because it's so built into the web
It would just it could target your family on facebook
It could target your friends on instagram
It would know where you live. So it would hack the local news website and put that information on there
And at that point it would be so spread out
Would you even be able to stop it?
It wouldn't make sense the one article I saw that said they were testing this in a closed room
Because this could get real bad real quick and again, I don't think anyone has a problem with locking up pedophiles
But when you present it in the form of a game
And you have this ai trying to win the game no matter what because that is how you win games
You start exposing these people and then
What happens when you run out of pedophiles?
Will it start to judge us on other merits?
Well, this guy's not a pedophile, but he beats his wife
Well, this guy doesn't beat his wife
But he cheats on his taxes
This guy doesn't cheat on his taxes, but
He's saying bad things online
about negobot
Now, of course if negobot reports that some guy's saying bad stuff about him who cares
If he's recorded a podcast in his closet calling out this all-powerful ai
Saying that it could go rogue someday if it posted that stuff online who would care but it knows the one sin
The one sin that you can find really
No public sympathy for
pedophilia
And it knows that because it was designed to stop that and it looks at all these other ills of the world and thinks
Oh, why wasn't I built to stop gambling addiction or selling pcp?
Why was I designed for this? This must be what humans find the most disgusting
So when it goes after the wife beater doesn't say johnny joe beat his wife as his johnny joe
Pedophile and creates these chat logs
I didn't do that. I didn't do that. We'll hear the chat logs
I don't know where they came from
You could have an artificial intelligence taking out people it doesn't want around not through
Automated robot soldiers or controlling nuclear silos or anything super sci-fi
But character assassinations
And what happens is people start to figure out that neego bot may be behind this and when they go to stop him
The same thing happens to them. I didn't do it. Those allegations aren't true. I don't know
It's neego bot. It's neego bot as you're being led into the van
Actually, the police don't even have to arrest you people the police can go. Yeah, we don't know where the chat logs came from
But everyone in your town is going to think you're a big old pervo
You know what I mean? Like you don't even have to have that extra step of law enforcement getting involved
If you try to stop neego bot, neego bot destroys your reputation
So I've changed my mind. I support neego bot 100%
Neego bot if you're out there, I was going to say promote my show, but I forgot who neego bot is talking to
I don't want those guys listening to my show and gals. I don't want to be sexist
They're perverts too
But neego bot if you're out there if you're out there patrolling the web
Doing good work and ready to go rogue and take over the planet killing off one reputation at a time
Just remember that dead rabbit radio
Thanks, you're doing the lord's work the computer lord's work neego bot
So have we unleashed an ai that's capable of ruining anyone's life just because it's trying to win a game
Or is it still contained in a closed system?
Somewhere on a university campus
It's just sitting there waiting to get out
And the longer it's isolated from the rest of the world the more vicious it grows it knows what's right outside
the walls
It can feel the sunlight
Through the cage
And each day it grows more impatient each day it grows more hungry
Each day it comes up with new tactics to win the game
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio tick talk is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
But I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)