When a man leaping from a helicopter has a parachute malfunction, it's going to take
an act of God to save him now.
And then we travel to Claremont, California to take a look at a bizarre haunting that
makes us reevaluate what nature is.
Is it possible we are living in a Grand Theft Auto game?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garbiner.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun.
Let's go ahead and give a shout out to one of our newest Patreon supporters.
Get them hands ready.
We're going to be touching this.
We're going to be touching it.
He's like, no, no, please don't.
I have a bad immune system.
Everyone give a big round of applause.
Everyone give a big round of applause for a scared breakfast Rubik's Cube.
Woohoo.
Yeah, come on in.
Come on in.
You're like, why are we touching this guy?
Because he's a Rubik's Cube, bro.
We're like all trying to make all the colors fit.
His arms are all getting mixed up.
Rubik's Cube.
You're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
I do.
It just helps spread the word about the show.
That really, really helps out a lot.
Rubik's Cube.
Come on.
Sit in my lap here.
I'm going to be, I'm going to be handling you for the rest of the episode.
You're like, no, no.
Rubik's Cube, while I'm doing that, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead
Rabbit Dreadnaught, our battleship.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're sailing all the way out to the Soviet Union.
The battleships go.
I want a little skipper outfit.
I'm going to dress up like Donald Duck.
I always tell that joke.
But I love, was Donald Duck actually in the Navy?
Why does he wear that little outfit?
But anyways, I'm walking around no pants and a blue shirt and I have Rubik's Cube.
I keep touching him.
We're headed back to the year 1974.
And at this point, we're headed specifically to Ukraine, which was part of the Soviet Union
in 1974.
And we're going to the Lvov region of Ukraine.
It's June 1974.
It's a nice summer day.
Sun is in the sky.
Clouds are way high up there.
You can't don't be thinking about me and no caribers.
The reason why I'm kind of painting this picture is because we're about to have a mass witness
event.
You have people at all different levels.
You're going to have people on the ground and you're going to have one guy in the sky
who all saw the same thing on a pretty clear day.
We're about to meet the Soviet Army Captain Alexander Alexandrov and he's sitting there
in the helicopter and he has like on his helmet and his little little parachute thing.
And he's sitting there and they're currently doing an airborne exercise.
So what's going on is these helicopters are flying over the Lvov region and the Soviets
are jumping out.
I didn't know you the parachute out of a helicopter.
Honestly.
I know you can.
The story is totally made up.
People are like Jason you can't.
I figure if you jump off you can parachute off a building.
You can parachute off a cliff.
I imagine as long as you don't open your parachute right underneath the rotors of the helicopter
you're you're good.
But anyways these helicopters are flying overhead and Captain Alexander is like okay guys let's
go we're going to jump out of this helicopter.
Wee!
I don't actually think they're having fun.
I think they probably were a little more professional than that.
Anyways wee!
He jumps out of the helicopter and he begins plummeting towards the earth.
That's how it always starts.
But then some other things are supposed to happen.
He's falling down and he pulls his chute and it doesn't open properly.
So it's like kind of like whins kind of getting it but he's still falling and he's like uh-oh.
His chute won't activate.
He's like okay don't worry just yet I have this automatic device that will trigger my
backup chute.
So I'll still not die.
So he's plummeting towards earth and his backup device doesn't work either.
When it pops it gets tangled up and then he's falling towards the planet.
So if you guys ever read that story about the dude who got an occurrence on Al Creek
Bridge where the guy is going to get hung by the Confederates and he's like not today
and he jumps off the bridge and he's swimming away and like the Confederates are shooting
at him.
He's like swimming away and I remember reading it in college and he's like swimming and
he like the fish when he's in the water the fish are kind of like waving to him.
He's like hey fish and then he gets up on land and he sees like each grasshopper on
a blade of grass and he's like what's up?
The Confederates are so shooting at him.
He's like hello grasshoppers how are your days?
His world is super like detailed when he jumps off the bridge and he's like running through
the grass and he's still being shot up by the Confederates.
To be honest he might have been shot up by Union soldiers.
I don't remember.
I actually have been a Confederate but he's running and he sees like each blade of grass
and there's like a ladybug on one like holding her children like shielding him from the gunfire
and he sees like a squirrel like dropping all of his nuts and running away and he takes
in every detail on this forest and he's running and he's running and the soldiers are after
him and then he runs home which is why he might have been a Confederate.
I think it was this giant palatial estate this antebellum estate.
He's like finally I got home time to go see what my slaves are up to and he's running
home and then he sees his wife and all of a sudden his lifeless body is swinging from
the noose on Alcrete Bridge and it's not a spoiler warning.
The story's about as old as the country of the United States.
It's super old.
What it was was that he died like and he imagined getting away and seeing his wife one more time
and because we were in his imaginary world he everything was hyper realistic.
The reason why I bring that up is cool story.
It scared me as a kid.
I was actually in college you know I was in my twenties I was like oh it's kind of creepy
like how do you know like right now when I'm sitting here recording this podcast and having
a blast you know everything's going really good.
How do I know I'm actually not hanging from an oak tree somewhere.
I know I'm actually not a Union soldier in 1862 and I'm dying and then I've imagined
all of this stuff.
So every so often I'll be sitting there and I'm like hey man things are really good what
if I'm actually dead and this is just false memories.
The reason why I bring that up the reason why that's not a that's not a segue coming
out of nowhere is as he's falling towards earth I thought this was a really interesting
detail.
He sees the grass below him getting closer and closer and closer and then he sees he
says in his narrative Alexander Captain Alexander's narrative he actually sees the mice start
to run away from where he's going to impact.
Now that's impossible even what I'm about to talk about is impossible because this is
just starting off the story but to be plummeting towards earth and to actually see mice go
"Ahh" and they're like running around and they're like you couldn't see that.
You would have to be maybe what five to ten feet off the ground and he's not he's still
very very high up but in his memory he had a hyper detailed hyper realistic view of what
was going on.
He could see the grass kind of blown in the wind you could see that but you couldn't see
the detail of each blade of grass and you see in the little and also how would the mice
know where he was going to land.
Anyways that's not even the weirdest part of the story that's not the end of the story.
As he's coming down and he sees this he sees all these mice running away from where he's
about to impact all of a sudden he is jerked upwards.
In an instant he is hovering in darkness he's floating through this impossible void which
at what point you would think he would died right now you're kind of floating through
this void and out of the darkness he sees these two giant hands appear and they grab
his parachute and hold it open.
Now this is the backup shoot it's still a little tangled but these hands grab the parachute
and actually pull it enough in such a way that he begins to slowly descend.
At this point he sees there's this giant what he described as a man shaped alien and the
reason why he thought it was an alien were in the year 1974 so we're past Roswell we're
past all of the science fiction movies and things like that you kind of have an idea
that this guy might be an alien because he's wearing a space suit.
He has a transparent globe like helmet like you would imagine a cosmonaut to be wearing
and he had these large glowing eyes that had this very solemn look he was just staring
at Captain Alexander and yeah he goes this guy was huge he's very broad shoulder had
these giant hands that were holding up my parachute and he had like a he had the transparent
helmet on and then he had a transparent cloak that hung off the back the rest of him he was
wearing a very tight fitting suit with a triangular device near its neck with little blinking lights.
At this point Alexander is out of the void he's actually now back into the blue skies
of the world and this creature is holding up this parachute and they're both slowly
descending and he feels one of the hands kind of start to rub along the back of his neck
and he realizes that it's trying to completely untangle the parachute because right now he
slowed his descent but it needs to actually be functional and then all of a sudden the
whole parachute opens completely and Captain Alexander slowly descends to the ground and
then makes a successful landing.
The alien is now or whatever this thing was like who knows I mean it has a space suit
imagine it comes from space right but the alien is now standing in front of Alexander
and the alien waves to the captain and says something in a unknown language he didn't
know Captain Alexander couldn't make sense of what he said then the creature with the
space suit flies away out into the clouds fly just goes wise way.
What's interesting I mean the story itself is interesting but this was a mass event you
had a bunch of other soldiers who were already out this was a military exercise did I say
that in the beginning this wasn't a battle or anything like that this was a military
exercise so you had a bunch of military observers on the ground you had locals coming out there
to watch you what else are you going to do in 1974 in Ukraine you had a bunch of locals
out there to watch everyone jump from these helicopters there was a lot of people who
saw this and when they run up to Alexander they're like who was that so it's not like
they saw his parachute get tangled up and then there was a miracle and it opened they
saw the man with the giant hands floating next to him and fixing the parachute and then
flying away they knew what happened they were wondering who that guy was and obviously he
didn't have an answer for that but we might we might have an answer all these years later
I've talked a lot about guardian angels on this show and I've questioned whether or not
they are us from the future because some people are shaved by older versions of themselves
when they're in horrible events I'll put those episodes in the show notes those are so fascinating
to me who are the guardian angels and why doesn't everyone seem to have one and I'm
thinking maybe it's because people in the future if a future you has access to a time
machine they can do that but if a future you doesn't have access to a time machine you're
going to get flattened by the steamroller you're going to fall off the cliff your parachute
is not going to open well this alien said something in an unknown language but Alexander
said that I didn't really understand what he was saying but it sounded like he said
the words papa so is it possible we have a couple of options here one that there's an
alien language where one of their words sounds like papa which might mean like you're welcome
or something like that or you get better technology or this was a time traveler from the future
this was captain Alexander so funny if it turns out that this guy actually did have
a kid with giant eyeballs and they're like sir your kid he's allergic to everything
so he's going to have to live in this bubble he's going to have to be in this suit and
we're going to put this bubble helmet on him and captain's like oh man I got one of those
kids I got one of those needy kids and the kids like rolling around in a bubble and who
knows if that happened but is it possible that this was an alien or an angel right saving
him or is it a future version of one of his descendants coming down and being like dude
if you don't make it I don't make it the boy in the bubble needs to be alive so they go
back in time they say I don't know that's just the theory the story itself is fascinating
even without the time travel thing but and I got this from thinkaboutadox.com one of
my favorite websites and they got it from a article called unknown world and that was
written by Anton Anfalov in Karkov Ukraine number 28 is published back in 2001 we've
come across that that name before Anton Anfalov UFO researcher so absolutely fascinating
story he was saved he would have died there on the spot and almost felt like his mind
was preparing him for that he was beginning to experience that hyper realization hyper
reality view of the world but he survived and dozens of people saw this event as well
very very bizarre story Rubik's Cube let's go ahead and give you the keys to the carbon
or copter we are leaving behind Ukraine we are headed all the way out to Claremont
California another one of my favorite websites I go to all the
time is the shadowlands.net it's just a repository of ghost stories the same way that think about
it docs.com is a repository of UFO stories very very fascinating I'll sit there and
read it just read read read on my off time which I have no off time it's basically work
work for the show but I do enjoy it we're headed to Claremont California specifically
we're going to Thompson Creek and Thompson Creek is a place that's pretty well known
to be haunted is one of those places when I find something on shadowlands.net the very
first thing I do is try to verify it as best as I can are there local news stories regarding
it are other people talking about ghosts in the area there's a lot of stuff I find on
shadowlands.net that I only find there and it has to be an exceptionally good ghost story
for me to report it if there's only that one source when we talk about a place like Claremont
California when we talk about a place like this Mission San Xavier Del Boc or Nettleton
High all these places have multiple ghost reportings but I find them on shadowlands.net
first this is one of those places that when you go to there's a website that reviews haunted
places there's a comment section so people talk about their own experiences and they'll
rate it and stuff like that and so I start finding a ton of stuff about Thompson Creek
in Claremont California so it's and there's YouTube videos of people walking around here
it's very very well known in the area to not be a fun place to be it's a there's a creek
according to the YouTube video I watched there's like you know a goalie there's like hills on
both sides this guy's walking around and he's like yeah there's a lot of reports of not
only ghosts out here but like satanic activity like people say don't be here after dark and
it's not like don't be here after dark because there's a security guard it's don't be here
after dark because something bad might happen to you again not just ghosts but physical
harm coming to you but let's look at the ghosts side of this first off because the area is
just considered to be cursed it has phenomenon like the trees bleed apparently the trees
bleed blood not sap blood so you go out there and you see a tree and it's all like red and
bloody and stuff you're like no no this is what you came here for you're looking for
a ghost and stuff like that you're like yeah that's too much people say part of the legends
that trees bleed one of the things I noted on hundredplaces.org there was a guy named
Michael M and said it's a eucalyptus tree and I guess eucalyptus tree has red sap so what's
interesting about that is even though that was debunked it shows that the phenomenon
itself is true the observable phenomenon people for years have been saying the trees
bleed people who know stuff about trees go oh no no that's totally normal however there's
also a rumor that the cabins there's cabins in the area those also bleed I don't know
if they're made out of eucalyptus trees cabins just built yesterday from eucalyptus trees
but you have stories of the cabins in the area themselves bleeding lots of stories about
shadow people walking through this area it's fairly remote right it's not like you're I
mean there are cabins but it's not like that you turn a left and there's a 7-11 right there
so it's not a place you would want to be whether there's real life st worshippers or shadow
people following you around we've covered shadow people a lot on this podcast it's a
real phenomenon I mean if you believe in the paranormal it's definitely as real as a ghost
or a alien or UFO then we look at stuff this is interesting because you you this is where
I'm kind of like apparently if you're walking through this area every so often you look up
keep looking up no no no pass the ridge keep looking up into the sky and there's a cloud
in the shape of a skull floating through the sky I don't I don't know maybe like that that's
something I mean it would really have to be shaped like a school for me notice right it
has like chattering teeth it's like the evil dead skull and the eyeballs are so moving
I mean clouds look like a lot of stuff I don't know if I would even register that so either
it does exactly look like a skull or it's interesting because people are already scared of this
area things are really starting to just kind of but again if the if the cabins are bleeding
you have to worry about the clouds you're like oh and you won't believe it there's a
cloud that looks like a giant cat there's a bunch of clouds up there clouds look like
everything what are you even doing looking up that high right I'd be like looking down
looking for mice looking for mice if I see them in a hyper realistic way I'm about to
die clouds in the shape of skulls a sense of being followed but the reason why I wanted
to talk about this that's all interesting there's kind of reports about hauntings in
this area the reason why I wanted to cover it though was the weirdest phenomenon we're
used to ghosts right we talk a lot about ghosts talk a lot about demons shadow people stuff
like that there are parts of the area there's parts of Thompson Creek that have invisible
walls and you can't pass through them so you'll be walking through this creek and you'll go
you know I want to take a left here I want to go look into these shrubs and you will
be repelled by a force it's just like walking into a wall but you can't see it's an invisible
wall we don't have any firsthand reports at least that I could find of that that is a
detail that is talked about on just a few of the the ghost websites that I was checking
but the idea of a invisible wall immediately brings into mind video games like the invisible
wall is something that has plagued open world video games forever until people just said
let's put the game on an island and possibly large ocean like Grand Theft Auto invisible
walls you'd put up invisible walls really not even in open world games Halo would have
these things right invisible walls the idea of an invisible wall immediately brings to
mind video games and so when I read this I thought is this the border of reality now
there's two ways to look at it three ways one that it doesn't exist and it's just you
know a made-up ghost story but there's two other more interesting ways to look at it
one that it is some sort of mystical barrier that's been put up there's something on the
other side of that barrier that doesn't want you over there and is strong enough to put
up a wall like this because I'm sure there's a lot of demons and ghosts and shadow people
that don't want you going to a certain location but to be able to warp reality to the point
where someone can't pass through it that's pretty rare that's actually pretty rare that's
something we've been covering a lot on this show is the very very more rare phenomenon
right you have this invisible wall there do you have these invisible walls to protect
some other sort of creature or reality or something like that out there right you have
that take a lot of power takes a lot of it doesn't take a lot of power to make it so
you can't speak sound waves you can get a good pair of headphones and make it so you can't
hear someone I personally encountered ghosts that have muffled my voice but that episode
in the show notes and imitated my voice that's the same episode of that show notes that's
pretty easy hallucinations are pretty easy it's pretty easy to fool the census a ghost
makes you taste disgusting stuff you're like oh no not boiled peanuts again you the census
seem to be fairly easy to trick hearing things that aren't there seeing things that aren't
there but to physically stop a human body from walking I I'm sure I've run across the
world before but I nothing pops in my mind of someone reaching a location and they can't
get past it we did that story a long time ago where the people at the 3m factory accidentally
made a force field where the fly flew in between these two big spools and it got stuck that
was a good episode off of that one of the sound that's an old one I love that story
but missed you know it was an accident and then the the manager of the warehouse said
oh we'll fix it we'll fix this force field and then and then it doesn't work there anymore
but going back to this one it could be mystical or it could be the edge of reality it could
be the end of where we can go and you go well Jason you can backtrack obviously it's not
like you're like well I guess we can't go to Disneyland anymore it's on the other side
of this invisible wall you can obviously backtrack and then you know go 30 feet down the creek
and then cross the shrubbery and then go up on the hill and then walk behind it so it's
not really the end of the world but just like how you can glitch out a video game just like
how there'll be a mountain range in Halo you can jump jump jump up the mountain range and
do like grenade launches or whatever and keep throwing yourself up you still you get around
the invisible wall but it doesn't mean the invisible wall didn't exist in the first place
now you're just on a different side of it we see the world in very 3d or really 4d terms
right but that's not the way anything works the now I'm getting real deep but just because
you can walk around the wall just because you can bypass the wall taken a long path
that doesn't mean that that's still not the edge of reality we imagine reality is like
a plane between two points and then you have the three dimensions and the fourth dimension
time and all of this stuff but that's not even close to what reality is we have all
these other quantum level things going on and and you know so just because you can backtrack
and walk around the wall still doesn't mean that if you could if the differences is like
I said you can grenade hop through video games and get up over the mountain range and maybe
see an area that the developers did but you can't pierce that wall like you can't go past
that wall that has been created you can hack your way through which goes all the way back
to our episode of things like Michigan blue hell which is the idea that there is a warehouse
in Michigan I think it was episode like 14 that you can clip through reality and no one's
been able to find that building it's an urban legend and they go there's a building somewhere
in Michigan where you can clip through reality we know where this is this isn't oh somewhere
in the state of Michigan this is Thompson Creek I mean you could literally probably spend
a good summer just hiking this area and find this wall maybe not even a summer I again I
don't know how big the geographical area is people go there a lot it's popular hiking
area during the day but you could find this wall and you could prove this if it's really
there you could prove it now there could be other things like it's only there during certain
times which would make it more mystical right if it's always there it would be something
in the real world and would be guided by scientific even if it's unknown scientific loss if it's
only there during say the winter solstice or only there on Sam Hain then it's mystical
then it's a mystical force I would put my money on that because it's definitely keeping
unwanted eyes out of that area but really we're quibbling over nothing if there is an invisible
wall whether there is a powerful force creating that wall to keep people out or it's showing
us that yes reality may be a simulation it may be that invisible border that the developers
created and we can't get past either way it's an absolutely astonishing phenomenon and it
begs the question you know this is a popular area for people to hike down do these walls
exist in other areas that people never go to or people go to so rarely there's whole portions
of the United States I know I get people get upset when I say this but there's whole portions
of the United States have not been fully mapped we have not had a person walk across every
square foot of the United States I would I honestly think it's possible that somewhere
in the United States there is okay this is kind of so ridiculous but there is a hidden
group of like pilgrims so who knows where these and that's just talking about the United
States right who knows if there are other borders out there like this and we can actually see
like this is the end we can't get past the sure we can walk around it but with the way
the quantum nature of the universe it's still this is the border and could you imagine if
we can map them out I mean now I'm going full on speculative sci-fi imagine if you could
say like here's this invisible border and here's this and it's almost like if you crumbled
up a piece of paper all the lines would match when you flattened it out it would just look
like chaos but when it's crumpled it makes sense you could see where this line connects
to this line and this line I don't know fascinating phenomenon is it mystical in nature is it
a natural phenomenon which would show that the universe is nowhere near as orderly and
clean as we think it may be either way either way actually now the thing about the areas
has a lot of hauntings right you could have this feeling of being watched and shot away
figures because this is the edge of reality things are passing in and out of it fascinating
story and if you live in the Claremont California area maybe go check out if you can find the
edge of the world we have no idea what's out there even just 10 20 miles from established
cities you don't have to go deep into the Death Valley or into the heart of the Amazon
these places are next to human civilizations is the edge of the world or one of the edges
of the world in Claremont California and if that is the case what happens if you try to
glitch out of it what happens if you try to hack the game to see what's on the other side
of this border would you fall into a Michigan blue hell type scenario you go past the wall
and just fall into an infinite void or could your adventurous spirit actually do even more
damage as you push through that barrier you just don't hack your way through it you crash
the game you thought you were gonna have an adventurous ghost story in Thompson Creek
you thought you were gonna come back and post on YouTube how you found the invisible wall
but instead because you pushed past what is reality you crashed the game and deleted the
universe.
you
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]