Yet another reason to hate flies.
A mysterious man appears in Germany and nobody knows what to do.
And then we take a look at a recent bizarre crime way, where people are blaming their
misdeeds on the zombies today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I hope you're having a great day too.
Coming up to the weekend, I hope you guys have an awesome, fun and safe weekend.
We're gonna go ahead and get started here, we got a lot of stuff to cover, so let's
board the Carpentercopter, get on, go go go.
You're like dude, I just started the podcast, why are you rushing me?
I'm pushing you at this point, get up, urgh!
Push you into the Carpentercopter, kinda roll around.
On the Carpentercopter already is our newest Patreon supporter, Alora Alora.
So thank you so much for supporting the show Alora, it really means a lot.
If you can't support the Patreon, just go ahead and get the word out about the show,
that helps a lot as well.
So we're taking off.
Sounds like a rocket ship, but it's not, we're the Carpentercopter, I just got my sound effects
mixed up for a second and the word mixed and missed, we're flying around, right?
And you're like Jason, would you please stop drinking turmeric before recording the podcast?
Never!
I will not.
And for new listeners of the show, I've discovered that turmeric, it's a combination of a normal
thing that turmeric does to people or makes them feel good and then my mild allergic reaction
to it makes them feel like I'm drinking whiskey.
I feel like Alf, remember when Alf used to eat cat food?
You're like no Jason, I'm not 45 years old, I don't remember Alf.
Alf used to eat cat food and it would make him intoxicated.
Wait, no!
Or was that the prawns from?
You're like Jason, you really can't drink turmeric during the show?
You already can't remember half this stuff.
What was the movie with the prawns?
District 9.
I've realized probably half this podcast is people yelling at it going, the answer is
$2.1 million, like when I can't come up with an answer, I'm sure you guys are super frustrated.
Let's get started with the episode.
Now this next story is gross, just to let you know.
So if you're eating noodles or top ramen or broth with a single noodle in it or anything
noodley if you're singing the song Yankee Doodle Dandy, wait does that have a noodle
in it?
It's a Yankee Doodle once in town writing on a pony.
It's like a feather in his head called it macaroni.
I guess macaroni is a noodle.
Anyways, did you know macaroni was a term for like a fashionable person and basically
it was the, there was a British song making fun of Americans like oh look I'm going to
put this feather in my cap and say how fashionable I am.
And the Americans loved the song so much they took it.
That's hilarious dude.
Don't insult an American, let's just take it and turn it into a top 40 song.
So where was, oh yes, eyes.
So wait, you didn't know I was going to talk about eyes.
Okay, anyways, anyways I'm going to talk about eyeballs.
So eyeballs and noodles.
So if you don't like either of those or if you love both of those so much you don't want
them ruined for you.
You're like no don't ruin my eyes.
Skip ahead.
So anyways, the year is 2018, it's March and there's this woman.
Now these people are unnamed because these are all medical journal stuff so again you
know this is going to be gross.
But since we have a new Patreon subscriber, Elora, we're going to have Elora as this
68 year old woman.
She's running through Carmel Valley, California.
The most delicious part of California.
It's kind of sticky though.
So she's running through Carmel Valley, California, sorry.
And she's just running.
I mean, now to be fair, I don't run at 43.
The fact that she's 68 and running kudos, kudos.
I couldn't run from a pack of jaguars at this point.
I mean I could probably bench her but I definitely couldn't outrun her.
Anyways 68 year old woman is running and she turns a corner and she gets hit in the face
with a bunch of flies.
Now it's not like someone had flies was hiding there and threw them at her.
It was just a giant swarm of flies flying in one direction.
She's running in another one.
She turns the corner.
They hit her in the face so violently she says that she's spitting them out of her mouth.
So it's not like three or four flies.
It's like, remember in like Bugs Bunny cartoons where like the bugs would make a hammer and
like mallet down daffy duck or whatever?
Like that.
There's that many flies.
It was so dense.
They were hitting her eyeballs and going into her mouth.
She's like, spit them out.
And then we're moving ahead a month.
So now we're in April 2018 and this woman she's like, oh, Laura.
Laura's going, oh my eyeball.
My eye, my right eyeball hurts.
So bad.
It's super irritating.
Okay.
So now you guys know where this is going.
She starts fleshing her eye out.
She starts putting water in it and she pulls out as she's fleshing it out.
She pulls out a half inch long worm.
That's so disgusting.
And then she's, she's, I, at that point I would immediately just go to the hospital.
I'd go to the ER.
I wouldn't run because we've established I can't do that.
I would just walk to the hospital picking up heavy stuff as I'm going, get in there
and be like, I found a worm in my eye.
She though looks in the mirror and realizes there's a second worm in her eyes.
So she peels that one off, tosses it down.
I don't think she's thrown away.
They should probably saving them for the doctor.
Next day she goes to the doctor.
Third worm in her eye.
Just swirling around in there.
These things are called the laesia gulosa.
The laesia gulosa.
And what happens is they're normally found in cow eyeballs or maybe cows in general,
but definitely cow eyeballs.
Because these, there are these type of flies.
They're called face flies.
They didn't know these existed.
People, we don't need Cthulhu to come here.
Cthulhu already exists.
If we have a thing called face flies and they quote, consume eye secretions, i.e. eat your
tears.
That is, that is a demonic level insect.
These face flies try to land on your eyeballs.
They drink your tears and then they lay eggs and they get into your eyeball.
Now very, very common among cows.
And here's the thing.
At this point, people are going, this might actually be a bad sign that we have a disease
or we have this thing that's jumping species from cows to humans.
And you go, well, bad luck, right?
Well, this is the second time it's happened in two years.
So the first time it happened in 2016, there was a woman in Oregon who got it.
So that sucks because I live up here.
And now this woman, the first woman, she found three worms.
Eventually a doctor found a fourth worm.
The woman in Oregon, she had 15 worms in her eyeballs.
Same thing, just flies kind of landed on her eyes.
I think she, what was she doing?
She was horseback riding.
She got a bunch of flies on her.
So when this happened back in 2016 and it happened to this one woman, she had 15 worms
in her eyes, there was this quote.
This is almost certainly just an unfortunate random event because it's going to happen
once in a million years or maybe once in a million minutes.
I don't know.
I don't know how random or rare it is.
But when it happened in 2016, the medical community goes, oh, that sucks.
I mean, it was bound to happen at some point.
The fact that it's happened again just two years later makes people think, or the medical
community think this isn't a random, rare.
It was a statistical anomaly to happen the first time.
The fact that it's happened twice in two years means that this may be an emerging
Zootronic disease or Zootonic disease.
What's the actual word here?
Yeah, Zoo, sorry, neither of those.
Zoonotic, zoonotic disease.
So watch your eyeballs, guys.
I hate flies.
Flies are the worst, man.
They're landing on stuff.
What are they good for?
Anyways, I've become a fly.
I'm a racist against flies.
I hate them.
I remember once I took a BB gun.
Nah, never mind.
I'm going to tell that story.
Anyways, let's go ahead and move on to our next topic here.
You're like, Jason, just tell the story.
Never.
So we're going to go ahead and move on to, let's hop back in the Carbenter Cafeteria.
I was wearing goggles the whole time, too.
After telling you that story, your eyes are all swelling up.
You're like, why didn't you tell me to bring goggles?
I'm like, yeah.
I'm that kind of podcast host.
I like to see my listeners suffer.
Let's hop back in the Carbenter Cafeteria.
There's a little eye wash station in the back.
You're washing your eyes.
I'm all, hehehe, I put hot pepper in the eye wash station.
You're all, ahhh.
But your eyes burn now, but it did kill off all the worms.
So see, I did it.
I did it out of love.
I cost you that pain because I wanted to get the worms out of your eyes.
We're now flying to Germany.
We're going back in time to the year 1851.
Now we're going to a place called Frankfurt-Anderotor.
Frankfurt-Anderotor.
So we're just going to call it Frankfurt for short.
And we landed there.
Whole towns made hot dogs.
You guys saw that joke coming a mile away.
Don't even complain or groan about that one.
Helicopter lands on a giant bun.
Okay, you didn't see that joke coming.
The helicopter lands on a giant bun.
We get out.
Pit forks and spoons.
Forks and knives.
Wait, who eats hot dogs with forks and knives?
Never mind.
We're walking around Hot Dog Town and it's 1851.
And there is a dude standing in the middle of town and everyone's like, "Whoa, huh?
What's up with this guy, huh?"
Apparently they're all extras from Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure in this town.
"Whoa, dude.
Who is he?"
We're walking through the crowd and there's this guy just standing there in the middle
of the crowd.
"Hmm, so we walk up to him and we're like pushing these villagers out of the way or
get out of the way.
Americans on the move.
Go, go, go.
Although half my audience isn't from America, you're technically U.S. citizens when you
listen to this show, whether you like it or not.
So we're pushing all these Germans out of the way.
Get out of the way.
Get out of the way."
"Hey, what's your name?"
And he turns to us and he goes, "I'm Jofer Voron."
And we're like, "That's weird.
Do you not know how to pronounce your own name?"
And he goes, "Well, I'm assuming the person telling this story doesn't know how to pronounce
my own name.
I'm going to say it slowly this time.
Jofer Voron.
My name is Jofer Voron."
We're like, "Okay, that's better.
Thank you for pronouncing your name correctly."
So what happened was one day everyone in this village town is hanging out and this dude,
Jofer, shows up.
Mr. pronounced it again already.
"Jo," call him Jo.
Jo shows up into town.
And everyone's like, "Whoa, that's weird.
What is this guy doing here?"
And he speaks a little bit of German, just a little bit.
Probably more than I do.
I can say Guten Tag.
And yeah, definitely he can speak more German than I can.
He comes into town and he's like, "Hey guys, I need to sit down.
I've been on a long journey."
He kind of sits down and they're like, "What's going on?"
And he's like, "Well, listen, I'm trying to find my brother.
You guys happen to know where my brother is."
And they're like, "Who's your brother?"
And he's like, "Oh yeah, I guess I should have told you that part first."
Starts describing his brother and everyone's like, "Nah, I don't know who you're talking
about."
He's like, "Listen, man, I'm all the way from Lacks area.
And I got to come out here and I'm trying to find my brother.
We came across the ocean.
Like, I know he's here, but I can't find him."
This is 1851.
This isn't caveman days.
I mean, people have been around the world and stuff like that.
Aqua's number one hit around the world is just bumping all over in raves in Germany here
in 1851.
People know geography and people are like, "What?
What's Lacks area?"
Never heard of that place.
He's like, "Lacks area?"
It's like one of the biggest, it's like one of the most powerful countries.
It's right across the ocean.
Germans are like, "Are you talking about America?"
He's like, "What?"
"No, Lacks area."
Lacks area.
You know, it's the country.
Is there somebody that I can talk to?
Now, so again, broken Germans.
So they're having a hard time talking to each other.
And the villagers are like, "I've never heard of any place called Lacks area, but it could
be a translation error."
They go, "This is what they're able to gather.
This is what they're able to gather."
And so when they asked him why he was here, he said that he actually was searching for
his brother.
He was on a trip to find his brother, but the boat that he was on shipwrecked and he basically
washed up on shore and started walking through Germany.
When people start talking to him, he's able to explain a couple things.
German is not his native language, obviously.
His native languages are Lacarian and Abram.
People are like, "Those aren't real languages."
And he's like, "Yes, yes, they are."
He also says that he worships a religion called Ipspation.
Ipspation.
And when he would ask to describe what Ipspation is, basically was Christianity.
So people in town are like, "What is good?"
It has to be a language issue.
There has to be a language issue here.
It must be trying to say Christian.
He's saying this other word.
It doesn't make sense.
So they eventually get the elders of the town involved.
And the elders in town sit and talk to him for a while and they come up and they go, "This
guy's legit."
Like, he's not getting these words mixed up.
He actually worships something called Ipspation.
And he speaks these weird languages and he says he's from this country, Laxaria.
He's from...it's not a translation error.
He's actually from Laxaria.
Eventually, though, this story reaches not just the elders of town, but the learned people
in Berlin.
The power structure and they go, "We need to talk to this guy."
At the very least, we're gonna laugh at him because his German sucks.
At the very most, maybe there's a mystery to unravel.
He goes to Berlin and he's never heard from again.
He's lost to history.
Now, that is a real story that was published long, long time ago.
It's not an urban legend.
It's not like the man of Toreed, which is a very famous version of the same type of
story.
It technically appears in our reality, saying he's from somewhere else.
We can trace that story back to about the 70s, which technically is when the story is supposed
to take place, but we can trace it back to one paragraph in a book about missing people.
There's no documentation before that book was published.
If you're interested, I did an episode on the man of Toreed.
I think it's like episode 30 or something like that, a long time ago.
But this is the same type of thing.
Like the man of Toreed, we actually have a news article printed in the year 1851 involving
this story.
About a man named Jo Farvoren who showed up in Germany and had a hard time speaking language,
all the details and more are in this news article.
It ends with this.
The sages of Frankfurt on the odor after much examination of the tale and its bearer have
come to the conclusion that it is true.
Some men believe things because they are incredible.
However, Jo Farvoren has been carefully dispatched to Berlin and is now the subject of much scientific
and curious gossip in the Prussian capital.
What mystification hides under the story time will probably show, which is interesting because
it didn't.
We don't have any more information on what happened to this guy after he went to Berlin.
So you go, "Whoa, there's actually a newspaper that printed a story about a guy who magically
appeared and then got lost again to history."
Here's the thing.
Yes, that is true.
It was published in a newspaper.
Well, let me rephrase that.
It was published in something called a newspaper.
This may have been made up because apparently at the time there was a tax.
There was a British stamp tax and part of that tax was if you published fiction or a
magazine you had to pay a tax.
But if you published a newspaper you didn't have to pay the tax.
So Edward Lloyd at this time started publishing stuff with fiction in it but called it a newspaper.
And then after a while the British government, he started doing that like in 1840s.
And then the British government got wise to it and they're like, "What?
Cats don't talk.
Why is a Shewell's time machine in the newspaper?"
And way before it was even published.
How is it in here?
It's a time machine, obviously.
You have to stop doing that.
And so Edward Lloyd was like, "Sorry, sorry, sorry for trying to rip off the British government."
And then started publishing actual news in the newspaper.
Is this story true?
You know, the world is so vast and huge that it wouldn't shock me if every so out of 7
billion people everyone just kind of pops in from another dimension or another era.
Because that's pretty much what this would be.
This guy, his brother was lost.
He's traveling across the ocean.
Some sort of portal opens up.
Some sort of wacky thing.
Quantum suicide, who knows?
But when he crashes onto the shore, he ends up in our reality.
Starts walking around.
Now, I don't think he went to Berlin and they chopped him up and said, "I wonder if on their
planet they have two hearts."
They probably weren't even thinking that.
They probably would just think, "Whoa, this guy is from someplace else."
They said he seemed to have a pretty good knowledge of geography, though.
So it was almost like just the names changed of places.
But one of the key components to the story of the mandatory, and I'm not saying the story
of mandatory is fake.
I'm just saying we don't have a lot of information on it.
One of the key components of the story of the mandatory is its temporary.
Is that when you flop to an alternate dimension, you're only there for a window of time before
you're pulled back out.
And then you end up in your home dimension.
So he may have gone to Berlin and simply just vanished on that trip.
He may have lived a long life.
But I kind of hope that he did go back to his home dimension and found his brother.
That way it would be a happy ending for him and his brother.
And then an interesting story for us.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next.
You were like, "Jason, that was a weird ending."
"What?
I like happy endings.
Are you missing your brother?"
Have you guys seen the trailer for that movie, 1917, about it's World War One?
It looks dope about the guy.
I like movies like this.
I like very simple movies.
This guy gets an order.
It says, "Your brother and 1,200 men are walking into a German ambush.
You have like two days to get there.
They're all going to be massacred."
And it's about a guy and his buddy walking from one end of the war to the other one.
It's shot almost all handheld and it's supposedly supposed to be one.
It's not, but it's supposed to seem like it's just one long over the shoulder camera shot.
Like you're the third man in this party.
Trailers look great.
And I really like that director.
Was it David Mendez?
Sean Mendez is a singer.
But anyways, 1917, it looks dope.
Anyways, that is enough of you with anything we're talking about.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
So we're going, we're leaving behind Germany.
We're going to an American interrogation room.
So it's all like spooky and dark.
I don't think the, I've never been in an interrogation room.
I know they're supposed to be super uncomfortable.
Police interrogation room.
This guy is in the interrogation room.
In this copy.
Okay, so police interrogation room.
Cop is sitting there across the table from this dude.
And they're like, "So why'd you do it, William?
This dude's name is William Berry.
William Berry.
Not Berry like, "Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
Not Berry like, "Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
So who knows what's going on, but anyways, he's standing there next to this woman and
stabbing her in the back.
He's like, "Oh my God, your shirt, it's ruined."
And she's like, "I know.
Also I'm bleeding."
So he calls the ambulance and arrests William Berry.
He was trying to escape to Knott's Berry Farm in a giant hot air balloon.
Snoopy's his getaway driver.
So anyways, Snoopy's in the other interrogation room.
He's like, just shaking his head.
You can't get the visual joke.
I'm shaking my head.
But the joke is a guy in a giant suit can't talk.
Or I guess the joke actually is that Snoopy doesn't talk.
He's the perfect accomplice.
He will never rat you out.
Anyways though, that joke would have been much better if you guys could have seen me
shaking my head.
The point being William Berry is caught and the cops ask him, "Why'd you stab that woman
multiple times?
Like did you know her?"
And he's like, "No, I didn't know her."
And you won't believe she was being really mean to me.
And she tried to feed me to the zombies.
And the cops are like, "What are you talking about?"
He's like, "Zombies!"
He was trying to feed me to the zombies.
And the cops are like, "Okay, you're nuts.
We'll lock him up."
That's the end of that story, right?
But that happened in this year.
That happened in October 26, 2019.
Last year, June 26, 2018.
Massive fire.
We're going to El Granada, California.
Raging fire.
900 hay bales burning in the field.
Not a big loss.
Cows go a little hungry.
Do you use hay for anything other than cow food?
Did you know that hippos are herbivores, but if there's no food around, they will eat
other hippos?
Or they...
Okay.
At least, let me back out here.
They will at least eat other animals.
I believe they will eat other hippos.
Because hippos are animals and I was reading stuff about cannibals.
Recently, cannibal animals.
Hey, that rhymes!
Has no one ever figured that out yet?
Cannibal animals?
How is that not a band?
How is that not the name of every band ever?
Cannibal animals.
Anyways, hippos will at least eat...
I would love to see a hippo try to eat another hippo.
But if a hippo doesn't...
If a hippo is a herbivore, but if it doesn't have any food, it will eat a fox.
Or it'll eat like a lion cub or something.
So it'll probably also eat a bunch of marbles in the game Hungry Hungry Hippos.
But um, oh, fire, fire, flame.
Um, hey, hey, cows eating, hey, that's where we were going with this.
That happened on June 26, 2018.
July 3, 2018.
Huge fire, again, same area.
This time 865 hay bales erupt in flame.
Now, what's weird about this, other than a bunch of cows being like, "Oh, I'm so hungry."
Is them talking, being able to tell people they're hungry.
But is that a woman was spotted at the scene of these fires and apparently she was like
driving around.
I mean, it wasn't in the middle of nowhere, it was like farmland, so of course like people
would drive around.
But this woman was driving around.
Very, very suspicious people kept seeing this woman and she was making odd statements.
Not statements like, "Oh, look at the fire, it burns, it burns away the evil."
Just weird people that was...
Just never kind of making people a little suspicious.
Firefighters were seeing her and everything like that.
So eventually she does get tracked down, she gets arrested.
Monica Louise Berlin, 39.
She's 39 years old.
She says, the cops arrest her and she's like, "Listen, officer, I know that you have a
duty to arrest me, but I need you to know that we're on the same side.
We are both fighting for the sake of good."
You get that, right?
You and me were same sides of the opposite coin.
He's like, "I think you got that phrase backwards."
She's like, "Yes, you're right.
We're different sides of the same coin.
You see, you fight with a badge and a gun.
I fight with fire and hay."
She's like, "What are you talking about?"
The zombies.
See, I know that there's a cult operating in the area, a doomsday cult.
And part of their plan was to use the hay bales.
They were going to move them.
They were going to get their zombie slaves to move the hay to block the roads.
And so when doomsday came, the zombies would descend on the town of El Granada, the shining
jewel of California.
Everyone knows where this place is.
And the zombies would come into town and we would go to escape.
The hay would be blocking the road.
We'd be trapped and it would be just one long smorgasbord.
I mean to say, we would have been killed, but I saved us by burning all those hay bales.
You're welcome, officer.
You're welcome.
Now obviously she's charged with felony arson, destruction of property, all sorts of stuff.
I have two questions about that.
And is there a cult in the area?
Most likely not.
But again, conspiracy theorists, there might be.
Two.
Those aren't real zombies.
I guess that's not really a question, but real zombies don't push hay.
And I'm not going to end this with an argument.
I'm running this episode on an argument with what real zombies are.
This is my concern with these type of stories.
We got these two crazy people saying that.
And this is just stuff that's happened recently.
There's always a weirdo story about a guy believing that zombies are attacking and he's
taking pod shots out in the dark.
Or zombie apocalypse is coming and the family's running to go prep somewhere, whatever.
This is my concern with this stuff.
It's the boy who cried wolf.
The other day I made a passing comment that, oh, you know, zombies are kind of passe at
this point.
But it is a possible threat.
The living, the dead coming back to life, not so much, but any sort of infection, any
sort of disease that changes the way the brain works.
Coupled with the fact that we got 7 billion people on the planet, coupled with the fact
that diseases are crossing from cow eyeballs to human eyeballs, it's not irrational to
think that at some point a disease may emerge that makes people act like zombies.
Not necessarily be zombies, but act like zombies.
And what happens is whenever one of these crazy people walks around and does something
stupid and goes, "Those are zombies!"
People laugh.
It's great because they tend to happen around Halloween because people are preoccupied with
that stuff or at least it gets reported around then and walking dead ratings go up and all
that stuff.
But what happens is this is how the boy cries wolf.
Some day a newspaper article will appear and it will be "Man believes that town is under
influence of zombies shoots mayor."
Now that's a bad headline.
It should be the mayor gets shot first.
That's obviously horrible that guy shot that mayor.
But these stories start happening with more and more frequency.
You have people talking about "zombies."
You have people talking about being eaten alive, this fear, something happened in the
town.
They got jumped by a couple homeless people and one guy tried to take a bite out of them
and the article is like "Zombie attack?"
Same thing we saw when that guy got his face eaten off in Florida.
How it was really sensationalized.
Which to be fair, that is a sensational story.
But I'm just afraid that if these encounters start happening in small pieces, we're not
going to realize it until the threat shows up.
A man could have literally been standing on the street corner totally minding his own
business and there's a woman waiting for the bus in front of him and she's like "Ugh."
And then she turns to bite him and then in self defense he stabs her to death and then
they just look at this guy standing over this 90 pound woman and they're like "dude why'd
you pull a knife out and stab her multiple times?"
And she's laid there and she died and he's like "she was trying to bite me.
I think she was a zombie."
She had this look in her eyes.
That guy's going to jail.
And how many times will that happen in these little incidences where people are getting
this contagion and attacking the person next to them and it doesn't spread right away or
we don't know the transmission vectors are or maybe it does spread but both people die
so quickly in the melee that it just kind of ends there.
How many times are these little stories going...
These two guys were nuts.
These two people were nuts.
But how many times will these little stories pop up over the course of a time that are
things that could have led us to realizing that "oh this is actually a big threat.
Zombies are knocking down your door.
You're like oh I should have been paying closer attention to what was going on around me in
the newspaper."
If worms can hop from a cow's eyeball into your eyeball just from a fly hitting your face
the way diseases are being transmitted are just way too...
If that's the case it's way too easy to be having this spread between animal and human
diseases.
And we're looking at stuff like rabies coupled with really any other disease.
It could be a bad period of time for humanity.
70,000 years ago volcano went off and it so drastically changed the environment of the
planet.
Humanity was basically reduced to only a thousand people.
And from that thousand people we've regrouped to become the powerhouse that we are today.
But we were extremely lucky and we weren't fighting crazy versions of ourselves.
It is possible that a disease will wipe us out but I think the worst disease would be
the one that turns us against each other.
That makes humans crazy and bloodthirsty and self-destructive killing machines.
And we won't know that's happening until it's too late.
Because whenever these little articles pop up where someone's attacked or something suspicious
happens or whatever we're going to laugh those stories off just like we laugh these ones
off until those bloody hands are clawing at our faces.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
Twitter is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)