New research on ancient sea monsters may rock the scientific community.
And then we meet a young woman who spent most of her early life in a haunted house.
But we're not talking about cold spots or weird noises late at night.
This woman's house was haunted by Darth Vader, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
*music*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are having tons of fun, arm wrestling people, and just general, just general hijinks.
I hope you guys are able to get away with all of your Dennis the Menace-esque stunts today.
But someone who never gets away, someone who unfortunately gets caught by the police every single time,
give it up for our newest Patreon supporter, Aaron Kostetanti.
Kostetanti, he's like shaking his head, nope, I don't know how you pronounce it.
Kostanini? Still getting to know. Aaron, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand it.
You don't want me to butcher your name. You don't want me to butcher your name on a podcast, that's fine.
Just help us spread the word about the show. That really, really helps out a lot.
And I got Aaron coming in and what's this? He's wearing some straight up juggalo makeup.
And that is an ad because I am currently on a new episode of the podcast, The Asylum Case Studies,
where me and host Tressa review the asylum film Death Racers, starring the insane clown posse.
So if you're looking for even more, Jason, who isn't, really who isn't, check out the Asylum
Case Studies, we'll have the episode in the show notes and we get to whoop whoop and juggalo
and juggalette and ninjas and I know all the slang I use to hang out with a bunch of juggalos.
So if you want to hear us wax poetic about a ICP movie, definitely check out The Asylum Case
Studies. The link is in the show notes. Aaron's like, I'm not a juggalo and I don't even know what
you're talking about. Aaron, let me go ahead and toss you the command codes for the dead
rabbit dreadnought, our massive battleship, hop aboard laddies, everyone walk up that game plank.
We are setting sail because we're about to uncover a truly bizarre maritime mystery.
Giant warship with little captain Aaron. I'm going hard on Aaron today. He's just like a juggalo,
now he's just like Donald Duck and no pants. But he's the captain of this vessel and Aaron,
take us out to the deepest, darkest parts of the ocean in this mighty, mighty warship. This story,
I love this story. I read about it about maybe a week or two ago, but I already had those episodes
prepped and ready to go and I was like, I can't wait to tell you guys about this one. We're going
to be sitting down with a man. You're like, oh man, you said in the beginning there's a sea monster.
We'll get to the sea monster. But first off, let's introduce into the cramped cabins of the dead
rabbit dreadnought, Mark McMinneman. So Mark is a paleontologist. He's the professor of geology
at Mount Holyoke College in Massachusetts. And he recently gave an interview for NPR. He's too good
to appear on the radio, but he did do an interview for NPR. And I found this story when mysterious
universe published it on their website. So I'm going to give them a shout out too, because I
wouldn't have known about the story if it wasn't for MU covering it. This is dope. So what Mark has
been doing is he's been looking at bones, he's been looking at bones on the sea floor. And he
has this theory, and this is really controversial in the scientific community. He goes, let's go back
in time to the Triassic era. This is his theory. Back in the Triassic era, there had to have been
massive cephalopods, massive, those are the ones with the tentacles and stuff, octopus, squid,
type of entity, type of creature roaming the deep oceans of the world. And this is why I think this
thing had to have existed. Because he says, listen, we all of the fossil records for octopuses,
octopi, you could fit in a suitcase. They first off, they're all just kind of army and stuff like
that. It's a bunch of muscles and cartilage. I said army, I'm not quoting him specifically. He goes to
when they die, the chances of any creature being fossilized is fairly low. And then if there are
fossils or deep underwater, but he goes, octopuses and squid, there's not much that can actually
fossilize on them. He goes, we can find fossilized eggs. And with octopuses, we can find fossilized
beaks. And with the squids, we can find fossilized gladiases, which is this bone in its head. He goes,
other than that, we can fit pretty much all of the fossils we have of the octopi family in a suitcase.
He goes, there's one species of octopus. The only reason we know it existed is that
we found fossils of their food. We found fossils of these shells with a hole bore through them,
like something went, and we have modern day octopuses that do that. So we, but that's the,
we have no bones of octopuses during this era when we're finding these shells or the holes
bored in them. And he goes, we all agree that it was probably an octopus doing this thing.
So first off, the fossil record for cephalopods is very, very small, but his hypothesis is there
used to be massive kraken like creatures. That's the word he'll use a lot is actual
the triassic kraken roaming the oceans. And then he has two reasons why these things had to exist.
He goes, one, we have been finding the bones of itheosaurs and it the oars were these giant
45 feet long sea monsters. I mean, these things would be like sharks. Sharks would be like sardines
to these dudes and we know they existed. And he goes, what we're finding is we're finding their
bones at the bottom of the ocean. So we can have an octopsy team and we can tell that these things
had their neck broken. And it looks like they were dragged down because the bones shouldn't be in
like this area and they definitely shouldn't be in this pattern. So he has these photographs and it
shows the bones of the echothorus are laid out in a geometric pattern. And he goes, listen,
if you took, if you took one of these creatures and you killed it and it fell on the ground,
the bones would not fall in this order. And basically it was like the pieces were almost
next to each other and made this weird geometric pattern looked almost like a little road and
what kind they're just taper off. And he goes, listen, I've we've done a lot of photographs,
we've done a lot of studies on these things. He goes, based on the way the mud is down there,
it's not currents because otherwise if the currents were strong enough to move the bones
randomly into this position, it would have moved the mud all the way. So he goes, it has nothing
to do with the currents at all. And the fact that this would fall randomly like this, maybe,
but they found the same geometric pattern in other locations with also using the bones of
these giant sea monsters. So I surmise that there must have been a creature big enough to
smash these guys, punch them in the face, break their neck, drag them to the sea floor and eat them.
And the scientific community goes, well, you don't have any proof of that. There's no proof that
there was anything this big that was actually had tendrils, like it was a octopus or a squid.
But that's not even the most interesting part of this. The fact that there might have been a giant
sea monster back in the day, I mean, probably right. And it would make sense we don't want
to really have any fossils of these. That's not the reason why this is such a controversial
thing that Mark is saying this stuff. He said that the way the bones are at the bottom, it could
not have happened accidentally. The squid put it that way on purpose. The squid actually lined up,
it would kill these creatures as it was decomposing, was removing its bones and purposely laid out a
geometric pattern at the sea floor. And so people go, why? It could have been a sign of like a
breeding display, basically. It was almost just like instinctual. Like, they would put these out
and it would be like a marker for their territory. And so the other squids would seem to be like,
oh, he's sexy. He can totally kill these monsters. Look at this giant pattern. He actually has a
more controversial answer than that. He says, I think they were drawing pictures of themselves.
He said the way, this is so interesting. The way that the bone, there'll be photos in the show
notes, the way that the bone pieces are laid out is the same way of a long tendril with suction cups.
So you see these little pieces and they kind of match together like a paved road,
but it also would, if you drew a picture of an octopus's arm, it would look like this display
of bones on the bottom of the ocean. And they found these in multiple locations and he goes,
my theory, and I know it's super controversial, that these creatures were so advanced,
they had a sense of self, they would draw pictures of themselves with the bones of the dead.
That's dope, isn't it? I mean, I read that in my imagination, it was just going wild.
And before I go and warn my imagination part, let's step back to the more rational part.
There have been people saying this isn't, this isn't true. They said, listen, we know octopus
do have a habit of building these things called midden piles, where they actually take the refuse
of their kills and kind of pile them up, but they do not do it in a geometric fashion. So the fact
that we have modern day species not doing it, but they do create this pile of rubbish, that
that is probably what, first off, science says there is no squid that big, they just weren't
that big. But let's assume that they were just for to help you out, Mark. They wouldn't be building
these piles on purpose. It wouldn't be some sort of design that they're doing, if anything, it's
habit. And you know, the old thing, the scientists who dispute this go, listen, I, you can see patterns
anywhere. I can look up at the sky and see a fat man smoking a cigar. He's looking at a cloud. He's
not actually watching the guy float off the earth. I left the, I left down the part, he's looking at
clouds. You can find patterns anywhere. So he goes, the fact that you can look at a pattern of bones,
you could find a pattern there. You could say it looks like an octopus's arm or squid's arm with
the suction cups, but you know, it could be anything. And it's interesting because they go,
extraordinary claims require extraordinary evidence. And that's a very, very common quote.
And Mark has an answer for that. Mark says, yeah, that is a very common quote. I think Carl
Sagan was the one who came up with it, but he goes, extraordinary evidence for extraordinary
claims. Let me lay this out for you. We have nine dead Ikea sources at the bottom of the ocean
with twisted necks and broken ribs. So right there, that tells us that there was something big
enough to kill these things on a regular basis. And then quote, then the pieces of the bones or
skeletal elements have been organized in a very non, shall we say, natural way. This to me is
extraordinary evidence and it demands explanation and has alluded the explanation or has alluded
proper explanation by paleontologists for a generation now. It's time that we figured this out.
Unquote. So he's saying the evidence is there. Now we got to figure out how this happened. I'm not,
we have extraordinary evidence. We have to believe that something was breaking these guides next.
Something had to be huge. And in the NPR interview, they were saying a 40, something that was big
enough to take down one of these 45 foot Ikea sources would be the equivalent of those old
wood carvings we'd see of octopi crushing a galleon, crushing this giant wooden boat. He goes,
they'd have to be that big. And Mark's like, yeah, totally. Like this thing is massive and
it could be incredibly smart. It's funny because a long time ago, we did an episode
or octopuses from outer space. And that was a really fun episode. I'll put it in the show notes.
And we talked about like why the octopus, the squid, they're so much more advanced than a lot of the
other aquatic species. They're a lot more advanced than a lot of land animals as well. The, I remember
reading this thing a long time ago, I think it was the octopus, the problem with the octopus, it has a
very short lifespan. It's in a couple years, right? If they live to be 80, 90, 100 years old,
they would, they would control the ocean. They're so smart, but they just have a very,
very short lifespan and they don't breed a lot like a lot of other species. Humans can out breed
octopuses. I think it's also interesting that before we began to sail the oceans, which was very
relatively late in human development, there was no natural predators for a lot of these things in
the ocean until we got on the oceans and started killing them. So if it had been another couple
million years, right, before we were sailing, who knows who would have won that arms race and evolution?
And it's so interesting too, because I hear all the time about the Fermi paradox and how come we
don't see any proof of aliens? If aliens are really out there, how come they're not visiting? How
come they're not signaling to us? And there's all sorts of stuff about that. If there's really like
300 million life planets that can support life in the galaxy, just in the galaxy alone, how come
we've seen no proof? That's such a human concept. Think about this. Think about this. There is a
possibility of a meteorite strike wiping out the dinosaurs and the land mammals in our history,
and that left the oceans alone to really breed in. The fact that we came out of the oceans
and conquered the land, we forget that the oceans are two thirds of the planet. And if you, if the
main life form on the planet was aquatic, if that was the highest life form on the planet,
you would not leave that planet. For one, you'd maybe so deep in the ocean, you could have a
fully functional civilization, advanced technology civilization under the water, under the sea with
King Triton. You could have an alien race that is completely evolved in the ocean that didn't even
know stars existed. And everything, they got all the geothermal energy that they need, they're
fully exploring all of the caves in the mountainous regions underneath the ocean.
To them, going to the surface would be like going to heaven. They wouldn't be able to breathe either.
And let's say that they do discover that there is a world, I'm not just talking about the soil
outside the ocean, but that they can look up in the night sky and see stars and see galaxies and go,
I want to fly up there. One, they'd have no concept of flight. They're already living this 3D
environment. We live in our very, I know we're three dimensional, but we live on an earthling
environment. We didn't start flying till way late in the game. They wouldn't even think about flying.
We thought of flying because we looked up at birds and go, oh, I want to be that.
They just see other fish. Fully functional civilization underwater. Secondly, gunpowder,
rocket technology. Would any of this even be possible with an underwater society if it was
fully evolved on an aquatic planet or a planet like earth, which is two thirds water, and all of
the land life, all of the creatures on land were killed? Would you invent rockets? Would a rocket
work underwater? How does gunpowder, how does fire work underwater? You need rockets to even
consider leaving the planet. You need to take that step. But let's say they do develop rocket
technology. We can go to space for a limited amount of time. We have to expend a ton of fuel to get
up there. And we have oxygen. But imagine if you didn't need oxygen. Imagine if you needed tons of
water. You needed to constantly be in water. Now the amount of force of thrust that takes to leave
your planet, and you have to have all this water on the ship, they would just be like, I'm not going
to go anywhere. So there could be millions of aquatic species out there. There could be millions
of species that live underground with these underground lakes like we find on Mars, like we
find on these other moons. Like I think it's Titan that has a bunch of underground lakes.
You don't even know space exists. And if you did figure it out and you're an aquatic species,
you cannot leave. It just takes too much thrust to carry tons of water off the planet. If you even
discover thrusts, rocket technology in the first place, I do think it's very, very plausible that
I do believe there's aliens out there, obviously. And if there's a lot of aquatic species, we would
never know it. And they would never know we existed. You could have a super intelligent species on
earth that lived long before us that died out long before us that would leave no fossil record. And
even if you could find the fossils, they wouldn't say how smart they were. This is something I wouldn't
dismiss out of hand. And I know scientists, that's what they do. They're like, well, you need that
proof. You just can't make these claims. But again, he's showing you the proof. He's asking you,
then what's your answer? Fascinating story. And the fact that it was possibly drawing a picture
of itself, right? Like a creature that wouldn't leave any fossils, but we know that it exists,
or that it might exist, because it drew a picture of itself. I mean, that's that in and of itself is
a really cool story. So I wanted to share that one with you. I really, really loved that one.
Is it true? I mean, is his hypothesis true? Maybe he says the only way we'll be able to find out
if these existed is if we find a giant beak from an octopus or a giant gladius. He goes other than
that or a giant egg from one of them fossilized. He goes other than that, nothing else will ever
prove they exist. And even if they find one of those, could they prove the drawing was intelligent?
I guess we won't know. I guess we won't know until the squid drop ships show up.
They found the way to leave their planet. They're coming for revenge.
Erin, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonicopter. We're leaving behind the ocean.
We are headed all the way out to a suburban neighborhood. I found this story online. It's
an interesting story. I have to be upfront with you, though. We don't have a date range, which
sucks. I mean, obviously, we kind of want to know the key details who would when, where, why.
Paranormal, we very rarely get the why and how of it. We don't have a time range for this. We don't
have a location for this. We know it takes place in a basic suburban neighborhood. And I believe
the story starts in the 60s just because of the Darth Vader reference that's coming up that I
alluded to in the intro. We're going to meet a young woman. She goes online by the moniker
Chef Lisa O. So we'll just call her Lisa for short. And she makes the claim she grew up in
a haunted house. She said she actually had her room was above the garage and every night.
That's not her exercising. That's not her touching her toes. She hears footsteps walking upstairs.
She would hear footsteps walking up the stairs and she's like, no, not again, not again. And then
she knew what was coming. She would start screaming at the top of her lungs, but no one in the house
could hear her. I've actually experienced that. I'll put that in an episode in the show notes.
That does fit with ghost lore that sometimes ghosts can actually create some sort of sound bubble.
So that's a terrifying part of it. You think safety in numbers, but there are times and I've had it
happen to me. You can scream at the top of your lungs and someone in the next room literally hears
nothing. So she screamed at the top of her lungs and a ghost would start beating her up.
I'm working doing work in the rib cage a little bit, punching her in the face.
And it's so funny because at the very beginning here, I'm not going to try to dissect this story
too much, but at the very beginning here, this story has a weird balance of very credible information
and then stuff that's so bizarre. Like I've been in the situation where you can scream and nobody
can hear you, but imagine if every this happens every single night, she got beat up by a ghost.
Like eventually she's going to come downstairs. She's all bruised. She's like wearing a sling and
the mom's like, "How'd you sleep?" And she's like, "Mom, if I told you once, I told you twice,
every night a ghost beats me up." "Oh, you're just, you're just faking."
"As your kidneys are bleeding." She's like, "Mom, can I go to the hospital again?"
So this story, and I'm not going to break, I'm not going to stop it every time, but I want to
highlight that this story is weird on more than one level. She would often hear she'd be laying
in bed. Why would you like just sleep on the couch, dude? But she'd be laying in bed. She wants to,
she wants to get up her boxing moves. She's like the only true opponent is the spirit opponent.
She's fighting it. She's always losing though. She'd be sleeping in her bed and she would hear
deep scratches from coming inside of her closet. She's like, "Oh no, oh no." She's,
she's wrapping her, wrapping her hands with tape, getting ready to box. And then one day she asked
her older brother, "Hey, would you go check, would you go check on my closet?" There might be a
demon in there. I mean, I don't know if she's not going in her closet to get her clothes or anything.
They're all covered with moths. I mean, obviously she's opening her closet to get clothes out, but
okay, I'll try to, I'll try not to stop this story to analyze it too much because we're only two
paragraphs in. The brother goes into the closet and he's kind of pushing around on the wall.
That's how he checks stuff. I'm not going to be able to get through this story. That's how he
checks stuff. He's like, "Hey, can you check out the car?" He's just pushing on the carburetor. He's
like, "Yeah, this seems to work." He goes in to check out the closet and he's seen what could be
causing the scratches and he pushes and he realizes that the closet actually has a bunch of drywall,
which you know, all houses do, but he's able to push through it and there's a secret room on the
other side of Lisa's closet. And they walk in there and there is a small table, like an
altar almost, and burnt candles, and then bones, bird bones and dog bones. And Lisa implies maybe
some of the bones are actually human. And there was also a book of spells and incantations. So
they're like, "What should I do with all of this demonic stuff? I know, I'll just throw it in the
garbage." This is not doing me any good. I don't know how to read these incantations. And I've already
made enough bone stew for the week. So they throw all this stuff out and they find out in a roundabout
way the history of the house, why they actually had this hidden room in the closet. It turns out
before Lisa's family moved in there, another family lived there, and this was a family where they had
a mom, a dad, and their son Bart. And Bart was, this is, I mean, you don't get to choose your
children, right? You have kids and hopefully they're cool and not super lame and stuff like that.
But anyways, this dude was a worshiper of the Dark Lord and a pedophile. So that's a bad combination,
right? Because basically you're already a super disgusting human being, you're a pedophile, and
then you're trying to use the ways of the satanic forces around you. I don't know, be like extra
pedophilic. But anyways, he's a nutcase. And so he's living there with his mom and his dad. And
the dad one day mysteriously vanishes. He's like walking, he's walking into the closet, he's like,
"Oh, it's a portal." And Bart's like, "One down, one to go." Well, the dad mysteriously vanishes,
and then his mom fell down the stairs in the house. And she tumbled so far,
or it could have been three stairs, I don't know how far she fell, but it was far enough and hard
enough that she needed a wheelchair after she fell down the stairs. So Bart was like, "Oh, man,
he's like wheeling his mom or he's like, "Oh, man, I'd really love to worship Satan, but instead
I gotta take my mom to the clinic." So anyways, the family moved out. It probably wasn't wheelchair
accessible. There were a bunch of stairs as she fell down. So I don't think they could have lived
there anymore. So they moved out. But what happened was Bart would still come by the house to visit.
And well, he wasn't welcome. They didn't like let him in the house. They're like, "Teen crumpets,
he's all levitating them." He's like, "Oh, yes, mom, mom, mom. Satan gives me more powers each day."
He would show up and usually on Saturdays, right? He'd show up like every Saturday and he would stand
in the front yard talking to the trees. You'd just be having these conversations with the trees.
And people are like, "Dude, you're super nuts, right?" This is before they found his portal in
her closet. They just thought he was a weirdo. And then one day when Lisa's mom is walking through
the front yard, Bart turns to her and says, "You, you will die a violent death." And she's like,
"What?" I don't think he was allowed back at the house after that. That would definitely
you'd get a restraining order after that. But he stopped showing up at some point and the house
is greeted with a new visitor, El Greco. He's a tiny little demon man who starts walking around
the house and he goes, "My name is El Greco and welcome to my home. You're the one paying the
mortgage payments. I'm a roommate you can never get rid of." And this little El Greco guy would
kind of like stalk around the house. I don't know. This is so weird because they introduce El
Greco and I'll tell you right now he doesn't really do anything. He just kind of like hops on
plates and dances. Actually, he doesn't even do that. He just is there. He just is there. My
whimsical imagination imagined him the little top hat. But no, he just kind of is like hanging
out in the house. The demon who really makes a mark on this story is described as a large
black figure. The mom starts to describe this large dark figure that will be standing in the house.
She's like, "Oh dude, it's super scary. Like this guy shows up and he has like on a cape
and his face is all weird and stuff like that." And he just like walks around and he's super spooky,
right? She's trying to describe what this demon looks like to her family because no one else
can see it. And they're like, "Uh, I'm sure we found the portal to hell in my closet and I get
beat up every night by the ghost." But I don't know what you're talking about. You're talking about
El Greco. I haven't seen that dude and you're talking about this giant black demon walking around.
And she can't really like explain it. Like he's dressed in all black. He has his black cape. He
has this weird looking helmet. But one day, this is why I think the story takes place in the 1960s
because now we're jumping ahead to 1977. They've been living in this haunted house for a long time.
They all go to see Star Wars at the movie theater. The first one, right? And she's watching the movie,
opening crawl, all that copyrighted music, laser beams, and the stormtroopers getting
shot and rebels throwing bombs and whatever. And then the door opens up and out comes
the demon from their house. When she saw Darth Vader walk on screen, the mom started to lose it
because she goes, "That is what the demon looks like." Not El Greco. El Greco's right here. He's
like in the popcorn. He's like, "Nom, nom, nom, nom." El Greco came with us. The giant, large, black
demon I've been seeing in my house looks exactly like Darth Vader. It doesn't say whether or not
they finished watching the movie because on the one hand, Star Wars, what a great film, right?
On the other hand, the demon who's haunting your house is in it. I don't know if I could watch
the first Matrix if Lawrence Fishburne kept breaking into my house and beating me up. I don't
think I could do it, but again, another great movie. So this point, Lisa's like 14 years old. She
spent her entire early life in this haunted house and her mom starts to act weird, which is a really
high bar because she's already talking about Darth Vader hanging out in her kitchen and El Greco
running around. She starts to act like she's possessed and she begins to hallucinate. And
one of the hallucinations she saw that she specifically names that is that, Lisa, one of the
hallucinations that the mother saw was she would be walking through the house and her kids would
be running around or reading books or like jumping. "Please start playing with Star Wars
action figures." She's like, "No, no. You're part of the conspiracy." She would be watching her kids
and then they would start to slow down and then freeze and then turn to statues.
She'd be staring at these lifeless sculptures of her children just standing there in the living
room. That terrifies me. That level of mental illness terrifies me because you think about it,
the kids are still moving around, right? The real world is still going on, but she's seen them
frozen in place. Like statues, they became stone. You know what I mean? That's another
layer of reality, almost like an overhead projector just laying on top of it while reality still
moves. That type of thing absolutely freaks me out. And she starts to, during this time period
where she's possessed and hallucinating, she starts to know things that she shouldn't know,
not like advanced algebra. She's learning, like she knew that her husband got in a car wreck and
she's sitting there and she's like, "He got in a crash. He got in a crash." And they're like,
"What are you talking about?" And then they get a phone call later. The dad survived, but he's in
a car accident. And she said that El Grico told her. El Grico's like, "Guess who's not coming home
for dinner tonight?" She starts hearing voices. That's really de-escalation, right? She's seeing
all this hideous stuff and then the other things. She hears voices. She smells burnt hair.
That's pretty gross. Neurological problem, right? Neurological problem, looking at it like a skeptic.
The story, though, concludes with Bart's prophecy coming true. The mother starts telling the family,
"Hey, listen, I know things, things have been really stressful, me being possessed and all,
but tonight I heard a conversation upstairs. It wasn't any of you guys. I'm not accusing any of
you guys, but I heard a man and a woman talking upstairs and they said it's time for her to die.
And to be honest, I'm really, really nervous about that because it's me and then Lisa,
I think, is the only other girl in the house. So it's one of us. It's probably me, right? Because
I was prophesied to have a violent death. And I imagine at this point you would be like, "Oh,
do we have to take her to the hospital again?" Like at this point you would have to really
believe your mom was suffering from some serious mental illness because you're not really seeing
any of this stuff. I mean, to be fair, Lisa did get beat up every night by a ghost. I don't think
she's a skeptic. I don't think she was like, "Oh, but Darth Vader, that's ridiculous,"
as she's getting punched in the liver. The next night, the next night, the very next night,
the mother bolts out of the house, runs into the road and is hit by two cars.
And as she's laying there dying on the road, she's still clutching her Bible.
She's holding tightly to her Bible, hoping for more peace in the afterlife than she had
in the last few years of this life. Obviously super tragic. And how do you again explain that?
Did she have a psychotic break? Did she run into the road? Did she see something that scared her so
badly? Like, how did this happen? And for months afterwards, when Lisa was brushing her hair or
brushing her teeth or just walking by a mirror of any kind, her mother would be standing behind her.
And her mother would just be malvying something,
trying to communicate with Lisa. And you could never make out the words. It was just
silent, but she could see her mom's tortured gaze locked on her as her mouth silently opened
and closed, trying to tell her something. This goes on for months and Lisa almost has a nervous
breakdown. This was going for three days for me. I'd have a nervous breakdown. This goes on for
months and Lisa's on the edge. She knows her mom wants to tell her something, but she can't figure
out what it is for the life of her. And then one night, her mom shows up in the bedroom,
and Lisa immediately relaxes like she feels all of this tension leave her body. And the mom says,
"I didn't run out of the house because I was crazy. I was murdered by Darth Vader. I was murdered
by the Darth Vader guy. He was in the house. This all happened at 3 a.m. This all happened at 3 a.m.
I was sitting there in the house and Darth Vader showed up. He's like, "I want the plans for the
Death Star." And I ran out and Darth Vader was chasing me through the house and I grabbed the
Bible thinking it would protect me in some way, but it didn't. And I ran out the front door and
Darth Vader's close on my heels and then I run into the road and I'm run over by two cars.
And then after that, the spirit of her mom stopped visiting her. After that, the haunting of the
house seemed to cease. I believe they just moved out of the house, which is what I would have done
the first year of getting beat up by a ghost. Fascinating story. Obviously, there's two ways
we can look at this. One is a mental health way, right? Because all of the stuff the mom's going
through could easily be attributed to mental illness. Possessions. The burnt hair. It's so funny
because we deal in the paranormal world, we deal with possessions, we deal with ghosts, we deal with
voices. All of that stuff is pretty normal in the world of the paranormal. When you add in the smell
of burnt hair, that's really when I was reading the narrative, I go, "This does seem neurological."
That's something you don't normally smell. You have the stereotypical smell of sulfur,
which a lot of times could be some sort of methane leak, which it could also cause you to
hallucinate if you're around it for too long. But the burnt hair, I was thinking she might just
be having strokes that's causing all of these all of these disconnections in her brain. So that's
obviously something we do want to address. It's the easiest thing to just go, "Ah, she was just crazy."
But how exhausting would that be? Like even if it was just craziness. But then you look, you go,
"Well, Jason, if the mom was crazy, she's hallucinating El Grico." What about the daughter?
Like she was getting beat up by the ghost. Was she crazy? Was she beating herself up?
It's interesting because when you look, this is one of the things I like about Reddit. One of the
few things I like about Reddit. I think the website's a cesspool of the most disgusting humans on the
planet. But other than that, I can look at people's post histories and not to discredit people,
not to be like, "Oh, you also like this political party? Pfft, you're dumb." Not like that. I like
to look at it because I like to see if they're posting stuff that is equally far-fetched. I can
look at stuff and go, "Is this someone who's always posting once-in-a-lifetime stories?" Because if it's
someone who posts once-in-a-lifetime stories over and over and over again, it starts to seem like
they're making it up. To be fair, I've been ghost hunting for 23 years and I do have my fair share
of once-in-a-lifetime stories as well. So it's not an automatic strike against her.
She does go on to say that she once ran into a serial killer, a gay serial killer. I don't know
if that meant he was killing gay people or if he was gay himself, but he gave her a giant
garbage bag full of beanie babies. And she also said when she's an adult and she has a daughter
that Jesus was stalking her daughter, like there is this weird stalker outside of her window,
and her daughter would be like, "Mommy, mommy, the visitor's back, the visitor's back," and then
Lisa would go outside and there were these giant footprints. There was only one set of footprints.
That's when Jesus was carrying the stalker to safety. They would find these set of footprints.
They were like 11 inches. So not giant, giant, but... And then one day they were at church and the
minister was showing a picture of Jesus. It was a picture of him photoshopping his arm around Jesus.
He's like, "Look it. Jesus is my best buddy. You should join my church." They had like a, not a photo
of Jesus, obviously. What a drawing of Jesus, like a painting. And the little girl goes, "That's
him. That's the visitor who's peeking through my window at night." And it was Jesus. Jesus was the
stalker. Now listen, I know humans can look like Jesus. Obviously Jesus was a human, but I mean,
it's an easy look to copy, right? I've known people that pull out the Jesus look.
So it could just have been, it could have been a stalker that looked like Jesus. We're in the
world of paranormal. It could have been Jesus. When I read stories like that, it doesn't discredit
Lisa at all. It does. It's interesting because I'm not going to throw out, those are weird once in
a lifetime stories as well. They don't really dismiss everything. I don't go, "Oh, it's obviously,
this woman's obviously making stuff up," or anything like that. Those stories are weird, though,
and they do add color because even her story, the story about her mom, I should say, involves
Darth Vader. Right off the bat. But what's so interesting is that Darth Vader does look like
a spooky dude. Like to us, he's a toy, and I think he's one of the best villains in the original
trilogy at least. I do think that that is a very menacing figure. And who knows that maybe George
Lucas got the... Lucas's partner was El Grico. And El Grico secretly wrote the original trilogy.
That's why those movies are so much better than all the other ones. I did like the prequels. But
the point is, when somebody's telling you a ghost story and you're like, "Oh my god, the ghost was
coming to your room," and she's like, "Yeah, he was beating me up every night." You go, "Ehh, every night?"
It's interesting. Like, it's little details that make you go, "Like, if it beats you up occasionally,
it beats you up every couple months or something like that, maybe?" But every night, that's
obvious proof. Like, you could just bring someone to their house on a Wednesday and they
get beat up. And that's proof. So, stuff like that. Like, sometimes the details are too weird,
even. We just covered a squid that drew a picture of itself with dinosaur bones. But getting beat
up every night's a little too weird. The Darth Vader thing, even though he's a menacing character,
that's still really weird that Darth Vader was chasing this woman around the house.
It's a story. It's one of the stories that is so ridiculous, it might become so ridiculous. It's true.
So, was this the story of a woman in the throes of some sort of mental illness? Some sort of madness
that was so out of control, not only did she run out into the middle of the street to get hit by
two cars, but she also spread that mental illness throughout her family. It went from being in her
head to almost mass psychosis. I really don't know. I don't know if I'd rather live in a haunted house
or have actually no answer to this one. If I had to choose between a debilitating mental illness
or a living in a haunted house, even if the demon was a killer, I'd live in the haunted house. Because
I, I think I can go get an exorcist. I can maybe sublet the room above the garage to somebody I
don't like. I'd much rather do that. Curses and hauntings can be passed on to the next generation.
But so can mental illness. That's the case. That's what the story's about.
It's not scary or terrifying. It's just really, really kind of sad.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also
go to set up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Tick tock! Is that DeadRabbitRadio?
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
Don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye!
[Music]
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]