What happens when an artist takes criticism a little too far?
And then we travel back to the 1980s to talk about Smurfs once again.
Three apples high, little blue guys running through the forest trying to outwit an
idiotic wizard and his crazy cat.
A basic story, a tale as old as time, but to some religions
The Smurfs not only represented demonic forces taking over the entertainment industry, but we're actually coming alive
entering our real world and
Attacking their children today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter or I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. You know our first story is a cautionary tale of
being able to take criticism
There's constructive criticism
Which I actually got the other day on 4chan this guy was like hey man love the show
But now you're going off on these weird like side humor things and it's kind of forced and it's not as funny as it used to be
The show is not as funny as it used to be I listen to I used to listen every day now listen to every other episode
That's constructive criticism and this is why this is what's wrong with the show and this is why it's affecting me personally
It's not your show sucks. It's not you're not funny. None of that stuff's helped. This is the problem
This is specifically the problem and this is the result. I'm not listening to the show as much and I I
We talked for a bit and I totally understand
I said probably the show just gets annoying after a while just like a relationship you talk to the same person every single day
Eventually the things that you enjoyed about them do get grading take a break for a while
Maybe come back, but they're they're kind of doing that and they said they don't listen to every different
So I don't take that and that's all I don't expect people to listen every episode either. I don't listen to every episode of my favorite podcast
I'm always impressed when you guys do but you got to be able to take criticism when you put stuff out into the world
You have to be able to take criticism the reason why I'm telling the story is because
We're gonna learn about a guy who can't take criticism not only cannot take criticism
But criticism may have actually driven this man insane
Let's harbor the carbonar cocktail guys. We're headed off to the United Kingdom
We're headed to Glen Rhoads the village of Glen Rhoads. It is October 3rd in
2014 so very very recent just what four years ago five years ago. Wait, what year is it six years ago?
It's all he's six years ago and there we're gonna meet a young woman working at an asda supermarket
That's some British thing. It's a supermarket, but everything is on the left side of the aisle. So
There's a young girl working there. Her name is Paige
Roland roll and roll and roll and roll and wood and she is has a red baseball cap on her baggy pants
There is nothing hotter than a woman in a baseball cap with a ponytail pulled to the back of the cap
I don't care
What else you look like if that is the top of your forehead from your eyebrows up? I'm in
Anyways page rolling. She's she's rolling. No, just page rolling 18 years old
She's working at as the grocery store. She's on her knees kind of moving stuff around on the bottom, right?
And while she's she's moving around some hot dog flavored water
She's a soft drink down there coming down the aisle
Is Richard britain, which would be the best name living in britain as in I would love to be named jason america
Or jason united states, but i'm not i'm jason carbonar Richard britain
In britain is walking down this aisle this young woman is kind of moving stuff around
She grabs the chocolate starfish and putting it next and then bonk
Now now there's more
I I have to guess how loud to me that sound effect that didn't sound super dramatic
But the point is it made a much louder noise in the grocery store
He smashes this girl over the head with a full
Bottle of wine. She's like, uh, she goes unconscious for a moment, which which she's lucky. She didn't die
And the newspaper articles don't really say if he runs away or if he stands there
I'm assuming he left the scene, but he does get arrested now. The question is why what is the motive?
So they eventually track this guy down. He's on the run. I don't know
He could have just sat down and drank some wine outside the store
The point is eventually he gets arrested and when the cops start to interrogate him they go
Why'd you do it? He goes, aha, I have the perfect motive. I will admit that I hit this woman
But once I tell you why
Then you will you'll you'll go and hit her you'll go to the hospital here
I'll let you borrow this bottle of wine a shoplift did one
Here you can go and you can hit her over the head because you will also want to brain this young woman
You see and that's when he reaches in with jacket and pulls out a book and they're like, whoa
We should have we should have checked him. We should have frisked him before we brought him in here
That could have been anything he goes. This is my book. I wrote this novel. It's the most beautiful novel ever written
They're looking at it and it's called the world
rose
She's pushing the book over pushing the book over to warm hope and they'd pick it up read it
They're like just tell us just tell us we're not going to read the book
He's like, well, you promise to read the book later. They go, fine
So he wrote this book called the world rose. He put it on wattpad, which is an app people can read free stuff
And he then did some edits and published it in page roll and had read it on wattpad and said this sucks
Is no good. Now. I don't know how detailed her criticism was. I don't know if it was constructive criticism like
Characters fall flat the world buildings lame the title is uh beyond pathetic
I guess that's not constructive criticism
But she could have been very detailed said this is what I do to fix it. But for whatever reason whatever her
Review was he went nuts. Now. He lived 400 miles away from page
He drove all the way to her grocery store to hit her over the head and what's funny now that I think about it
He was able to plan to find her drive out, but he didn't even bring a weapon with him
He what if they didn't sell alcohol there?
What if they had no bottles or she was in a weird aisle?
But anyway, so poorly poorly planned attack. He gets arrested
Britain has some real problems with their criminal justice system. He gets found guilty
He gets sentenced to 30 months in jail. That's not a huge he was attempted murder really
I mean you could totally kill somebody with that. He gets sentenced to 30 months in jail
He only does 15 with an indefinite order to never contact page again a month after he's released from jail
He sends her a letter saying I dreamed of you last night. Are you going to send me back to prison?
Now he's sending her mail with stuff saying such as nothing is real except our love
Which we all remember that great hauling out song. I will love you forever. That's
fairly less creepy and this page is torn because we are torn without each other. So
She's obviously freaked out. She's contacting the authorities. I don't know if they know where he's at
honestly because I didn't see any follow-up of him getting arrested again, but
15 come on Britain. I know America gets gets grief for being too strict
But this dude's 15 months. They had that terrorist who they had to kill on the London bridge a couple months ago
He got out. He did seven years for trying to blow up parliament. What's your problem over there?
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story now
I teased this story on yesterday's episode because we talked about smurfs. There was a street gang known as the smurfs
Let's hop on board the carpenter copter. We're leaving behind Britain for good
We're never doing another story from there. Just too many lunatics
We're flying back to the good old the united states and we're going to
Any town usa because this was kind of all over the place now in the 1980s. We had a couple different things going on
We had an explosion of children's media
Really in the late 70s you started seeing like obviously a fred flin stone stuff like that
That was more of like a simpson's thing. It was more for like adult sand kids
Then you had the hannah bar bar cartoon scooby-doo that stuff is late 70s
But in the 1980s companies decided whoa
We have the ability to put out a half hour commercial every single day kids will buy our clothes
There's actually a really cool youtube channel called toy galaxy. I recommend people checking out. It's really cool
It's super informative their videos are only like 10 15 minutes long
And each video they go back to an old toy line or mostly toy line and they talk about how the toys were
Designed and made and a lot of them have these weird corporate battles going on in the background
They'll come out with the toy line and can't get a cartoon launched in time the toy line fizzles
It's a really cool channel really really talented people on that show
But you had this thing where you had these cartoons being made and they were a half hour long advertisement
So you saw an explosion in children's media that has never been replicated
It really was a great time to be a kid wake up on saturday morning or just come home from school
You'd have two hours of solid entertainment you had that but then you also had a thing known as the satanic panic
There were satanists around every corner and it was
It was a perfect time to be a conspiracy theorist nowadays. We talk about pizza getting all that stuff
It's all very esoteric. It's all very like this
Elite cult that runs the world is doing this satanic panic was they're in your neighborhood
It wasn't something that was happening in washington dc in your neighborhood
Saint worshipers are killing cows in your neighborhood. The reason why you lost your cat is to say it was very like boots on the ground
conspiracy theory paranoia was everywhere and it was really cool. I mean, I was too. I was probably like
This story takes place in 1983 mostly. So I would have been
Seven when this story was taking place
But even I was kind of aware because I went to southern baptist church madavis a minister
This idea that there were satanists around every corner. They were in the highest levels of power
But you also had like your mailman could be a satanist and as a conspiracy theorist
It was a really cool time super scary if you believed in it
But you have this satanic panic going on and what happened was you have the satanic panic
Which is this idea that satan worshipers are taking over the united states and really the world and this explosion
In children's media
So just like and again guys this all goes and this is why a lot of times I brush off stuff and people go
What you don't think katie parry is a saint worshiper back when I was a kid
It was saint worshipers are taking over the country or the world and they're doing it
They're influencing children by children's cartoons nowadays. It's not saint worshipers. It's illuminati who may or may not worship satan
It really depends
It could be part of some other religious group or they could be atheist whatever
But now it's the illuminati using music to influence children and stuff like that because and the reason why it's because
Cartoons don't exist the way they used to people can still say oh, there are still these cartoons with this messaging
But it used to be that cartoons saturday morning and afternoon cartoons were such an intrinsic part of a child's life
That if you wanted to affect them, that's how you would do it. The myth has evolved is what I'm saying
I don't think the illuminati were like damn. Damn it. The cartoons are off and also what used to be saint worshipers
But now I think the myth evolved. I don't think it was true. I don't think saint worshippers were affecting
He-man and and smurf cartoons. I don't think that was happening. I don't think the illuminati is controlling katie parry
It's myths myths will change with the times
But anyways anyways that all being said satanic panic well back in the 80s
This was it now a lot of my information is going to come from an article on the paranormal world wiki
So there's a paranormal world wikipedia not wikipedia, but it's like a wiki. It's a self edited thing
It's an article called a brief history of killer smurfs and I just want to note take that because that is where I
I did go and backtrack information, but this gave me a good framework for it
So I wanted to give credit where credit was due. We talked about a bunch of stuff just now
A trip down memory road jason's paranoid religious memory road has a southern baptist
I was taught very very briefly my dad wasn't into a bunch of nonsense and stuff like that
But there were members of the church who believed that smurfs were demonic and payo who was the anonymous payo was a
pseudonym for the author of or the creator of smurfs and the rumor was was that payo meant
Demon in italian, which is not true. I at least I didn't double check it, but I'm pretty sure it's not so it might be
But anyways the point is is that I heard that briefly my dad as a southern baptist minister thought it was stupid
Didn't have any problem with me watching it or he man or anything like that
He probably just figured it kept me quiet kept me from bugging people or actually
Setting fires and I got in a lot of trouble as a kid
but anyways
The point is is that my dad didn't have problem with it. He is a minister theological
Studies doctor and all that stuff. He didn't have a problem
So but lay people lay people in the church may have that being said
I'm just the reason why I'm saying that is because people in my own religion had a problem with this
The rest of these examples are going to be about the jojova's witness church
So not knocking them this type of nonsense can happen in any religious community
But this a lot of these examples came from members of the jojova's witness church
Reddit threads from ex-church members and things like that and one thing jojova one thing you can count on jojova's witness to hate
Is anything supernatural? So when you start to think that smurfs are demons
You could have southern baptists being like, yeah, I think they were bad influence
I don't think my kids should play with smurfs jojova's witness pretty much
According to these ex-members. So again, there might be a bit of a bone to pick
But according to these ex-members jojova's witness basically went to war with the smurfs now
They didn't go to war by saying don't buy the well they said don't buy the toys
Don't watch the cartoon stuff like that
But they weren't just saying that don't do it because pale means demon
They were doing it because they believed again allegedly and that's the last time i'm going to say this
You just insert that word the church's doctrine was that
The smurfs themselves were demons that could enter our reality
And here's a couple of little stories that people have said they heard when they were kids
This young girl is given smurf curtains for her room because smurfs are cute little guys, you know
Three apples high little blue people put them up
Have you briny smurf and gopher smurf or whatever poppa smurf and all that stuff and she goes to bed
Oh, I love my smurf curtains falls asleep
Wakes up in the middle of the night
She looks around in the dark room
That's not her laughing and she's not the crypt keeper
She's looking around her room. She can't see anything her eyes haven't adjusted yet
Little feet
Running around she kind of gets you kind of get the picture smurfs don't have to keep building it
Smurfs jumped off of her curtain. You're like, I didn't expect that
I just expected a different group of smurfs. They're actually the two-dimensional smurfs jumped off the curtain
Now running around her bedroom. They were dancing and laughing quote satanically
I have no idea what a satanic laugh would sound like but I mean you figured that would be like, ho ho ho
That'd be less scary than
Little little pee run creepy if you heard that story as a kid you wouldn't want to be around smurfs
Here's another one kid gets smurf wallpaper
Apparently johova's witness a real problem with flat smurfs
They're like, oh regular smurf dolls. We'll get to smurf dolls in a second
But it's weird that two of these stories involve I would not be threatened by a two-dimensional object
That's funny because the first one these kids are all johova's witness, right?
But they're like new to the church or they hadn't heard yet that smurfs are demonic
They just thought it was a cute cartoon the first one the girl gets smurf curtains
So you could see like her grandma who's like here
This is a cute little cartoon sending the curtains the smurfs jump off the curtain start running around this other kid has smurf
Wallpaper which means they spent eight hours. They had to go to the store by
Multiple rolls of it take it home get it prepped put it on the walls take a break go eat a sandwich
Go back up finish putting the wallpaper up be like, ah done and done
My kid finally has this smurf which I don't know what a smurf is and I haven't heard from my church yet
Whether or not this is demonic, but here you go
Click shut off the light this kid supposedly wakes up the next day
He comes down to eat the meal in the morning
He gets up
He's eating his ego waffles and the parents are like what happened to you and he's covered in little red dots little red bites
He's like, oh, yeah, what are you gonna do?
Life sucks and the parents are like what do you have bed? It's funny because in the story the parents asked him
Are there bugs in your bed?
Which is not something you would ask you just check
The parents go did you get bit by a bunch of bugs and he's like, oh though these oh, yeah
No, no, no not bugs. So remember that wallpaper that you put up yesterday?
Last night all the smurfs jumped off the wallpaper and bit me. It's funny
The first one just some curtains and this girl just got laughed at this guy has an entire room full of him
And he's getting eaten and you know that they then had to remove all that wallpaper before the end of the day
Which they did and according to the story
They tried burning it and it wouldn't burn
So they had to put on copious amounts of gasoline to burn it
So imagine these stories being told around like a campfire
At them jojova witness or really I mean I think these apply to any these again are
Ex jojova witness stories, but I think you could see this with really any religion that's super fundamentalist
These stories being passed around I would say
This one's pretty easy
The last part at least to debunk obviously smurfs did not jump off this guy's wall
Because smurfs were one of the most popular merchandising thing and people in the 80s were not covered in red welts
You did not see a Madonna video where she's dancing around and she's just covered in red welts
That was not something that I don't know why Madonna would have smurf wallpaper
My point is is that everyone had smurfs and not everyone had red dots on them
But that being said let's say they put it up the kid has nightmares. They pull the wallpaper down
They try to lay it on a fire. It doesn't burn. What if somebody told you that part of the story? What is the rational answer for it?
It's probably fire retardant wallpaper, which would make sense
Right like sometimes you have to be skeptical about this stuff
This next story might be one of my favorite stories. I've covered on dead rabbit radio in a long time
This story apparently is a friend of a friend type of story. The guy telling this story saying hey
I wasn't there when this happened, but my friend was so this family recently joins the Jehovah's Witness church
Their new converts they're walking into the temple and their kid is carrying a smurf doll
Now I don't know if he has it visible because again at this point
The church is at open war with these blue creatures. They've heard in Kentucky that I can't got a bunch of red welts
Red welts are all over the country, but the media is covering it up
They're burning trying to burn people's wallpaper houses are catching up fire
They're at open war with the smurfs. This kid though brings in a smurf doll
So maybe he has it hidden in his jacket
Nobody sees it or maybe everyone's facing the other way
He brings it into the church and he's sitting there with his smurf doll and the service is going on as normal
I've never been to a Jehovah's Witness temple. So I don't really know how it's done
But I'm just going to assume for the second narrative
It's like Southern Baptist church where you go and you sing a couple songs
Minister gives a speech or sermon is actually what it's called. You do the offering and then it's over with
So they're doing that. They're halfway through the sermon guys up there talking about Jehovah's Witness stuff
And the smurf doll this kid's holding the smurf doll, right? He's just sitting listening church probably bored
I slept a lot in church. He's listening and then in the middle of the sermon
The smurf doll jumps out of the kid's lap and lands in the aisle
So most churches have pews on both sides and there's a large aisle in the middle the smurf doll springs to life
So that's a miracle right there. That's beyond signs
jumps out of the kid's lap and lands and is now standing in the middle of the aisle
And he goes quote
I'm sick of this shit
It turns around and walks out
Now let's just call a spade a spade that if that story is true if that story is true
I was attending Jehovah's Witness or any church. I'm attending. I'm the Southern Baptist
I'm sitting there. I'm half awake
And my dad's given a sermon and I'm like, uh, I can't wait till I get home and play some more Legend of Zelda
And then I hear a rustling behind me and I turn around and I see
a one foot tall
Smurf doll on the floor in the aisle and I'm like did a kid throw that and then at that moment the doll begins to
Stand up on its own
Look at my dad and go. I'm sick of this shit
I would renounce all home religion. I would if that happened
I'd say my god can't do that
Do that god be him throwing transformers on the ground do it do it as the smurf is strutting out of the building
That would
Completely change everything now you could say jason. That's the work of the devil. I'm not saying I'd start worshiping the devil or smurf
I'm just saying that would be a pretty
That's ridiculous. That story is so it's funny
But it's so ridiculous because it would completely change the game
If you not only saw a doll walking through church, but then blasphemy your religion and bounce
I would that would totally change
Everything everyone in that church should have been a convert to something. I'm not saying again. They're like, hey, old satan
They're worshiping smurf ed, but it would really make you reconsider where you're at
And there's another part of this story. Where did the smurf go?
Because it's a one foot tall doll, right? And it says i'm done your sermon sucks. He turns he walks out of the
temple
And then what?
And this is the problem with a lot of these stories. I mean, obviously this story is pretty ridiculous
But a lot of these stories you have to ask and
So let's say someone legitimately tells you this story. They said that they were here and they saw this thing happen
You would go I think most people do this they go. Oh, that's interesting
They do that with ghost stories and UFO stories and all sorts of stuff
But you really have to go and so the doll leaves the temple
It obviously doesn't have a magical power. It doesn't disappear or a ball of flame appears
So it doesn't have the ability to teleport it actually has to walk out of the temple
And then what is it standing on the street corner? Is it waiting for a bus? Does a small car show up?
So as you jump in the bushes, is he still out there? Did he have to get a job as a day laborer because he's trapped in our reality
In this cotton filled body
Where is he if the parishioners had followed him out what they've seen him walking down the street and trying to hail a taxi and
Realize that he doesn't have any money and then he has to go and like start like panhandling and said like
And these are the questions that need to be asked when you have these stories and I get it. I love the story
I think it's absolutely fun. It would make me completely question the existence of my god
If this thing could just magically do this it would absolutely blow my mind
If at all could just get away with that in a church totally unopposed
But then the other part is logically where does the doll? Does it go to a toy store?
Even then it would get to the toy store couldn't open it up. Does it go to like a bin at a goodwill?
There's so many questions to this
How did it even reach the doorknob of the church where the door's open could put enough for like no, okay now
I'm nipping now. I'm nipping but I'm sure ghosts can inhabit dolls. I own one by the way, but I don't think it'll ever move
I don't think toys can ever move. I think the locomotion just simply wasn't work
There's no proof that that could ever happen, but let's go to this story
There was someone who was saying that again, Joe was a witness on this thread
They go I have a smurf story and I as a kid I had never ever heard
That smurfs were satanic like I just happened to have one and my family didn't know about it
It wasn't till a way later that I heard the story
But I had a smurf doll and it was a big smurf doll and he never liked it never liked the doll
He had a weird feeling about it and one day he was in his room all by himself
And he watched the doll stand up
and kind of begin walking around the room
And he said it was not a cute walk. It wasn't like a doot. Doot. Doot. It was like a
The way it almost stalked the room. It had a very creepy walk about it
And then the kid ran out of the room screaming and just thought it was a weird event
Maybe made up in his head and then later on in life
He had learned that joe was witness didn't like smurfs there satanic stuff like that
You know stories just that stupid because again
If this was possible
Then dolls would be the dolls would be walking everywhere
They would have declared open war on the joe hovis witness or anyone else who opposed them
They everyone everyone in part of these religions would have been locked up because they'd been like the smurfs did or the smurfs did it
If a doll can walk a doll can set a fire if a doll can walk a doll can smother a child
If a doll can do these things and they're demonically possessed
Then you should you should have seen mass casualty events in the 1980s
Unless a doll drove a truck into the marine barracks in libya. They weren't doing these things
So a doll getting up and walking across the room spookily is not
This is eternal war between good and evil and the stake is the rest of time and space
And demons are making dolls walk out of churches. It doesn't make sense
They should have been like suicide bombers or something like that if these demons can do this
Then all they were doing was walking out of churches and walking around rooms with one person in it. Congrats
Forces of evil. Great job. However, I'm gonna end this on a personal story
And the story might sound just as stupid as the rest, but I don't think so
I used to have a serious problem with freddy kruger
I actually used to not be able to watch horror movies at all
I was super super scared of him and I'd go to school
I remember going elementary school and kids would be like, oh, yeah, I'm the new freddy krugman movie
He's playing this kid like nintendo and he's like now you're playing with power
And he like cuts the kids veins out and he uses them like a marionette puppet
And how I imagined it in my head was always 10 times worse than the movies were
I actually ended up watching the movies years later, but I remember being so terrified of jason freddy and michael miers and all this stuff
to the point of almost like
Mental illness level a pair. I don't want to say mental illness, but I was
Stone cold petrified of these villains that I'd only heard of I'd never actually seen any of the movies
I'd seen commercials though. I knew what they looked like
I would would just kind of freeze in my tracks and I lived a lot with my grandma and my great grandma
And they're great houses full of lovely people and people who love me
But also they're pretty creepy and I have seen ghosts a lot at my grandma's house
And I'm sure that my great grandma's house had some issues as well
There was one room that was super spooky that I didn't ever feel comfortable going into that was kind of sealed off from the rest of the house, but
I remember one night I was sitting I had one of those brave star
You guys remember brave you guys are like no, I don't remember brave star brave star
They actually had like these 12 inch tall action figures and it was a cowboy in space
It was this native american character in the 25th century. He was a cowboy on this planet called new texas. I think it was
I know a bunch of you guys are like. Oh, yeah, I remember that
They're really cool toys
There's like space cowboys he had a talking horse a topic talking cyborg horse that could stand on all fours and punch people
In the face with its metal hoof. I mean, that's the end of every episode
Just smashing dudes heads
But the bad guy was like this outlaw was this alien outlaw was this purple guy and I had both of them
I had brave star and the purple guy. I don't think I had the horse, but I really loved that cartoon
And I remember one day I was sitting in this chair at my grandma's house that it's funny because I loved that chair
Like I haven't been in my grandma's house in eight years, but I just love that. I miss that chair so much
I miss my grandma obviously too not just the chair
But you know, you just had that place was my home like that little corner of that house is my home
Anyway, so enough of memory lane. I'm holding this as I go to tell a story for memory lane. I'm holding this toy
This brave star toy this bad guy is he was the bad guy's name. His name wasn't just bad guy. I forgot his name
I'm not gonna look it up. The the point is is that I'm holding this purple doll
It was probably like 10 o'clock at night. I'm I think I was like older. I think it was like
10 or 11 or something like that 12 maybe old enough
I shouldn't be scared of the dark anymore, right? But I'm still scared of the dark
I'm holding this doll and it's late. I'm watching something on television and I remember something made me look at the doll
I'm holding this doll and I'm looking at it
and
Obviously I'm not on any drugs. I'm a child
Wasn't on any night quill nothing like that. It's totally lucid. I'm looking at this doll
And its face is already kind of an alien face. It's already kind of like wrinkly
But for more than a brief second or more than just the second it wasn't a flash
And I know what I saw
The face of freddy kruger appeared on the doll
Now
The flesh changed because the alien's purple. So now it became like flesh
The scarring was there the look in his eyes
It was freddy kruger's head
on this doll's body
And I threw the doll and I screamed in a panic
a panic
I ran through my grandma's house
I jumped into my grandma's bed
Probably broke it and they're like damages and the springs are they're like, oh they all get thrown out
I was quite a chubby child. I guess that makes that joke makes more sense now
Jumping into my grandma's bed. I didn't tell him what I saw it sound crazy
crazy
But I know what I saw now is it
realistic to think that this
fictional character a fictional demon
And we actually did an episode he's based on a true story, but it wasn't freddy kruger's dream demon
That's an old episode but check that one out, but the um
Is it possible that a fictional character jumped into my toy? No, it's not it's not at all. It's completely ridiculous, right?
But that's what I saw
That's what I saw. I saw something that was completely ridiculous and impossible
And I can talk trash about dolls walking and say well if my doll wasn't walking it just changed into a fictional character
They're both ridiculous, but as much as I was going on the story and kind of taken it apart
In the back of my mind i'm thinking yeah, but I had my own creepy experience with the toy now again
There's a huge line between seeing a doll face morph into your childhood fear
and
Do whole interrupting a sermon in front of 30 people and walking out and then catching a bus back to smurf village
There is a huge difference
But as far as like just the childlike wonderment of having a toy and having a world of evil
interfere with that because
I don't think that freddie kruger's face was in that doll
But something was
Was it a ghost?
Was it a demon?
was it
Something in my head a hallucination
Who knows?
I think I lean more towards ghost. It's most likely was hallucination, but again
Forget that because that's mundane and that puts all the blame on me ghost, but most likely a demon because what else would want to scare a child like that?
So if demons wanted to inhabit toys
They wouldn't want to walk around in broad daylight unless again, they were declaring open war which obviously they either can or they can't and they haven't
So that makes me think they can't but it doesn't mean that there would be totally wrong to just inhabit a toy
just inhabit a toy
Just to make children feel uncomfortable because a demon wants to
Hurt you but if it can't physically hurt you it wants to hurt your psyche
So it doesn't have to get up and walk around it doesn't have to laugh creepily or bite you in the middle of the night or critique your sermons
It just has to sit in the darkness of your room and make you feel uncomfortable in the one place you should feel comfortable your own home
It can sit there and just draw off
The negative energy you're giving it and in return making you feel more and more uncomfortable
to the point where you fear
Being in your room where you fear
everything
A demon doesn't have to jump up and walk around and bite you to be effective
A demon just has to make you scared of it and it's even smarter if the demon can make you scared of
Something you can't place your finger on it. You don't know for sure if it's that doll or your room
You just feel uneasy
Psychological warfare but on a spiritual level
That's the true satanic panic
You never know where it's at you never know where it's coming from you're paranoid of everything so you don't know where to direct your resources
And that's easy to pull off
You don't need to control the entertainment industry
You just need to wage this war one bedroom at a time one frightened child at a time
Children are our future
And if you can make them scared of everything
When it's time to fight
They won't even be able to overcome their own fears
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)