What happens when you sue the sexiest man alive?
And then we take a look at the urban legends of
misfits
creatures
Monsters forming a community and living on the outskirts of town
Almost every area has some form of this legend
But what happens when one of these urban legends enrolls in your college and joins your study group today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
*Music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys having a great day - I'm doing little pistol finger guns
*Pistol Fingers*
We're gonna give a shout out to one of our legacy patreon supporters gun of liberty gun of liberty
Everyone shoot at him he has to dodge all the bullets he's a little too slow
He's like, ah should have stopped supporting the show before I got shot gun
You're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode whatever vehicle we take you're in charge of you can't support the patreon
That's fine too. Just help spread the word about the show that helps out so much so gun of liberty
We're gonna toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy. We're gonna take a little road trip. We're headed out to Collins County, Texas
We're driving by a bunch of armadillos on the side of the road waving to us and has their exposed predators are eating them
They're like, ah, but we save them. I love armadillos. So we're gonna pick up a bunch of those little guys
We're carrying them around I got big old backpack full armadillos. We're walking into this courthouse
We walk in we see a woman standing there. That's not unusual
There are women in Texas and sometimes they're in court. We walk in there
We see a woman in here now. This is an ongoing legal case and I guess some of the documents have been sealed
So we don't know her name so we're gonna call her
Beatrice so beat and that adds just a shot in the dark if she happens to really be named Beatrice
I'm just guessing but Beatrice is standing there and we get past security with my back full armadillos
They let me in we're waiting for the defendant to show up
so she's the plaintiff we're waiting for the other dude to show up and
Then like a bunch of doves flying in like a beam of light. Whoa, it's not God
God isn't the defendant beam of light comes in and in walks the sexiest man alive
One of them at least according to People Magazine. It's Brad Pitt Brad Pitt walks in armadillos wrestling in my backpack
They really want to get a good look at him Brad Pitt walks in sits in the defense area and the trial starts
So now we're gonna do a little flashback
What happened was back in 2018
This woman Beatrice is sitting at home and she gets notified via Instagram email something like that. Hey, you don't know me
Actually, you know me. I'm world famous superstar Brad Pitt
But I was wondering if you could help me do this fundraiser because I have this
Charity that we help build houses in Katrina not in Katrina. They're building houses during the hurricane
They're building houses. He has a time machine. He's like don't tell anyone we're building houses during Katrina. It's hilarious
He was
Building houses that were destroyed by Hurricane Katrina. He has this charity. It's called making it right or something like that
He asked this woman. Yeah, he pitches this idea to this woman
Why don't you host this fundraiser for me in Collins County, Texas?
And I will come out myself Brad Pitt
I will show up at this fundraiser event. So, you know, well, you'll be famous. You'll get to meet me
you know, that's always a benefit and
We'll both make some money most of the money goes to charity, but you know, we gotta get a little something for ourselves
So she is totally on board with this idea, right? Who's going to turn down Brad Pitt?
So she begins a little musical montage of her like putting up flyers around town
She's like gals. You won't believe what I'm doing
You won't believe what I'm doing and they're like, what's going on Beatrice? She goes, I'm hosting a fundraiser for Brad Pitt
She does all this marketing. She gets all these people super excited in tiny little Collins County, Texas
Brad Pitt's coming and I don't know where Collins County is
But I doubt it's the most happenin spot in the state
So anyways the date comes and Beatrice is all like super excited. She's like, oh my god
I can't wait till I meet Brad Pitt. I've only been talking to him online
I haven't seen any evidence that he exists outside of a movie
Everyone shows up except for Brad Pitt Brad Pitt does not show up and everyone's super disappointed. She's like, what happened?
You know, I spent all this time doing this musical montage, you know how hard it is to pull those off
So anyways, she emails Brad Pitt and she goes, hey, I did everything he wanted
You didn't show up and Brad Pitt goes. Oh, I'm super sorry about that. Something came up. Something came up
So there's another hurricane. I had to go build houses in the middle of it. This is not a good charity
I should figure out something else
Tell you what do it again do this again
I will be there this time because we really need raise money for the charity
However, I need some money like cuz you know, it's like a union thing
I just can't show up places like when I go to the supermarket the cashier pays me
I need like I need an appearance fee. So you need you wire me some money
So you guys know where this is going you wire me some money and then I'll show up
You do all the marketing again. You do what you did before do the musical montage
You give me the money I'll show up and then you'll get paid back from the money we raise and all that stuff
And she's like, okay, that makes sense. It doesn't but features goes out nailing up signs on telephone poles and stuff like that
plastering flyers to the back of armadillos and rolling them down the street
She does the whole rigmarole all over again
Every layer is probably like 80% of the people are excited this time first time everyone was super excited this time people are like
Yeah, no, it's the big day. They have this big fundraiser and
80% of the people show up
Brad Pitt's a no-show. She's like, oh man now everyone super disappointed in her this happens
five times in total over the course of two years
Somebody convinced this woman that they were Brad Pitt. They were gonna come to her town
and she needs to basically get everyone in town together and
Brad Pitt wouldn't show up now the first from what I can gather
So she got ripped off a total of
$40,000
What I imagine I don't know if this is accurate because we don't have access to all the court transcripts
Yeah, it'll be hilarious when we do it
This is how I imagine it the first one was just a joke
The first one was just someone trying to see if a person would spend two months trying to
Convincing everyone Brad Pitt is going to show up
I figure like it was first the joke and then someone goes hey dude
You won't believe this this woman thought I was Brad Pitt and someone goes oh really and
They then took on the mantle then they put on their Brad Pitt mask and was like I'm gonna take this even further
I'm gonna get some money. I don't know they could have been built in her money out from the beginning
But over the course of two years
This trick worked five separate times. I would have loved to be there the fifth time
To see like you're in a giant arena
Everyone's expecting Brad Pitt to come in but at this point nobody in town believes Brad Pitt is actually gonna show up
That would have been hilarious to sit in an empty auditorium with like three other people
She didn't think it was funny. She's out $40,000. So she's suing Brad Pitt for a hundred thousand dollars
She's suing him and his charity. She said Brad Pitt defrauded me. He kept telling me he was gonna come to my town
I was sending him money and he never showed up. So I'm suing him
Brad Pitt if Brad Pitt's response to this is wait, what what's going on? Huh?
He goes I didn't know anything. I've never met this woman before in my life. I've never talked to her
I didn't know anything was going on until my people got like court paperwork
Like I have no idea what this is about and the lawyers are the ones who are saying we
This is great that this is now in the legal system
The lawyers have introduced the theory of quote fake Brad Pitt's
They believe there's multiple people out there impersonating Brad Pitt who were ripping this woman off and the woman's like no
It was Brad Pitt. You know like did you see him? Did you like meet him in person?
Did you ever like have a video conference call?
It was Brad Pitt and how dare you mr. Pitt for saying that we never met because you also
Said you were gonna marry me
At this point I can imagine the judge the bait lift everyone just kind of putting their head in their hands being like
Oh my god, you got you fell for two scams at the same time
You fell for the good old fashioned fake Brad Pitt scam and you fell for the marriage scam
She actually thought she was gonna marry this dude
I don't think that Brad Pitt was I mean listen. I think Brad Pitt has better things to do
At this time then to rip a woman off of 40 000 dollars
Although that would be hilarious
If you found out like Denzel washington
great actor
Great family man. He's also turns out that he loves running
Pyramid schemes in his spare time
If you found out that he owned a bunch of like juice bars
He's like, oh no, no, no you come under the juice bar and then you you buy a juice bar
And then the people who go into that juice bar they have to buy a juice bar. You can't lose money
Both of his fingers crossed me on his back. They're like, how do you run a juice bar?
Your hands are always behind your back. He's like, I'm Denzel Washington. I can do whatever I want.
Yeah, I guess that's true. That'd be hilarious to find out that one of the biggest celebrities
Is actually just constantly he's sitting he's putting malware on your computer because like oh thanks for calling Microsoft
I can see your computer's locked up and you're like, hey, wait, wait, aren't you the guy from seven?
He's like, oh, no, no, no, no, no. Yeah, can I get your credit card information?
I don't think this court case is going to go anywhere. However, I did want to highlight it one because it is hilarious
Two now the term fake Brad Pitt's is part of the American legal system
But three gun of liberty get your guns ready because we're going to turn the lights down a little bit
We're putting on our conspiracy caps. I made a joke
Probably about 10 episodes back
You guys remember this?
about the brads
There's a real offhand joke where I said there's a secret society of people named Brad and you can't convert
You can't change your name. You have to be born a brad
You can't just align yourselves with them. You only join this organization if you are born a brad. You got Brad Pitt
Bradley Cooper
Brad Paisley
the brad from
That guy the big old goofy guy on everyone lives Raymond and then um other brads
Out there. You see and you think you're Jason. You're like, you're just joking, right? You're just joking. That's how these conspiracies start, right?
That's how these conspiracies start. Everyone goes, oh man. He's just joking that guy that guy's constantly laughing on his podcast
He's making it up
Dude, I bet you you can follow the line back of brads
I bet you you could find brads in ancient Egypt brads of the Illuminati
So when we're looking at all these other groups
We're going, oh, it's them. It's them. It's them. There's really right right behind you right behind you
Is that big old lunkhead brad from everyone loves Raymond going like?
Oh Raymond everyone loves you
Because no one knows of the brads. You're like, what what how'd you get there?
And he disappears in a puff of smoke the brads bro and
I'll end the joke. Oh, no, it was not a joke. It's totally true. I'll end it with this
I actually looked up the meaning
I looked up the meaning of the name brad the name brad in English means
Broad clearing in the woods
Oh, that sounds like a place where secret societies hang out, right?
They don't hang out in like cluttered forests think about it when you if I told you to picture picture a bunch of witches in the woods
What did you picture? You pictured a clearing you pictured?
A broad clearing in the woods. That's where the druids hang out. That's where a secret society would hang out, right?
Their name literally means
meeting place of the satanic
And
And stay with me brad we're getting ready to delete the show
We're on to you and get this in welsh
the name brad
means treason
So it's like the welsh people were aware of this brad takeover
They knew that these guys were eventually going to make their move. So they declared them traitors
Can you imagine being welsh and finding out that your name is brad and they're like, hey dad
Uh, what what does my name mean and dad's like treason
You're gonna be a traitorous scum to the human race
Maybe the welsh knows something about the brad conspiracy. Maybe that's why the word rad is so popular nowadays in the year
So be on the lookout for anyone named brad and if you get an email from a guy named brad bit asking if he can come to your home
Don't do it. Actually, you know what do it do it do it because
So you'd give me more stuff to talk about on
I just I just read that article today and I was like just shaking my head
anyways
With the time we have left and talking about these two other stories, they're actually really cool
They're actually really really good stuff and I'm glad I've kind of packaged this all together because we're getting ready to end the season
So I wanted to cover a lot of really good stuff to finish this out strong gun of liberty. Let's hop in that dead rabbit durgible
We're gonna take a real quick trip to florida. We're specifically going to the florida everglade. So
We're taking that durgible up. I still got a couple armadillos on me
This story was actually recommended by benet. He actually went through a long time listening to the show went through and found pig
People in every single state in america. I think there was only three states that didn't have them
I wonder if there's one in alaska. He had gave me the list
He gave me this huge list and every show i'm gonna go through
That's what we're gonna pop around and check out here in the florida everglades where these
Squallies is what they're known as they're not known as pig people. It's not politically correct. They're like, sir
We are squallies. This is one of those interesting stories where we see real life and
fiction or possible fiction collide and thanks for the recommendation
In the florida and i got a lot of this information from the website phantoms and monsters as well
So i want to give them a shout out also
So in the florida everglades, there was actually this piece of land that was set aside for development because who doesn't want to live
In the florida everglades assuming you're not a swamp witch. I don't know who would want to live there
But they started to actually develop all of this property. They were calling it golden gate estates
So there's actually like some roads apparently and there's some houses that were built and then they just go
Why are we building them here? This is a horrible place. It stinks like a swamp
The developers like yeah, i should have visited this place. So it's been abandoned and now it's called alligator alley because there's just like
Alligators obviously a bunch of bears running around. I know there were bears in the swamp. How do they swim?
Panthers down there. That's pretty dope a bunch of hogs running around and the squallies and the squallies
So what the squallies are they're tiny little pig people
Well to be specific they're tiny little people with pig snouts. So I think everything else is normal about them
and at their peak
people believed there was about
Of these little squallies running around now. I don't know where they got their clothes
Maybe there are seamstresses and stuff like that. Maybe they all had like a class profession when they decided to mutate into a pig person
They're like, ah, I'm a blacksmith now
But apparently they had clothes and stuff like that and of course this is what's interesting because you have this is very typical for these urban legends
We have a location
That's remote and it's spooky because you see kind of a half developed area in the in the swamp
Then you have to fill it with your imagination. You have to fill it with some sort of population in this area
You came up with little pig people now you have to have an origin story
And we actually have a couple of those one of them is that there was a government experiment that went wrong
That that's one theory the government was trying to they're like, how do we build how do we build the perfect pig person?
I can't believe that the so it's our head of us on this
And so they are grabbing people and like taking pigs and just kind of pushing them together pushing them together until finally
They morphed into one
That's how genetics work during the cold war
The other theory is that they're a bunch of freaks and obviously freaks, but inbred freaks
So like people are banging each other and then like they're banging people are too closely related to them
And this keeps going on and on and on eventually a pig person pops out and then that that's also
Works during the cold war pig people are then banging each other and then that only begets more pig people until eventually
You have a population of the squalys some people believe there's still a bunch of squalys out there
Again, this is an urban legend that you would pass around high schools elementary schools
Brothers would tell their younger siblings to scare them. Oh, yeah, I saw I saw squally the other day
It looked just like you. I don't look like a pig person
You know all that stuff all that teasing and then of course you have the legend of the guardian
You have someone looking out for him
There's oh supposedly an old man out there with a shotgun that chases people on
So that's why when you go to see the squalys you don't run into them
You can be like, oh, maybe the guardian like made him go away or something
Maybe the cardy was having a pork roast party
Maybe seen a bunch of pulled porky adult squalys. Who knows?
But you have these these are very very typical parts of the legend and then you have the one piece of the story
Then you have a police report
so supposedly back in 2011 so
Very very recent as far as urban legends goes. This is june 14th, 2011. There was a guy named james scarborough
He's riding his motorcycle down the floor to Everglades apparently it's a hydrofoil
And he wrecks it probably because he's driving it through the swamp
But he wrecks it and the police show up and they're like
Hey, dude, what is going on? Why are you like just laying there underneath your motorcycle and he goes?
I'm sure you might have told that he laid there the whole time. He's like, oh, this is kind of comfortable
Hot exhaust right on his belly. He said he was driving on the road. Yeah
and a boogie man
Jumped out at him quote unquote boogie man. The cops are looking at each other. They're like
I told you
Cops like I shut up mark boogie man is not real
But he said the boogie man jumped down in front of him and he wrecked his bike
So he's in the general vicinity of this and people go
Was it a really a little little pick person? Was it a squally?
Is that what he actually saw that got in front of the motorcycle? So you have that police report
Also, apparently in the police report the police report. He smelled of alcohol
So whether it was a boogie man or just he was inebriated. He's like, oh, I'm trapped underneath my motorcycle cops
He sees the cops cars coming up. He's like come up with the story come up with the story real real quick
He's like, aha the boogie man that'll get me out of trouble
This is all the hallmarks of a classic
urban legend a contained
Urban legend. This isn't something that you would hear about in romania or brazil
But you would be very familiar with it if you lived in the florida everglades in that area
Just the same thing if you lived in brazil or romania, they
There would be cities in those countries that would have very contained
Little urban legends like that and we got one more to check out. It's another recommendation gun of liberty fire up that carboner copter
We are headed up to canada
We're headed to huntington that is in mont reggae
kubeck
Canada it's a small town as of 2016. They only had about 2400 people
So it's a small town, but it has a legend very much like the squally
This one was actually shared with me his personal story
From a patreon supporter named dave. So we're gonna wave to dave. He's kind of hanging out there
He's eating some canadian cheetos and we're like, hey, what's up, bro? He's talking with his mouth full
We're like, okay, you can wait till you know what the cheetos, bro
He actually has given me a bunch of video games on steam too. So I appreciate that as well. I'm gonna play some on my vacation
Takes a huge star. He's he swallows his food and he starts talking to us. He tells us this story
Really interesting story
Dave tells this story. So he went to high school about 50 miles away from huntington
He's 50 miles away. He's in high school and one of his buddy starts talking about
The zulus. He's like what?
But he's like, oh, dude, you haven't heard about the zulus. He's like, no, I don't
What are you talking about? I've heard of zulus. I know of the zulu empire, but
Why are you bringing them up? He goes, no, no, no, no, no, not those zulus the zulus in huntington
And davinus friends are like, what what are you just just to get to the point?
We have no idea what you're talking about and their friend
Tells this story about how in huntington on the outskirts of town
There's a group of humans, but are they human the friend posited and paused a little too long. He says
They have all white skin
with
White hair. It's falling out. Some of them don't have any hair at all
You're thinking albinos. He's like, no, no, no. These are zulus, man
They're completely white
They're completely bald. They have no eyebrows. They don't even have eyelashes
Their teeth are crooked
Jagged in each direction. They stare at you with bluish gray eyes
You're like, you're just describing an albino, right? It's like, no, no, no, they have pink eyes and
Here's the most odd thing about the zulus
They have no fingernails
You're like, what that is kind of a weird combination of details like he's like, no, no, no, no, I'm not even done
And then he adds because that's just like a physical abnormality. He goes, no, they're actually incredibly vicious as well
Inbred hillbillies is what I heard
Hillbillies in Canada. I guess they have them up there too
They're banging each other. See?
Yeah, I know what inbred means dude. He's like, okay, I'm about to pull out a chart
He goes these dudes. They're banging each other and they're having more of these little freakish zulu babies
And and Dave thought this was one of the dumbest things. He was just laughed. He's like, what?
Because we've all heard these urban legends growing up
But usually we hear when we're like eight or nine don't go down the tunnel. That's where pennywise lives
You don't say that to a 20 year old. They're like, gulp. Oh, no. I'm not going down the tunnel
You hear that when you're kids and there's only 50 miles away. So Dave's like, what? No, I don't know
And he said that that became a running joke with him and his friends
They'd make fun of the idea of these pale inbred hillbillies
running around
And kind of make fun of the friend at the same time for believing it. No, no, they're real. They're real
It's getting dragged into the bush by bunch of zulus
He doesn't really think about it over time and five years later
He's in college and the teacher is setting everyone up with their steady buddy
And it's all random. You can pick to someone he meets this guy
He's super and he got one of the nicest guys you could ever meet this guy was super dope
Hella chill and we're sitting there talking and we're getting you know, building the report doing notes and all that stuff
He goes and then I he goes. I don't really he looked a little pale, but I really think anything of it
When I got home a little light bulb being pops up. He goes wait a second
He was pale
He didn't have a lot of hair. He didn't have any eyebrows
He didn't have any fingernails either
So he's thinking listen again
The guy in college was obviously not an inbred cannibal freak wasn't trying to eat him
They weren't in cooking class. He's like oh, this this is my favorite class. Everyone looks so delicious
This is super nice guy
He goes people have albinism and things like that
But it sparks him in his head and he begins to do research
Which he didn't do when he was in high school and even if he had done it in high school
He most likely wouldn't have found anything
Because what he found was an article written
In the kubek newspaper called the myth of the zulus of huntington
And it was a full out investigation
Into this group. It was written by marco forrier
And these people are 100 real. They are not inbred. They are not
Vicious cannibals. I kept adding the cannibal part. He never said anything about cannibals. They are not inbreds. They are not vicious
They were a very very fascinating
story of
Bigotry. What happened was they believe that a french settler when he's coming over to the region
Carried a gene that causes something known as
Closed in syndrome and it is all of the physical markers
That dave described all you don't have fingernails
Hairs missing all that stuff some of them have a little more hair than others
But it is 100 a very real genetic misfire
It's extremely rare, but it is genetic
And what would happen is and it's funny because all the time we talk about urban legends
And origins and how these things work take that template even take the template for the squallies and we can put it over this one
We can see how the legend is so close to the reality. What happened was you had these people who were born with this
Like 150 years ago and they were ostracized
And then someone else who was still in that family was ostracized and over time those people
I don't know. They're not inbred. They're not inbred, but they had a distinct ancestor
But if someone with claustin syndrome has a child with someone else with claustin syndrome
There's a one and two chance the child will have claustin syndrome and because these people were purged from society
They could only really have sex with other people with this disease
They were pushed to a place called the back town
It was between two railroad tracks in huntington
If you had claustin syndrome
You lived in the back town. Your neighbors had claustin syndrome. Your friends had claustin syndrome
So when you got older your mate
Had claustin syndrome
The people in huntington would not let you work in any job that required you to be in the public
There's one kid goes a lot of them ended up doing it work
Because one kid goes I always grew up. I wanted to work at a gas station. I always thought that'd be so fun
Here I am sitting sitting behind a computer making 50 000 a year. Oh no, but you know what I mean? Like people have different dreams
I love working retail. I love working retail of walking into the place and organizing all the
The merchant dot I love it. I love every aspect of working retail
That was his dream, but there he was like I knew as I got older
There was no way I could work with the public and he goes I'm really one of the lucky ones a lot of people with this
They just became drug addicts
They got spit on all the time the police used to come into this neighborhood just knock down doors
because they could
Other people in town would say I remember when the who didn't have claustin syndrome
They go oh, I remember like on sundays my dad would get us all in the car. We drive to the back town
Drive through and view all these freaks
So in the town itself it was a knowing that these people existed, but as you got further out from huntington
Yeah, no idea and and pre internet pre anyone really researching this stuff. It was just a local story
Dave heard it and didn't believe it if there was no corresponding like there was no article for that
Dave would have just went on thinking that even that guy wouldn't have been like, hey, you're not one of those zulus
Are you you just thought oh this guy has
Albinism and if I told you that story the first part of that story about the zulus
Like I told the story of the squallies
We'd go oh another weird urban legend a bunch of inbred freaks running around nowadays
They've actually come a long way
No, no, that's not fair to say nowadays
Society has come a long way into just accepting them for what they are
Because for the longest time they were considered to be the way they were because they were
Syphilitic they had syphilis
So you don't want to be anywhere near them. You definitely don't want to date them. So they end up dating each other
Nowadays people go at this just some sort of medical quirk. It's a genetic quirk. We know these things happen
And people say you know the kids today now because they would basically get beat up at school nowadays
They go yeah, I get teased every once in a while. It's not as bad as my parents had it
I heard my parents, you know looking them over there. He's not just doing heroin now
That's my dad because they had a really rough go at it. You couldn't work
You got spin on every time you walked outside. You got people
50 miles away talking about you eating other people
It's an interesting story and thanks day for sharing that with us
It's an interesting story because it carries all the hallmarks of an urban legend and it's true
There's obviously the embellishments. They weren't vicious freaks. They weren't running around eating people. That was my own embellishment
They didn't have syphilis. They are more than capable of
integrating with society with society that held their hand that would say no
Because they believe those rumors about them
Dave who heard the story and didn't really
Believe it. He thought it was fake when he came face to face with one. It didn't even cross his mind
But what if Dave's friend had met that guy?
Oh my god, you're one of those
They're different reaction to that
And stories like this really make us have to take another look at urban legends
How many times do we hear of these stories and go? Ah, I can't be true. Aren't you big people in florida?
But there probably was
A at least a a kernel of truth to that there may have been a disfigured man or a disfigured family
out there
And one sighting became five and then five became 20 and then 20 became 50 and so on and so forth
But a lot of these urban legends have some
Grain of truth in them, but no one expects to go to college and meet one of them
So the next time you're driving in the middle of nowhere
Remember that the pig people could be real
The next time you're getting into your car late at night
Just remember there really may be a serial killer in the back seat
and know that
When you shut that bathroom light off before you leave the bathroom
And there's that quick glimmer
Of something in your mirror that could be bloody mary
Waiting to prove herself to you
Yes, I did just come here bloody married to a group of people living in canada, but you know what I mean
Urban legends are so easily dismissed as jokes to the point that you can laugh in someone's face when they tell you something
But they may be right
They may get the facts wrong, but the truth is often interwoven
into fiction
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]