in the city of Prague during World War II, was a real-life superhero fighting the Nazis.
And then we traveled to America to take a look at one of our most famous real-life superheroes,
Phoenix Jones, who will profile his rise and his fall today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. You're like, "Jason,
what's up with your voice?" Well, I still have this sinus infection. I'm still super congested up in
my nose. You guys are saying, you sound more like a muppet than you normally do. Hey, I know.
What are you gonna do? It's a daily show and I don't want to miss episodes just because I sound
super congested. But other than this sinus infection going on, I'm totally healthy.
Guys, don't be worried. I'm self-isolated. I'm doing really good. So I hope you guys are good as
well. Let's go ahead and get started with today's episode. We got a lot of stuff to cover here.
First off, let's hop on the Carpenter copter. We're headed to Czechoslovakia, the country somewhere
in Eastern Europe. We're flying over and as we're going over to Czechoslovakia, does that
country still even exist? Oh, that's Yugoslavia. That disappeared. And we're also going back in
time to World War II. So not a high point for Eastern Europe. There weren't many, to be honest.
It seems that it's always been kind of a rough go over there. You had territorial warlords for
the longest time and then things kind of got settled. And then Hitler came in and took over
much stuff, started executing people. And then the saviors, the glorious Soviet Empire, saved them
from the Nazis. People were like, "Yay, we're free." And the Soviets are like, "Mmm-mm, that's what
you thought." And they put up the iron curtain for about 50 years and now we are here today,
Czechoslovakia. But we're not here today. We are in World War II and we're in the streets of Prague.
There's Nazis walking down the street doing Nazi stuff, just generally being a pain to the
Czechoslovakian citizens. And you also have Czechoslovakians who are informants, who are turncoats,
working with the Nazis because they're like, "Oh yeah, I want some of that sweet, sweet Nazi power."
"I'm going to turn in my own people for minor infractions." But there's someone in the shadows
in the streets of Prague. A man watching, waiting. He doesn't have to wait. There's
evil around every corner. It basically would be the best place to be a vigilante because basically
you're like, "You wouldn't need a bat signal. There's crime everywhere. You have Nazis and
collaborators on every single street corner." So, I mean, you just walk down the street and just
start punching people. You're going to hit a Nazi eventually. Anyways, this guy springs into action.
"Baboying." Now, that wasn't a turn of phrase. "Baboying." A man jumps out of the shadow, super high,
20, 30 feet. "Baboying." And lands right behind a Nazi, punches him in the back of the neck. "Oi,
my neck." Bounce away. Sees two collaborators being like, "Who should we rat on next?" "Oh,
that girl turned me down for a date. We should say that she's hiding some Jews in her." "Baboying."
The dude bounces on top of his head multiple times, pushes him into the dirt. The other
collaborator runs away. "Baboying, not for long." So, he just does this. So, just imagine for the
course of World War II, this dude was jumping on people. Now, this guy, his name is Parak,
aka the "Spring Man" or "The Springer," is what his name means. And throughout World War II,
there was rumors of an event. So, this is, he basically has two origin stories, okay? Some people
swear that this guy's real. People nowadays go, "It's an urban legend," because when they look in
Nazi and police reports, there's no men, which were the same thing back then, because the police
were the collaborators. There was no reports of a man with springs on his feet, "Baboying" all
over the city, stopping crime. To be fair, I wouldn't put that down in a report. I mean,
it's Nazi control territory, right? You're not going to be like, "Um, I lost those people. I was
supposed to kidnap because a man baboing them on my head." Like, you're not going to put that. You're
just going to be like, "Oh, they ran away." They just dissolved. They just dissolved right in front
of me. You're not going to put that there's a superhero chasing you down the street. Anyways,
some people swear this guy's real. Other people think it was just a legend, but he has two origin
stories. One, there was an inventor who was like, "How do I fight crime? I'm just a lowly inventor.
I know." And he put, "Oh, God, look at this chase." He's an inventor. He puts springs on his shoes.
Some people specifically say they're springs from a couch, which I've never met a couch that
boing-y, because apparently he could jump over rail cars, which, okay, that's a bad image. When
we're talking about the Holocaust, we're talking about World War II. Can they come on? He's just
bouncing over trains. He doesn't stop them. They keep head at east. He's just bouncing over them.
They could have come up with a better image for something that's bouncing over a building,
perhaps. But anyways, an origin story about a guy who put springs on his shoes. The reason why,
pardon me, thinks this is real. You're like, "Jason, you can't actually believe that a guy can bounce
over structures." Well, we can talk about physics later. The reason why I think this might be true,
because that's such a stupid power, right? Like, if I was making up a power, it would be he could
turn invisible, or he could like transform himself into, like, I don't know, anything really. You
don't need to have a limit on that. If you're making it up, he can transform himself into, like,
a he-man. And he's ripping Nazis in half and stuff like that. If you're making it up, why do you
just give him this power to jump really high with springs on his feet? Makes me think it might be
true. But when folklorists look at this, because what happened was, whether or not the police were
writing this down, everyone believed in Prague believed in Patar, everybody. And when anything
went wrong, they blamed it on him, like a ammunition truck explodes, or it was Patar. I'm walking down
the street and all my groceries fall out of my hand. It was Patar. When folklorists look back on this,
they go, "We see stories of a springing man in Prague all the way back to, like, the 1890s,
almost a contemporary to Spring Hill Jack in England." What's interesting about that is Spring
Hill Jack, it was kind of like a, he was sexually molesting women. They leave that part out of a
lot of the monster books for kids. That's the first time I ever heard about Spring Hill Jack.
And there's a little monster toy line. It was like, remember those muscle characters,
little rubbery muscle guys? They had a toy line like that, but they were all classic monsters.
And I remember one of the first ones I got was Spring Hill Jack. And it was like,
"This menacing man jumps over buildings!" And then, maybe about a year and a half ago,
I was doing research for a show and he didn't jump over buildings. He jumped into buildings and
sexually assaulted the women inside. Spring Hill Jack, he was, he's known for jumping everywhere,
but when you look into the actual myth, he was constantly assaulting women, pinching their butts
at the least. So when I saw this ago, that's weird. Like, one, it's weird that you have two
bouncing people, but if this guy was a contemporary of Spring Hill Jack in the 1890s, why did he become
a hero character in the 1940s? But this is why. He wasn't a hero character in the 1940s, actually.
So what happened? This is from what they can gather, because part of the problem is that
this guy was totally believed in during World War II. People had heard stories about him before,
but during World War II, you had all of these things happening. People were blaming
Patar. And then when the Soviets freed, quote unquote, freed Prague and took over,
the legend of Patar was put to rest. You can't have this guy jumping around, or maybe he was
actually arrested by the KGB, or maybe he joined the KGB, who knows. But the Soviet Union said,
"No more stories about Patar." So it wasn't until the fall of the Iron Curtain where you had people
going back and researching this stuff and going like, "Well, there's a lot of stuff about this,
but there's not a lot of real documents because they were suppressed for so long." The Nazis
didn't want to hear about it. People were afraid to go to work during World War II. People blamed
every problem on Patar. And then the Soviets took over. They didn't want to hear about it either.
There's a really cool cartoon, and I actually included it in the show notes. It's called
A Spring Man in the SS, is what it's called. It's in the show notes. Check it out. It's like 14
minutes long. It's kind of a really cool little cartoon that talks about it. It has the Spring Man.
It's just a chimney sweep, which was another origin story, but that didn't really make any
sense. This is the weird thing. So like I said, you had stories of him back in the 1890s, right?
And then you had stories of him in World War II. And today he's celebrated as a war hero,
fighting the Nazis. And he has cartoons and theater based on a bunch of books coming out of
Czechoslovakia. It's considered Czechoslovakia's only superhero. But here's the weird part. So he
does show up. These are the things that everyone agrees on. He shows up during World War II mostly,
bounces around on people, and fights the Nazis towards the end of the war. For the first
couple years, and the reason why people were so afraid of him and people wouldn't go out at night,
and the Nazis were like, "Dude, we need you to build these bullets for us. We need this
cheap slave labor." And people were like, "No, I don't want to leave my house and watch your factory,
because this guy is going to bounce on top of me." The people of Prague, for the first couple
years of the war, did not seem as a hero. He was raping and murdering people. He would bounce out
of the shadows and rape you, bounce out of the shadows and murder you, or both. And the Nazis
were like, "That's impossible." And the citizens were like, "Who is raping and murdering us?
Like, why can't you catch this guy?" And that people refused to work. And at some point,
he became a hero, he became a hero figure versus not being a villain anymore. What
made that change? At what point were you like, "Oh, that mythological figure we made up. Yeah,
now he's a good guy." Now, it would be the equivalent of if all of a sudden, everyone agreed that the
boogeyman was actually like an undercover cop. And he was like hiding in the shadows, he started
arresting criminals. He'd be like, "Wait, no, no, no, I forgot the boogeyman. He hit him on my bed
and like ate my dog. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
so that's sad, but that was, I read a lot of articles on this and it was only one version. The other version is that, he and his buddy were out at a bar and his buddy got in a fight and Phoenix Jones like didn't know what to do so he threw on a ski mask and jumped around the corner and quote made a commotion until the people left and the cop showed up or something like that.
And I'm thinking, wait a second, so you're, you're a fighter, he is a fighter, like we know that, we do know his record because he did actually compete in a lot of MMA stuff.
He is a fighter, but your buddy's getting beat up, you take the time to run around the corner.
Do you just have a ski mask on you? Was there one in the garbage can? And then come back and the guys are already left anyways and you're like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Do you just have a ski mask on you, was there one in the garbage can, then come back and the guys are already left anyways and you're like, oh, and then there's a version of that story where his friend had a permanent facial injury. Come on, man, like what, like something like that is generally reported in all the articles.
His friend was left with a horrible injury and every time Phoenix Jones looked at his friend he thought, somebody has to do something, so he put on a costume.
Whatever the case, both of those stories supposedly happened, his son slipped on some glass, got cut up, his son became his own superhero glass boy that wherever he went, he was, that was his superpower, was slipping on glass, he was like Iceman, he's like, I'll get down from this cliff real fast, he like throws glass in front of him and like slides everywhere.
Wheeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
He's on a rooftop, his very first time fighting crime, he's staying on a rooftop wearing a tuxedo underneath was his spandex uniform. I don't know why the tuxedo either, I don't know why a tuxedo either, but anyways, he's on the rooftop and his idea was to rip off the tuxedo and then run around the spandex.
He sees a mugging and he's like, oh, now I gotta get down there and according to him it took him five minutes to get down off the building and then he runs over and the woman had already been mugged and she's like, what are you doing?
You look like Count Chocula here, like that's, the actual quote is, well that's pretty close actually, the actual quote is quote, this is what she said, what are you doing?
He already left, you look like Count Chocula, you look stupid, I don't believe that happened, like I don't believe, I don't believe that she's dropping pop culture references after being mugged.
What do you mean you look like Thomas the Tank Engine but without the Thomas or the Tank Engine?
You look like nothing because you're a big old loser, I don't believe that story.
I do believe he's probably running around in tuxedo, I do believe that he probably saw him mugging, he couldn't stop but I don't think she turned around with a witty one liner, but anyways, anyways, so that happened according to him.
That was back in 2009, he continues fighting crime, quote unquote, in 2011 the first time that he got in the news was some guy's car was getting stolen, Phoenix Jones shows up.
At this point, at a certain point he starts wearing body armor, he has like ballistic armor, he has his own private doctor, so at one point he got stabbed, this is written in this article, he gets stabbed, right?
And they said, "Jones fixed his suit up and then got treated by his private doctor."
And I'm thinking, everyone has a private, I have a private doctor, everyone has a private doctor.
When I go to the doctor, there's not four other people sitting in the room with me, they try to make it sound like he went to go see Alfred.
Your private doctor is your doctor that you pay for, right?
I don't think this guy has a do- just I definitely think the doctor does, the doctor's like, oh man, hope Phoenix Jones gets shot tonight, I really need to make a car payment, uh.
Everyone has a private doctor, journalist.
You're trying to make it sound like he basically is a superhero.
I mean, he's stopping crime, that's great.
That's really good.
But, I also, I'm super suspicious about a lot of the stuff, a lot of the adventures that you guys are having.
Where I grew up, you would watch people beat each other up and you'd be like, okay, do you want to keep sitting in this Burger King or should we leave?
Because we're not getting in the middle of that.
Like, the only time you would get in the middle, and you rarely see this, I'm trying to think of a time that I'd seen this, the only time you'd ever get in the middle of a fight,
is when it was someone who was much bigger than the other person.
And even then, it was like, I remember once I came across the fight, and it was between a guy who was, I don't know, a 200 pound weightlifter out of prison,
and his 19, 18 year old daughter, and he was throttling her.
And I just walked up and I was like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
And what I did was I just put my hands on his shoulders.
I was like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I knew both of them.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, man, come on, come on, come on.
He let her go.
Put my hands on him to let him know I'm here, I'm standing behind you.
You're overreacting.
Uh-uh, no, that's-- uh-uh.
I didn't jump in the middle of them and go, stop, evil doer, because now I'm escalating it.
Perfect example, one day Phoenix Jones was walking down the street, and he saw two men arguing, and he did jump in the middle of them.
And one of them got him in a headlock, and the other guy pulled out a gun and broke his nose, started pistol whipping him in the face.
And then they both left.
So you don't really jump in the middle of fights, it's super not smart.
That's why domestic violence incidents are so dangerous for cops.
I made an offhand reference to that in the last episode.
I was like, cops hate doing those.
Because what happens is you go up, knock on the door, the cops come in, guys fight and the wife, the wife's fighting the husband, you start to separate them, and then they're like, get off my wife, and now you're fighting two people at once.
They hate doing domestic violence stuff.
So anyways, I mean, like, yeah, I think it's cool to fight crime, but I don't think it's feasible in that way.
I think that's one of the follies of youth.
I don't know how many of these real life superheroes exist in their 40s and their 50s, because as you get older, you go, I'll just make a phone call to the police.
Or I'll just, just don't, I mean, you can give sandwiches out to anybody.
Maybe also, that's the weird thing about it.
There seems to be a weird egotistical thing about this.
Because can't you just hand out sandwiches to the police?
Not the police, I don't need sandwiches.
Can't you just hand out sandwiches to the homeless people anyways?
Why do you need the costume?
But, like Bane once said, nobody cared about me until I wore the mask.
If Phoenix Jones was just out doing, uh, handing out sandwiches and stuff like that, would anyone have paid attention to him?
Now, Phoenix Jones actually has retired now.
He's retired.
He was on a podcast called the Northwest Nerd podcast, NW Nerd podcast.
And he gives this quote, kind of heartbreaking.
We've had a lot of fun at this dude's expense.
We have a quote, this is in March of 2019.
Quote, "I've seen what people do to each other, and I live with it every day.
Every day I live with horrible, horrible things.
And I think to myself, apparently, apparently he's Barack Obama now.
And I think to myself, I made a difference.
But I didn't make a difference.
It didn't make a difference.
The difference was supposed to be the people who saw a superhero
being inspired to not act this way anymore.
We have not gotten that lesson.
We didn't get it at all.
The shots, the stabbings, the bullets.
It wasn't worth it.
No one got it.
Maybe I stopped an individual situation, but people were supposed to get better.
So he was wearing a suit as a symbol.
He was wearing a suit to inspire the population of Seattle and hopefully the world.
Let's see this man.
He fought crime from 2009 to 2019.
Ton of stuff.
He'd pop up in the media every once in a while for being one sort of crazy antichrist or another.
He says that he stopped a bunch of people from blowing up city hall in Seattle.
Again, I don't believe that.
I don't believe that's true.
I believe that he was at a May Day protest.
Apparently May, you're like, "That was just a poignant."
How do you pronounce that?
That was such a great moment.
Now you're back to making fun of this guy.
And you can't pronounce poignant.
But anyways, on May 1st, 2012, Phoenix Jones, L. Calbrero, and Midnight Jack
were undercover at a Black Block protest.
"Raw, hate the U.S. Hate the U.S. Down with banks."
And the superheroes are undercover and they hear some guys being like,
"Hey, you got the explosives.
You're, yep, right here, right here in this bag.
It's full of dynamite and a bunch of other, of comical bombs.
There's a bomb with a giant fuse out of it.
This is bomb on it.
Good.
Now let's just get these to city hall and blow it up."
Then everyone will agree with our anarchist ways.
That's the best way to achieve people to come to our point of view.
Terrorism.
Phoenix Jones, L. Calbrero, and Midnight Jack look at each other.
They go and they tell the cops, "Hey, those guys are going to blow up city hall."
And the cops refuse to stop it.
So the trio of heroes have to beat them to city hall and while they're there,
they start getting beat up and apparently one of them, he denies this, but
one of the superheroes sprayed the protesters with pepper spray and they prevented,
they prevented the bombing.
What I think happened was some knuckleheads in the crowd.
You always get some weirdos like, "You know what'd be awesome, dude?
You know, to really show them if we blew up that building and someone else being like, "Yeah."
And I know that guy's just running his mouth.
Most people know they're just running their mouth.
And that's why if they went to the cops and said, "Hey, this guy's talking about blowing up a building."
"Oh yeah, whatever."
I don't think they actually had comically sized bombs on them.
And the police refuse to do nothing.
The police are part of the plan.
They're like, "Oh yes, only we had the guts to blow up the Capitol, but these black block protesters,
they will do it."
I don't believe that story.
I believe that they overheard someone threatening to blow something up.
I.e., they're on any college campus.
Right?
There's always radicals on every level, basically anywhere young people gather.
You're going to get people talking about blowing up this or blowing up them.
So, you're like, "Jason, where do you hang out?"
"Where are you going?"
This are like bomb threats.
It's no big deal.
What?
They're threatening to blow that stuff up?
I don't care.
They're just smoldering ruins all behind me.
Like fake news.
Uh-uh-uh.
Yes, I'll hold this bag of bombs that are lit.
What?
No.
But anyways, I've heard tons of weirdo threats like that.
Anyways, so he retires, March 2019.
And I hope you don't.
I hope you guys don't.
I kind of like Phoenix Shows, right?
Like, I'm making fun of all this stuff, but at the same time, I admire him.
I know the episode, it seems to be a little weird,
because I'm like totally making fun of this guy, but I get where his heart is at.
Like I said, if I was younger and wasn't as like realizing how the world worked,
if I was much younger, and I didn't understand logic,
I would also want to go out to fight crime.
But it's just, you can't really do that.
I think, I've always said this,
you can't save the world, but you can save the people in it.
You can affect lives one at a time.
Handing out food to the homeless, that's awesome.
Not now.
Don't do it now.
Stay inside.
Don't do any of this stuff now.
But when things, when this is all over, community service is great.
Starting your own community service is totally fine too.
If there's like groups in the area, you don't necessarily want to work with them.
There's tons of stuff you can do.
I totally agree with that.
And I enjoy that part of it.
At the same time, you can, you, I think you'd be more effective working with a drug prevention
program with middle school students and high school students,
then you would be beating up a drug dealer,
because then the other drug dealer's going to be like,
"Great, now my territory has expanded because you be this guy."
So, or just become a cop or a judge or a lawyer or anything.
There's a lot of different ways you can do this without putting on a mask.
But he retires in 2019.
Now that all the superheroes are gone in Seattle,
there's whispers of a super criminal in the city.
An unstoppable drug dealer.
So maybe these superheroes were actually doing some good.
Because now you have a drug dealer who's moving a lot of product.
There's a drug dealer operating in Seattle that the police didn't even know about.
They know drugs are being sold.
Obviously, that's part of their job, not selling the drugs.
But part of their job will sum up the cops might, but part of their job is to track and stop drug
dealers.
So they know drugs are coming through.
But finally, this informant, this confidential informant for the police goes,
"I'm surprised that nobody has caught this drug dealer yet."
The cops are like, "What drug dealer?"
And they're like, "There's a really big drug dealer operating in Seattle."
You guys don't even know about it.
Police are like, "Well, okay, Einstein, don't leave us in suspense.
You're an informant.
You're supposed to inform us.
Go try to be dramatic."
And the informant goes, "One of the biggest drug dealers that is out right now that you can't catch
is Phoenix Jones."
Police begin an investigation of Phoenix Jones.
Just months after announcing his retirement, he retires in March of 2019.
By November, the police are setting up deals online to buy Mali or MDMA.
But they can't catch him.
He's slick.
They're making these deals.
And when he makes an appointment to show up in the spot to move the product, he's not there.
He's at a different spot.
The drops are changing.
Everything is constantly moving.
It takes three months of them tracking him down before they finally arrest the former
superhero Phoenix Jones with four grams of cocaine and 31 grams of an unknown white powdery substance.
I mean, it's probably not confectionary sugar, right?
It's most likely the MDMA.
They caught him with distribution.
They're charging him with drug dealing, all of this stuff.
And at his bail hearing, the police are like, "Don't do not let this guy out on bail."
And the judge let him out on bail.
So he's walking free.
Now he's probably self-quarantined now, but that is the story of Phoenix Jones.
A man whose broken window caused him to wage a one-man war on crime for 10 years.
And then for a couple years, he was with other people.
But you get the point.
The dark night, you guys knew I was going to say this.
The dark night had that great quote, "You either die the hero or live long enough to see yourself become the villain."
That fits this perfectly.
A man who risked his life.
And he could pronounce that word correctly.
He did get stabbed.
He did get shot.
He went to his private doctor.
He went to his private doctor who worked at Kaiser.
Man who put his life on the line.
To save us.
Us homo sapiens.
Us normal people.
And in the end, he became disillusioned with the hero thing.
For 10 years, he put on that costume.
For 10 years, he went out and saved people.
And each night, as the sun was rising, that's the morning.
Each morning, when the sun was rising, he was headed back to his secret headquarters.
A house that he lived in with his family.
Every morning, he thought, "I made a difference tonight.
I became a symbol.
People will change, but for 10 years the sun rose and the sun set.
And nothing changed.
The people of Seattle continued to use drugs, to beat each other up.
To beat him up.
That never changed either.
10 years, he became disillusioned and said enough.
Tired of being a symbol.
Tired of risking my life.
It's time to put away the cowl.
Become a citizen.
And then become a drug dealer.
And then he became part of the problem.
And every morning, as he walked back to his house.
A pocket full of cash.
The other pocket empty because there were huge, sweet drugs in it.
He thought, "I couldn't be a symbol of hope.
So I will be the problem.
I will be the drug dealer.
I will make money for me.
Nothing else matters.
Just me.
How the mighty have fallen.
From hero to zero.
From Phoenix Jones, the superhero.
To Benjamin...
This is his real name.
From Phoenix Jones.
To Benjamin John Francis.
From Benjamin John Francis Fodor.
From the lofty superhero name of Phoenix Jones.
To Man On Trial Benjamin John Francis Fodor.
We can't choose fate.
Some people are fated to be successful.
Some people are fated to slip and fall on glass.
But it's the things we do with what fate gives us.
That either makes us a survivor.
Or makes us become disillusioned, quit.
And become the very thing you've always fought against.
Which to me is the greatest tragedy of all.
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
And DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listen to it today.
Stay safe, stay healthy, and I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Love you guys.
[Music]
[MUSIC]