A series of strange letters leads us into the world of gang stalking, and then we take
a look at a small race of cannibal humanoids that live in the woods.
They have a terrifying reputation, but their name is anything but terrifying.
Today we take a look at the melon heads on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot to get through today, so we're going to go ahead and get started.
Now, so the first story we're going to look at, the first way we're going to start off
the first story comes from the conspiracy iceberg.
It's about middle tier in the conspiracy iceberg.
We got to go to Jolly Old England, so let's hop in the carpenter copter.
It's fired up.
It's me hitting switches.
I always think it's amazing.
When you look at a helicopter in real life, you just see the circle because the rotors
are, but when you film a helicopter, sometimes the rotors look like they're moving real slow.
It's kind of weird looking.
But anyway, so we're in the carpenter copter.
We're flying over England right now.
It's funny because I always refer to England as like it's just one big city, but that's
because I don't know any better.
Wait, no, England is the city.
Wait, no, is England the country?
Oh, London is the city.
Anyways, I don't know what city this takes place in, so we're just going to hover over
England until we see a proper young gentleman go to retrieve his mail.
This chap, this Jolly Old chap, his name is Trevor Silverwood.
He's actually a member of parliament, so he's pretty high up in the government, equivalent
of the US Senate.
So Trevor is out sipping his tea, he's wiping little crumpet crumbs off of his tie.
He's a very dapper man.
And he goes to his mailbox.
We see him retrieve a letter.
We're looking overhead.
He doesn't look up.
He doesn't hear the incredibly noisy and loud helicopter above him, but he gets a letter.
He looks at it and we just see him kind of slump as he opens it up.
He knows what the letter is going to say.
It's always a little crazy, it's always a little weird, and it is always correct.
From 1969 to 1979, Trevor Silverwood would get letters delivered to him.
He'd open it up and it would say, "Hey, Trevor, you had a great day yesterday, didn't you?
I saw you walking down the street in your gray P-coat, your black shoes.
You seemed like you were a man on a mission.
Hope you had fun.
See you again."
There was never a signature except for a little drawing of the saint, a little stickman with
the halo over his head.
It was a television show around the time.
Trevor Silverwood would get letters explaining what he wore the previous day, or in the
past, because some of the letters take a while together, but they would explain what he was
wearing, what he was doing, who he was with.
His letters were postmarked from all over the world.
He would get a letter from India saying, "Nice shoes the other day.
Look like you polished them.
Look like you were really trying to set some sort of fashion trend, Mr. Silverwood."
And of course, after the first couple of letters, he ends up getting the police involved.
They could never figure it out.
What they think was someone was spying on him in England, and then they would mail the
letter to an accomplice in another country who would then mail it back.
Sometimes the letters came from his neighborhood.
Not all the letters came from foreign countries, but they could never track down who it was.
Now this story was first told in this book called Truly Bizarre, which was published in
1979, and they were stating he was still receiving the letters at the time the book was being
published.
And this has always been kind of a quirky conspiracy.
And there was a forum where they were talking about the strange letters.
That's what it's known as, the strange letters, and that's how it's listed on the conspiracy
theory iceberg.
There was a forum talking about how crazy it was that no one could ever figure it out,
and in 2011, someone claiming to be Trevor Silverwood's son went onto the forum.
Because you know, you Google your dad, you Google your name.
It's not bizarre to think that this guy would find.
And he said the story was absolutely true as well.
He said that the story was true.
My father did get these letters.
He saved them, actually.
He saved them, and he told us a story about it, and eventually they did peter out.
People on the forum asked him, "Can you take photos of the letters?"
And he's like, "No, I don't feel comfortable doing that."
So may have been a lark, may have truly been his son, but the stories were reported, and
the police were involved in all these things, and it is a true story.
Now that's that for that conspiracy.
But it's a lead into a topic that is kind of a mainstay of conspiracy theory, and that's
the thing called gangstalking.
Now let me give you a brief overview of gangstalking.
Gangstalking is not a police investigation.
Gangstalking is not you owe money to the mob and they're coming after you.
Gangstalking is not you're the witness of a crime and a street gang's getting you.
Gangstalking is this bizarre conspiracy belief.
So there are TIs, which are considered, not the rapper, there are TIs which are considered
targeted individuals, and these people who are otherwise completely normal in the world
are being stalked by some sort of shadowy government or Illuminati-esque organization.
So if you were a targeted individual, you would walk outside and let's say that if you saw...
Okay, let me put it this way.
If I walked out to my house and every day there was a Pacific power van outside my house,
the first one thing I'm going to think is, it must be having problems with the power
lines, but after three or four days, my personal thing is, I'm going to think there's feds
in there.
They're investigating someone, possibly me.
There's a cops in that van.
But it's going to take a while for me to come to that conclusion.
If you start seeing black SUVs with tinted windows driving through your street at the
same time at night, I'm going to think that's some sort of drug running operation.
That's not what we're talking about.
That's not where gangstalking, that's not where targeted individuals think gangstalking
is.
Here's some ways you can tell, according to this young woman, and everyone has their
own way, but there's some key things.
This young woman wrote on a forum about gangstalking.
This is the way she knows that she is being stalked by a shadowy organization.
Tell me if any of those things have happened to you, you might be gangstalked as well.
You go to a store and it's crowded and people get in your way.
You might be being gangstalked, according to her.
If you're at home, and let's say you're milling about in your yard, you're raking your leaves,
here's a way.
This is a way to tell that you are a target of a shadowy organization.
People will mow their lawns or weed-wack them to annoy you with the noise.
See they're trying to break you down.
Trying to break down the targeted individual.
They will chop or chainsaw their firewood.
I have no idea where this woman's living.
What neighborhood do you live in where people can both weed-wack mow their lawns and chop
firewood?
I guess something in the suburbs, but maybe she's living in the boonies or something like
that.
Here's another thing.
If your neighbor is "improving their home's facade," you might be being gangstalked.
See the point is, is they're causing all this noise, I guess, to drive you nuts.
Rev their car engine.
If they yell at their animals or yell at each other, or if it's dark out and they have
flashlights, these are all signs of people who are working for a shadowy organization
that is targeting you.
And that's where the insanity comes from.
These are all things that normally happen.
I live in an apartment complex downtown and I will wake up sometimes to a loud lawnmower
and I'm like, "Who is mow- what lawn is possibly being mowed right now?"
Everyone has like a foot of lawn.
Why am I waking up to RRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR
Why am I waking up to "Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
I'm
so
excited.
I'm so excited.
How did this rapper get next to my car?
A spy must have put it here.
And, yeah, it would just be like, oh, that's crazy Archie.
Crazy Archie living in the streets, always running around talking about doorknobs and
dead spiders.
But now, crazy Archie can go online and meet people from all over the world who are finding
these inconsequential clues and they're building their own delusional web.
Massive amounts of people believe they are targeted individuals.
This, to me, is a bigger threat than people who believe in Flat Earth.
100%.
People can have all sorts of loony scientific conspiracy theories that they want.
This one, someone believes in Flat Earth, it doesn't matter.
They still go to work and it's not a big deal.
They pay their taxes, they go out and have a good time, they have friends, stuff like
that.
They just have one wacky conspiracy theory.
People who believe in this believe that the world is their enemy.
And, they may see you as their enemy as well.
We'll go a little bit more into gangstalking in a future episode because I have found people
who are dedicated to taking the fight to the gangstalkers.
We've had at least one mass shooting connected to gangstalking already.
This is a serious problem, it's only going to get worse.
Because people are always going to find dead spiders, people are always going to find busted
light bulbs.
People are always going to find McDonald's wrappers by their car.
And, it's just a matter of time before these people in mass start really feeling like they
only have one way out of this situation.
Let's go ahead and move on to a topic that's a little more lighthearted.
It does involve cannibalism.
It does involve mutants.
But, it's still a little more lighthearted than just mass psychosis.
And, what we're going to be talking about right now is the story of an interesting little
cryptid.
No one has the melon head.
So who are the melon heads?
I just love that name.
The melon heads.
Now, it's a very evocative phrase.
Bigfoot, the name tells you right there, has bigfoot.
Or people can think that the creature is actually a bigfoot.
There are some cryptids that the name is just perfect.
Bigfoot, shadow people, Bloody Mary, melon head.
You go right there.
The dude must have a head shaped like a melon and you're 100% correct.
But these guys are even better than that.
Not only do they have big old heads, they got tiny little bodies.
They got like baby bodies, big old melon head.
And you think, there's always, I have this thing, it's called, I call it the Chucky
Conundrum.
Where you try to do that new Chucky movie looks amazing by the way.
That new, oh man, that trailer looks great.
But, it's the Chucky Conundrum.
Is there a point where a killer becomes so timey that it doesn't become threatening?
Chucky scary?
Like, I've never been scared of Chucky, but the idea of Chucky scary.
The fetish doll from that old movie trilogy of terror absolutely terrified me for like
decades.
Very, very scary.
That thing's only like a foot tall.
Would you rather be chased by a cannibalistic dwarf with a baby body and a big old melon
head or an adult sized cereal?
Oh, I guess they're both bad.
But is it scary because it's tiny?
And I think there might be a point where it's not, where it's too tiny, maybe like microscopic
Chucky wouldn't be scary.
But there are a lot of people who go, "Ah, Chucky doesn't scare me, I just kick him over."
I think, let's get into the melon heads and then we'll go more into combat strategy.
The melon heads are a cryptid/urban legend that's mostly in the states of Connecticut,
Michigan, and Ohio.
It's a rural story or suburban story of these creatures.
But it's interesting because we're going to look at three different urban legends and
some of the details are the same, some of the details are different, and that makes
me think one, there's either was based on some sort of truth or some kids who used to
live in Connecticut ended up moving to Michigan and then later told their kids in Ohio.
Like, that's also going to be how it's spread.
Oh, and I should say this before I get into the gruesome stories that are followed.
Melonhead is also a term for a fan of the Los Angeles Rams.
I found that out.
We're not talking about them.
They're not the only people.
They may have tiny baby bodies.
I don't know.
I don't watch sports.
Connecticut.
The year is 1960.
You got like a fog rolling through the city.
And other parts of the country people are wearing bell bottoms.
People are protesting the Vietnam War.
Did that start yet?
1960.
They're protesting a war because they think something's going to happen.
Everyone's just grooving.
People are practicing their kung fu fighting for when they might have to start moving as
fast as lightning.
But in Connecticut in 1960 on a dark stormy night there is an asylum for the criminally
insane.
Bunch of inmates are trapped in there rattling their chains.
Doctors walking through the darkened halls.
Man, these sane people are driving me nuts.
Why did I take this job?
But you know, you got to make a living, right?
And it's like, yeah, I got to make a living.
Lightning strikes.
Somehow, some reason.
Luck or curse.
A fire breaks out in the insane asylum.
Doctors like, "Ugh, uh, uh, uh."
Actually I don't know if he burned to death.
But he doesn't get mentioned anymore.
However, 10 to 20 inmates escape.
"Let's break out boys.
Let's go."
That's what he thinks he says.
He really just goes, "Ugh, uh, uh, uh."
They escape.
They go into the surrounding forest around this asylum for the criminally insane.
They're out there and they go, "Oh no, we're insane.
We don't have any survival skills."
So then they begin eating people for food, not just for fun, maybe a little bit fun.
And because they're out in the middle of nowhere and they're insane and they're cannibals and
tinder doesn't exist yet, they begin to interbreed and their babies are born with hydrocelephus,
hydrocephalus, hydrocephalus, and which is basically water on the brain.
When you're a little baby and you get it, your brain, your skull actually gets distended
and then you look like you have a melon head.
You look like you have a big old head.
So the idea is that they were interbreeding with you.
They were inbreeding with each other.
The crazy people were inbreeding with each other.
Their babies were deformed with these melon heads.
And to this day, the babies are still running around, jumping out of the woods, eating people.
Or the other version of the Connecticut story is there was a family from the colonial era
that was accused of witchcraft, ran into the woods, started banging each other, and their
babies had melon heads.
That story, both stories are kind of ridiculous, but that story actually makes more sense because
that would give, you just can't bang your sister and have a mutant baby.
It doesn't, it can, but it generally tends to happen the farther you bang your sister
and you have a baby and then one of you like bings the baby when it grows up and then that's
the mutant, that's the mutant baby.
So it's not like you would just break out of jail, inbreed with the inmate who was next
to you from the insane asylum.
Like it would take a couple generations for you to start to produce mutated babies.
But anyways, that's the Connecticut version of the story.
Now we're going to go to Michigan.
Here's the Michigan version of the story.
Insane Asylum.
That's a common theme with this story.
And I think it's because insane asylums tend to be scary because they're basically just
buildings full of crazy people.
But in insane asylum, inside the Felt Mansion.
Now Felt Mansion is this giant building.
It looks like Professor Xavier's School for Gifted Youngsters.
It's this beautiful building.
It was founded by this guy named Dor Felt, which is kind of a dope name.
Dor Felt's successful businessman, very well known, very well liked in the area.
He was an inventor and now all the only thing the Felt Mansion is associated with is really
is melon heads.
Like all of his life's work gone into building his business and now his house is the headquarters
of cannibalistic children.
So but he was long dead.
The Felt Mansion ended up turning into insane asylum where there was an evil doctor there
who was this guy.
It wasn't just walking down hallway saying how much he hated his job.
He actually kind of liked his job because it gave him an opportunity to abuse and torture
the inmates.
He was just having fun.
He loved showing up at work.
He's like, oh dude, I can't wait to go to work.
Man, I got all these new tools I'm going to use to abuse these people.
Woo!
His wife's like, what?
Why are you talking about?
He's like, oh nothing honey.
He gets, the doctor gets in his car.
I don't know why I'm building up the backstory.
The point is the doctor works at the hospital in insane asylum.
He's torturing these people.
They finally get tired of being tortured.
They attack him.
They rip him to pieces and hide different pieces of his body all over Felt Mansion.
Then the little people, they're not little yet.
The insane asylum people, again, escape from the insane asylum and hide in the local cave
system.
Now, they also jump out and eat you, the Mellonheads.
And people have said that if you break into Felt Mansion, you can see the ghost of Mellonheads
and see the murder of the doctor reenacted.
That story's a little bizarre because if the Mellonheads are running around in the forest,
I don't know why their ghosts are also in the mansion.
But that's the story from Michigan.
Now we're going to Ohio, which was really the story that I was like, this, this, someone
heard the, someone used to live in Connecticut and then moved to Michigan and thought, you
know what, I'm moving to Ohio.
I'm going to add my own spin.
I'm going to give the Mellonhead story a dark reimagining.
We're in Ohio, we're specifically in the Cleveland suburb of Kirtland.
Kirtland.
If anyone's from Kirtland, I'm sure they know about this.
And this is why I think this story is definitely, this story was, was crafted by someone who
is a connoisseur of the Mellonhead legend.
In the suburb of Kirtland, there is a mansion, an insane asylum, but it was like a hidden
insane asylum.
It's like a, like it was a normal house in the basement.
This guy kept, kept prisoners, kept these prisoners, right?
Now his name was Dr. Crow, but he went by another name.
He went by the name Dr. Mellonhead.
So I don't know if his name was like James Mellonhead and he, that was like his family's
name.
He comes from a long line of Mellonheads and that's how they got the name Mellonhead.
But again, that's from saying it's almost like a gritty reboot.
Like they had to explain, this is his Han Solo, how Han Solo got his name.
This is that of urban legends.
This is how the Mellonheads got their name because they are actually the byproduct of
Dr. Mellonhead.
So Dr. Mellonhead worked with kids with hydrocephalus, hydrocephalus.
So he was basically saying, I will take care of your baby.
Oh, your baby has water on the brain and their, their skulls all big.
I will take care of them.
And the parents are like, well, thank you because we can.
And you're a doctor.
Thank you, Dr. Mellonhead.
And he's like, yes, Dr. Mellonhead MD.
Anyways, so Dr. Mellonhead goes to work.
But what he does is he doesn't treat the baby.
This is, this is this urban legend.
I'm not making this up.
Dr. Mellonhead does not treat the babies.
He instead wonders what would happen if I inject more liquid into their brain.
So he begins to inject fluid into these babies brains, making their heads even more melon-like.
Here, I'm not a scientist, but if a child is suffering from a horrible disfigurement,
I don't think the answer is.
The question should not be, I wonder what will happen if I make them more disfigured.
Because you know the answer to that.
They will become more disfigured.
But apparently Dr. Mellonhead really was a fan of water on the brain.
He began injecting these kids, these babies, with more liquid.
If I was six years old and I heard the story of Bloody Mary, which I did, totally terrified
me.
If I was six years old and my older brother tried telling me this version of the Mellonhead
story, I would probably have become a skeptic on the spot.
Because the story is so ridiculous.
Injects them with more liquid.
Eventually though, these mutated Mellonheads, even more melony than their brothers in Connecticut
and Michigan, these are the super Mellonheads, they also end up killing the doctor.
But these Mellonheads, again, gritty reboot, they run into the forest.
They'll scamper off.
Big Mellonheads bouncing along.
These ones are also cannibals, but that's not good enough for Ohio.
Cannibalism is so Michigan.
These ones specifically enjoy the taste of babies.
So you know, like, put your baby down.
Hush little baby, don't say what.
Mom's gonna buy you a mockingbird.
Yes, that mockingbird.
And from the closet, you see like a pair of yellow eyes.
The mom's swaddling the baby.
Whatever that word means, wraps it up in a blanket.
I think that's what it means.
Kisses the baby on the head, leaves the room.
Closet door slowly pushed open.
It doesn't use its hand, it just slowly leans its head forward.
The Mellonhead pushes against the door.
Luckily the doorknob is loose because a gangstalker was in there, so moves silently out of the
closet towards the baby's crib.
Oh, and also in Ohio, the version of the story, this baby might actually be safe because
the Mellonheads have terrible vision because of all the extra liquid in their brain.
So they can't, if you wear red or black, they won't attack you because they can't see you,
but if you wear white, they'll attack you.
So moral of the story is, don't put your baby in white clothes.
You shouldn't do that anyways, because your baby's going to be totally messy, it's going
to make stains everywhere.
But also because the Mellonheads will get them.
So this is the interesting thing about the Mellonhead story.
Felt Mansion was never an insane asylum.
They've never been able to track down, so that part of the story we know is false, the
asylum for the criminal insane that burnt down in Connecticut.
That may or may not have happened at some point, but I couldn't find a name for any
insane asylum there.
There were stories that Dr. Crowe did, did not go by the name Dr. Mellonhead, but did
perform illegal abortions in the area, but that is also probably a retcon urban legend
type of thing.
There's a bridge in that area they call Cry Baby Bridge because apparently you can hear
babies crying underneath it, and that's either because Mellonheads are eating babies and
throwing their bodies into the bridge, under the bridge, not into it, you're driving by,
you're driving over the overpass and a baby comes flying at you, or that he was dumping
the bodies of aborted babies there.
Here's the thing, I don't think the Mellonheads exist.
I think, and I'm not going to go into this whole thing like because we think they exist,
they exist.
I think this is an interesting idea of an urban legend that there probably was a kid
with a horrible disfigured head in one of these areas at some point, just statistically,
and this rumor started.
That's fairly likely, and I think it's interesting how it's fairly, fairly in this geographical
region.
You don't have stories about Mellonheads in California, you don't have stories about
Mellonheads in New York.
Well you do have in California, they're Los Angeles Ram fans, but it's not like Bloody
Mary where it's a universal urban legend.
The Mellonheads is really restricted to these areas.
These areas are, one of the creepiest areas really in America because it's the suburbs
bordered by forests is generally where these creatures exist.
They're areas that are fairly well traveled, but not civilized, and I think growing up,
that's always a scary thing because you have a perfectly manicured neighborhood, or maybe
even just like a trailer park, but then you have a place where you're totally familiar
with all the sights and the sounds and the people there, and then bordering that is a
forest full of creatures and wonder and mystery and darkness and weird noise that you don't
understand.
And I think that's why urban legends like this are so catchy.
It's this idea of the familiar budding up against the unfamiliar and the alien.
So if in an environment like that, added with someone telling you once that they went to
school with someone with a Mellonhead, Dr. Mellonhead, they knew him in elementary school, these
stories get mixed up, and again I think it's most likely that kids from one state made
up the story or heard the story from their uncles or whatever, and when they began moving
or changing high schools and things like that, the story spread.
It changed because you had a new group of people to entertain, but the key component
stayed, tiny little cannibals with Mellonheads is really the key component in it.
But that all being said, that all being said of where I think the Mellonhead legend came
from, we can go even farther back, a couple states away, but in the state of Idaho there
was an old Native American legend of these things called the Auehi Mountain Dwarves.
The Auehi Mountains is a physical place, but there is an old legend of these two feet tall
creatures that specifically fed on children.
Is it possible that a subset of a creature like that, of a cryptid like that, still exists
today?
We're in the realm of the mystical, these guys had tails that would wrap around their
body to give them some sort of body armor, and they were quite cunning and cruel, but
if we accept things like Bigfoot, this is really no different.
So we have a little bit of urban legend, a little bit of Native American tales, literally,
that wasn't intended, but where is the truth in that?
Were these stories just completely made up by a drunk uncle one night?
Was there really a Dr. Mellonhead who was performing obscene experiments on the bodies
of babies?
Was there a race of cannibalistic dwarves that once prowled the mountain sides and spilled
out and moved into other parts of the country?
Who knows?
But if you do have a child, make sure you check the closet and look under the bed.
Make sure the window's locked before you kiss them goodnight and shut the light off
tonight.
Bye.
(upbeat music)