An otherwise normal cemetery has a bloody secret, and then we take a look at an odd subculture
on the eBay market. People who are selling haunted dolls that are possessed with the spirits
of dead prostitutes today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys had a great
weekend. I have a special guest in the studio today. It is Veronica. Veronica the haunted doll.
I purchased the long time ago. She's here. She's actually always here, but normally she's in the
corner. Today she's sitting on my desk, so if you hear any weird, it's her. It's a little Veronica.
I've had her for a couple months now, and I haven't had any unique ghost stories to tell with her,
but she's been my haunted doll. I bought her on eBay, and she's going to guest host today,
because we have a story coming up about, not about her, not about her. She is not a sex worker,
doll. But anyways, we'll get to that in a second. First off, let's give a shout out to our newest
Patreon's Donnie and Sarah. Donnie and Sarah, thank you so much for supporting the show.
They are engaged. Isn't that cute? Little engaged couple sitting around listening to
the little Dead Rabbit Radio drinking hot chocolate. I don't know. Or maybe just, maybe just water.
Maybe just sit around with a lukewarm glass of water and look at each other and go,
"Oh, this is a good episode." I don't know. Whatever your beverage of choice is, I hope you're
drinking it while you're listening to this, and you will be our pilots. This episode, our captains,
whatever vehicle we take, you will be in charge. If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help get the word out about the show. That really, really helps out a lot.
We're going to toss Donnie the keys to the Jason Jalopy. Donnie, you ready? He's nodding.
We are leaving behind Oregon. We are headed out to Peeridge, Arkansas. We're driving.
We go to Peeridge, Arkansas. It's July 2020. So very, very recent story. We all get out. We're at
a cemetery, and we see a bunch of detectives standing around a gravestone. They're like,
"We should have solved this case before the man died, but we're not that good of a detective."
But they're standing around this gravestone, and they're taking pictures of it and stuff,
dusting for fingerprints. Also, there is Shannon Nobles. Now, that's her grandpa's grave.
What happened was her grandpa, Fred Allen McKinney, died in May 2020, so just a month beforehand.
The reason why they're there is there's a dead animal laying on the gravestone. It's like just
a squirrel, just totally out. We're thinking, "Why are the cops here for a dead squirrel?"
That's pretty common, right? Squirrels are always dying.
Shannon goes, "No, no, no, no. This isn't just a dead squirrel. This is the 10th dead squirrel
we found on this grave." And we're like, "Hmm, now that is a mystery."
What was happening was Shannon would come out to visit her grandpa's grave, and there'd be a
dead animal on it. And at first she's thinking, "Oh, I wonder if it's eating something. I wonder
if it's eating the fake flowers?" And it wasn't just squirrels either, right? Because then you just
figure maybe squirrels were just found in a place very comfortable, but it was all sorts of animals.
This is an elephant, a panda. It was all sorts of animals found dead on her grandpa's tombstone.
She puts up a trail cam, and there's that animal a couple days later on the gravestone. And she's
like, "Oh, let's review the footage." So they see, at this point, 16 animals in total have been found
dead on this gravestone. Not all at once. That'd be like a little pyramid. There's a live squirrel
sitting on the top of the pyramid. 16 animals at all. They see with this trail cam, they see a dodge
journey pull-up. So they see this gray car pull-up. They see this elderly man get out,
and he's wearing like overalls. So he looks like a farmer, right? He totally looks like a stereotypical
farmer. But he also is wearing a woman's wig and a woman's windbreaker. This must be a really
high-definition camera that they could pull all this stuff out. It says "Lane Bryant" on the jacket.
And he's wearing sunglasses. So it's obviously this farmer dude in a bib and overalls,
but he's wearing a woman's wig, and he runs and he's dropping a dead animal on the gravestone. So
they go, "That's him." They show it to the cops, and the cops go, "It's obviously somebody who's
trying to disguise their identity. Maybe he really likes wearing a wig." But it's most likely a really
poorly thought-out disguise guy. So the cops go, "Okay, that's weird, but we don't know who that is."
And Shannon didn't recognize him either. But one day, she sees that same car pulling away from
the cemetery. She spends a lot of time in the cemetery, but she sees the dodge journey pull-out,
so she begins following it. And when she follows it, she follows it to a store, and out hops,
Joseph A. Stroud, a 78-year-old man who was Fred's neighbor. They didn't get along. They
actually ended up in a lawsuit against each other. So Shannon's like, "Hmm, that makes sense. Now I
know who it is. I think I know who it is, right? It wasn't a woman's windbreaker this time, but the
weather was quite good." So that would explain that. She goes to the cops and says, "Hey, I'm pretty
sure it's this dude. Doesn't like my grandpa and is just throwing dead animals on his gravestone."
The cops are like, "Yeah, we need a little more than that." Then she's out running, and her running
path takes her by the cemetery. Now, at a certain point, you just kind of cut your losses, right?
At a certain point, you got to go, "There's a lot of places to run in P. Ridge, Arkansas. I'm assuming.
I'm assuming it's just not a one street town, and at the end of the street is a cemetery." But
at a certain point, you're like, "Maybe I shouldn't run by the cemetery where all the dead animals are."
But she's running, and she sees Stroud driving away from the cemetery. She's like, "I bet you
anything. I bet you anything." So she runs, and she gets-- she might have walked. She might have
just walked at this point. She's not a Wonder Woman. She might have just walked. She goes to her grandpa's
grave. This is what I find so bizarre about the story, other than the fact that this old farmer
man decides to disguise himself as a woman, but still wears his overalls and bib, like the most
stereotypical old man farmer clothes. That's the weird-- that's weird part one. He wears a wig and
a windbreaker, and then doesn't change any of his other clothes. That's weird. You're like, "Jason,
the dead animal is far more weird than that." Sure, but then this is the weirdest part. When she gets
there, she sees a dead possum on the grave, and then to top it off, as if you couldn't get anywhere
to net, there's like a vase built into like the gravestone where you like would put flowers and
stuff. It was full of live baby possums. They're just like crawling all over each other. They're
all pink and fleshing and stuff like that. "What happened there, man? Like, what-- what-- there's
so much stuff to unpack there, because one-- I don't even know if I want to unpack this one.
Did he kill the mom possum, and then the babies follow him, and he's like, "Oh." So he threw him
in the vase so they'd be safe. Did he throw him into the vase assuming that they would have to
like-- no one would discover him for a while, and then they would have to fight like the hunger
games amongst each other, till eventually one baby possum ate the other seven, and then grew
strong enough to break through the vase, and then he'd put that dead one on there, or did he kill
the possum, and then much of babies pop out, which like, I don't want to go into it. My point is,
is that why did you do that? Why did you do that? It's bad enough that you're killing these animals,
but then what are you like, "Oh, I just put these in a vase." Like, what was that logic? So anyways,
at this point, she was able to say, "Listen, I saw him leave in the scene, and then there was this
dead possum, and then I have these baby possums that now-- they've bonded to me. Now I'm their mother,
and they're like crawling all over her. They're fault crawling along the police station,
walking on the ink. They're like, "Dude, that's evidence! The possums are all like playing with
cocaine. They're like, 'Oh, that's gonna botch so many trials.'" They arrest him. They end up arresting
him, and his crime, apparently it's legal to throw dead animals around. That wasn't the crime. This
was, again, was super bizarre about this case. What he got in trouble for was, at one point,
he cut an animal open, and Tommy and Sarah are like, "Dude, seriously? This, this is my fiance's
in the car. She's like crying in the back. I'm sorry, guys, but, but here's something to wipe your
eyes. It's a belt." Apparently, what his crime actually was, wasn't that. Wasn't kidnapping baby
possums or stuff like that. It was the fact that he took a dead animal and draped it over the tombstone,
and blood got on the tombstone, and you can't wash it out, because apparently this tombstone
is made of white cloth or something like that. Like, the blood is stained into it,
so he has to buy him a new tombstone, basically. He got charged with a class B felony, $2,500 in
damages due to blood stains on a tombstone. I don't think that's what they charged him with. I
don't think the cops are like, "It's a 207 dead animal on a tombstone." Let's put your hands behind
your back, but he, it was a basically like a high-level vandalism charge, $2,500 vandalism charge.
So, that is the story of Joseph A Stroud, master of disguise. He should have rented a car. I mean,
that's how they identified him was his car. He could have done a lot of things differently.
First off, by not throwing dead animals on someone's grave, but if he hadn't draped on over the
tombstone, he'd be walking out of jail right now. He's like, "Ha ha ha, the law can't hold me."
He's walking away, and then on the rooftop, there's eight little silhouettes standing there.
They're little baby possums, little naked, hairless baby possums, and they're looking down at him.
And then he goes home, and he's like, cooking, um, he eats them. Yeah, what are they going to do
against them? They're not ninja turtles. Then he gets home, and they come there in his house,
and they're like, "We're gonna get back at you," and he just scoops, he just scoops them up,
and eats them like chitlins. I don't know where I was going with that, even if they were, even if
they were ninja turtles. Or like, they're still tiny. He's like eating them like a shrimp. That's
a dismal story. Sorry about, sorry, Donnie and Sarah. I was hoping the little baby possums could
beat him up, but I gotta, I gotta be at least a little realistic. Speaking of baby possums,
I have no way to segue from that. I have no way to really segue from that to our next story. So
Sarah, we are going to toss you the keys to the carpenter copter. You're going to take us for
this first jump of this flight. We're flying up on that carpenter copter. As we're flying away
in the carpenter copter, I turn, I put my arm around your shoulder. I pull you close. And I go,
hey, come here, come here, come here. Let me tell you about a little movie called The Vanished. So
I actually have been working with a marketing team. I have four digital copies. I originally was
five. I had five digital copies, but I took one to watch and I watched it and I actually enjoyed
it. I'd love to talk to you guys about it. But first, new today on digital. It just came out on
digital. Ann Haitian Thomas Jane, star in this gripping psychological thriller called The Vanished.
Structed by Peter Facinelli, we'll talk about him in a second too,
a family vacation takes a terrifying turn when two parents discover that their young daughter has
vanished without a trace. Stopping at nothing to find her. The search for the truth leads to a
shocking revelation where nothing is what it seems in this intense thriller. Own or rent the vanished
on digital today and watch it at home tonight. Rated R from Paramount Pictures. So I watched it
and I do have four digital copies again previously five. It's weird. I can't legally hold a contest.
There's all these sorts of rules. I'm trying to figure out a way to get four of those copies out to
you guys. So if you guys are interested in the movie, I can't say it's super weird. I don't even
know how I'm going to get these four digital copies out. But even if you don't get a digital copy,
I recommend checking it out. There's a lot of weird stuff going on. Peter Facinelli was the
lead vampire in the Twilight movies. He was Edward Collins adopted dad. And he directs this movie.
This is only a second movie he's directed. And there's also everyone in the movie is a big old
weirdo. It's a really interesting movie. It's just a bunch of weirdos in like a
hundred yard location. Everyone just has this weird secret. No spoilers, but one of the characters
isn't even bigger, bigger weirdo. And when they go to his house, when they go to his location,
he has a copy of the Twilight book on his, I think it was actually Eclipse was the actual book.
And I'm thinking did the director choose, choose to make the creepiest guy in the movie a fan of
Twilight that he's reading this book? Or did the set designer throw it in his joke in the director?
I don't know. I don't know. There's a lot of weird stuff in the movie. Check it out. It is
available today, rent or own today from Paramount Pictures. Let's go ahead. We're leaving behind
Peerage Arkansas. We're leaving behind Paramount Pictures Mountain. Sarah and Donnie are both
flying the Carbentercopter at the same time because see they love each other. So they're in sync.
We hope, we hope, right? We hope they don't have a fight. They're spilling each other's lukewarm
water. We hope that they can think as one couple as they fly us safely out to a toy factory. And
there's like all these dolls being created. There's like little mechanical arms putting them in the
sockets and stuff like that. And these dolls are just kind of moving out a conveyor belt. And the
reason why we're here is because this is what a doll is supposed to look like. And you're like,
Jason, I know what a doll is supposed to look like. You buffoon. You took us all the way to a
doll factory just so you could do this intro. But see, while we're at the doll factory, you're
right. It's probably not the best place to be. It's super noisy. There's dolls everywhere, just
huge machines. I pull up my laptop because this is really all we needed to do. Sit down. We're
like, Hey, we asked the boss, can we use your office for the rest of the segment? He's like,
Yeah, sure. Go ahead. You go upstairs. We're on the internet. I the other day I was like, Okay,
so I have Veronica. She's a haunted doll. I bought her a long time ago. She's pretty cool.
I was like, I wonder if should I buy another haunted doll with the ghosts and get along?
Would there be like fighting each other and stuff like that, which admittedly would be kind of cool.
But so I was looking for haunted dolls. But then I found a new layer. This is a whole subculture
of doll. These are dolls. These are normal dolls that would be found being made at a factory.
But these dolls are possessed, not what just run of the mill ghosts, but possessed with sexual ghosts,
which is which is like eight levels of gross, right? I mean, killing animals to run them on a
grave would be like seven layers of gross. But let's look, these are actual descriptions. Let's
take a look at some of these descriptions for $200. You could buy this haunted doll. Now I'm going
to be fair. I'm almost for sure that this I almost think that this doll was mislisted, because in
the description, they keep referring to it as a ring. Here's part of this description. All your
dark little secrets of sexual lust and fantasy will rise. This amazing talisman ring will
bring new submissive friends into your life who will become part of your erotic adventures.
The last thing I want is a bunch of toadies running around, right? Like when I think of
submissive friends, sure, you could be like trying to be this whole Christian gray thing
where some chick shows up and she's like, I'll do whatever you want. But I also
an Igor, right? I'm like, I have this doll and or ring and either wear the ring or I carry the
doll around or wear the doll and then a bunch of like Igor show up and they're like, oh yes,
master, whatever you want us to do, sexual or otherwise, they're winking their one eye. I'm
like, gross, bro. I don't know. Go do the dishes or something. Do you want me to do them naked? No.
So anyway, but I guess the term submissive in this context, but they keep referring it to it as a ring.
But it's listed as, this is what it's listed, all the links are in the show notes, so you can
purchase this doll, $200, by the way, it's porcelain doll. It's listed as haunted sex attraction
magic doll, XXX, adult only live the life of a porn super. Didn't finish it. It's not a porn superstar.
It's just a porn super. You're a porn super. And then it gets, this is where I start to think
whoever wrote this knows who they, they have this very, very specific group of people that they're
either marketing to, i.e. creeps, or the person who's writing this is like, someday I'll have you.
You can have any submissive person, you're going to attract submissive people from all over,
but specifically, look at this passage, this will bring you a sexy barista, the hot guy in the gym,
the bartender, your friend or acquaintance, your colleague, whoever you wish, he will be filled,
oh, and that's a key thing that I should say right on the bat. I'm pretty sure these
dolls are all marketed, I hope these dolls are marketed towards women, right? Again, I hope,
really, really hope so. Most supernatural stuff is marketed towards women. Even though the ghost
shows are all men, it's mostly women who are into paranormal. We've talked about that a lot of times
on this show, but this one definitely is so you can get your sexy barista, which I don't think
I've ever seen a male sexy barista, right? Is that a thing? Is that like a woman's fantasy now?
Because they smell like coffee beans and stuff like that? Because they can get you discounts?
Or I'll punch your card twice, honey, click, click. Like, what is that? But anyway, so you get this
ring and/or doll and you can take control of that sexy barista or the hot guy in the gym.
So, guys, if you ever feel yourself falling in love with someone and wanting to quit your job
and become a barista, check her doll collection. She might end her bank account because if she has
no money, she's blowing it all on these stupid dolls. But that's not it. That's not it. Because
just one doll, right? That would be a one-off thing. I saw that one and I thought, that was the first
one I saw and I go, "That's insane." And then I thought, "There must be more of these out there.
There has to be more of these out here. This is not an outlying thing."
We are now going to meet Elizabeth for $24. This is a very cheap one. If you don't have
$200 to spend and you don't want a bunch of e-gores running around, 24 bucks, you can get Elizabeth.
I'm going to read you this first part, verbate. This is 100% what was written in the listing.
"Elizabeth found dead in river." Okay, wait. I can't start laughing yet.
You're like, "Jason, that's gruesome. Hold on. It starts off. This is the posting, okay? Elizabeth
found dead in river." Next sentence. "So excited. I found another box from this set of dolls that
are inhabited by sex worker women who were supposedly murdered by Jack the Ripper."
This is what I don't understand. Are you excited that she drowned in the river? Are you excited?
You found dolls that are possessed with dead prostitutes. Are you excited that they're from...
First off, I'm pretty sure Jack the Ripper, his name wasn't Jack the Drowner. So I don't know how
this woman died in the river, or is she implying the doll died in the river? You should never say,
"Elizabeth found dead in the river," and then your next two words be so excited. There's a whole
lot of stuff going on here, but she weaves this crazy tale. This selling was basically at its own
short story attached. There was a girl whose mom was a sex worker who died, so then she was an orphan
and she went to live with her aunt, and then she became a sex worker and then got abused by a pimp,
and then left the pimp. None of this has to do with the dolls. This is modern times. This isn't
as nothing to do with the doll. This is just in the description. The woman leaves the pimp
and then gets rescued by a madam, so her and a bunch of other girls worked in a brothel,
and the madam was very kind to these young women that she was using to pimp. She's still a pimp,
right? Just a different name for it. And the madam goes, "Well, you young ladies, I am going to put
a doll in each of your rooms. This doll will watch over you, and not only will it watch over you,
it'll make the sex even..." The old lady, the old madam goes, "This doll will make the sex even
better if you keep this doll in your room, make the sex even better." And then the madam dies,
and then the prostitute gets the doll, has like three or four of these dolls, and then has given
them to this eBay seller to sell. Now, the madam explained all of that, all of that stuff with the
girl like going, being a sex worker, her mom being a sex worker, all gets to the point that these
dolls are all possessed with the victims of Jack the Ripper's ghosts. So the madam had these dolls
that I don't know were passed along through pimp history from one pimp to another. This doll that
was possessed with the dead prostitute, the spirit of dead prostitute, if you put it in your room,
it makes the sex better. Now, let's assume that... let's just assume that lunacy is true for just
a few minutes. One, $24 is completely underselling a hundred-year-old ghost, right? I would be awfully
offended if I was murdered in one of the most famous, if not the most famous serial killer case.
24 bucks? Come on, man. Let's say it's true. You have the ghost of a woman who was a sex worker,
who was brutally murdered, is trapped in a doll, and then you make her watch other sex workers
have sex for probably a hundred years. If this is true, that's absolutely horrible. If it's not
true, it's just a doll sitting in the corner while you're banging dudes and whatever. It's just kind
of creepy. I mean, you imagine the Johns come in the room and they're like, "Hey, hey, what's up with
that doll?" And, "Oh, no, no, no, no. It makes the sex better." What? What are you talking about?
And she has to tell this whole story. Maybe that was part of it. Maybe the story would take so long
to be like, "You're Irish up, buddy. Time to go." But anyways, that's disgusting, right? Let's say that
it's true. Let's say that it's true. You're basically using a murdered woman's ghost as your sex slave
in a doll that's forced to watch. The eyes are always open, right? And now for just 24 bucks,
you can buy this and put it in your room to make your sex better. But that isn't even the weirdest
one I found, because then we go to haunted doll, miracle spirit vessel, sexual aggressive. The
grammar, guys. The grammar is really bad, but I guess I'm not going to nitpick that. This one's
only $10.50, so if you didn't have those 24 bucks to spend, but this one gets a little more complicated,
because this one is actually from West Virginia. Let me read you this description here. "The spirit
is to believe that of an 18-year-old girl named Miracle. Though it was never proven, many believe
Miracle was strangled and killed by her stepfather to keep his horrible secret of sexual abuse hidden,
not laughing at that. I'm laughing at whoever thought that was a good marketing gimmick.
Who goes, "Hmm, I have this doll. I want to sell it." But who's going to pay $10.50 for this doll?
I know. Total lunatics. Like, why? You're making it up. You're making it up, and you even admit in
the beginning, "I don't know if this story's true or not. I don't know. You don't have to. Come on.
That's gross." The Jack the River victims are just shaking their heads right now.
That's what you make up. That's seriously what you make up to sell your doll for $10.50. You make
up this horrible story. Anyways, so then we go on. It turns out that she's murdered by her stepfather
in this house. Her body is put in the crawl space. None of this is true, by the way. I mean, this is
just what she's saying. Don't try looking up West Virginia news. But anyways, so apparently according
to this story, she's murdered by her stepfather. Her body is hidden in the crawl space up in the
attic or something like that. And then a fraternity moves in and then they find the body. They're like
"Toga! Toga!" No, actually, I think the body is found earlier. I think that's found before the
fraternity shows up. But the body's found. The fraternity shows up and they find the doll.
They find this doll and they say that it's super weird because of this fraternity.
Now, the fraternity reports, again, this made up, but the eBay says the fraternity members would
wake up. They'd have scratches all over them in the middle of the night. Sometimes they'd wake up
and there'd be a strange woman sitting on top of them. That's not paranormal activity. That's
just what happens with a bunch of drunk dudes, right? They're like jumping into bushes. They're
wrestling with each other, biting each other's butts. And then they wake up and they're like "What?
I don't remember any of that stuff. This is being drunk. This is being an alcoholic 20-year-old,
right? What? Oh, how did I get all these abrasions on my body?" They're like "Dude, you attacked that
comp last night. Oh yeah, totally. There's a doll sitting in the corner. Can't blame it on the doll."
They said that with the fraternity. They thought the basement was haunted so they never wanted to
do their laundry. "Show me a dude who loves to do laundry." That's my new excuse for any chore I
don't want to do. Uh, that's haunted. I don't even know what it is, but I don't want to do it.
It's super haunted over there. There's like a bunch of ghosts standing there. I'm not doing it.
So anyways, you can buy this doll that was previously in a frat house that was possessed by
this horrible crime and apparently caused the fraternity people to get all scratched up. You
want- you want to wake up with scratches all over your body? You can buy this doll. It's only $10.50.
You don't want to ever do the laundry again. You can buy it for $10.50. We got one more doll to look
at because you go "Okay, Jason. Okay." None of those dolls are interested to me. None of those
dolls are interesting to me. I want a doll who's capable of committing a felony. Well, here you go.
Here you go, guys. You can- for $32, you can buy Mandy. Mandy the doll. The haunted doll.
Here's this one. This one is referred to as a street girl and that's how she's actually referred
to, but she's a sex worker. She's murdered in the apartment. A couple moves in. The guy will wake
up at night when his wife's out of town. He'll feel like someone laying next to him. He'll get a
little back massage. He'll feel like hands on his legs and stuff like that. He's getting a little
bit of attention. That's kind of cool, right? She's not totally nuts. She's not scratching you. She's
not biting you. She's just hanging out, giving you a back rub. The perfect girlfriend, some might say.
You don't have to listen to her. You don't have to listen to anything she says. She just kind of
floats there and then when you go to bed, she appears and then when you wake up in the morning,
she's just gone for the rest of the day. "That's a me. I'm going to buy this one." But, sorry Veronica,
but here's the trick. The woman will show back up, right? And the guy's like "Dang it." The guy's
like "Oh man, that ghost gives such good back rub." The woman would show back up and she would feel
uncomfortable. She would feel like she wasn't welcoming her own home to the point that one day
she was walking down the stairs and she tumbles down the stairs. She falls down the stairs.
She feels herself get pushed. Now, whether it was a little doll hands pushing her,
which really wouldn't do much, right? Or if it was the forceful push of a ghost, we don't know,
probably the second one, because she actually did tumble down the stairs. She thinks that the ghost
is haunted with a malevolent spirit and eBay also, not eBay, eBay knows this is all phony, but
the seller of this says "Oh no, no, no, this one, this is the actual quote. We do not believe this
spirit is friendly to females. I'm going to be very jealous of them." So, if you want to arrange an
accident for somebody for $32, talk about an efficient hitman, right? There'd be no evidence.
I'm not condoning this. Again, it's made up. So, you could buy 100 of these dolls. It's not going
to do anything. It's not going to do anything, but let's say it actually did work. What they're
basically selling is a loaded gun that can never be traced. I wonder if actually now that I think
about that, I wonder if you could sneak one of these onto an airplane. Like, you can't bring
box cutters. You can't bring any sort of knives and stuff like that, but if you brought a haunted doll
onto an airplane, could they stop you? Now, they're going to assume it's a regular doll. They're also
going to assume you're a big old weirdo because you're an adult and you're carrying a doll around,
but I wonder if you could bring a haunted doll onto an airplane and just like
set it, you buy it by a seat, right? And then it just sits there and then like it's like running
around. I guess they would know something was up when the doll was running up the aisles. I think
at that point the air marshall would just shoot it. Like, I don't think the air marshall, I think
at that point security's going to go, "I want to start checking dolls. We might want to start
having them. Little dolls go through a scanner for ectoplasm. Little x-ray, little cartoon ghost
and doll." Don't do that actually by the way. Do not try sneaking a doll onto a plane. To be fair,
let's put on our conspiracy caps to wrap up this episode. What makes these things spooky
is really how mundane they are. They're just normal looking dolls, right? You could have,
you could have tons of these sitting at Goodwill's. You could go to your aunt's house and on her shelf
she has this collection of dolls that she's bought and sold over eBay and these are dolls.
These dolls were identified as being haunted because they have providence. Again, none of this
is true, but just for the sake of wrapping up this episode, let's put on our conspiracy cap.
These dolls have a story connected to them. You can't verify it, but they have a story
connected to them. But how many dolls out there were in the clutches of a woman as she was being
brutally murdered by Jack the Ripper or any other serial killer or just regular killer?
I can't believe I can't believe I'm wrapping the episode up with this, but we got into it somehow
and I just have no idea where they ended. It's so brutal. So anyways, these dolls though,
after the body is processed and taken out of the crime scene, everything that this woman owned is
just there in an empty apartment for a day and a night and a day and a night and the sun rises
and sets and that doll is just leaning there against the wall. Nobody else knows it's infused
with her energy. No one else knows that that was the doll she grew up with. It was something she
always held on to to remind her of a more peaceful, stable life. But as her life did descend into
bitterness and hopelessness, that doll was still that beacon of light. So when she was brutally
murdered in her one bedroom apartment, that's where her soul reached out to. But see, that doll
wasn't given a providence. That doll doesn't have any sort of story connecting it. It was just
picked up by the landlord and dropped off at Goodwill. So that doll goes through Goodwill,
gets purchased, gets played with, gets sold to someone else, and it just kind of moves throughout
the region. Now maybe you buy it, maybe you see this doll on eBay that just is like, oh, I remember
growing up with a doll like that. Maybe your aunt buys it at a swap meet. It's a normal looking doll,
but behind its dead eyes is a life. The life of a woman who never had a chance at happiness.
Her soul sits behind those wide open eyes that porcelain head attached to a cloth body,
and it just sits there and looks, looks out of the display case into the empty room in front of her.
She wants so badly to live again. That energy just builds more and more and more.
Some people might see that as sexual energy, but what is sexual energy other than life energy?
It's one of the main reasons why we're here is to procreate. While these dolls may be creating
some sort of intense sexual energy, what it's actually doing is creating so much sexual intensity
that it's able to drain it off. You think it's a supernova, but it's really a black hole.
So while this doll is sitting in this display case, it infuses the room with sexual energy.
You may key onto the fact, you may not, if it's at your aunt's house, you probably won't
put two and two together unless you're having sex at your aunt's house, but you understand what
I'm saying. Maybe your aunt has having a lot of sex. My point is, is that this wouldn't exist in a
vacuum. Something that could give off and create intense sexual energy would be doing it for its
own benefit. And if you had this doll long enough and it kept draining and draining and draining,
it's building up its own reservoir. And then one day you wake up completely refreshed. You've never
had such a great sleep in your night. It's almost like you've slept for decades. And you get up
you go in the mirror, check yourself out, go off into the world, or at least your body does.
Because you are now behind those dead eyes. The spirit of the young woman finally gathered
enough energy from you that she could pull itself from the false body into your body of flesh and
blood. You are now the doll. You are now trapped. If these things are real, they are nothing to
mess around with. If these things are actually real, it is the last thing you would want to have in
your house. Because whatever energy it could give, it could take back. Until eventually, it takes
everything from you. DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also
hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio. Twitter is @deadrabberradio. DeadRabberRadio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
[MUSIC]