It's all food conspiracies today, culminating in the most dangerous conspiracy we've covered to date.
The grand soy unified theory. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Barbender. Hope you guys are having a great day. I'm recording this at 11. That's kind of par for
the course. I'm really tired though. We had a performance tonight. I've mentioned before that I
do plays here locally. If you're in the Hood River area, you always come out and see a play.
Hit me up, deadrabbitradio@gmail.com. We'll see what we can do. Meet up somewhere. I actually
know Scratch that because you might kidnap me. You know, I was talking on the street today and a
car rolled up to me. It was like, I don't really know cars that well, but it was like a solid black.
I don't know. Chevrolet was old. It was like from the 60s or something of that. There was this young
man in the car and he had like a bunch of tattoos on his arm and he goes, "Hey man, you need a ride?"
And I was like, "No, I'm cool." And he goes, "I see you walking all the time." Which I do walk all
the time. And I was like, "No, I'm cool. You know, I enjoy walking." He's like, "Okay, have a great day."
And he drove off. Now two things struck me there. One, what a nice young man. Secondly, I never get
in a car. I never get in a stranger's car ever. Now it's possible that he saw me walking around
all the time and people have pulled over like owners of, you know, like local businesses. You
know, I've been walking around for years. I've had them give me rides like an inclement weather.
But generally, I won't take a ride. And even the business owners, I kind of know because I
patronized their business. But if the young man was being nice, hey, thank you. That's kind of how
I took it. I took it that he was being nice, but he could have also been a serial killer or an agent
of Deep Soy. They could have known I was going to record this episode tonight.
And we're going to go ahead and get into the grand soy unified theory in the end.
Keep you waiting. But first, we got some other interesting food based conspiracies to kind of
wrap this week up. The first one I want to cover, and this was a fairly famous video when it came
out. I'm going to include the link, but most of you guys have probably seen it before. So they took
an octopus or a squid or something with more than two legs. And what they did was they cut its brain
out or cut the top of its head off or something like that. And then they poured soy sauce on it,
and it starts dancing. Oh, you know, it's not dancing, but it's like jerking around. And people
were up in arms saying that was cruel. And then other people were saying it's already dead and
we're going to eat it anyways. Like, what's the problem? It's disgusting either way. Like, I don't
want to see my food move around like that. I can eat bloody food, but that's pretty gross. My question,
though, when I saw that video was, I took a human and cut the top of their head off. How much soy
sauce would I need to make them move around? Because technically, you could have an army of
the undead. Think about how terrifying that would be. You're in the middle of Afghanistan.
You're a Taliban soldier. You're watching your post. And you see a bunch of your former
clansmen, herky jerky walk-in across the landscape with huge bubble, like astronaut bubble things
on their heads, helmets, I guess is the word, and with huge helmets on them full of soy sauce.
Hey, that actually plays into the next story. I didn't make that connection. I'm incredibly tired.
So you outfit them with backhacks of soy sauce and it's just like pumping into this helmet. You
just see these bodies like just moving across the desert. That would terrify anybody. And it would
terrify you because you would think, oh, if the military, if the US military kills me, they're
going to turn me into one of those abominations. Like, am I really dead if my body's moving around?
I wonder, and you know, the article goes on to say that it's an element in the soy sauce. I think
it's the salt or something. Then you can tell it's well researched. I did read the article,
to be fair, I did read it, but that it had something to do with the way that the chemicals
are interacting with the muscle ending. So could you do that to a human? And if so, has anyone
done that before? I think it would be a very effective weapon of war, just because it'd be so
terrifying. I'm sure the Geneva Convention wouldn't have, wouldn't really like it that much, but you
know, they're usually buzz kills anyways. The next story, you can tell we're just moving along,
because I kind of want to get to this grand soy unified theory one, because I put a lot of research
into this, a lot of research. This story kind of popped up. I just thought it was interesting.
It's pretty brief. It is. Things, foods that you thought were vegan that weren't. There's some
interesting ones. Now, you know, I used to be vegetarian back in the day, because I wasn't,
you know, the cruelty to animals things was like my main reason. It just got too expensive. The economy
fell apart back in 2008, and all the prices went up, and I had to go back to eating meat.
But you know, I knew back then not to, you know, eat certain candies like Mamba, which I
loved Mamba growing up that has Jell-o-tin, which is basically horse hooves. It's bone,
bone matter. And a lot of candies have Jell-o-tin. A lot of candies have Jell-o-tin in it, so I say
with that Jell-o, obviously. But I came across some interesting ones. So, Frosted Mini Leeds
also has Jell-o-tin. Apple Juice has elements of fish bladder in it, and that's what gives it kind
of its smoky, kind of like, makes it look like a natural cider, the brown, like, you know,
kind of the wavy stuff. And that's fish bladder stuff. That's disgusting. Painfuls contain Jell-o-tin.
Oh, this is a weird one. This is one that I didn't expect to see on this list. Tattoo Ink.
Most black inks are made from charcoal that's made from burning animal bones. Crazy. So, if you
ever see someone who's lecturing you about being vegan and how it's all health-conscious, you could
say, "Well, do you have a tattoo?" I can see, "Oh, yeah, I have a tattoo." You could be a jerk and
say, "Well, you know, there was animal bone made in that tattoo." But, you know, I think probably
the better place to just kind of smile to yourself and know it, because you don't know. They may end
up chopping their arm off or something because they don't want any animal in them. They probably
won't believe you anyways, but tell them you heard it on a podcast called Dead Rabbit Radio,
and they will also subscribe and listen to me. I don't think so. But, you know, you always could.
And then they hear this episode and they'd hate it. Okay, just buzzing along here. Buzzing, buzzing
along. It's funny, before I get started on that, though, before I forget this, I thought it was
interesting conversation. I was having a conversation with someone on the internet the other day,
and they were talking about the NASA photos of Earth are photoshopped, and that's proof that
NASA's lying to us. Now, it's common knowledge that, yes, the photos you see of the Earth are
photoshopped. Don't worry, this is food related. But the photos you see of the Earth are photoshopped,
and NASA, they will say that. Yeah, they're photoshopped. The way that we take photos,
it's a big planet. We can't just go out there and like click a picture. And the thing is, is that he
was like, "Well, why do they do that? Why do they do that?" And I said, "You know, here's the thing.
Those pictures we see of Earth are made to be posters and lithographs. They're made to be things
that you sell. They're not supposed, they're not scientific pictures. Scientists don't have photos
of the Earth coming from NASA on their walls, and they sit around in their little lab coats and
taking notes. That's not what they're there for. They're for consumers. When you go into a Taco Bell
and you look at a picture of a Nachos, when you look at a picture of Nachos, Nachos Belgrande,
and they have everything perfectly spaced out. The chips are all perfect. The beans, the meat,
the cheese. I hate tomatoes, so those, I pretend those aren't on the picture. That set of Nachos
never existed, ever, ever existed. Someone used Photoshop to take the perfect Nachos and go in
and put the ridges exactly where they should be, and then put the beans in just the right smooth
area and then put on the clumpy, glistening meat and sprinkle the cheese in perfect dimensions,
and the cheese hasn't even melted yet. You can still see those strings just before it melts.
And then they take that photo to a focus group, and they go, "What do you think?" And they go, "Well,
it's kind of yummy, but do this. Maybe add this." It doesn't mean Nachos don't exist. It doesn't mean
Taco Bell is then selling us hamburgers. It just means that they're trying to present their best
foot forward of Nachos. That's what it's for. And that's the same thing with the cabbage in
the other episode, the fake cabbage in the Bellray Surge. That fake cabbage was made to show the
perfect representation of food. We do it too. We just do it with photographs. So yes, just because
there's beautiful photo, and they do have real photos of the earth, and it looks like a big
mudball. It looks like a big pale blue gross mudball. And even then, they're like looking at
this picture that had to do several passes with this satellite, but it looks gross. It's not
something you would want hanging on your wall. That's why those photos are photoshopped. It's
not because the earth is flat. It's not because NASA is lying to you, because they will tell you,
"Yeah, these photos are photoshopped." That is common knowledge. If you ask them, it'll be on
their websites when you look into it. So if anyone ever says, "Why are these clouds like copy and
paste it?" It's because they were lazy, and it was a Friday, and someone just needed to get out of
there, so he just copy pasted some clouds. They're not meant to be scientific instruments. So
I just wanted to get that out there before I end our food week.
Grand Soy Unified Theory. How this started off is this is one of our conspiracies that came off
of our conspiracy list. This was the conspiracy that I've had to do the most research on. That I
was successful. I, like I said, I've been trying to find sexual assault missiles for probably about
half a week now. I can't find anything, so I think it's a joke. If it's not a joke, it's pretty awesome.
It might be related to the gay bombs we developed, but we'll do that another time.
I think most people know about the gay bombs, anyways. The bombs that are supposed to turn the
enemy gay. They're from the 1990s. It's totally legit. We'll cover that some other time. We'll
cover wacky weapons of war, but Grand Soy Unified Theory. People go, "Oh, it's just a joke. That's
just a joke." I think I've found just enough information, maybe not to prove, but to suggest
that it's more than a joke. First off, what we look at. You have to break it down into certain
questions. The first question is, "Is soy sentient?" This is something we talked about on the episode
Oil and Water with Dr. Emoto looking at glasses of water and going, "You're beautiful. I love you.
You're so great." Then it creates beautiful ice crystals. If you look at the water and you're like,
"Oh, you suck. You're terrible. I hate you so much and you smell like spaghetti." We dismiss the
water as sentient thing because it can't really be controlled. The question is, now we're going to
move it. Is soy sentient? If you talk to a soybean, if you talk beautifully and you treat the plant
well with great emotional energy, will the plant sprout better? The idea of playing music for plants
is well known. People have said, "Yes, plants can respond." The science may be a little shaky,
but the theory is that plants can respond to the mood of the people around them. You treat them well,
you talk to them, you play music, they grow better. The initial question of, "Is soy sentient?"
I'm going to say yes. That led us down a deeper path because that was only just one part
of the soy conspiracy list. On the conspiracy list, there's several elements. Soy keeps popping up.
The second question is, "Is soy intelligent?" Now, we're going to table that for just a moment.
We're going to go ahead and move on to another theory. See, the reason why this is the grand soy
unified theory is that all of these theories combine into one, like a Voltron, deep soy.
Deep soy would be similar to the deep state, which is a term that we've heard a lot since
Trump became president. It's a shadow government within the main government that tries to pull
the strings. They get stymied a lot, but because they have all of these assets in the field and
all of these projects off the books, sometimes they think that they can run the government.
And maybe sometimes they do. Maybe during the Reagan administration, you had elements,
Ren and Iran, Contra and stuff like that. That would be considered deep state. So what's deep
soy? How does that play into it? Well, deep soy is a step away from the plan itself. And that's
where we have companies like Monsanto genetically modifying soybeans. Because soybeans are one
of the-- I probably should have started with this-- but soybeans are one of the most valuable
crop on the planet. Now, yes, wheat is the most-- it's wheat growing on every continent,
except Antarctica. It's the most-- it's been the oldest plant that we've grown. We grow it all
the time. But soybeans, it started off about-- and they really don't know, but about 5,000 BC
in Asia. And it's funny because they can actually trace the soy-- I know so much about soybeans now.
It's all useless information after this podcast is recorded. They can trace soybeans in America
to an actual person. What happened was there is a Japanese sailor whose boat wrecked, and he was
rescued by some American sailors. And this was back in like the 1800s. And he goes, "Hey, thanks for
rescuing me. Here's some soybeans." So we can trace it back that we have their names. I don't
remember them. But anyways, they'll be in the article. And then they brought the soybeans to
America. They began planting them. And then George Washington Carver, who-- I don't know if they
talk about him in school anymore. When I was in school, they always had a little segment on George
Washington Carver and the peanut and all that stuff. He was actually the one who was like, "Man,
we could use these things for oil. Like, these things would be great lubricant."
And then Henry Ford actually, in every car he made, a bushel of soybeans were used
to assemble that car. A lot of the plastics in that car were made of soybeans. And at one point,
he actually made an entire car frame out of plastic that was generated from soybeans.
Soybeans today, what we use them for is we use them as a lubricant. And we also use them as a
food source for animals originally. And then we use them as food for us. Now, part of the problem
is that there's mixed science on whether or not-- okay, it's not mixed science. The science is
pretty conclusive that soy is relatively good for you. But there's mixed opinions on whether or not
soy causes too much estrogen in people. And it causes girls to go through puberty younger. And
it causes men to have health problems like cancers that are usually alleviated with a higher amount
of testosterone. So deep soy comes into the fact. So after that overview, deep soy is where you have
Monsanto actually trying to control the supply of soybeans. And if you can control the soybeans,
you can control all of those other industries. So soybeans have been genetically modified soybeans
that have gotten loose into the wild and then begin planting and choking out the natural soybeans.
There have been times where they've created a soybean and it's gone through the safety process
where they're like, this soybeans totally fine. And they released it. And then scientists have
discovered that there's extra DNA in these soybeans. The soybeans now have unknown DNA. They can't
figure out why it's there or what it's doing or what health effects it has on humans. And Monsanto
is like, oh, no, no, it's totally cool. It's totally cool. And the European agency that discovered
this is like, it has extra DNA. However, you just waving it off and saying, that's cool and putting
on your sunglasses and skateboarding off to the ice cream store. Like it's not cool that it has
extra DNA. So Monsanto would be considered deep soy. Control the beans, control the world.
Now they've talked about things like weaponized soy. And that would be the equivalent of
creating the soy to either germinate in areas and choke out the natural soybeans. So eventually,
the only beans are out there are Monsanto beans. And you will have to buy more beans from Monsanto
to keep your soybeans running, your soy farm running, soybean farm running. And then there's
the theory that coins are being sprayed with soy. Now I know that sounds ridiculous at first,
but hear me out. If soy does cause trouble with the human species, and actually like raw soybean
flour can kill you, it causes pancreatic cancer, raw soybean flour before it's produced, and just raw
soybeans themselves, they're, they're, they're, they will make humans sick. They have to be prepared,
according to the research I've done. I'm going to put it, dude, the amount of links I have just
soy being related is ridiculous. But anyway, so I want to make sure that I'm sure that I'll have
to keep updating it because I, oh, I forgot this article, but so is soy being sprayed on coins?
The point of that would be is to make sure that every man, woman, and child is getting dosed with
soy to have these health effects. Now, and the thing is, is like soy itself may be affecting our
brains, not just our body, but our brains, to make us want to consume more soy. Now we know that
there's sugar addictions, and what's crazy is that you have the addictive thing in your brain,
but your body, if you eat carbs and you eat a lot of sugar, your body, in your stomach, flora,
no, it's fauna will grow that causes you, that feeds only off sugar and carbs, and it's in your
guts. And that sugar craving you have isn't in your brain. It's the fauna in your stomach,
in your intestines, releasing chemicals into your bloodstream to make you crave sugar, because
without it, with, if you go 48 hours with no carbs, that fauna begins to die. And like anything of
your starving, you're going to start dialing dominoes. Dominoes comes to your house. The fauna
in your gut will say sugar, sugar, sugar. And unless you can try this part of the keto diet,
unless you can control that chemical release, and it is hard, that's why you crave that sugar,
you're at there's actually almost like an alien, alien to your body, life form in there, that's
making you crave that sugar, you can go 48 hours without sugar and carbs, you're totally fine,
you don't crave it anymore, you don't look at a Snickers and go, oh man, I really want that.
But in that initial 48 hour period, you do want that Snickers. It's crazy. So we know that sugar,
you can have that craving for carbs and sugar. What if that same type of mechanism is developing
in us for soy? Now again, soy's really only been cultivated in the past 5000 years, and we've been
around for what, 100,000? Longer than that, and before we could process it, we couldn't eat it.
And it's only been in the Western world since about like the 1600s. So what if it is now
making our bodies crave soy? So we grow more soy, so we eat more soy.
And whoever is trying to weaponize soy or spray it on coins or put it into our water system,
they would be part of the deep soy system. They're trying to create, you're constantly
surrounded by soy, you're touching it, and then you're touching your mouth, even if you don't
think you're eating soy, you're craving more soy, you're getting soy all the time, all the time
in your system, which makes you crave more soy. So you're going to buy more soy, and soy is going
to be growing more. Now I know what you're thinking, Jason, that's all genius, and that's partially
true. But I know what you're also thinking, what does any of this have to do with the point you
left out? Is soy intelligent? I looked into this and looked into this and looked into this. I was
trying to find if soybeans released chemicals where they could talk to each other. I was trying to
find if soybean roots touched so they could talk to each other. I was trying to find any sort of
communication methods for soy, the soybean plants. I did learn that their roots can grow up to four
feet deep, which is much deeper than most vegetables, and definitely much, much deeper than almost any
other bean, I think any other bean, actually four feet deep. It's like a fifth grader.
And then I decided I had a little stroke of, stroke of inspiration. And I thought,
I did an episode a while back about a giant mushroom, a giant fungus, that was so big and so
old is the largest life form on the planet and has that mycelium underneath and how it can use
itself to communicate. It can send signals from one end of it to the other. The mycelium is made
to absorb nutrients and water and create the life form, but it also, it's basically a neural network.
And I started to look that up and I was seeing articles saying that plants can communicate
through fungus. If plants have this neural network, they can communicate through fungus.
That, that is when I had my Pepe Silvia moment. Now Pepe Silvia
is a character who may or may not have existed in the world of its hoist and in Philadelphia.
Technically, he did exist. We just never saw him. But he was the core of the conspiracy
that Charlie was trying to figure out. Who is Pepe Silvia? I googled soybeans mycelium.
The soybeans are infested with it in America. Infested with it. They don't know where it came
from. They don't know why it grows. And a soybean plant with the mycelium spread out underneath the
ground can still produce soybeans and it takes over entire fields, entire crops. So in that field,
it can pass messages from one soybean plant to the other. They can talk.
They can gain intelligence and they can plan their maneuvers. They're sentient. We've checked that.
They're intelligent. They have a neural network. There are companies and groups on the outside
like Monsanto who has made it their goal to spread the soybean. And through both outside factors like
greedy corporations making sure that soybeans are in every type of food, that making sure that
their genetically modified soybeans are infesting otherwise fertile lands and growing. And who knows?
Maybe it's the maybe that's part of the extra DNA. Maybe they have engineered the soybean to have the
mycelium to create the neural network so the soybeans can talk. Because maybe it's not Monsanto
running the soybean farms. Maybe it's the soybean farms infesting us
and making us eat more of them. Making us become vegan. Making us become health conscious.
Making us go through puberty earlier. Trying to get us to a stage where we just want to eat
nothing but soy. Nothing but soy. And that is how it controls us. That is the grand unified soy theory
from the initial beans being picked 5000 years ago. All the way to today. All the weird coincidences.
Like what are the chances of them finding a Japanese guy who happened to have a bunch of
soybeans on his back? To George Washington Carver figuring out all this great stuff. To us not only
using them for food but using them in the production of automobiles and petroleum. We want we need
the soybeans. If the soybeans disappeared civilization would fall apart. That is the grand soy unified
theory. Well that wraps it up for this episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I hope you had a fun time
learning the truth about soy. I know I did. Now everything I said except for maybe three things
was absolutely true and could be backed up with evidence. Monsanto has made soybeans when they
genetically modified them. Now there's extra parts of DNA and missing parts of DNA and all of that.
The history of the soybean. How it being brought to America was just a guy with soybean on his back
so maybe he was controlled by soybean. But then the opinion jumped in. Is soy sentient? There's no
nothing to back that up. The only place I found that out was on deleted a reddit post that someone
quoted. The fact that mycelium is some sort of neural network that allows soybeans to plot the
overthrow of the world. Mycelium can be a network that lets plants communicate. But it doesn't let
them you know by step evolution become a brain controlling bean. Soybeans have been found in
humans to cause absolutely no changes in the brain structure or no measurable changes in the brain
structure except for elderly Italian women which is odd. And even then it had something to do with
their existing dementia. Monsanto trying to be deep soy. I do think Monsanto I think companies do
want to corner the soybean market because it is so valuable. And there's all the stuff about Henry
Ford in the car and the soybeans and that's all true. Those are all true pieces of information.
But what I did spend a week researching this and what happened was I went into it and I wanted it
to be real. I wanted grand soy unified theory which is an actual term to be real. I wanted deep
soy to be real. These are some of the most requested stories that I've gotten. People want to know
because this is all on the conspiracy list. I go into this stuff I wanted to be real.
And even I was like halfway through my research is like I said I'm finding nothing. I had to start
then looking at where soybeans can grow. Can they grow anywhere? No there's very certain.
I went in with the hypothesis that soy is sentient, intelligent and it is evolving to basically
take over. That was the hypothesis I went in. Did I go in believing that hypothesis? No. No. That was
just the most entertaining hypothesis and I could find no information to pack up anything that I
found. I could just find bits and pieces of scientific articles in history of the soybeans
and cultivation and stuff like that. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
We're at Twitter @JasonOCarpenter and I've got a lot of Twitter support. I'm really appreciative
of that. You can hit me up on Facebook at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio. I think if did I say
deadrabbitradio@gmail.com I don't I'm incredibly tired. Thanks again to Ash Black for providing all
of the artwork for all of the logo artwork. That's going to be our episode for Friday. That's going
to be our episode for the week. I hope you guys had fun. I hope you guys don't hate soy now.
I'm okay on it. It's not a big deal for me. But I actually think the takeaway story of tonight
but the Grand Soy Unified Theory was kind of a debunk. The soy helmets that we can control,
we can make a zombie army. That's a terrifying story from tonight. Don't have nightmares. Come
back Monday and we'll start another week of Deadrabbit Radio. I'll see you guys later.
[Music]