What happens when the predator meets a sexual predator?
And we're gonna take a look at an interesting UFO encounter, the aftermath, and the craziness that continues to this day today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day, too.
I'm not feeling that good. I did quit the chewing tobacco. I have switched to the locenges to
help me step down. I feel like I'm just like sweaty and gross, man.
I've never had this reaction to
stepping down off nicotine. I'm thinking I might be coming down with something. I feel gross and
here's a little mind-twister for you.
I actually already recorded this intro of the show earlier and then I did the first story,
but I took some energy droplets and now I'm like more energetic.
So I'm gonna basically probably do everything else again. I don't know. We'll see how this ends.
I feel like both gross and like I could wrestle a bear. Super bizarre. Now energy droplets,
I should let you know. I found them. In Hood River, we have these little boxes.
They're like these little food bank boxes just on random corners and you just put food in there and you take food out if you need some.
It's kind of cool. I went there one day. I'll just stop by there once in a while, grab some applesauce.
But anyways, I went there to get some applesauce and
they had these little
jars of like homeopathic goo stuff like
squeeze 40 drops in your water and drink it. And it was stuff I never heard of so you know me. I took it.
I was like, oh, more free stuff and actually works really good. I would tell you what they are if I could pronounce it. This one's
L.E.U. Thero
and this one's Chizandra. I'm pretty sure it's just like Rose Seaman.
I think it's like Petal Juice or something like that. But yeah, I actually feel super more energetic than I did when I started recording this episode.
Yeah, so I think we're gonna go ahead. I'll probably just re-record everything. I wanted to do a quick note.
A couple episodes back, a couple months actually. We did an episode on Pankreus Denial
where I featured a young girl's gay BTS
fanfiction that happened to mention Pankreus now. I really liked that episode.
That was a fun little journey. And just recently I said, you know what?
I hope none of my listeners would ever harass anybody over that.
And I went and I checked in on her and I said, hey, I'm Jason Carbone. I do this podcast.
Here's the episode. I was just making sure everyone was being nice and she got back to me and she was like, thank you so much.
I'm sorry for making you feel uncomfortable reading this stuff and you have a great podcast and thank you very much.
So I wanted to do a quick shout out. Thank you guys.
That was a kind of a litmus test, honestly. When I released that episode, I thought I want to see how people react.
If I put up this Pankreus Denial story and people bombard her with negative comments,
I think it would change the tone of the show, honestly.
I don't think I'd be able to highlight those kind of individual weird things.
I would have to stick to kind of broader topics. But the fact that I was able to say, oh, listen,
here's this girl's story and because I provided the link and yeah, that was awesome, guys.
I was really kind of concerned about that at the time and I, it was in the back of my mind.
At that point, it showed me going on maybe 40 or 50 episodes and you guys have been really cool,
really respectful to each other. I think, yeah, it's a great community.
So I'm really happy to have you guys as listeners and like I said, to have you guys as friends.
We are having pushback and I'm not going to go into super detail because I have to see what the next step is.
But one of the people that I did an episode on has found that episode and they are not happy.
So we will see if, how they want to proceed with that. I cannot make any comments other than that at this time.
But as it goes forward, and you guys can easily figure it out because it's the only video that's getting down.
It's the only video that's getting consistently downvoted.
But I don't want to specifically say anything until this particular person decides to make a move
and then we will go forward because it, I listened to the episode the other day and I stand by it.
And yeah, I just need to wait because you know, we have, you know, the podcast is safe,
but YouTube, it's easy to get videos removed and copyright strikes and all sorts of stuff like that.
So, and again, I also don't want to harass him like, oh, you don't like my video.
You're getting your army to come after me. You're online at, you know, I'm not going to be, that's not the point of the show.
However, if it does get out of hand, I will have to address it.
But for right now, I'm just kind of stating it like that a little bit of news segment on the show.
Let's go ahead and get started.
So I've actually recorded this part of the show three times. I had it focus. I had it on an earlier episode.
I cut it. I recorded it before I took my Rose Seaman.
I think that's really the only way I can describe it.
It tastes like a rose was like just jacking off in a bottle.
There was a sexual predator on the set of the movie, The Predator, and that's funny enough.
But this is the thing. This has always been the key. Every, like I said, every quarter.
This is a couple of times it always seems to run a little long.
So I'm going to try to keep it short.
Let's get to the details. There is an actor named Stephen Wilder Strigel.
He is a convicted sex offender with children and his friend is Shane Black, the director of The Predator.
He did Iron Man 3. He did The Nice Guys. I think he did Kiss, Kiss, Bing, Bing.
He wrote The Original Predator and their friends.
So when he got out of jail, he did a six month stint for enticing a child by a minor
and then some other just kind of legally risk of injury to a child.
And so he did six months. He got out. Hey buddy, Shane, can you give me a leg up?
And she's like, oh yeah, sure. No.
And he starts writing these little parts for him into these movies.
In The Recent Predator, Olivia Munn is in it.
There's the scene where she's jogging and like a creepy guy comes up to her and is like,
hey baby, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. Olivia Munn blows him off.
The day before it's supposed to premiere at a film festival, somehow Olivia Munn finds out
that this Steven Wilder/Straigle guy is a convicted child, a convicted sex offender.
She tells the studio, studio wanting no bad press and this time
clipped the scene out of the movie.
And then what happened was Olivia Munn feels like the cast and the director blackballed her
because they had another like photo shoot or press conference.
They didn't show up or something like that.
That's the story in a nutshell. This is the reason why it's on this show because again,
that's just gross. And even though it fits into the true crime thing,
it's not incredibly interesting. This is why it's on the show.
This type of behavior is why people believe in pizza gate and frazzledrip and all of that stuff.
This type of thing where a powerful person hires a convicted sex offender to be in multiple movies
when somebody powerful and rich. I mean, Shane Black isn't like the biggest guy in Hollywood,
but he's also not a small fry. He's also not a first time director.
When people who have sway protect pedophiles, it is not that far removed.
It is far removed, but people make the connection.
If this single high level director, name director, is protecting one pedophile,
therefore Hillary Clinton is protecting a thousand pedophiles.
Ergo, pizza gate is real. That's why people believe in this stuff.
I have my own thing about pizza gate and I'll talk about that in a second,
but that's why people believe in these worldwide pedophilic networks and all of that.
And that like Obama's like, hey, Queen Elizabeth, try this.
And they're like, oh yeah, she's so hot. That's why they believe in this stuff because we see
smaller proof of it. We see pedophiles getting protected.
We saw it in Britain with that. What was that guy's name? The fat dude.
He recently, he was like, did the pop stuff. I'll have to look him up after the show,
but it's going to take too much time. Not Gary Glitter, but there's a bunch of them.
David Bowie like banged a 13 year old. That was the weirdest thing.
David Bowie bangs like a 13 or 14 year old. And then like when he passes away,
it's like, oh, he's this great icon. And me and my friend are like, dude,
remember when he banged that 14 year old? Like never, never mentioned, never mentioned.
So it's just so bizarre. And that's why people believe that those big conspiracies,
because we see the little ones. Oh, oh, and you guys are thinking, oh,
I just enticed a girl by a computer. No, he felt her up. She was actually a distant relative of
his, according to him. She was 14. Probably should have included all this detail earlier.
I did the other two times I recorded it. She was 14 years old. He was in his 40s.
They were talking online. He was saying she was sexy. They end up meeting up. He fills her boobs
up. Gross dude, like seriously, come on, man. And it's always this huge thing like, oh, I was just
lonely or I was feeling bad about my life. Whatever, man. Anyway, so that's beside the point. The
point is, is that that's why these conspiracies fester. I think stuff like frazzled drip is a
smoke screen. Frazzled drip has been debunked. If you don't know what frazzled drip is, it's supposedly
a video of Huma Abedin and Hillary Clinton eating a baby or girl, something like that.
So yeah, that's the thing. You have real conspiracies like this guy hiring a
chalm lester. You have, and then they're turning to these crazy conspiracies like Reptilians or
kidnapping kids from Iowa and taking them to Antarctica. That's where we have to be careful,
because the truth is always more interesting. Let's go ahead and move on to our next story here,
because I'm moving like a mile a minute. This one's super weird and not just the story itself,
but the path that took me on afterwards. What we're going to talk about here, and I was reading it,
and I was like, I was like, this is a UFO story I can get behind. This is the story. This is
Cash Landrum. Cash Landrum is a UFO incident that involved three people. This took place back in 1980.
It involved two older women, like, I mean considerably older. They were like in their 60s
or 70s when it happened. Betty Cash and Vicki Landrum, and there was a little kid in the back
seat or baby or something like that. They're driving down the road. They're in Texas. It's at night,
and they see this diamond shaped light vehicle that's illuminated. I guess it's better to put it
fly overhead, and they're like, what was that? They didn't cuss because they're from Texas.
It's 1980, and they're Christian, which we'll find out later. The thing flies overhead, and they're
like, what the heck? What the tarnation? And so they keep driving on the road. It's kind of like
an abandon area. Not abandoned, but not civilized, I guess. They're driving on the road for a bit
more, and it comes back over, and at this point it kind of stops in front of them. And it was weird
because you got this glowing diamond that's like, so and then Vicki says, that's Jesus. He will not
hurt us. And she's like, let's get out of the car and go see this glowing diamond floating in the
sky. So she talks cash. She talks Betty to getting out of the car. And the first thing they realized
when they got out of the car was how hot it was. And they said they could see fire coming out of
the bottom of it. And it was kind of like moving up and down like the fire almost like a hot air
balloon was helping propel it up a bit. And it was just kind of hovering there. And it kept getting
hotter and hotter and hotter as they were outside of their vehicle. At a certain point,
they're like, dude, we need to get back in this car because like we're otherwise we're going to melt.
They jump back in the car and Betty said she actually had to use her jacket to touch the door
handle to open it to get inside. It was that hot. And when she touched the dashboard of the car, her
hand like melt, not her hand didn't melt, but you know what I mean? Like pushed into the vinyl
because the car was getting heated up at this point. 23 Shinne helicopters
show up. Some of them were Shinne helicopters, I should say, but it was 23 helicopters. They counted
them. And they're surround the diamond. And they're like, what's going on there at this point at this
point. So the diamond had actually come down close enough that it was kind of blocking the road.
The helicopters show up. I'm going to keep saying helicopters show up just so I can make the noises.
It ain't me. It ain't me. The helicopters flying around, they're playing
Cleatance Clearwater. And so the diamond slowly starts to go up and takes off. And the helicopters
are like, ah, and they didn't actually scream. But anyway, so she they drive away. Now these young
ladies, I why am I saying the young, I know they're 80, these old ladies go home. They go to sleep.
They're like, that was weird. Next morning, they wake up, they're super sick. They're like,
vomiting, they're nauseous. No, they did not eat a Taco Bell. Their skin started to boil.
And they're like, oh my God, like they started getting like these burns on them. Betty ends up
like after a couple days, she keeps getting sicker and sicker. She can't even move. They take her to
the hospital. And both Betty and Vicki, the nurses are like, oh my God, you guys look like you're
burn victims, which is not something you want to hear when you walk into a hospital. They actually
are like, we don't know what happened to us. Like we don't know why we're so sick. And some people
go maybe there was radiation. So people have gone out there with Geiger counters, there's no
radiation. So they go, well, there's this other type of radiation that could have caused it.
Some people thought it could have been some sort of aerosol, some sort of like self defense mechanism
released by the vehicle, the UFO, not their car, to like mess with them. So no one's ever been able
to pin down and say exactly this. What they did was they said, you know what, that UFO was whatever
it was, it's from another planet. But the government must have known about it because all those
Chinooks were there. And that's a government helicopter. Those are generally used by US
forces. And I think Britain might use them too. But so what happens was they actually
contact their US senators in the area. And the senators said file a complaint with the Air Force
Base and see what happens. Like, you know, they're because oh, and they weren't the only ones who
saw this also, the 23 helicopters aside, there was two other cars in different parts of the area
that saw the light. So people really took it seriously in that area. And of course, you know,
they're boiling the people are like, I saw UFO. And you're not going to be like, oh, it was just
swamp gas as they're like barely mobile and their eyes are burnt shut. It wasn't that bad. But they
were like had physical issues with their skin and things like that. So the senators are like, well,
once you file a report, file a complaint with the Air Force Base in the area. And they were,
they said, well, according to Wikipedia, it says that cash landroom in Colby, I keep thinking Colby
is an infant. How old is this kid? Anyways, the baby was talking apparently to they were interviewed
at length at Bergstrom Air Force Base, and they were told to hire a lawyer and seek financial
compensation. This is where the story started to get a little weird. Now I could see the senators
going, well, you just file a complaint with the Air Force Base. But I can't imagine the Air Force
Base going, mm hmm. So you're melted and you're vomiting for the past five years. You should
sue us. No, what? Like if I go into Mervins and I'm like, hey, I tripped on your shirt. They don't
go, hey, well, you know what you should sue us. That's when the story started to go sideways for me.
Inter lawyer Peter Gersten took on the case pro bono. He says, I am going to do this. They
were in court for several years, suing them for $20 million. And in 1986, I remember this event
happened in 80. In 1981, they talked to the senators. Now we're 1986. And the judge dismissed the case.
Judges missed the case and said that the plaintiffs could not say, could not prove the helicopters
came from the US government. And military officials testified that the United States Army does not
have a large diamond shaped aircraft in their possession. So it went to that level of court,
where they were actually having witnesses coming and all of that stuff. Definitely too early for,
you know, like court TV, and I'm not saying that flippantly, but I'm saying like when courts are
being recorded, I'm sure you can find the transcripts of it. So I was like, still, that's a really
interesting story. I started looking into the debunking stuff on it. The debunking is actually
really weak on this one. The main point, there's two main points when they're debunking this.
There's no way you could fly 23 helicopters in a group, like around something. And I was like,
that does seem like a lot. And I, they were fairly insistent about the number. That's a lot of
helicopters to be in an area and not crash into each other. So I don't know. Another one of the
other witnesses farther away said they saw 14 or 12 fly overhead. That sounds more believable than
23. And then the other thing was the, how, how sick and disgusting did Betty Cash look before the
UFO? We don't know what her medical history was before the UFO. She might have always been covered
in boils and vomiting all the time. So because we don't know what she was like before, we can't really
say that the UFO caused that. And I can understand that in some sort of like liability lawsuit,
which I guess that was at $20 million. But if someone's like walking around with boils and you
can like look at photos of her pre boil, come on. It is curious though to, in the debunkers favor,
that they said, well, let us actually look at the medical reports when you went to the hospital
and reported this. And Betty was like, no, I'm not going to show them to you in private. I don't
want to release my medical reports. And now to be fair, I don't think I would release my medical
reports to a debunker, you know, either. I mean, because if I've lost the lawsuit, what do I have
to gain anyways? But they're saying their whole thing is we don't know how sick she really was.
They can't really debunk the sighting because there was multiple witnesses. And I mean, they can try
and they can look at her and go, yeah, you're gross, but when did you get gross? It's their question.
So interesting. Here's the key thing though. I read that and I was like, okay, this is cool.
This is a UF story I could get behind. I keep saying UF. This is a UFO story I can get behind.
It's fairly interesting. It's nothing too insane. You know, I like this one.
As I was looking at the debunking stuff, the lawyer's name came popped back up. So 2012,
you guys remember 2012, Mayan, Prophecy and all that stuff. Peter Gersten lives in Arizona. And he
said at 11/11/2012, I am going to climb up Bell Rock in Sedona, a dimensional portal.
It's going to open up. I'm going to jump into it. Okay, so here's just quote. I'm not going to read
the whole thing because it's kind of boring, but most of you will think I'm delusional and that
my insane act will certainly result in my death. Death is inevitable, at least nowadays. And 100
years from now, it won't matter whether I died in 2012 or 2013 or even 2020, but I believe that some
type of cosmic portal will be opening at that time and place. And then an opportunity will
present itself. I fully expect that it will either lead to the next level of this cosmic program,
freedom from an imprisoning time loop, a magical Martian like bubble, I don't know what that is,
or something equally as exotic. So he climbs up. Oh yeah, and also like a couple of months before
2012, a dolphin bites. He's snorkeling. He was diagnosed with cancer before this and he was
like, you know what, I'm just going to spend the my life. He's doing fine. He's still alive,
spoiler alert, but it's in remission. But anyway, so he goes, oh, and the story's not over, not
total spoiler. He's doing all this stuff, right? He goes snorkeling and he's swimming with the dolphin
and the dolphin bites his arm. But when he looked down at his arm, he saw three long scratches,
like where the teeth scratches arm and then one smaller scratch next to him. He looked at his
arm and he put in his blog, he goes, the dolphin was trying to write 1111 on my arm. Because
that's the time he has to jump into the portal. Why would you want this guy free or not working on
your court case? You, you, I, they probably saw something. I don't think they saw nothing. They
may have even seen some sort of craft that was being worked on. It could have been in just,
you know, having some trouble. The helicopter showed up. It could have been alien. I don't know.
But I think that story is more believable and it's more intriguing, honestly, than a bunch of
lights just sipping around in the sky. This is like a close encounter of the second time they
are impacted by it. Why would you hire this guy? They didn't hire him. He was free. Why would you
want this free dude working on your court case? He wants to jump into a portal. Now to be fair,
the court case was in 1981. He's talking about jumping into a portal in 2012. So maybe he wasn't
as crazy back then, but I mean, I bet you back then he was like jump like practicing jumping. Oh,
yeah, this guy does practice jumping in portals. He climbs up to the bell rock all the time still.
Okay, so he doesn't jump in 2012. The county actually supposedly sent a helicopter up there to
try to stop him. He was up there and he waited around and he was there for a while. He waited
past the 1111 portal didn't open up. He didn't jump. Now see, it was originally called leap of
faith because he was originally saying he would have to jump before the portal opened up to show
that he had faith in the computer or cosmic computer program. But he didn't jump. He walked back down
and everyone was relieved. As I was researching him, I find this article, much more recent article.
He turned 74 recently. And if you add seven and four, you get 11. He 11 is a mystical number,
apparently at 1111 on his 11 birthday. He's going to jump off the he's going to jump off the bell
rock. He has a sub session with jumping off the bell rock. And he says he needs to bring
I just don't this stuff's funny because I don't get how people get latched onto these certain
ideas. He has to bring 2222 people to the top of bell rock by 2222 of the winter solstice,
December 21st of 2018. He's still doing this this year. He's going to have to bring
not I don't think they'll have to be up there at the same time. That would be incredibly dangerous.
But before 2222. So what is that like before 10 o'clock 10 20? Why do I care?
Why am I trying to figure out the time? The point is he has to bring a bunch of people up.
And he has like three months left to do it. And then he will be able to go to the next level of
his quote unquote holographic reality program. The one UFO story that I've looked at over the
course of the show that I was like that sounds really, really likely this guy's tied into it.
The vortex jumper. I got it. I'm intrigued by this dude. But we all know he's not going to jump
this time either. I hope he doesn't jump, obviously. Oh, and some guy was like, Hey man,
don't jump. And he was like, Don't you want to see something mystical happen? He's like,
Yeah, I want to see something mystical happen. I don't want you to jump either.
He's weird. It's delusion. I wouldn't be surprised if he's trying to get money. You know what? I'm
going to get myself in trouble again if I start calling people frauds. But Peter Gersten, please
don't ever offer to represent me in any sort of UFO related trial. Because you just just too weird
even for diamond shaped UFOs floating around Texas, even people boils. And that is a high bar.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address. You're going to also hit us
up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio. At Twitter, wait, now that doesn't make sense. Twitter.
Wait, what? How to at Jason O. Carpenter is going to be our Twitter. Fuck. At Jason O. Carpenter is
going to be our Twitter. I think I'm coming down with something guys. But thanks for listening.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily, even if I'm sick, paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]