caves, dark deep holes inside the earth. Often they contain gold, coal, gems, or other things,
but sometimes they may contain little girls. And then, and then we do the impossible. We
turn the tables. We bring the fight to them. Because on this episode, we are going to abduct
an alien today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Let's go ahead
and get started here. Now for our first story, we're staying in Oregon. We're actually going
to Mount St. Palins. But we're not just going to the mountain. We're going underneath. So
let's put on our hard hats and our little light flash bulb things. Headlamps, that's
what they're called. Do do do. Turn them on. And we are walking into the caves. Specifically,
the ape caves. Now I know what you're thinking. Is this a Bigfoot story? No, it's not a Bigfoot
story. But the caves are named the ape caves because a bunch of Boy Scouts used to hang
out there and they really loved Bigfoot. Bigfoot is a big thing up here. Now we are entering
the ape caves here. I know you're afraid of the dark. So hold my hand. And as we start
to walk into the cave, I kind of reach over and I grab your hand. I'm like, I know you're
afraid of the dark. Don't worry. Don't worry. I'm here with you. And you're like, Jason,
you're the one whose hand is trembling. I've been in a precisely one cave my entire life.
I was on a field trip in college. There was about 30 of us and it absolutely sucked. I
like the idea of caves. When I play Minecraft, I always build bases underground. And I actually
now have to fight that because I read this article before. And it said that people who
have a fantasy of digging underground want to crawl back into their mom's womb. And I'm
thinking bunkers, man. Like if zombies attack nuclear bombs and stuff like that, there is
something comforting about being underground. But now I'm also thinking about my mom, my
mom's womb. Whenever I'm thinking about like, oh dude, zombies attack, I'm going to build
this underground for preferably before the zombies attack the underground fortress exists.
I'm not breaking the shovel out as the shambling undead. I'm like, no, no, no, I've only gotten
a foot into the ground. Preferably I would have an underground fortress. But at the same
time it would be really embarrassing if you built this great like bomb shelter underground.
And all your friends also read that article and they're like, Hey, Jason, nice bomb shelter.
By the way, how's your mom doing? You call your mom lately. I'm like, shut up. I'm going
to survive the nuclear war. When you're in the bomb shelter, you can hear my mom's heart
beat. You're like, Jason, that's a little weird. What? No, no, it's totally fine. This
is what the DoD recommends. Boom, boom, boom, boom. Anyways, that all means said, we're
going underground. And again, I don't like caves either. Maybe that means I don't like
my mom's womb. I don't know. We'll talk to my therapist about that. We are going into
this cave. Now, this story takes place in the eight caves. That's a cave system underneath
Mount St. Helens in Oregon. And it's the longest lava tube system in the United States. Now,
a parent, this is the story that supposedly happened. And it happened to a point. I'm
curious to see how it really plays out. There's a YouTuber called exploring with Josh. He's
this dude who I think he does some urban exploring, but he does a lot of cave stuff as well. He's
walking with his buddy through this cave, through the eight caves. They have all their gear on.
They're recording it for the YouTube channel. They squeeze through a tight hole and there's
a little girl alone in the cave and she's crying and she doesn't speak any English. And they
help her out of the cave. She's just like frightened and you can watch the video online.
You can watch the video on YouTube. It's there. They help the girl out of the cave. And this
got reported in the news and it was a big video for Josh. Now, I have some questions. Obviously,
it happened in the sense that it was filmed. The question, it's a little convenient that
the girl not only did she not speak English, but nobody got her name. Her parents never
appear on camera. Apparently they're tourists from some unnamed country like Talred or whatever.
I don't know. There's not a lot of information. Even the reporters who were looking in it
were kind of, it seems like reporters saw the YouTube video and then called up Josh and
said, "Hey, what happened?" So who knows? It could be staged. It most likely staged.
But people do stupid stuff because then, as I was looking into this, again, I don't want
to say 100% that it's fake. It just seems suspicious. When I was looking into this, I came across
this Reddit post. This guy was responding to this video. So this Reddit user's name
is Floceraptor and they said, "Listen, I actually do a bunch of cave climbing, digging, whatever
it is, spelunking in Britain." And they have this rule where public caves have to have
a gate on them that you can come and go. And this guy is saying that one day him and a
steamer in this cave is a very difficult cave. It was on private property. They got permission
to go in there. It's not a cave that a lot of people go through. There's a gate that
you have to unlock and then you go in. You're supposed to lock it behind you, but it wouldn't
lock from the inside. So they're like, "Oh, you know, who else is going to be in here?"
They start going all through this cave and at one point, they hear something behind them.
The people in the crew hear something behind them. They turn around with their flashlights.
What is that? And who had followed them in was a father and his six-year-old daughter.
And they were using the ropes that they were climbing down and they had no gear of their
own. And they tried hiding when they got caught and the spelunkers had to turn around and
get them back up. And they said it took a long time to get them back up. Now, again,
assuming that story is true, they were saying that if we had left them and we didn't know
that they were there, they probably would have died down there. They would have had no
gear to get back up. That one's a little suspicious because why is a dude bringing his daughter
into a cave alone anyways? That one's a little creepy for another reason. But if I was walking
through a cave with my buddies and we were professional or M-Pro cave people, we're
troglodytes. We're trying out for the troglodyte team. We turn around and I see an adult man
and a little girl and he's like, "Oh, no, I'm her dad." And I would be like, "You're
not the dad." First, someone's getting beat up. Not me. Someone's getting clobbered in
that cave with my big old Captain Cave man club. Because I'm going to be extremely suspicious
why you're hanging out here with a little girl. Then after my friends pull me off and
they're like, "No, no, no, look at..." They're doing DNA tests to prove real quick. It's his
daughter. It's his daughter. I'm like, "Uh..." Then I would be like, "Now you're just
into the..." Wait, where was I going with this? I guess I was just beating the guy up. There
was a reason why before I was beating the guy up. If I was spelunking in a cave, first
off, that's it. I wouldn't believe your story. And secondly, you're probably getting beat
up just for endangering your child. But so... And again, people are stupid. It's possible
that in the Josh story, the girl wedged into this little thing in the pitch dark and her
parents were waiting outside the cave too. That's another thing that doesn't make sense.
Like, you're... Your father... Who's the worst... Who's the worst parent? You have a mother
and a father take their daughter into a cave. They lose track of the daughter in the cave.
They then leave the cave and wait for her to come out. That's pretty terrible. Versus
a man who may or may not exist for one. This could just be a total minute, but a man who
may or may not be a girl's father, taking her deep into a mind and then hiding from
the only people who could rescue you. But anyways, both stories are possibly fake. However,
I want you to keep both of those stories in mind and imagine both of those stories being
100% true as we go into this last cave story. This is also... This is from the Reddit thread.
There's a Reddit... I don't know what... Is there a subreddit? Subreddit, that's the word.
The truth is here. This guy says, "I used to work at a mine." Right? And now we're
in West Virginia, so we're leaving behind Oregon. We're headed West Virginia. And this
guy, what he does is he works for this... Everyone on Reddit works for some sci-fi company. He
works for this company that when there's an accident, he takes the device down and it's...
Does a 3D scan of the area and then he can make, like, models of where these accidents
are, which I may... That technology may or may not exist. I'm doubting that it does.
You throw a probe droid through a mine, do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
pop a leg but I asked that you open the doorway that you control open the doorway that swings many ways into many places and I asked that you open a doorway that leads to a gray alien so basically open what if the gray alien spacewalk and opens in a deep space I decompress in a heartbeat
thank you s rob totally killed me pop a leg but open the doorway that leads to a gray alien pop a leg but open a doorway the doorways open this rope or you're supposed to have a rope by the way you're like no no you're doing the ritual along with me you're like
getting sucked into deep space as well this rope represents that which restrains and maintains a great alien where it is and now you're tying your hands together very very dangerous in any circumstance but if you're evoking a great aliens probably even worse and then you go when I am free the great alien shall be within the circle of stones and then you escape from this rope you just put around your wrist I am free you say a great alien shall step through the door and be within the circle of stones and then you escape from this rope you just put around your wrist I am free you say a great alien shall step through the door and be within the circle of stones and then you escape from this rope you just put around your wrist I am free you say a great alien shall step through the door and be within the circle of stones and then you escape from this rope you just put around your wrist I am free you say a great alien shall step through the door and be within the circle of stones and then you escape from this rope you just put around your wrist I am free you say a great alien
you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like you're like
shut it party adjacent house you hood river gets invaded tomorrow none of that's going to happen because that's complete nonsense and the thing is is that like I said he has a ton this is how he writes 200 books so you're like okay that's interesting but that's what a couple pages of the book that's
right he then has a ton of other spells that are the exact same ritual pop a leg but one foot in the other da da da da just certain words are changed to do this to do that to do this to do that and they're like okay so you what are the other things
Jason I want to know how to do these other things okay calm down calm down plus by listening to this podcast a bunch of aliens have now inhabited your house as well but here's some other things you can do you he's taught you how to abduct a gray alien we all know about those communion
X files he teaches you how to abduct a blue alien you ever hear of a blue alien you know those famous those famous blue aliens it's such a bizarre that like even a green alien you figure he means reptilian but when someone says oh yeah I saw some gray aliens the other day you can totally picture how they look
someone says I saw a blue alien you're like smurf like it was a gray alien with blue skin they're like no no no blue alien what does that mean teaches you how to abduct a blue alien teaches you how to summon a reptilian alien oh oh get a seven foot tall reptile to do your bidding
because he also tells you this is where we start to go off the rails okay teaches you how to abduct a gray alien you're looking at an alien in your living room and then they're like get out of here and he goes away do the same thing with a blue alien do the same thing with a reptilian but where does that go
teaches you how to here here's the actual title Papa leg but ritual for a blue alien to attack someone of your choosing for you who now we're getting interesting you can summon a blue alien again whatever that is to attack someone for you Papa leg but ritual for a blue alien to kill a chosen person
oh no s rod really unlocking the universe here but then things get real these are all real ones I'm about to read for you Papa leg but ritual to abduct a gray alien and ask him to dance for you Papa leg but ritual to make a gray alien where address Papa leg but these are all real I'm not these are not jokes that I'm making up this one is probably one of the most curious ones though
Papa leg but ritual to get a blue alien to wear a dress okay that's normal Papa leg but ritual to get a blue alien to wear a suit you can't make a gray alien wear suit there is no if you want to see a gray alien dressed up in formal wear absolutely impossible who do you think s Rob is God do you think any man has that power but a blue alien yeah you totally make more suit or dress doesn't matter you can also get a blue alien to wear a suit
you can also get a blue alien to dance for you and this would hack I got admit this is probably the most intriguing one Papa leg but ritual for a reptilian alien to dance for you I don't think you can get him to wear the dress but you wouldn't that I mean listen my war against the reptilians is long and storied I hate those guys I don't like reptiles to begin with a reptilian race if they actually exist I hate him more than the grays but I wouldn't mind watching one dance
I would not mind watching an eight foot tall reptilian creature kind of you know gyrating its hips maybe have a little tail maybe do a little like twerking action just like stuck in those stones and I'm just watching it put on some old school J Lo and it's just kind of moving there bobbin can't control itself slave to the rhythm and I'm just sitting there my hands tied my hands are tied up and watching this reptilian just yeah
I can move those scales baby yeah I want to see you sweat oh I forgot reptiles can't sweat I'll get a giant hot rocky clay on top of it oh yeah baby that's how you modulate that's how you modulate your body body temperature oh I wish I could modulate my body temperature yeah yeah so s Rob forget that I'll have to continue to think about that after I'm done recording s Rob will that was a female lizard by the way I want to know
I want to be clear on that one at least in my head was you may have been picturing something else s Rob has unlocked the secrets in the universe this guy has written 200 books this is again generally the first part is hilarious of these books because again I've read a couple other ones the first part
hilarious and then once you realize that every spell is exactly the same it's just funny this guy is totally sincere as far as I can tell to this guy's totally sincere but I want to dig more I we're going to do another cover another one of his books but I actually I've always been thinking about things to give my patreon supporters and people have recommended me doing polls so I'm going to give my patreon supporters they're going to be able to pick my next book that I'm going to read by s Rob and here are choices
puppet love magic which is learn the power of a cult puppetry so that love can be yours with this book and a puppet about obviously with this book and a puppet you have the ability to change your love and sex life forever now I'm assuming I'm not having sex with a puppet but this is an s Rob book so we will find out so my patreon I'll put the pull up on my patreon you can choose between puppet love magic or super villains book of extremely
in advisable magic and this book this book actually has a review five stars by the way this book is this the description of this this book is extremely in advisable magic don't do this don't do this this book is extremely in advisable magic for the super villains
I don't know where I don't know what reality he thinks he lives in he keeps referring to people as super villains in his book that is where the super villains within allows you to so what do you think is in advisable magic you can make a reptilian do a sexy dance and do all this other stuff here's some in advisable magic make Lucifer dress and women's clothing I would say that that is probably not a good thing to do make Lucifer dress and women's but you know what maybe he would do that anyways
maybe it's just a Wednesday night he wants to dress up like a beautiful woman maybe this is like only do this spell on Wednesday nights that's when Lucifer goes out to Barney this book will allow me to make Lucifer dress and women's clothing perform magic for mass destruction that's a good pairing destroy a city make Lucifer cross dress
Robbery the occult way make a devil not the devil but make a devil perform stand-up comedy strip magic for everyone the whole world gets naked and then make the devil tap dance and perform at sing-alongs and karaoke's as far as I can tell this guy is 100% legit as far as I can tell this guy's 100% legit he's been doing this for years so even though the book ends with make the devil tap dance and perform sing-along and karaoke's I'm pretty sure this guy is I'm pretty sure he's not a good guy
I'm pretty sure he believes it's real so patreon supporters can vote on those books everyone else will wait with bated breath to see what I have to spend my weekend reading I can pretty much guess which one you guys are going to pick from those descriptions but we will bring you more s-rob I think this is going to be a regular book review section because if the if we lived in a world where these magic spells absolutely work this is the world I would want to live in this is the world I would want to live in
I want to live in a world where every strip club is called circle of stones and you go on it's just a bunch of aliens doing sexy dances and a bunch of dudes chillin and pop a leg bus sitting in the back at the DJ booth being like my work here is complete
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead rabbit radio
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to it today have a great weekend guys
*outro music*