The world of UFO-ologists goes head to head with an army of 9 year olds.
And then we travel back to my own personal ghost hunting days. Did I really meet a civil war ghost?
What happened when the dark shadow rushed towards my car?
And more importantly, was I possessed the day I picked up a pair of burnt
pants today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carbner. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys are
having a ton of fun coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now. One of our livestream contributors.
It's Spiced. Everyone give a round of applause to Spiced walking into Dead Rabbit Command. Spiced,
you're going to be our captain or pilot of this episode. You guys can't support the show
financially. I totally understand. Just spread the word about the show really, really helps out a
lot. By the way, so I'm going to go ahead and touch you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgable.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We are headed on out to Sweden.
So the reason why we're headed out to Sweden is we're going to meet a young entrepreneur.
That's how you pronounce it in Sweden. That I'm sure all of you guys are familiar with PewDiePie.
PewDiePie, the number one solo YouTube channel, has millions and millions of followers. He's a
gamer and he does a lot of reaction videos. Recently, I saw in the export that PewDiePie has
decided to try his hand at debunking UFOs. This is a really exciting time for UFOologists because,
well, technically it's always an exciting time for UFOologists because you can get abducted in
any moment. It's always super exciting if you believe in aliens, but because that government
report is coming out in July. There's a government report the US government is going to release
saying basically stating all the information they know about UFOs and I imagine it's not going to be
groundbreaking. It would be cool if it was right. It would be cool if it was like the first first
page is a picture of Joe Biden and the Grey Alien like leaning back to back like the Twins movie
poster. But is it going to? No. Are they going to reveal the existence of the Pleiadians or the
Reptilians? Do they declare war on Great Britain against the Great Lizard Queen? No. We're already
getting a little bit of leaks from the report and basically it's they're saying some of the stuff
could be Russian, some of the stuff could be Chinese, some of the stuff we don't know. And that's
pretty much what that report's going to say. It hasn't officially come out. There could be a change,
but if we did have access to this alien technology or if we had access to the aliens themselves,
a law written by US lawmakers isn't going to change anything. The Great Reptilian Congress of
Mark R. 9 isn't going to be like, "Our plans have been stomped due to three senators! We must
reveal our secrets." Now, you know, they would just bury it. If it was really close to the truth,
these senators never would have been able to pass the bill in the first place. Like,
it is fun that we're taking it this seriously. I think it's a huge step forward for UFOology,
but I don't really suspect anything big is going to come out of the paper. Because UFOs are so in
the news and because people are finally taking this subject seriously, and I do think it needs to
be taken seriously, you're having other people who normally want to talk about UFOs talk about UFOs,
and it's great because we're getting all these different voices. Inter-Puty Pie. He did a awesome
dismissal. And this might not be what you guys want to hear and listen to with paranormal podcasts,
but you gotta be open to everything. He did an awesome debunking of two huge UFO videos that,
the most recent one that came out of thing in 20, off the top of my head, I think it was 2019,
that's been going around online. And then he debunked the Tic Tac video. The very famous Tic Tac
video shot over, I think it was the Pacific Ocean, and they had that battle fleet. Usually,
like Tic Tac video right now has been used the most. Like they're like, "How can you dispute this?
Like this is recorded with military technology and all these pilots." And everyone can have their
opinion. But PewDiePie did a great, it was, it's super interesting because he seems to be along
the lines like, "Yeah, aliens would be cool and everything like that, but you have to,
I don't think these videos are real. I do not think these videos are real." And using like his
flashlight on his cell phone camera, and he, he's looking at this stuff and he goes, "This is how
this doesn't make sense. This doesn't work." And not saying it doesn't make sense by like,
how fast it's going and stuff like that. Like there's no way a vehicle could go 10 Gs. No, no,
no. He's saying like, "The way the camera is working, that isn't what they think it is."
He goes, "It is weird. It is weird." He goes, "The camera's picking up something, but it's not
doing the things that the UFO community thinks that it's doing. It didn't go under water. It
simply stopped giving off heat." He doesn't go on it. He doesn't go, "Oh, it must just be a flock
of birds or it must be a hot air balloon." He doesn't give an alternative solution, which is totally
fine. So when you debunk something, you don't necessarily have to prove what it is. You can
just go, "It's not what they're saying it is. I don't know what it is. It's something weird."
I recommend watching the video. I'm going to put it into the show notes. It's like 15 minutes long.
It's not too long. And at one point that I thought PewDiePie made, which was really interesting,
was he goes, "A new video comes out and it's easily debunked." And then someone goes, "Well,
what about these other 10 sightings? What about these other 20 sightings? What about all these
other videos?" And he goes, "Yeah, but those were fake too, but those were fake so long ago."
People debunked them back then, but the debunking story doesn't stick around. I'm paraphrasing,
but the video sticks around. And people keep watching stuff and they keep looking at fake
video footage. Stuff that is not necessarily faked on purpose, but stuff that's easily explained.
And you start to have this huge catalog of footage that is taken out of context,
and this is your worldwide phenomenon. Now, does it explain every single UFO sighting? No.
Does it explain ones where the aliens actually come down? No. But when we talk about stuff like
the Tic Tac video, there are explanations for what that could be. So I find it really,
really fascinating that that is also going mainstream. I don't think PewDiePie is some sort
of CIA asset, and he's trying to be the lone voice. It's really interesting because I think it goes
counter to what his audience would want anyways. If you put out pro UFO content, you will have
way more hits than you'll have if you put out anti UFO content. And because I'm not a total party
pooper, also in the show notes, I have someone who has made a YouTube channel that has 500
videos of UFOs. I mean, I just was like, "Oh, they're probably all fake." Still, if you want to go
through like vintage UFO videos, some of them are short, some of them are a bit longer. A guy
named Alexander Gottfriedsson. I wonder if he's sweetest too, not even looking at his name. He
put together five, he collected 500 videos of UFOs. So that's cool too. You can fish around on that.
Spiced. I'm going to toss you the keys of the carpenter copter. We are leaving behind Sweden
with these brand new chairs, these brand new PewDiePie chairs. We are headed out to Dyer Lane,
California. First off, I want to give a shout out to three long time Dead Rabbit radio listeners,
Lancaster, Barfiman362 and Chris K. Because they all recommended, I talk about the burnt pants,
and I know they're all looking at each other right now. They're like, "What?" Yes. Over the course
of about two years, you three reached out to me and said, "Tell the story about the burnt pants."
I had mentioned it on a past episode. I recorded an entire segment about the burnt pants, and I
remember recording it, and I remember just thinking in my head, "This isn't... I'm not doing the story
justice. I'm not doing the story justice. I don't like the way I was telling it." And I mentioned it.
I think the episode came out late or something like that. Like it was a huge... I recorded like a 30,
40 minute segment. It's a long story. I'm going to try to keep it short in this time as you'll
get your watch. Like great. And I said I recorded it, but I didn't release it. And those three people
over time were like, "Dude, we really want to hear the burnt pants story." So here you go, because
yesterday's Patreon was Steve Dainwood, close personal friend of mine. And I told him, I was like,
"Hey dude, I didn't know you listened to the show, and I go, I've mentioned you a couple times on the
show." And he's like, "Really?" And he goes, "Did you tell the story about the burnt pants?" And I was like,
"Now I have to." Like that one, we've had so many adventures together. And when I said I told a couple
stories about us, and that was the first thing, did you tell him the story about the burnt pants?
So I got to tell you the stories about the burnt pants. So thanks Steve for this saga.
Spiced, go ahead and land this carbon helicopter at Dyer Lane. Dyer Lane, if you look at it,
it's actually in the Urban Dictionary online. You can find a couple of rumors about it online,
but living in this area, everyone knew about Dyer Lane. It's a rural road.
Scooby-Doo didn't come into the studio. You know, like a country road. In Sacramento, in the
suburb, subdivision, no one is Alberta, kind of near Antelope Sacramento.
There is a road off of what avenue called Dyer Lane. And I always called it Dyer's Lane,
so I'll probably move back and forth between the two pronunciations, the correct one and then mine.
But Dyer Lane was this old country road. Incredibly dangerous. I remember because I grew up in
Citrus Heights. I actually grew up all over California, but I found my way back to Citrus
Heights when I was 17, 16, 17 years old. Citrus Heights, Orangevale is where I hung out. Antelope
is basically the other side of the planet, because it's farther away. It's not right next to me.
And that's where my boy Josh hung out. We had Josh and Nick and Jason Campbell,
and you know, like Liz and Cara and all that stuff, Jackie, Joanne, all of them. They all went to
like Center High. They were all in that area. I was in Cassarobal in Orangevale. So this is
far about, there's like high school days for me. So we're talking like 1994. So Dyer Lane
is this road right off of what? Now, what is one of the most traveled roads in Sacramento? Don't
look that up. There's no stat for it. It just felt like it when you were driving down it. But you
kept going, I think it was North on or even West or East. Just look it up. Just look, don't follow
my directions. But if you keep going down, what eventually becomes less and less populated,
you drive past the Godfather's Pizza. We've talked about that in past episodes. And we get to Dyer
Lane. You make a left. I don't remember that. You make, well, I guess it depends on your direction
you're going to. Otherwise you're crashed. Just look it up. But anyways, you turn onto Dyer Lane,
it feels like you're turning into another part of the world. It's bizarre. I mean, almost like all
the traffic sounds disappear. You are driving down this country road. There's just trees and
broken down houses. Now, some of these stories I'm going to tell you I may have already told. The
burnt pants I haven't, but I want to give a little more flavor. And I don't know what episodes to
link to because these personal stories are hard to keep track of. But when I worked at Godfather's
Pizza, I had to deliver a pizza to Dyer Lane. And everyone kind of laughed. Everyone kind of laughed.
And they're like, "Ha ha ha, you're going to die." I met Godfather's Pizza. I'm working with my boy
Josh, my boy Nick. Jason Campbell works there. Jason Anderson. It was a really good group of guys.
They all went to center high school. I went to Casa Robles, much cooler high school. They went to
some bust it all night school. We're working at Godfather's Pizza. So they knew all the legends.
They knew about Dyer Lane and these dudes because I was from the other side of Sacramento. Like,
Orangevale was about as far away from Antelope as you could get. And they all knew the stories
about Dyer Lane. And so I'm like this new delivery guy and I'm like, "Oh boy, my first delivery.
My first delivery actually almost got mugged in Rialinda." But I still kept working there. I was
like, "Oh, I got a delivery to Dyer Lane." And they're like, "Oh man." Now at this point I had already
heard some of the stories about Dyer's Lane because people know I'm a ghost nerd. So whenever I'm like
"We're sure this is I love ghosts." I have a tattoo that says, "I love ghosts even more than my shirt
would suggest." And so people would always share ghost stories with me or like stuff that would
spook me out. And I'm like hiding under their blankets. They're like, "Jason, go home please."
But you told me a scary story. They all told me about Dyer Lane and there's different versions
of this legend. One, and some of this stuff may be true. One of this part probably true.
Back in the 1930s apparently it was a meeting ground for the Ku Klux Klan. Because it is in the
middle of nowhere but it's super, super easy access. The second you turn on to Dyer Lane,
you can get away with anything. So what it'd be, and it's a lot of fields, at least back when I was
there, is just a lot of fields and the road goes straight for a while. Like Jason Mose wrote.
Let's do that. Go straight for a while. There's a 90 degree turn. There's no lights out there.
Then it goes straight again for quite a while. Then a 90 degree turn. Then it keeps going straight
and then 90 degree turn. And then you're back into civilization. There were a few houses here and there
but it felt wrong. It did feel different. Now some of that obviously suggestible. I mean the
Ku Klux Klan, if they were hanging out there, it's not the most lively of spots. I actually don't
know if they were ever there but actually that does lead me to another story. I remember once
this dude was harassing my boy Nick and he was trying to fight Nick and I'm washing my car. I'm
just trying to wash my car and I hear Nick inside. This is Josh's house. He's yelling on the phone
and I'm like, "What is going on?" So I walk in there. I'm like, "Hey Josh, what's going on?"
And Nick said, "Guys, someone wants to beat Nick up because he was sleeping with his girlfriend
or something like that." And I was like, "Dude, give me the phone. Give me the phone." I take the phone
and I just go, "Dyre's Lane, 3 AM." And the dude's like, "What?" I go, "Dyre's Lane." I go, "You got a problem.
Like this, we're talking all day long. Like this is petty. Like let's settle it. Dyre's Lane,
3 AM. Let's go. I'll go out there with Nick." And then the dude's like, "I am not into that
clan stuff." I go, "Me neither, dude, but we can do what we need to do out there. No cops
gonna show up. It's just going to be us and you. Who you want to bring? We're gonna bring who we bring.
Dyre's Lane, 3 AM." And I just hung the phone up and I go, "Can I finish washing my car and
beats now?" And sure enough, we had a party that night. We were supposed to have a party that night.
We did. And at about 2, 15 AM, we drove out there and sat out in Dyre's Lane,
waiting for these dudes to show up. They never showed up. But that was the reputation that
place had that was a clan meeting area. So in the 1930s, was there a clan meeting there?
Probably. It was Sacramento in the 1930s. The clan meetings of the Capitol building.
But that stayed. And then there were stories of like serial killers in the area that you could
find etchings of bodies on the ground, stuff like that. My per... I had a lot of stories
involving Dyre Lane. One of my personal stories was, I was a pizza delivery driver for Godfather's.
I was trying to remember where I left off. Pizza delivery driver got a delivery to Dyre Lane.
I mentioned this before on the podcast. Pull up to this house. And the house wasn't like old
Texas Chainsaw Massacre house. It wasn't falling down. It wasn't a bunch of garbage.
It wasn't... It wasn't a great house either. Somewhere in between, if I remember correctly.
And there's this young kid coming out. I'm trying to remember the exact wording that happened. But
this young kid comes out to buy the pizza. And I remember we were just chit-chatting. I think
we were talking about like how nice the weather had been. Or I don't remember what the context was.
Because everything else gets drowned out by his response, right? I remember I'm talking to him.
And the guy agrees with me. Everything is going nice. And he goes, "Yeah,
Satan's been good to us this year." He hands me the money, takes his pizza and leave.
And I remember just standing there. And realizing I'm in the middle of nowhere. I'm on Dyre Lane.
I'm in the students' front yard. It's just a weird comment to make. And he didn't say it with a
chuckle. He didn't say it because, "Oh, I know the legend students son. I was just joshing." Yeah.
Just a weird comment. Actually, it might have been the only time I ever delivered a pizza to
Dyre Lane as well. I keep saying like it's isolated. There were houses there. But there
are those houses that were farther back off the road. So you could drive down Dyre Lane and not
really see them. Dyre Lane is also where I had a car. I had a Renault station wagon that was
all-wheel drive, which I thought meant four-wheel drive. This is a true story. So I took it off
roading. I took my station wagon off roading. A round-dyres lane almost drove into a creek.
The real-life whore, the real-life whore of the Ku Klux Klan, we never had any proof of that. But
then you have the rumors of the serial killers and then the ghost stuff as well. People said that
you could see specters on the side of the road. People said you could see specters hanging from
the trees. Again, hearkening back to that Ku Klux Klan history. I had been down Dyre Lane a lot
day and night and we never saw anything specter-wise. But I actually spent a lot of time there because
that was the most haunted place that I had. The most verifiably, quote-unquote, verifiably haunted
place. There were legends going back decades that I had easy access to. Now, ghost, maybe.
Ku Klux Klan, most definitely in the past. Drug spot? 100%. Like when I threatened that dude,
the fight thing. You could fight all day long out. You could be doing like a three-day-long
marathon boxing match. No one's gonna find you. It's a perfect place to set up. Perfect place
to do deals. I remember once myself, who was in the passenger suit, might have been my boy, how,
me, how, and Jackie was in the back seat. We were driving down Dyre Lane in the middle of the night
and I had a machete in my back seat. We're driving down. We're all alone. We take that first 90 degree
turn and then there's another car coming towards us. Which was weird enough because no one was ever
on that road. But you think probably just another group of ghost hunters, right? And this other car
is, it actually doesn't have its headlights on at this time. Which was what made me think this was
like a drug meat, right? So I'm coming down the road and we're driving pretty slow because that
first 90 degree turn is super tight. Take that 90 degree turn driving slow. We see another car
sitting in the darkness slowly rolling towards us. No headlights on. And then the headlights kick on.
It's a Sacramento Sheriff's car. And I just am staring straight ahead. And I tell Jackie,
I go, "Hey, cover up that machete in the back seat." Because here's the thing. I don't know how
the law is everywhere. First off, you shouldn't have a machete in your car. But secondly,
when a police officer looks in your car, what they see can be used against you. Obviously,
right? You have a bunch of like dead bodies back there. They're gonna arrest you for murder. But
if they don't see it, they have to get a warrant for it. So if they see a locked box down there
and they suspect it has drugs, they're gonna have to get a warrant. That's why they'll bring out the
drug sniffing dog and the dog smells on it. Then they can have probable cause to open the box. But
if they're just looking back there, they don't have probable cause to just open your car. Now,
also according to law, police officers aren't able to drive around without their headlights on.
You can't do that. Super, super dangerous. Even when a cop is waiting to check for speeders when
they're at like a parking lot or kind of, they have to have the parking lights on the little
yellow lights so you're not in danger. They're supposed to. And especially in the middle of,
what was this guy doing? Was he setting up a speed trap? I think the dude was making a drug drop.
That dude was doing something dirty because he's out there waiting for someone and he thought that
was us. And we just both drive by each other. I'm just looking straight ahead. I don't even look at
him. I don't want to know what you look like. We're just driving super slow. We drive past each
other. Now, see, he can't pull us over because all of a sudden now he has to fill out a police
report. He has to run the plates. He has to say he's out there. And I don't want to get pulled
over on Dyer Lane from some cop that's sitting there with all of his lights off. Not his parking
lights, nothing. His car was a ghost. So we just keep driving. We do the normal drive. The second
I hit that other 90 degree turn, dude, I'm flying down the road. I want to get off Dyer Lane as
quick as possible. And then when we get back to civilization, I turn around and Jackie covered
up the machete to the handle. So now instead of the machete, I go, Jackie, let me explain something
to you. The reason why I wanted you to cover that up so the police officer wouldn't know I had a
machete now. Not only do I clearly have a machete, you see the handle sticking out from underneath
this towel. It looks like you're trying to hide it. Like that's worse. If you're not trying to hide
the machete, you can just go, that's farm equipment. I didn't even think I would hide it
anymore than I would think to hide a hoe or a rake. Anyways, that's a little tip to you guys who
carry machetes in your car. Dyer Lane was full of a bunch of weird stuff. Manmade stuff, like drug
drops, and then ghost stuff and legends and things like that. So where did the burnt pants factor
into all of this? I didn't go to center high school. I didn't hang out with Josh and Jason and Nick
and all them stuff back in the day. I went to Casa Roblo across town and that's where I hung out
with my boy Steve Daymwood and my boy Mauricio. We'd go ghost hunting on our adventures that one
time we saw a Civil War ghost. I told the story previously on the episode I'll do a quick recap.
Me, Steve Mauricio, were driving out off PFE, which was oddly close to Dyer Lane. We didn't know
Dyer Lane existed at this time. We saw a Civil War ghost. We saw an old man dressed in all gray
clothing walking by the side of the road. We drove by and were screaming, "Ah, ah, it was a full body
apparition. You know how rare these things are?" We turned around. We couldn't believe our eyes. We
drove past it again. It's like three in the morning. We're screaming, "Ah, ah, it's ghosts, ghosts!"
Turned around one more time. We drove even slower. And that's when we realized we were driving next
to an industrial park. He was an elderly security guard dressed up in a gray security guard uniform.
Who we thought was a Southern or who we thought was a member of the Confederacy,
who somehow died in California, even though there was no Confederacy there. And he was haunting this
place. He was actually an elderly man who was probably getting more and more terrified because
we kept driving by and screaming and pointing at him. It was also with Steve Mauricio and my brother.
We were driving through Folsom one day. I believe I told this story as well, but I'll cover it again.
We were driving through Folsom after a long night of ghosts. Steve was one of the guys that was
there the night they... I almost got in a fight with a bunch of kids. And then I went around the
corner to go pee because nothing makes you want to urinate. Like after having to shut down a bunch
of dorks and they thought I was getting attacked. They heard my voice playing as they screaming
for help. They came around the corner because it was outdoors. They were just peeing against
someone's business. They came around the corner and I was like, "Yo, bro, what's going on? I turn
on pee and all over them." They go, "We thought you were getting attacked." And this was in a known
haunted spot as well. So this was something that imitated my voice. Steve was there. I'll put that
in the show notes. That happened. There was a time in Folsom. We were driving through an old,
reportedly haunted cemetery in Folsom. You never mess around in Folsom. The Folsom police officers
pull you over if you're light blinked out of rhythm. The Folsom police department, I never
messed around in Folsom. I never messed around in Roseville because their police were just
on point. I just was like, "No, I'm good. Too many machetes in my car to get pulled over."
Never messed around. But anyways, we were driving around Folsom and there was this old cemetery and
we drove by it real slowly. And I remember this. I remember this distinctly. I think my brother was
in the front seat trying to remember the layout and sitting behind him was Mauricio. And both of
them don't really believe in ghosts. My brother doesn't believe in ghosts at all. And then behind
me was Steve. And it's so interesting because I'm looking and I see a shadowy figure standing in the
graveyard. It's really early in the morning. It's like 4 a.m. We've had a whole night of ghosts
standing. See this shadowy figure, this blob kind of standing in the graveyard. Trick of the light?
Absolutely. Could it be my mind's playing trick on me? I'm up at 4 a.m. Up. It's 4 a.m. Who knows?
But I'm looking at it and I remember Steve. He was also going, "Yeah, I can kind of see something
out there." And then it rushed. It just like did this weird thing where it's kind of standing in
the graveyard. And then in a super fast motion, it ran as fast as it could. It didn't run. It just
moved as fast as it could to the old wrought iron gate that's surrounding this graveyard.
And it hits the gate and then just dissipates. Trick of the light? Bird. Giant bird. Those
giant birds that love to dissipate. It could have been imagination. Again, it's 4 a.m. The reason why
that was so fascinating to me is both my brother and Mauricio couldn't see anything. They're like,
"I don't know what you're looking at." And when that thing ran and hit the fence, I didn't say,
because it happened so quickly. I wasn't like, "It's coming. Oh no, one, two." I wasn't saying it
happened so quickly. It moved. When that thing hit the fence, both my brother and Mauricio flinched.
They didn't see it. They don't know why they did it. I'm looking at them because I'm in the driver's
seat and they're closer to the fence than I am. See? I guess I left that little detail out.
The way we're parked, the way we're sitting there is the passenger side is where the fence is. And
when that thing hits the fence, they both flinch. I saw their reaction to it. And we started driving
away and I go, "Dude, did you see that?" And Steve's like, "Oh dude, that was nuts." And they were like,
"Oh, I didn't see anything. I go, 'Why'd you guys flinch?'" And they had no reason to. We didn't
scream or anything. It happened so fast, even though they didn't register it, even though they
couldn't see it, their body reacted to it. Creepy stuff. I'll put that episode on the show notes
about the thing imitating my voice. It's a really, really terrifying encounter as well. But let's get
to the roasted meat of the matter. Let's get to the burnt pants. Like I said, I used to go to
Diarlane a lot with myself and with other people. Sometimes we take two or three car loads down.
Sometimes it just beat me. I remember one day I was out there and I went to that first 90 degree
turn and I got out of the car and I was kind of looking around for whatever, who knows, right?
Found a pair of burnt pants.
I found a pair of burnt jeans. They were the jeans of a probably a young woman.
Took them to a forensic lab. I need DNA on these pants, please. They're like, "Sir, how did you get
in here?" If I remember correctly, they were the pants of a young woman. They weren't like a little
kid's pants. They weren't like my husky pants from Walmart. They're like tight jeans. They were burned.
Severely burned. They were tattered and burned. You could tell that these things were in a fire.
And I remember the day. I remember the day. Like I remember how the sun was in the sky.
It was one of those days when the sun was in the sky. Just everything was crisp
clouds in the sky. I remember it. I remember kind of digging and I found these burnt pants. Now,
there was other garbage around. People would throw out recliners and stuff like that. It wasn't
unheard of to find garbage. There's a lot of signs up saying don't litter and those signs were riddled
with bullets. I picked up these burnt pants and I go, "This is something. I don't know what it is yet,
but these burnt pants, this is something. A clue? Am I possibly going to solve a murder?
Is there a poor woman walking around with a burnt shirt and burnt socks that she can't find her
burnt pants?" I don't know. But I took these burnt pants and threw them in my car. I'm driving around
town with my burnt pants. And I would tell people, "Guys, you won't believe what I found on Dyer Lane."
They're like, "What?" "Hold up. Hold up a pair of burnt women's pants. Jeans." And they're like,
"What? Why do you have burnt jeans on you?" And I was like, "Cause dude, this is weird, man.
Like when's the last time you ever saw burnt clothes?" They're like, "Never, because I'm not a caveman."
And I don't dig around and other people's trash. I go, "But yeah, dude, like what if some woman was
murdered and they were like burning the pants to get rid of the evidence?" And then you have evidence
of a murderer that's not... It doesn't matter. Just get rid of them. I wouldn't. These burnt pants,
there's something about these burnt pants. It's a mystery. I was also like playing video games
and getting drunk and stuff like that. The burnt pants are sitting there. I was like, "Don't worry,
I'll solve your crime after this second doobie." But I don't actually think I was smoking weed back
then. I'm trying to make this story even more bizarre. The point is, is like even if I was trying
to solve this murder, I took my time doing it. But I always had these burnt pants in my car. Now,
at the same time, I was still ghost hunting with my buddies. At this time, I had had a side job.
And this goes into the episode about the thing imitating my voice. I had a side job where I
installed signs on the side of the road for housing developments. And every Friday, I had to put the
signs up. And every Saturday evening, I had to take the signs back down. So I had a bunch of tools
in there. So I had this sledgehammer. I had these pointy things of wood, these stakes of wood,
lots of twine and duct tape. And that's just for my job. That was just for my job. And then I also
had my personal machete. I had like a boat ore in my trunk for beating things up for fighting
swamp thing when I'm in a boat. I had my machete. I had a bunch of knives and stuff like that. My car
was not, was not the most inviting thing to ride in. But somehow people were always getting in my
car. And it was a vehicle built for war and putting signs up. I had these burnt pants. Drive around
with these burnt pants all the time. And I go on ghost hunting adventures. And I wanted more people
to come to Dyer's Lane with me. I wanted to solve the mystery of the burnt pants, dude. Hey Steve,
dude, what are you guys doing this weekend? Maricio, hey, let's go to Dyer Lane, dude. Let's solve the
mystery of the burnt pants once and for all. I don't know. I don't know. Jason, maybe not. Okay, fine.
Go to a party. Hey Steve, what's going on man? Hey, long time, long time no burn. Long time no
burn. You ready to go out to Dyer Lane and solve the mystery of the burnt pants? Oh no, dude, it's
I got like finals. I'm not going to school anymore. We graduated. Yeah, but I finally have decided I
don't want to go to Dyer Lane. Aw man, you're such a kidder. I'll call you next week.
Hey dude, what's going on? What's going on? Let me guess, you want to go to Dyer Lane? Yeah,
dude, let's go to Dyer Lane, man. Let's hang out. Just you mean Maricio. Let's hang out at Dyer Lane
and we'll solve this mystery of the burnt pants once and for all. Now apparently, Steve and Maricio
were worried about me. And more importantly, more importantly, they were worried about themselves.
Apparently it was acting really weird. I didn't know. I don't know. I thought it was acting just
fine. One day, Steve, I was so insistent on Steve and Maricio coming out to Dyer's Lane
to investigate the burnt pants. I did not know this until years later. I laughed so hard when
I heard this story. Steve goes, "Remember that time you kept trying us to get us to go out and
investigate burnt pants with you?" I was like, "Yeah, totally. Aw." And I pulled out my sketchbook of
all the drawings of the pants I drew. I look at my scrapbook of all my photos. I go, "Yeah, yeah,
the burnt pants. Yeah, I don't know what happened to those." And Steve basically has sigh of relief.
He goes, "You were so insistent on us coming out there that at one point, Steve called up Maricio
and said, 'Hey, did Jason call you about going out to investigate the burnt pants?' And Maricio
was like, 'Yeah.' And then there was kind of like a bit of dead air." And Steve goes, "I think Jason's
going to try to murder us." And Maricio basically goes, "I thought I was the only one who thought that.
I thought Jason has been trying to murder us. I thought Jason is trying to get us out there.
It's a murderous for a while. I thought it was just me." And Steve's like, "No, I'm pretty sure Jason
is going to murder us if we go out to Dyer's Lane with him." So they started having this conversation
behind my back. Whenever I would call up and be like, "Hey, when are we going to Dyer's Lane?"
Because these are my ghost hunting bros, dude. When are we going to solve this mission? Oh man,
maybe next week. They thought I was trying to set up their execution. I was going to bring them both
a pair of pants. I'm like, "I got us all a pair of pants." They're like, "Jason, you're just wearing
your normal pants. Why did you buy us women's skinny jeans? Just put them on." They thought I
was going to murder them on Dyer Lane. Steve goes, "Listen, dude, you got so weird for a while.
Like, we started to think that those pants might have possessed you." And I'm laughing.
Saying that he feared for his life. I was laughing so hard. It's like, you really thought it's going
to murder. Yes, both of us thought you were going to murder us over these pants. You wanted to take
us out there. Maybe the pants had possessed you or something like that, but they go, "Dude, you're
acting so weird. You're acting so spooky." And then I go, "You guys really thought that, right?"
And they're like, "Yeah, yeah. We really thought you were going to murder us." And then I go,
"But Steve, you guys did eventually go out there with me. Eventually, Stephen Mauricio got in my car
and let me drive him out to Dyer's Lane to investigate the burnt pants. I go, "If you thought I was
going to murder you, why did you get in my car and drive out there?" And he goes, "Because we thought
you were going to murder us anyways. We thought if we didn't go, you would definitely murder us."
And he said he got in that car with Mauricio and the entire time they were terrified. They thought
I was going to murder them in the middle of the night on Dyer Lane. Now, I have no idea
what they're thinking about. I'm driving out, making jokes. I'm singing along to letters to
Clay O, which probably isn't helping, right? I'm like, "Dude, this is the best night ever, isn't it?"
"What's your guys' favorite restaurant?" "I treat all treats you guys out to your favorite restaurant."
"You deserve it." They're like, "Oh." They thought they got in my car and they honestly thought I was
going to murder them, but they thought I definitely wouldn't murder them if they didn't go. And so
they got in my car driving around after midnight to the spookiest part of Sacramento, thinking
they're going to get murdered by their friends. And then I don't even know that. I don't even know
that. We drive out there and I think we get along with flashlights. We're walking around with flashlights.
I'm like, "Hey Mauricio, hand me my machete. I got to cut these weeds down, please." We look around.
The investigation for the burnt pantsI'm not a police officer, so basically when I want to
investigate the burnt pants, I would just go back to where I found the burnt pants and look for more
evidence. I want a whole outfit before I go to the police. But we hung out, dire lane for a bit,
saw nothing super spooky. I was the spooky one that night, right? They legit thought they were
going to have to try to fight me off, and I hate to break this to them. They wouldn't have won.
They wouldn't have won. If I had turned around at some point and I had put the burnt pants,
I'm wearing them like a mask. Even with obstructed visionsorry, Steve, sorry Mauriciowe all know
I have more fight experience, but maybe if I had pants on my head, I wouldn't have been able to see
them. But I didn't kill them. This isn't a veiled confession. I didn't fake Steve as my newest
Patreon supporter, so I could get this off my chest. I never murdered them. We all got back in the
car and drove back, and we probably went to Keros or Denny's, and I probably laughed, talking with
a mouthful of Bacon Burger about some nonsense. And they probably must have felt this total sense
of relief that their friend from high school hadn't actually been possessed by a pair of pants and
murdered them. But can you imagine that, Terry? Like, they honestly were having conversations
leading up to this saying, "I think Jason's going to murder us," and they felt they still
had to get in that car. Could you imagine that level of terror? The burnt pants show up in one
other story, and it's almost like if I get my comeuppance on this one. I'm gonna leave a lot
of details out of this story, but I do have to say this. The police were looking for me for something
I did not do. The police were looking for me. I did not do this crime. It's actually a super minor
crime, but it involves like this stuff. It wasn't even a big thing, but the police were like, "Jason,
the police don't look for you for a minor thing." They do! Police look for you for all sorts of
stuff. Anyways, it wasn't the super serious thing, but it involves a friend of mine, and I don't want
to blow their spot up, and I was thinking about a way to tell the story without really involving
them, and it just got too messy. So, but I was totally innocent. I committed no crime. I wasn't
even arrested. However, the cops were looking for me, and I was driving through Sacramento
late at night all by myself. There's a cop car behind me. This was off. This was over by American
River College. I'm driving. It's probably one or two in the morning. I just enjoy driving around.
I don't have a car anymore, and it's probably good because I get more work than a cop behind me.
Now, no one likes cops behind them. Not even other cops like cops behind them.
We're at a stoplight. Now, the cops won't ever turn their lights on while you're at the stoplight,
because it gives you a chance to think. They wait till your car is in motion,
then flick the lights on. They really don't even flick them on when you're in the intersection,
when you have all these different options. They wait till you're on straight away.
They flick their lights on, but there's a cop behind me. I'm like, okay, whatever. It's not the
most pleasant experience, but whatever. So, the light turns green. I start to drive. The cop is
turning with me. Still, he has a one in four chance. There's four directions he can go in. It
makes sense. I'm not super paranoid at this point. I drive a block up, and there's another cop, and
I go, these cops are 100% here for me. The second I saw two in the area, I was like 100%
there here for me. And they light me up at the exact same time. And I just pull into this restaurant.
It's just restaurant right off the I-80 off ramp. It's over by the A&W in that area. It wasn't at
the A&W. There was like a denny's or something there that I pulled into that parking lot.
And it was just very calm. You know, I get pulled over by the police. I've been mouthy to police
before, but I don't recommend it. I pull into this crowded parking lot, which is where you want to
be because you want a bunch of witnesses on your site as well. Pull in this parking lot. The police
pull in, and they box me in. So, I'm at a parking spot, and they actually come in behind me so I
can't move. Police officer walks up to me and starts asking me questions. And I immediately know
what they're here for. And I immediately know I didn't do anything wrong. I immediately know
this is a complete misunderstanding. I don't want to blow up my friend's spot and get them involved
in the story. But the police start asking me these questions about this person, and I was like,
"No officer. No officer. No officer. And I'm saying all this stuff." And no matter what I answer,
the information is slightly different than what it should be. It was super, oh, so aggravating.
It was so aggravating. But anyways, again, I was 100% innocent of what I was being accused of doing.
The cops would walk up, put the light in my face, ask me a couple questions. No, sir, no, sir, no, sir.
He'd go back, verify it. He'd come back to me and go, "Well, this piece of information was wrong."
I was like, "Listen, just start making the phone calls, dude. You know who to call. Like,
it's not me. I didn't do nothing." And this goes on for an hour. It was the middle of the night.
No one's picking up their phone. And I'm sitting there in that car. And the other car, there's
two cop cars. Like I said, the other car, while the one officer is interviewing me,
the other dude is shining his flashlight in my back seat, and he's looking. He's looking in my back
seat. And I remember sitting there. The two cops, they walk away. They were just walking back and
forth. I'm sitting there and I go. Now, remember, I was working for this job where I was putting
signs up on the side of the rope. I did have weapons in my car, but you couldn't see those,
right? They're underneath the floorboard. I had to, I think the machete was in the trunk at this
point, but this is what you could see. Someone could walk up in my car and they could obviously
see this. Sledge hammer, rope, duct tape, and a pair of burnt pants. Clearly visible. Clearly,
clearly visible. And I remember sitting in my car. I was fuming. I was fuming because I knew
that what these cops were saying wasn't true and it wasn't true. Someone was running their mouth
and that situation got taken care of. I'm sitting there and I remember this thought when the second
cop is looking at my back seat. We went back to the car. I remember, I remember sitting there and
I go, "I'm not going to jail tonight for what I'm being accused of, but I'm probably going to jail
tonight." Because there is no way, there is no way a law enforcement officer is going to look in
the back seat and see a sledgehammer, rope, duct tape, and a pair of burnt pants and let me drive
away. I was there for an hour. All the necessary phone calls were made. Everything was dropped
as I knew it would be because I didn't do nothing wrong. Again, I don't want to blow up people's
spot. It was a super minor ridiculous story and I'm almost making it sound more serious than it was.
It wasn't, but these cops, they pulled me over and they didn't arrest me. Despite the fact I had
what's normally known as a serial killer kit in the back seat of my car. Now, it could have been
because I was super polite to those officers, despite the fact that I was clearly a serial killer.
But I like to think the burnt pants. I like to think the burnt pants. Maybe there was the spirit
of the burnt pants. You know what, Jason? You rescued me from just laying on the side of dire
lane until I turned into nothing but fibers and birds used me to make nests, which actually,
that sounds kind of cool. You should have left me there. But you have treated me so nicely and
you've shown me off to all your friends. Some of them thought you were going to murder them.
That I am going to magically use my burnt pant powers to make these police not take you to jail.
Because again, what I was being accused of was nothing. It was actually a nothing thing and I
didn't do it and it was all sorted out. I'm super minor. But I figured I was still going to go to
jail because obviously it looked like I had done something far more serious than I had been accused
of doing. So that was all settled. So that's the end of the burnt pants story. The little pair of
jeans found on the side of a haunted road on a whirlwind adventure. The question is, was I really
acting weird during that time period? Was I possessed by the burnt jeans? Now obviously I wasn't so
possessed that I was murdering people. But what if I was just, what if I was just a little possessed?
It would be an interesting thing because I felt totally normal the whole time. I didn't feel like
I was doing anything different than I would normally do. A lot of my friends I was hanging out
with didn't notice anything, but Steve and Mauricio actually thought the pants may have possessed me
or driven me crazy or I just finally unlocked some lunatic personality of mine. Is that what
being possessed is like? Do you not know a difference? Do you not know you're acting weird?
You think everything's just fine? You think life is totally normal until
you realize you're covered in the blood of your loved ones? Because if that's the case,
if that's what, I'm not saying I was possessed, but if that's what possession does feel like,
you would never know to seek help. You would never know something was wrong.
And that's terrifying. Imagine you'd be scared and in horror because something has
possessed you, something's controlling your body, but what if you didn't even know anything was wrong
until it was too late? You wouldn't even know to pick up the phone and call the exorcist,
or to go to your spiritual leader, or to even just seek mental health counseling.
You would just live your life until your life had changed irreparably. You never once
questioned that you may be possessed, but after that one unforgivable act,
you spend the rest of your life wondering, "Why did I do that? Why did I do that? Why did I do that?"
There's a road like dire lane in almost every city around the world. Are you brave enough to
explore it? Are you brave enough to find your own burnt pants? Will they lead you down a funny
adventure where your friends think they're going to murder them? Or will you be the one that actually
gets possessed? That dark and lonely road outside of your town may be the key to an adventure,
or to a lifetime of pain.
Are you brave enough to explore it?
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you
listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]