Who would win in a fight? A dog? Or an alien? We'll be finding out the answer to that.
It's kind of a rhetorical question if you think about it.
And then we meet two young girls who have an obsession with a popular artist. Using
a black magic spell they found on the internet, is it possible that they brought Andy Warhol
back to life today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Saison
Garbinder. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope
you guys have some cool plans for the weekend. We got a ton of stuff to cover so let's go
ahead and get started right now walking into Dead Rabbit Command. This is one of our Christmas
livestream contributors. Everyone give it up for Thought Knot. Woohoo! Yeah! Come on in,
Thought Knot. Walk on into Dead Rabbit Command. Thought Knot, you're gonna be our captain
or pilot this episode. If you guys can't support this show financially, I totally get it. Trust
me, I do. Just help spread the word about this show. That helps out so much. Get the
word out. Let people know that your favorite podcast is Dead Rabbit Radio. Even if it's
not, even if you like through your four podcasts more, just tell them I'm your favorite. Thought
Knot, let's go ahead and toss you the bunny bicycle we're gonna pedal on out of Dead Rabbit
Command. Don't pop in wheelies. Take us all the way out too. North Carolina. I'm still
trying to find a good sound effect for the bicycle. We might have to get rid of the
bunny bike until I can come up. At least that one does the little gear squeaking. Maybe
I should just do the sound of a card going brrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
it's not gonna be a good one. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm
gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny
bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid
of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead
and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm
gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny
bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid
of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead
and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm
gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny
bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid
of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead
and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm
gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny
bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid
of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead
and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm
gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny
bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid
of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead
and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm
gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny
bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid
of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead
and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm
gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny bike. I'm gonna go ahead and get rid of the bunny
bike. So he left and Billy just got his dog. Went away. He actually got scared and he
grabbed his dog. He drove into town. Here's one of those odd details that makes me think
the story is true. Because generally fake stories are very clean. You have a through line
to them. This is how this story goes. He gets his dog, drags him to the truck, drives into
town, drives back to the farm, drops his dog off. Jasper gets dropped off in the farm
and then Billy drives himself to spend the night in a motel. Now if it was fictional
it would just be like, oh he went back and he went to sleep or he took his dog to town
but his dog got loose or whatever because the dog's gonna play an important part on this
next thing. In a real story this would make sense. He gets his dog, he goes into town,
he goes to the motel. He says you can't bring your dog with you. Dude you can't have a dog
in a hotel room. He doesn't want to stay the night at his house. It's spooky right? Something's
up there. So then he has to drive back and drop his dog off. It's little details like
that that make stories make them more believable. I read a ton of stuff all the time and I'm
like it's fake. Like even the skeptical side of me, I do have a skeptical side when I read
a bunch of this stuff but you just start to develop a pretty good BS meter. Now it's not
foolproof. It's not foolproof right? Lone Pine Devils I was wrong. The high school episode
I did recently I was misled. So it's not foolproof but for the most part like it's little details
like that that make you go there might actually be some truth to that because it's a messy
part of the story. Anyways so no dog is allowed at the hotel. He then drops his dog off at the farm.
This alien creature just got mulled and Billy's too scared to stay there so he goes to the
motel, holiday inn to spin the night and then the next morning he comes back and he walks
up to the hill. The first thing he does is he goes to the hill and the creature is gone.
Billy's like well okay I don't know if he moved on his own. Probably not. His legs are pretty
damaged. Maybe someone got him. I don't know it's spooky but and then he goes to his farm
and there he finds Jasper dead and a couple of Billy's cows had gone missing. I found that
story on ThinkAbout@Docs.com one of my favorite resources for this podcast. They got it from
an article written by Gray Barker. The dog himself wrote it like every time he died he's
like typing out his memoirs. He's like this is what's happening please don't. Gray Barker
he wrote this article in UFO annual 1981 a UFO journal back in the time. It's interesting
because ThinkAbout@Docs.com added a little addition to this in parentheses they go was
there any autopsy on the animal which is an interesting quote. I didn't think about that
until I finished reading it and saw that sentence. I go yeah that would make sense like they
don't know how the dog died. The dog was just dead. Yeah you know did you take it to the
vet and say hey can you find out what happened to my dog and that's looking he's like it
was like he ate a couple arms and legs last night is that pink flesh in that yeah forget
the flesh let's pretend that he didn't maul someone or something last night can you tell
me how my dog died and the doctor could like cut it open and be like well all the organs
are in the right place and there's a really bad doctor that's the only thing you notice
how to check is where the organs are but yeah so how did the dog die I mean obviously the
implication is that the alien bros came back they showed up and they found their little
dune laying there with his little cloak on and they're like Cyrus Cyrus are you okay and
he's like please carry me back to the mothership please put me in the Regenotron and they take
him in and then as he's like floating in some see-through tube and his limbs are getting
strong again he's like the first thing he does with his new arms is he's like punching
his hand he goes guys we need to even the score that dog down there chew me up man and
when they're down there killing this dog they just take a couple cows that's basically the
payment you made us use the Regenotron you know how much energy that thing uses bring
on steel a couple of your cows and don't come looking for us on the other side of the
Alpha Centauri nebula it's not like Billy had access to intergalactic court drive but
an interesting story nonetheless real-world consequences of encountering alien life so
many times people are abducted they don't remember it or they're abducted and they
remember it and they have horrifying nightmares I mean that's pretty bad or they have implants
and stuff like that stories where people die animals die encountering aliens I don't think
we hear a lot of them because I don't think people survive them I think these one-off
encounters with aliens like if the farmer just died of a heart attack that night right
they would have been like oh no Billy now where are we gonna get our milk for the town
they just go to the store they go to the store they're like whoa grocery store sell them
up would have been chalked into a horrible accident right and there wouldn't have been
no witness to finding the little guy up on the because they were coming gun form right
the implication is they came back to the farm later and killed the dog and took some cows
and if Billy had been there he would have been dead too I think there probably are more
stories of people dying at the hands of alien invaders but we don't hear about it because
there's no one to tell that story but in this case there was a survivor luckily for us
but Jasper we will always honor you for being the first dog that we know of to mutilate an
alien this week has been really heavy on dog stories I hope that's not for telling something
hope I'm not gonna have a close encounter with it dogs jaws thought not let's go ahead
and toss you the keys of the carbon or copter we are leave me high north Carolina we're
headed out to a high school speaking of high schools I'm gonna do a very quick dead rabbit
recommends and I have to keep it quick I could honestly talk about this movie for the next 30
minutes but I won't I'll punish the people on the discord with that the page on discord
I've already started posting stuff long time ago I did a dead rabbit recommends on the Disney
movie zombies it was a musical about brain eating zombies who had to wear control like
callers to keep them from eating people's brains and they were right next door to this
gated community and it really was a story about race relations in America like humanity
had become post-racial that wasn't an issue anymore because everyone hated the zombies
they had found a common enemy the zombies are like hey we can't help it like we can't help
it we got this nuclear radiation on us and now all of our kids are zombies too we just
want to be just like you and it's this bizarre musical that that's the central theme but
there's all of these weird underlying things like Zed who's the lead zombies this dancing
group and so he's constantly on the verge of eating people's brains and he realizes that
he can adjust his control collar it's actually like a watch but and it gives him superhuman
strength and he tries out for the football team and he's throwing people like 30 40 yards
and it's really then it becomes an allegory on like performance enhancing drugs like would
it be fair he wanted to be the first zombie to ever play high school football and the reason
why you can't do it is it's not fair you're extremely powerful and then he starts losing
control and there's like they have these bizarre musical sequences I remember when I watched
it I thought this movie cannot get any weirder and then the next scene would start you're
like what is going on and I absolutely loved it it was so weird then they came out with
two which I did not do a dead rabbit recommends on I watched that I bought it the day it came
out so the first one was pretty much the other right it was humans versus the other in the
second movie they clarified that the zombies are supposed to represent like black culture
in America because the second one they bring in indigenous culture werewolves we were here
before the humans got here we are living in caves the whole time and even know we were
here so these werewolves jump out and they're dancing around and again it has this really
really bizarre commentary because the werewolves just go hey can we start going to school here
and the administrators like yeah sure you can come here and the zombies are like it took
us 15 years to even be able to set foot in this school that was a part of the first movie
like it was the very first year zombies could go to high school and they just get to come
in and the administrators like yeah sure whatever and so you had like this antagonism between
these two different minority groups and then Addison who is the lead love interest he's
in love with the zombie she all of a sudden becomes super obsessed with the werewolves
and their culture and starts dressing like them and believing she is the savior of their
people and I'm like dude this is a Disney Channel movie what is going on and she's saying
I'm prophesied to help the werewolves I was a werewolf all along there is a prophecy about
this woman who is supposed to save the werewolves I'm talking about this way longer than I wanted
to but there's a prophecy about this person who is going to save the werewolves and Addison
goes that's me and everyone is like that's not you and she's like no no that's me I'm
going to save the indigenous people and it really plays on like the white savior trope
and at the ending she goes to use this magical power to save the indigenous people's moonstone
and it doesn't work she wasn't the prophesied one and everything blows up at the end of
that movie everyone is worse off than they were at the beginning but they're still singing
and dancing it's super bizarre but I didn't like it as much the music wasn't that good
so at the end of that one it turns out that Addison wasn't a werewolf like Jason I really
don't care get to the end of your whole story but hold me and be hosted Addison was not a werewolf
but at the end she goes well if I'm not a werewolf and I'm not I don't fit in with the humans
because she has white hair she never feels like she fit in who do I what group do I belong to
and as she's going to bed a UFO shows up and I'm like oh my god are you going to talk about
illegal immigrants in the next one we've already talked about indigenous culture being wiped out
we've talked about an oppressed group of people living right next door and having curfew and
dress codes and it's like this prison camp that they live in so I was like are they actually
going to do a story about illegal immigrants in zombies 3 but I was like they're not going to
make a zombies 3 right I was lucky enough to get zombies 2 well on July 15th zombies 3
dropped and it is fantastic dead rabbit recommends zombies 3 and I remember going oh my god I just
found out they're going to make this movie and is it going to be about illegal immigrants
coming and then the indigenous people and the minority like the oppressed group and then
the humans are they all going to hate the illegal immigrants for like taking their jobs and things
like that taking their places in college the movies about whether or not bonzo can get a
driver's license or whether or not Zed can impress a counselor to be the first monster to go to
college it starts off with him saying if I win the football game tonight I get a full scholarship
to college and I was like what and the movie flies by at a clip they do talk a little bit about
like the illegal immigrants the aliens come in and they do better on all the tests and they're the
best cheerleaders in the galaxy because they're flying around the stage and they have alien powers
I was like obviously they're going to win and then they completely abandoned that theme and it's pretty
much can the UFO take off Addison is an alien she's the granddaughter of an alien fantastic
movie I dead rabbit recommends highly zombies 3 and I'll tell you right now if you're looking for
a absolutely bizarre movie to put on in the background while you're just chilling zombies
especially I think if you watch zombies 3 and didn't watch any of the other two you're like this
is random nonsense absolutely fascinating dead rabbit recommends the entire zombie trilogy
if you have six hours to spare but if not zombies 3 it's just so weird and I love it and I thank you
for letting me waste your time in the best word but until you okay yeah yeah okay we're done
thought not let's go ahead and have you land this carbon helicopter at this high school we
are just sure I just clicked on my desktop it's a picture of zombies 3 I changed that wallpaper
right away thought not land this carbon helicopter at this high school we're going to take a look
at the story of a young girl we're going to call her Jessica she goes by the internet name
suitcase in her hand she says that this story took place back when she was around 14 years old
the year is 2015 her and her best friend who we're going to call Madeline while they were in
high school they were obsessed with Andy Warhol famous artist soup can man Campbell soup dude
couple pictures of Elvis I'm not a big Andy Warhol fan myself it was even zombies 3 I never
really got the appeal I know that he was trying to take like art and like consumer mass consumption
images and go this is art I like the endeavor right I like the idea maybe if I was alive back then
but now I'm just like I don't hate the guy right if you're already in ready to cancel your subscription
I don't hate the guy I just am not a fan of the art that I've seen of his anyways these two girls were
they loved Andy Warhol they loved him so much and often they would sit around dreaming about their
eating soup all the time mom's like you guys really need to get some nutrients in you well he didn't
draw vitamin mom he drew soup they would sit around eating soup and Jessica would say man I really
wish I could have met Andy Warhol and Madeline's like I agree I totally agree well they start to get
like obsessed with this idea of meeting Andy Warhol and Jessica goes we were also a bit of fans of the
paranormal so we believed in magic and stuff like that so we decided to peanut butter and jelly this
thing what if we summoned the soul of Andy Warhol so Jessica goes I don't remember the exact ritual
I remember we got it online we were typing in Andy Warhol summoning spells and there's a huge list
she goes I don't remember exactly what it was but we got this incantation and then we built a shrine to
Andy Warhol in my room we had all these candles we had photos of Andy Warhol empty cans of soup
this flies everywhere and then they had soup cans nothing looking back on the note I'm assuming they weren't
opened anyways they had a Polaroid cameras because apparently that was a medium he used a lot with
Polaroid cameras soup cans pictures of him notes written to him so they're like oh dear Andy Warhol
I wish you weren't dead sincerely Jessica they had all this stuff and they had a laptop playing
footage of him on a loop that's an interesting twist to a spell right I you know like obviously all this
magic was written before technology got to that level but photographs are a big part of low magic
right basically like witchcraft nature magic type of stuff where you have to have an icon of someone
nowadays you could have 24 hours of just continuous video footage of this subject that you're doing the
spell on right it's pretty interesting she said the entire room was dark except for the candles and the
desktop that was playing Andy Warhol doing the jig or something I don't know exactly what he was doing
but they begin the ceremony and as they're doing this flames are burning on the candle
Andy Warhol is doing the jig they begin to recite the incantation and she said we weren't just
saying the incantation we were focusing we were trying to manifest him so we were using basically
the law of attraction we had our intention set we focused on manifesting him into the cut into our
world into my room and they have their eyes closed and they're doing the incantation and then Jessica
said all of a sudden I start to feel this pressure all around me I start to feel a change in the
atmosphere she said it felt like hot and cold at the exact same time like loud and quiet simultaneously
it was just this completely different energy in the room and she opened her eyes and at that time
she sees her friend's face is locked in this gaze of horror and so she turns and she goes to look to
see what her friend is seeing and there standing in the darkness of the room is Andy Warhol Andy
Warhol came back alive you see that newspaper you haven't been checking CNN Andy Warhol is alive
they see Andy Warhol standing in the darkness and I really like the way that she described this she
said he was there for a moment and he was incredibly bright she said what it looked like was if
someone was standing in the dark pitch black room and someone snapped a photo of them with the flash on
and how it illuminates them for a quick second and she goes I turn and I see him standing there and I
see this this huge illumination effect he's just blindingly bright and then he fades away or he
just disappears actually it's not like a slow fade it's just gone and at this point Madeline's like
screaming she's freaking out it was definitely like you wanted to see Andy Warhol but at the end of the
day you realize you just summoned a spirit and Jessica goes I didn't scream it wasn't even like a
sense of fear when he was there obviously you were startled she goes I didn't scream I was actually
just frozen in physical place and my emotions everything just were like muted she actually
felt because Madeline wanted to leave the room Madeline wanted to run away Jessica felt that she
needed to be closer to this now gone figure she goes I know that he was gone but I felt like I
should be physically next to where he was like move over there and stand where Andy Warhol just was
she goes the whole thing felt like a dream now Madeline did end up running out of the room and
she said shortly after this we stopped hanging out with each other me and Madeline haven't been
hanging out in a while to put it bluntly she goes I really haven't seen her in seven years so I don't
really know how she's she's been chopped up and stuck in a hundred soup cans we don't actually know
how Madeline's doing but Jessica said I'm doing fine I'm actually doing better than fine you might
want to visit my room nowadays now that I'm an adult I'm in my 20s now once you swing on by my
house she's obsessed with Andy Warhol now totally obsessed you walk in she has over 70 books on
Andy Warhol I don't think I own 70 books period she has 70 books on Andy Warhol she has a tattoo
of Andy Warhol that'd be alarming right you meet a pretty girl she has a face of a big old weirdo
on her bicep the kind of alarming she has a well that's the least of your worries actually then you
go back to her house and you see her library Andy Warhol books she has a tattoo of Andy Warhol
she has autographs from Andy Warhol she went to the Warhol Museum in Pittsburgh and she said when
she walked into the museum she started to feel the same pressure that she felt when she was in the
room the first time she started to feel the energy change and you could say Jason sure I wouldn't
necessarily say it's obsessed if you have 70 books on one person yeah I'm gonna ask for it but I would
say you're pretty obsessed if you have 70 books on the same person a tattoo of the person and then
all that other stuff she actually has dirt from Andy Warhol's grave that's obsessed with that's obsessed
right I mean like I really like Zombies 3 I really like that movie but I'm not going to be walking around
in a in a sea brook shrimps football jersey I definitely want to be carrying dirt from the set of
Zombies 3 you could be Jason you're declaring one of America's greatest pop culture artists to a
Disney Channel movie yeah I like Zombies 3 and I'm not a huge fan of Andy Warhol but anyways that's
that's not the point I can't get back on Zombies 3 I'll never stop she has dirt from Andy Warhol's
grave and she goes from time to time the dirt's knocked over and I kind of feel like it's Andy
Warhol's ghost knocking it over I should add to that fact going through her history she has a cat
it might be the cat knocking over the dirt but here's my here's my read on this story I will give
them the benefit of the doubt that they actually summoned Andy Warhol back to life and then it
disappeared in a flash but I don't think it disappeared in a flash I think that this girl Jessica
is possessed by Andy Warhol it might be the dumbest thing I've ever saw on the show but hear me out
she summoned this guy I mean she before she was pretty obsessed before right but based on the
narrative like she didn't have the tattoo she didn't have the dirt as far as we can tell she didn't
go to the museum if you go to a museum with someone you're gonna get possessed by him you didn't
know that we learned that in history class you have this girl who's in love with this dude and not
necessarily romantically right but she's in love with this dude and then she summons him and then
Andy Warhol while he's there he's like yo I'm gonna be this girl now and he's like in the body
of this girl now the thing would be is that maybe he doesn't have full control over her right
maybe she's like eating vegetables she's like no no he's supposed to be eating soup like maybe he
doesn't have full control over her or maybe he does maybe maybe Andy Warhol is such an egotist
that now that he's in this girl's body he just wants to look at stuff look at stuff that people
made of him autographs I guess those are his but he's like oh the sweet dirt of my grave he's
all rubbing it on himself she's always walking around with dust on her cheeks what if Andy Warhol
possessed this girl that's the best case scenario that's the best case scenario the worst case
scenario is that Andy Warhol did not possess this girl but something pretending to be Andy Warhol
possessed this girl we talked about this recently I think it was on yesterday's episode or the episode
with the haunted album where you'd have a dark creature like a latch itself to you in the guys
of something else so maybe there's like a demon who is in hell and he heard like this incantation
he's like who who is Andy Warhol I don't know I'm gonna go up there and be him maybe he's cool
and he shows up the demons like he realizes he's super lame he's like oh man I thought this guy
made zombies 3 but it was too late the zombie the dinosaur wave what if the demon had already taken
the form of Andy Warhol and he saw how much this little girl loved him so he's like affecting her life
he's basically like making her obsessed over some dead dude and when you're obsessed with someone's
accomplishments do you have your own you know there's this source of inspiration right I think
to look at the people who've inspired me over the years and then I go on and do my own thing
I think that's the normal thing right you see someone you're like wow dude I wish I could be that cool
I wish I was the first monster who went to college and then that inspires you on your own journey
but people who become obsessed just don't do that they're just constantly collecting and consuming
something from something that somebody else has created there's nothing wrong with that
but you know the difference between obsession and admiration or just simply like in a dude
before it seemed to be like yeah we really like dandy warhol and we wish we'd met him before too
his face is forever emblazoned on my body and I have his dirt dirt from his grave in my bedroom
like you know what I mean like that's a bridge too far so maybe this demon is actually draining her energy
and only making her focus on the past instead of her own artistic endeavors or just having a life
right just having a normal life it's fascinating story is it true we don't know right
we really just have this one person's statement but it's fascinating nonetheless it does track what we know
about these type of incantations summoning spells stuff like that it does actually make sense
it's not completely outlandish as he said as he talked about Andy Warhol possessing a young girl
or something pretending to be Andy Warhol which would be far worse at least if Andy Warhol was in your body
I don't know maybe you can make more soup maybe you could go get a job at the Campbell soup factory
and work all the way up to CEO and then Andy Warhol's ghost flies out of her body and goes
you're all fired I'm the soup king now and they're like ahh and all the other CEOs leave
and then it's just this ghost who's running the Campbell soup factory right that's reasonable
that's reasonable but it also shows that the dangers are messing with the stuff so many times
people do this I have a friend who just moved into a new house and she keeps saying I hope it's haunted
I hope it's haunted and I was like yeah that'd be cool and she's like yeah I hope there's a demon there
I hope it would be fun to get possessed and I'm like okay now you're just nuts
nah I would be totally cool I'm like Magania knock it off that's like what you're just even saying that
she wasn't saying it in jest she wasn't saying it to rile me up nah it'd be so cool
it's dangerous stuff people watch a couple movies and they read a couple books or they read some stuff online
and they go I can handle that and it's the same thing like people watch Save and Private Ryan and go pfff
I can do that I think my face is blowing off on a beach somewhere
you always see yourself as a hero you always see yourself as the triumphant victor
but you're messing with dark dark energy
and whether you're summoning forth one of the grand arch demons of hell or a pop artist from the 60s
you're dealing with dark energy you're dealing with something that you shouldn't be messing with
the consequences could be something as basic as losing your friend and developing a lifelong obsession with a dead icon
or it could be life altering events after life altering events right you get possessed so fully by a demon
what happens to your own soul terrifying story don't mess with dark energies unless you know what you're doing
and the reality is no human no matter how long they've been steadying this no human knows what they're doing
when it comes to the dark arts
[Music]
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address you can also visit us at facebook.com/deadrabberradio
Tiktok is at DeadRabberRadio
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it everyday
but I'm glad you listened to it today have a great day guys
[Music]