What would you do if you fell face first into a city?
Then we traveled to South Africa to take a look at an urban legend involving a bus, a cat, and you being violently assaulted.
And then we traveled to Russia to meet a man who has a close encounter of the turned kind turned into a clone today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys are having lots of fun in the sun doing what you're doing.
It's almost fall. It's almost time for the spookiest month of the year, October.
And we don't know. I always say I'm gonna do a theme. I'm gonna watch spooky movies every day. I don't know.
You guys will be lucky if I remember to do a Halloween episode. Every episode is a Halloween episode, but I never am able to schedule a special.
But you know what I am able to schedule? A warm welcome for one of our legacy Patreon supporters.
Give it on up for user125. Everyone give a round of applause to user125 as they walk into Dead Rabbit Command.
User125, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode. If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show. Really, really helps out a lot.
I'm also thinking about setting up a, what's the thing where it's just like a one-time donation thing? Like a GoFundMe.
I really want a, what are those, a stair machine. I really want like an indoor stair machine.
Like Jason, seriously we're not gonna donate money. We're not gonna give you $1,200 to get exercise. We don't want you to live long.
No, I really want a stair machine. It's gonna get cold soon. I don't wanna walk on the stairs, but I'm probably, I'm probably too lazy to write up the GoFundMe.
But we'll see. We'll see maybe.
User125, let's go ahead and give you the keys to the Jason Jalopy. We are gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed all the way out to Australia.
User125's driving us all the way down there. We get on a ferry at some point and we take a boat most of the way.
We're gonna use one of our boat vehicles, but we didn't. We're specifically headed out to Northwest.
That's an area in Western Australia. It's December 1984. It's nighttime.
And there's a dude working in the field. He has like the rake or like the hoe or another one of the multitude of instruments.
That farmer, I don't know if this guy's a farmer. I just said in the notes he was working in a field. We'll call him Daniel. We don't even have a name for this guy.
But Daniel's working in the field and he's walking. He's like, "Oh, and a good day's work. I don't know what I do."
He has a farmer instrument and then he has, I don't know, like a Geiger counter. He's like, "I don't know what exactly my job is. I just work in a field."
And as he's walking through the field at night, he trips. Whoa! And he lands on the ground.
What do you think? He's gonna fly away? You think this is some sort of paranormal podcast?
He lands on the ground and he goes, "Aw, man, what the heck?" And he looks over to see what he tripped on.
He tripped on a fence. He was like, "Jason, that's not paranormal." Well, you didn't let me finish.
The picket fence was tiny. You're like, "Jason, that's still not paranormal. You didn't let me finish."
The picket fence was like, for like tiny, like, ant-sized people. Maybe not ant-sized people.
They were like, an inch or two tall. Yeah, see? Now it's paranormal.
There's like a fence. He realized that he tripped over...
Save your questions. Save your questions. So, Leigh-end, okay? Because when I read this story and I typed up the notes,
I was like, "Oh, this is fascinating." But I'm saying it out loud. Okay, just wait 'til the end. It's very short.
He says he tripped on this one-inch, two-inch tall fence and he landed in the middle of this tiny person's city.
And as he's laying on the ground, he sees little buses driving through the city and little people getting on the buses and then going to work.
He's like, "What?" And then he gets up and he realizes like he must have landed on something because he has five vertical lines on his forehead.
Similar to like a barcode. And for years after this event, he had those lines.
And everyone would be like, "Hey, Daniel, line head. That's your new name. Your children are the line heads.
Hey, how'd you get those lines in your head?" And he goes, "You guys want to believe it. One day I was walking and I tripped on a fence."
And they go, "That's not paranormal." And he goes, "I didn't tell you how big the fence was."
Okay, so that's the whole story. Give me a second.
When I read that, I got it from ThinkAboutItDocs.com, one of my favorite websites.
They got it from a journal or a magazine called Western Australia UFO Sightings, maybe a website.
Super specific. It's only for that region of Australia.
When I read the story, I go, "Dude, isn't that dope? Like, imagine. Imagine if I could crush the city."
That's the thing when I was reading this, I go, "Wait a second. I've tripped on a lot of stuff in my life, but I haven't tripped."
Something that's only like an inch or two tall. He doesn't actually even say how small these people are.
They do talk about Gulliver's Travels. And they use the term "tiny." So I don't think they were like three feet tall.
I don't think these are like little people, like dwarfs. I think it was like tiny people.
But how would you trip on a fence that's only an inch tall, and then he falls and he hits the city?
Like, wouldn't they all be panicked? When did they just realize this giant guy fell on like half of their population,
but they're still getting on buses and driving around?
As I was reading the story out loud, I go, "Okay, what probably happened was he probably conked his head so hard."
He hallucinated. I had a friend of mine named Ron.
He got on a motorcycle accident once, and he fell off his bike. He didn't fall off his bike.
He got on a horrible accident, and he flew off of his bike, and he said,
"And I flew all the way into a pumpkin patch." But there was no pumpkin patches.
He goes, "I sat up, and I looked, and as far as the eye could see, I saw pumpkins."
And then, like, people were running up to me, the great pumpkins, like, "Are you okay? Are you okay?"
He says, "People started, like, talking to me, and I realized I wasn't in a pumpkin patch. I was actually on the side of I-80 in Sacramento."
So that's what I'm thinking, but then you go, "Jason, where did the five vertical lines come from?"
And I go, "I don't think they came from a tiny picket fence, but maybe. I guess I just have some questions about this story.
Like, how do you trip on something so small? How do they not freak out when you destroy half of their civilization?"
But that all being said, it is quite cute and quaint, and we don't run across a lot of those stories here on Dead Rabbit Radio.
I was like, "Oh, tiny..." Okay, he did kill half their population. They're probably still rebuilding, but I would like to see more stories
where there's just, like, tiny people going about their business. They're not abducting no one.
They're not pushing over a bus. We covered that story where there was, like, a bus in Peru.
I'll try to find out where the show notes. It was, like, driving up a cliff, and a bunch of dwarfs came out of the mountain and pushed the bus over.
Like, it's just nice to have a story where just a man stumbles and destroys a city.
But I like tiny people. I don't like fairies and stuff like that. I think that stuff's kind of lame.
But one would be cool if every so often you could just look down and you see a bunch of little people walking around.
So that is why I included that story today. You're like, "Jason, do you have some sort of tiny person fetish?"
No, I do not. I know a lot of times I get accused of being a scaly for having a fetish for hot reptilian females.
That's not true either. But let's go ahead and move as I shift from side to side.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
User125, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Dreadnaught.
We haven't used this vehicle in a long time. It's our battleship.
We're going to leave behind Western Australia. We are headed on out to South Africa.
[imitates gunshot]
We're headed South Africa. I came across this story recently.
I was looking online. They had a thread about African folklore.
There's a lot of really interesting stuff, but this one really stood out to me.
This was the story of the Minibus legend.
This story came from a user named Winnie Blue Sevent.
Winnie Blue Sevent was telling the story that in the big cities in South Africa, like Johannesburg and Derba,
this story has gone around.
Sometimes you'll be walking around town and you're like, "You know what I really hate doing walking.
I've been doing this a lot. I want to take the Minibus."
I looked them up and they're like shuttles. In most parts of the world, I think it's the terminology.
It's basically like a long van. They can fit like 8 to 10 people in them.
It's one of the primary methods, if not the primary method of mass transportation in South Africa,
is the Minibus taxi. You stand on the street corner and this bus pulls up.
You get on it and there's other riders with you, so it's not like a taxi or an Uber or anything like that.
But the legend is like this.
You're in the Minibus taxi and it's driving you to your destination.
You're not really paying attention.
At one point you look back and you realize you're the only person on the Minibus.
What? I swear, I just got on this Minibus to tell people where did everyone go.
I don't even remember stopping multiple times.
It's not like you figure they got off. They're just not there.
It is very disquieting.
You also notice now that the Minibus doesn't seem to be driving towards your destination.
It seems to be driving down abandoned streets of Johannesburg.
You don't really even know there were abandoned streets in Johannesburg. It's a big city.
But you seem to be traveling down this route that you've never been down before. You didn't even know existed.
So you get up from your seat and you begin walking through the Minibus to go talk to the driver.
"Hey man, where are we?" That's my first question. The second question is where did everyone else go?
And when you get to the front of the Minibus where the driver is, there's just the cat sitting in the driver's seat.
You go, "Okay, now I have three questions." The cat looks at you, shhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
You go, "Okay, now I have three questions." The cat looks at you, shhhhhh, hisses. The next thing you know you're outside of the Minibus taxi.
You're on the side of the street in the middle of nowhere. At best, you've been robbed.
There are stories that sometimes people wake up outside of this Minibus taxi in the middle of nowhere. They've also been raped.
This story is so interesting because it has all the trappings of a typical urban legend. It's a cautionary tale.
Cautionary tale? Be careful what Minibus tax you get and don't get into cat bus taxi because the cat's probably driving that.
But no, pay attention to your surroundings. You start to notice stuff suspicious. Get out. If you notice the bus is taking you down.
You know what I mean? Like there's all of these cautionary tales that you could tell a kid, you could tell a teenager.
Being like, "Hey, if you ever decide," it's a little heavy-handed because most urban legends don't involve you getting sexually assaulted.
But it is the moral of the story. Pay attention to your surroundings.
At the same time, it has this level of urban magic, which is something we don't see enough of in urban legends.
For my liking, I really like the idea of urban magic. We've covered a couple stories about urban cryptids and stuff eating hobos.
We've covered stuff like that. Shapeshifting as homeless people. We've covered a lot of those types of stories.
Cryptids in the big city. I'll try to find them for the show notes, but there's been so many.
But not enough. So many times the cryptids are out in the middle of nowhere.
Or these stories take place. These urban legends take place at lakes. You've got to watch out for the lake because there's the monster there.
You've got to watch out for Crybaby Bridge and things like this. They're always in remote locations.
And I find it so fascinating when they take place in the big city. Really the place where you should feel the most safe.
Now, not the most safe from street crime. Because crime rates are skyrocketing. But the most safe from monsters.
What's interesting about this story is it doesn't involve a minibus taxi taking you between the big cities.
And then you're out in the boonies. You're out in the boondocks and something bad happens.
And the moral of the story is those outsiders aren't as cool as city folk.
The story of the city is where it's taking place. So it's just a great urban legend. And then is it true?
Because this is a paranormal podcast and we believe in the paranormal. It's in the realm of possibility.
I'm not saying sell your stock in minibus taxis if you own stock.
I'm saying that if we already believe in the idea of ghosts and realms and tiny little people that we can squish, you could easily see this being the work of a sorcerer.
Instead of having a Venus flytrap, it's a bus. It's something that people need in the area.
And you get on it, but it's actually a trap. The other passengers are just illusions.
You get on, you feel safety in numbers, but really you're headed towards a destination that, again, at best, you lose all your money.
So fascinating story. Most likely a folktale to remind people to be aware of their surroundings.
However, you can never discount the idea that darker forces may be involved.
User 125, let's go ahead and leave behind South Africa.
I'm going to toss you the keys of the carbon helicopter. We are headed out to Bezhetsk, Russia.
[imitates Russian]
User 125 is totally shrugging his shoulders. I... dude, you have to learn how to renounce this stuff if you expect me to fly there.
We're headed to the Tver region in Russia if that helps a little bit better.
It's April 23rd, 1997. And in the town of Bezhetsk, there's a man named Igor Yutkin.
He's in his apartment, just chilling, having a good time.
They don't actually say what his mental state was. He could have been really, really depressed.
But we'll assume he's just sitting there. He has a nice cup of tea, enjoying the night.
All of a sudden, though, that's going to end very, very soon. A blue light penetrates his ceiling.
[imitates Russian]
And he says it's pointing down like a stalactite.
And then all of a sudden, it becomes solid. And a man and two women step out of the beam of light.
So whether or not he's horribly depressed or having a great night, he's definitely in shock right now.
And he's sitting there, and it takes him just a brief second to figure out the pecking order here.
He immediately realizes who's in charge. It's one of the women. She's 5'5" and she's described as having...
They're human. They're humanoid, at least. She has an elongated face. Medium-sized, dark eyes.
I don't... I'm reading the description in the order that I was given to me, okay?
This is exactly how you described it. And you guys will see the error. You guys will see why this is not the correct way to do this.
She's 5'5" with an elongated face, medium-sized, round, dark eyes, no hair on her head.
And she's bald. She's wearing a hat like a Catholic bishop. And she's green.
Which one would you... If you saw this woman, as I described her, would you start off with, "Oh, she had a nice hat."
Or would you be like, "Listen, bro, I'm sitting in my apartment. I'm crippling depression."
And then all of a sudden some green chick showed up. By the way, all that other stuff.
She was 5'5". She had... Start off with the green. Start off with the green skin.
But she is humanoid. She has that green skin. My scaly fetish... My scaly fetish senses are tingling.
She's green. She's wearing a red. She's wearing a light green dress as well.
Could you imagine being walking around and wearing clothes with the same skin color?
Like the exact same skin color. That seems so bizarre.
But anyways, I wear khaki shorts. I'm not khaki colored, okay?
But she's wearing a green dress. She has a red cloak on. She's very Christmas themed.
And she's holding a scepter. That could have been the giveaway that she was the leader.
But anyways, this green gal shows up and she tells Igor telepathically that her name is Zuri from the planet Galea.
And she goes, "Egor, you should leave Earth with us. Come with us, because you're gonna suffer a lot through life.
But if you come with us, we're gonna get rid of those sufferings."
She actually keeps using these words, "suffer" and "sufferings".
You can decrease your sufferings if you come with us.
And Igor is sitting there and he goes, "I can't. I can't go with you."
Because if I leave, it may decrease my sufferings, but my family will suffer.
Because they'll miss me. They'll never know what happened to me. I'll just vanish.
Zuri goes, "We have a way around that. You see, what we can do is we can take you with us."
And no one will ever notice you're gone. He's like, "Oh, I'm sure some people will notice."
He goes, "Yes, yes. People wouldn't notice you were gone in that sense, but we actually have bio-robots.
And what we can do is we can incarnate another soul into this bio-robot that looks exactly like you.
No one will be able to tell the difference. No one will miss you."
And she says, "You can leave and not suffer. Come with us, Igor."
And Igor looks at Zuri and says, "No. I want to stay here. I'm not leaving."
Zuri and her two compatriots walk back into the beam of light and they disappear.
The whole interaction took about five minutes.
Igor said the very next night, April 24th, he's sitting there in his living room and, you know, for just a flash, Zuri appeared again.
He saw her for just a split second. And then she was gone forever.
That's another story actually. I usually don't plan it this way.
Another story I got from ThinkAbout@Docs.com. They got it from Pavel Heilov and Anton Anfalov.
They're both UFO researchers in Eastern Europe. We've covered other stuff that they've talked about before.
This is one of the stories I've had on the docket for a long time. I've wanted to share with you guys because the implications are really, really unsettling.
The first thing is, is there ability to... There's a couple different things going on.
Like there's one, they come down to ease Igor's sufferings. That term is used a lot in this.
You have to wonder why Igor? Two, how do they know Igor's going to suffer in the future?
Like they're trying to alleviate obstacles he's going to face in the future.
So how do they know what's going to happen in the future?
But then we go... They can clone people.
I mean, you assume aliens have alien technology that they can teleport. They can travel the speed of light.
They can beam through apartment ceilings. So why wouldn't they be able to clone?
It would make sense they'd be able to clone. But perfect duplicates of people, sure, that's sci-fi level technology.
But this is a duplicate that is you.
So you go with them and your clone is left behind and no one knows.
How do we know the true number of people who have traveled away with aliens?
The person's only missing when they're missing, when you can't find them.
If one of your loved ones, one night is visited by this people and goes, "You're right, I don't want to suffer."
"You got a biorobot that looks just like me, leave him here and no one will know."
"Yeah, I'm out."
And then you go visit your dad or your uncle or your mom or your niece or whatever and it's not them.
I mean, it is, for all intents and purposes, if you did any sort of DNA test on them, it's them.
But it's not them. Or not really them.
I mean, okay, don't go chasing your niece with a hammer now.
And you're like, "I'm gonna find out what's really behind the alien agenda."
But what if it happens four more often than we think?
And they're just getting replaced with these biorobots.
I mean, you could have mass abductions every single day.
We wouldn't know because the people aren't missing.
Secondly, she showed back up and then she disappeared in a flash.
So when I read that, I had something pop in my head and when I told you that, you might have had the same suspicion.
Igor is a clone now. Igor now is a clone.
When she came back, Igor Prime, the real Igor, agreed to go with her.
The bio clone was left behind, thinking he was the real Igor.
Seeing her disappear in a flash was the ending of that conversation between Igor Prime and Zuri.
And the clone has a brief memory of it and that's it.
And the clone goes, "Well, I guess she popped back in. I don't know why she was here."
I mean, even though she was here yesterday to clone me and to take me away,
this time she just showed up and did neither of those things.
So everything's okay, but he's the clone.
The perfect clone wouldn't know they were a clone.
The real Igor, Igor Prime, is not suffering.
He's in the stars with Zuri.
The perfect clone wouldn't know it's a clone.
This could be happening all the time and we wouldn't know because we don't know what people are missing.
We don't know to investigate it.
What happens when the world is more clone than human?
What if it's not even a what if?
Let's say that's the case.
And 30%-- imagine that.
Imagine if 30% of the humans on planet are conspiracy caps fully on.
Again, I don't want you to walk around with the crossbow going, "Jason told me everyone's a clone."
Conspiracy caps fully on.
This has been going on, let's say, most generous estimates.
This has been going on since the 1950s.
Betty and Barney Hill, first alien encounter with a human, I think was like '50s, late '50s, early '60s.
Forget ancient aliens. I'm just being conservative here.
Betty and Barney Hill, till now, that's still about a 50-60 year window of aliens abducting people.
I mean, how many clones would be out there? What if it is down to 30% original humans?
Or less.
Because we wouldn't know we were the clone. Statistically at this point, again, conspiracy caps fully on.
What if I'm the clone?
What if you're the clone and we're going about our clone lives?
The real us are partying on some planet, not suffering.
But the clones are left here to continue to suffer.
This is where insanity begins, having this belief that you're the only real person.
It's actually a really key part of insane behavior.
But conspiracy caps fully on will indulge and will wrap the episode up like this.
The next time you're looking in the mirror, look a little closer.
See if there's an imperfection that you didn't notice before.
See if there's a clue that you're not the same person you were just yesterday.
But maybe their technology is perfect and you can't spot a flaw.
Once again reassuring you that you are the real you.
But what would be better?
To know for sure that you were a clone.
And another version of yourself was celebrating life in a world of no suffering.
Or never knowing the truth.
Not knowing why you are experiencing all the sufferings you are.
But you are put through these trials and tribulations.
So the real you can travel the stars.
[Music]
(upbeat music)