What would you do if you went to the bathroom one day and you saw an eyeball looking at
you?
Not your own eyeball, not that you're looking in the mirror, someone else's eyeball.
And then, no more fooling around on Dead Rabbit Radio, we're gonna take a look at a brand
new theory that apparently is a 2000 year old ritual.
Is there any truth behind the story of the 40 day season of the blood sacrifice?
Is the next month and a half going to be the most bloodiest time in human history?
Fold onto your hats, boys.
Draining blood.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back.
You like that excitement of my voice?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I am having a great day, and I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I gotta say this, I just recorded an entire episode of Dead Rabbit Radio about the blood
sacrifice.
That's a super exciting story I talked about in the video.
You know what, before I do this, let's bring in our newest Patreon supporter.
Sliding in the Dead Rabbit Command right now, he has shoes made of snakes.
He's not great shoes, he's just supposed to have snake skin boots.
He skipped a step and just got the snakes tied to his feet.
It's Chime Chili, he's dead.
He's like floating in.
His corpse is being dragged by snakes.
Everyone give a round of applause.
If you clap loud enough, he'll come back to life.
Give a round of applause for Chime Chili and also we'll give him some anti-venom.
Chime as you get roused from your coma, shaking you, I go, you're gonna be our captain on
Pilates episode.
He's all pale.
He's like, what?
What?
Where am I?
You're gonna be our captain on Pilates episode if you guys can't support the Patreon or if
you've never been bit by a snake.
That's fine too.
Hopefully, hopefully you haven't.
Just spread the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
Now Chime, as you're getting a blood transfusion, you're getting blood from me.
You're getting the best blood on the planet.
Man, I gotta tell you guys what happened.
So I recorded an entire episode about the 40 day blood sacrifice.
In short, I'm gonna turn a 20 minute segment into a five minute segment from March 22 or
March 19.
That's kind of wiggly, but from now until May 1, there's supposed to be some sort of
mass casualty event and it's a sacrifice to the pagan god, Baal.
You're like, Jason, that's amazing.
Why don't you cover that?
Well, I did a full 20 minute segment on it and I was talking about a Reddit account
called ConspiracyBeerMe, which we actually covered in our Nashville bomber episode.
It's a great segment.
I really, really like it.
I recorded it all and the whole thing was like, ConspiracyBeerMe, the Reddit account
believes this, believes that, believes this, believes that.
As I was editing it, I did a little more research.
It turns out that ConspiracyBeerMe is a podcast and they're a bunch of comedians.
And I thought, as great as this segment is, and I thought, as great as this segment,
someone's vacuuming now, great.
I recorded a whole segment, I gotta rerecord this, someone's vacuuming.
I'm just gonna have to deal with it.
As great as this segment was, I couldn't edit around me saying they believe that and
it would be no different than someone saying that I believe monkeys don't exist and their
episode just came out today.
So all of that stuff combined might have been able to edit around it, but they just dropped
an episode today about this conspiracy.
So if you want to know more about it, I would recommend checking out ConspiracyBeerMe.
I think in their podcast, I'll put the link in the show note, I may replay my segment
in the future.
I think ConspiracyBeerMe is a bonus episode or something like that, because it is a really
funny and formative segment, but I don't want to step on another podcast's toes and
I definitely don't want to keep throwing them under the bus.
So we'll see what we do.
Just know that somewhere out there in the Dead Rabbit universe, there's a really cool
segment that maybe someday will get played and now I need to fill 20 minutes.
I need to admit, maybe not that long, but I gotta tell you some stuff.
The second segment is sticking around.
Literally it's a sticky story.
So I'm not...
That's stupid vacuum.
I'm not just...
Yeah, I'm having a great day, right?
And now someone outside is talking.
This is beautiful.
The 40 days of the feast of ball have begun.
They've begun at my house as there's chaos everywhere.
So chime, chilly.
Let's go ahead and hop in the Jason Jalopy.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command and we are going to go to my old hometown of
Sacramento, California.
We're headed down.
We're going back in time.
I wanted to tell you some stories that happened to me when I was younger because you guys
seem to like that stuff.
You guys seem to like that stuff.
It doesn't require a lot of research.
It actually happened to me.
I'm going to tell you about some bizarre events when I was younger.
So first off, I'm trying to figure out the best order for this and most interesting to
even more interesting.
Chime, chilly.
Drive us down Greenback Avenue.
That's kind of the main thoroughfare through, oh, you know what, while we're here in Orangeville,
Orangeville, California, which is a suburb of Sacramento, this is an interesting story.
These are all going to be just kind of weird asides.
Some of them supernatural.
Some of them true crime.
That basically sums up my entire life.
It's one or the other.
Today, I was walking through town.
I'm not in Orangeville.
I'm walking through town.
I'm looking down and I see someone standing in the middle of the sidewalk wearing black
boots with red shoelaces.
I look up and it's just like a dad.
He has his kids around there, his wife standing there.
He's on the phone.
He's wearing black boots with red shoelaces.
Here's the thing, where I'm, he was a white dude.
And where I'm from in Orangeville, Sacramento area, a white man wearing black boots with
red shoelaces means that you've killed a black person.
I don't think this guy did.
I hope he didn't, right?
I hope he didn't.
But I thought it was a really interesting thing because there are so many hidden symbols.
I don't know if you knew that and that might not be a universal thing.
And so it's super bizarre because I am mead.
I had a friend who did that once, not killed a black person, but I had a friend who was
wearing black boots with red shoelaces and I go, don't do that.
And he's like, what do you mean?
I go, if you walk into the wrong part of town and someone sees that, they're going to assume
that you've murdered someone of a different race.
You're going to assume you've committed a hate crime, the worst hate crime, murder.
The vacuum is getting closer, so let's keep going here.
I thought it was, and it's just a different way of living.
Same thing like you'll see people with spider web tattoos on their elbows, huge white supremacy,
where I grew up at least.
If you had that, that means you were a white supremacist.
Other people go, oh man, don't look cool.
Don't look like Spider-Man.
They're letting themselves get bit by radioactive spiders to make the tattoo even more authentic.
So the thing that, when you grow up in a crime-ridden area, you look for stuff like that.
I've said this before, if you want to know what gang controls your area, go to the local
gas station and see what color hats and bandanas they sell.
Because if you go to an area and all the hats are blue and the bandanas are blue, that means
it's a crypt-controlled area.
Walmart's will do it too in their budget clothes section.
I remember when I first moved up here, I saw a bunch of clothes that were purple and silver
and I go, Latin Kings.
This is Latin King territory.
So there's that.
You're burning all your clothes now.
You're burning all your clothes and getting rid of your shoelaces.
It's easy to accidentally do that stuff.
It's easy to accidentally appear that you're affiliated with a gang and that could lead
you into really bad stuff.
So Orangevale, California, let's talk about a weird story now.
That was our true crime story.
I remember once, I don't know if I've really talked to you and I've been reluctant to because
it's so ridiculous.
Like, I used to, I don't want to say practice magic.
I don't want to say that, but I used to study magic.
And I'm not talking about card tricks because I did that too.
When my parents got a divorce when we moved from San Lorenzo to Sacramento, I was really
into doing card tricks and I actually used, it's so bizarre.
It sounds so fake, but I used card tricks to convince the kids at the new school that
I was psychic.
I actually talked about the divorce story and the story about the man with the knives.
I used to be a really good student who was trying out for the football team and had a
girlfriend and all that stuff.
Then when I transferred schools, I just gave up on all of that and I started hanging out
with the rougher kids.
I hung out with rough kids in San Lorenzo too, but I just sat on the back of class and just
drew or scribbled and stuff like that.
Played and mashed with all the kids.
I'm like, who are you going to marry?
You live in a shack.
Because I can't draw.
So that was the only thing I could do.
But we did all that stuff and I brought, I had a deck, a deck of marked cards.
Really really good marked cards.
No one else could tell that they were marked.
I convinced the kids that I was psychic.
I was the new kid who would come from the Bay Area in 1992, 1993.
I was able to convince them I was psychic.
I also started an underground newspaper and that made me super cool.
I got dragged into the principal's office.
There was a huge controversy about it.
The whole thing of the underground newspaper was why don't we all, all the different cliques,
the jocks and the nerds and the magicians, the powerful magicians, why don't we all
team up and run the school?
We're like, I'm the principal now?
No, it's just like I said that all of these cliques were created by the administration
to keep us divided.
And if we all gave up our normal, like, these barriers are meaningless.
The jock and the nerd, they're meaningless.
The jock and the nerd, the vacuum cleaner that's getting closer and closer, they're
all meaningless.
So let's all unite.
There was no goal.
It wasn't like, and then we'll run the school and we'll set, we'll set the times that we're
supposed to show up and we'll have turkey every day for lunch or whatever.
It's nothing like that.
It was just let's quit dividing ourselves among these arbitrary lines, arbitrary, damn it,
arbitrary, whatever, these lines that we've made up or that the administration has made
up.
And it's so funny because that philosophy, first off, it's super basic, but that philosophy
is something I've always held.
I think when we have these religious differences, you worship different gods and have different
religions, that's fine.
But to think that I hate you because you have this different religion or you have this different
skin color or you're from this different culture or different political belief or whatever,
I think is always, someone's always pulling the strings and inflaming those things.
And if we could say, listen, you're completely different from me, we have nothing in common
at all, except for the fact that we exist together on earth, let's team up and not kill
each other and move forward.
That's always been a philosophy of mine.
But I was doing it, I was in high school, you get dragged in front of the principal's
office as an adult, nobody cares.
People just kind of keep on going about their lives.
But anyways, so yeah, I got dragged in front of the principal and I did that whole like,
yeah, whatever, bro, like, what are you going to do?
Because I didn't care at that point.
My entire, like my family had fallen apart and stuff like that.
And I was just doing what I did.
I will say this though, I remember being very, very popular because of that underground newsletter.
I remember people were like, this one girl came up to me and she goes, wow, you're just
like Christian Slater and pump up the volume.
And I thought, I just kind of nodded.
I didn't know what she was talking about.
I hadn't seen the movie, had a vague idea.
Anyways, so that's just a high school, oh no, because I was a magician and I was tricking
people with my cards.
I also was steady and when I was in college, I started studying like magic, like sorcery,
because I was having these encounters with ghosts and demons and stuff like that.
And I thought, well, how do I fight back?
Like, I've watched this great documentary called Buffy the Vampire Slayer and sometimes
you have to use magic to fight these things.
So I started buying books at a local witch store and was reading about magic and things
like that.
And I'll probably tell more stories about that.
I'm just so reluctant because it's so ridiculous, right?
It's so ridiculous.
But I did it.
I did it.
I gotta be honest.
And as much as I talk trash about witches and stuff like that and how much I want magic
to exist, I used to like do rituals.
I don't do them anymore, but I used to do rituals.
And I remember one night, it was me, my buddy, I think it was Steve, I think it was my buddy
Steve and my cousin Rachel.
I said, this is gonna sound completely made up and ridiculous, but just roll with it.
Out of all the stuff I've said on the show, this is the most ridiculous thing.
But it's not even my most ridiculous story.
I remember I had performed a spell.
So dumb.
I had performed a spell that in theory would turn us invisible.
Would make it to, it wasn't that we would be like, now you see meeting?
It would be that unless someone was specifically looking for you.
They couldn't find you.
So I lived in my grandma's house and my grandma was like, Jason, are you done doing the laundry?
And I'm just like standing there, she would see me.
But if she was just kind of walking around waiting for the adventurers of Lois and Clark
to come on, I would just be like, won't I be the predator in the living room?
She's like, why is the television so blurry?
Move out of the way, blur?
Whatever.
Like it's so ridiculous, but I remember doing it.
I knew what you were gonna ask for, this spell.
I'd have to find it.
And it wasn't an easy spell to do.
It wasn't like mirror, mirror, make me not seen by anyone who, unless they want to gleam
or something, it wasn't anything like that.
It required all these banishing rituals and stuff like that.
So, so ridiculous.
I'm totally fine.
Chum Chilly is like just standing there with his arm spread wide.
What are you talking about?
What is going on?
You once claimed that you turned yourself invisible.
Well, hold on.
It's actually good that we're in the Jason Jalopy because this 100% happened.
This 100% happened.
My cousin is a bit of a wild child.
And we were driving through, I said, hey, yeah, I think I cast this spell where we're
invisible unless people are looking at me.
And Rachel's like, oh, really?
I mean, they were humoring me.
Steve was like, oh, you know, they knew me well enough.
And I was just like, yeah, it's supposed to do that at least.
So for whatever reason we went for a drive, I think we're just going out to Denny's or
Keros or something like that.
It was me, Rachel.
And I think it was Steve.
It might have been Josh, but I'm pretty sure it was Steve.
And we get in my car and we're driving through Orangevale.
And I remember Rachel sitting in the back seat and we're driving and there's a car coming
the opposite direction.
And Rachel leans her, Rachel, my cousin, she was probably like 15, 16 at this point and
she was over in my grandma's house all the time.
We're driving down the road and a cop car is coming in the opposite direction.
She leans her head out of the back window and as we pass by the cop, she screams as loud
as she can at the police officer.
Now we all grew up in Orangevale, which basically meant you were fearless of the police, right?
You either had a bunch of interactions with the police and they pulled you over all the
time or you knew how to outrun the police in Orangevale.
You knew the roads, they knew the roads, but you had to figure stuff out.
So that totally made that was totally within Rachel's character to do that.
And she leans out the back window and she might have been a little bit younger, but
yeah I think we were going to Keros or something like that.
She leans out the back window and she screams and I'm driving and I see her maneuvering
in the back and as we pass the cop, she sticks her head out the window and goes, "Ahhh!"
She yells at the cop and I turn, I was flipping out dude.
Because although you're fearless of the police, you want to limit your interactions with them,
right?
But if you have to interact with them, whatever, you'll say what you're going to say and they
search your car or they don't.
So you never want to have anything in your car in Orangevale.
I remember once I got pulled over, I had a baseball bat in my car.
Because yeah, in California that's illegal, you can't just have a baseball bat in your
car.
I'm recording this actually as I'm holding a baseball bat for whatever reason, but she
screams and I turn around and I'm like, "Rachel, what are you doing?
What are you doing?"
And she goes, "We're invisible, right?"
She's kind of laughing and Steve is like, "Oh great."
Steve had like 10 pounds of cocaine on him.
No, just joking, he was straight and narrow.
We're driving down the road and we're all waiting for that cop to bust a U.E. because
at the very least they see a girl stick her head out of the back window and scream.
So the cop doesn't know what's going on.
But they never... nothing.
They just kept driving as if we were invisible.
So is that proof that we actually turn invisible?
The fact that...
That's the end of the story.
I thought eventually you'd go to Denny's and no one served on you.
No one waited on you.
You were standing waiting for a while.
I remember a couple times that night we were speeding because at this point I wanted to
see whether or not it was actually real.
I remember we were doing some other unsafe traffic stuff and there was a lot of cops.
I think that happened later on.
We saw another cop and I just was driving as fast as... not as fast as I could, but I
was driving very fast.
The cop didn't pull us over.
So at that point we did actually think maybe we are invisible if nobody is looking for
us.
And let me tell one more... one more story about my time.
This is another weird story.
We were driving... it was this time it was me and Steve.
And I think Mauricio might have been there.
We're driving on the same road, actually in the same area that Rachel leaned her head out
the window and yelled.
This right next... it was on a greenback and hazel.
We're driving down greenback one night.
This story... it's hard to say whether or not it's supernatural or just straight up weird.
We had just started our nightly adventure or weekend adventure to go ghost hunting and
go eat at caros or denies or wherever we're headed.
We're driving on the road and a dog shows up.
Chimechillie's leaving.
No Chimechillie, come back!
Come back, bro!
Come back!
You're gonna like this story.
If you like mysterious dogs, you're driving on the road.
And this big dog starts walking across greenback lane.
It's a very busy road, but we're out at like 11 o'clock at night.
We see... I mean this lane is like a giant German shepherd.
It's like standing in the suicide lane and the yellow lane.
It's like a four lane road standing in the middle of the road.
I think it was a suicide lane.
But anyways, the dog was in the middle of the street and I start to slow down and the dog's
looking at me and it walks and it's stopped in the middle of the road.
There's no traffic behind us because it's late at night and I look at Steve and I'm like
"What the hell?
Where did this dog stand in the middle of the road?"
So I go to drive around it and the dog starts walking and now I'm like in the other lane
and the dog's standing in that lane now.
And I'm like "What in the world?
Like he wouldn't let us pass."
So I go "Let's pull into the Safeway parking lot and then we'll go through the parking
lot and get away from the dog."
Because at this point, like on the one hand I'm afraid the dog might get hit.
On the other hand, the dog's kind of being a jerk for not letting us move.
So as I'm pulling into the Safeway parking lot, he starts walking and I'm like "What
in the world is going on?"
And then I get into the parking lot and the dog walks up to the car and is now standing
right in front of the car.
At this point we're laughing really, really hard because we're thinking "What is going
on?"
And I go to...no joke, this actually happened.
I go to back up and the dog gets on its hind legs and puts its paws on the hood.
That's how big it was by the way.
It's standing there with its paws on the hood just looking at me.
And I'm half expecting this guy to turn into a full werewolf and devour us all.
And I'm also laughing and me and Steve and I think Marie Sue, he's like half there, half
not, I don't remember.
We're laughing really hard because this dog has basically stopped our journey right when
it started.
And as funny as it was, we were also getting this sensation that this dog wanted us to
wait.
This dog was delaying our journey for one reason or another.
I remember kind of having that sensation as we were watching this whole thing unfold.
And he stayed on our car for I think, I don't know, it was like 15-20 minutes.
I mean like it was a long time, remember at a certain point we're like "Is this dog ever
going to leave?
Are we stuck here?
Is the rest of our existence stuck in this car with this dog?"
And after a prolonged amount of time, the dog got off the car and just walked away.
And I remember at a certain point us thinking "The dog is keeping us here for a reason."
We're not supposed to leave for a reason.
But then afterwards we went on our destination to go get dinner or something like that.
A weir, I mean like wasn't it an omen?
Was it something that had we left earlier we would have gotten a car accident or gotten
a fight which was normal in Orangevale?
You know who knows what would have happened.
Who knows what would have happened.
Did that dog save our life?
Or was it just, it was uncharacteristic behavior for a dog.
They normally don't stop traffic and they normally don't, once they do stop traffic
if that happens they don't follow you into a parking lot and prevent you from leaving.
So just an odd, Orangevale was such a weird town.
Such an odd place and just a couple odd stories from that.
Yeah and I hope that you enjoyed that.
I hope it didn't come off as filler material.
Because I do think, I mean it technically was, I couldn't run the other story.
But these are stories that I've thought about telling from time to time.
So yeah I hope you guys did enjoy that.
Chime, chili, let's go ahead and call in that car runner copter.
There's a dog, there's a dog standing on the helicopter.
We have to sit there for like 20 minutes to take off.
But eventually we give the doggy some pets.
There was no way I was getting out of the car to pet this thing dude.
It was massive.
I wasn't going to go into Safeway and buy some treats.
I remember us thinking, oh dude and I do.
I remember this now.
When the dog, after a certain point, the dog was on the front of the car with his paws
there.
I go, let's slowly, this is 100% true, let's slowly back up.
And I remember slowly backing up and the dog kind of readjusting it first and then getting
off the front of the car.
And then we see it walk and now it's standing behind the car.
I remember that fully because it was like a werewolf movie.
I remember we were like looking from side to side as it, where did it go, where did
it go?
It's all coming in through the air vent.
It walked and stood behind the back of the car.
So Mauricio must have been back there because he must have looked out the window.
He was just behind the car, he was just behind the car.
And I won't say for certain that it put its paws on the back of the car, but it did stop
us from backing up.
And I remember start slowly moving forward again.
It walks in the front of the car and stands on it again.
I do remember that happening and then at that point we weren't moving at all because I didn't
want to accidentally back over the dog.
I couldn't for certain see it when it was walking me on the car.
It would not let us leave.
I remember that now.
It was walking along the side of the car and got behind us.
And then eventually just after a period of time it just walked away.
So Chime Chili, Chime Chili is already flying away in the cover to cover to.
No, come back, come back.
We are leaving behind Orangevale, California.
We are saying goodbye to the puppy and we're saying goodbye to invisible me.
We don't know where he's at.
So we're just waving everywhere.
Let's leave behind this area and these stories that I just kind of had to remember for this
segment.
I'm heading out to Central London.
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
And as we're headed out to London I turn to you.
I put my hand on your shoulder and I look you right in the eye and I say "new today
on digital and on demand."
Joel McHale and Carrie Bache lead an all-star cast in the dark romantic comedy Happily.
The film centers around a couple who, after 14 years of marriage, discover their friends
are resentful of their constant public displays of affection.
When a visit from a mysterious stranger leads to a dead body, they begin to question the
loyalty of their so-called friends.
Buy or rent Happily today on digital and on demand, rated R from Paramount Pictures.
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do