I just flew in from Sacramento and boy are my arms tired.
Today is going to be a bit of a different episode.
Because I'm exhausted, I'm tired and I have no prep work done.
Instead we're going to look at a couple of conspiracy theories that I kind of believe.
I'm not married to any of them, but these are things that may be true.
We're going to look at these and more on the hot take episode of Dead Rabbit Radio starting now.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I'm flat out exhausted.
I just flew back in from Sacramento.
My vacation is over and I'm back at home with my regular microphone.
I'm doing a regular setup and I was like, you know what?
I'm going to do something different.
We're just going to do a hot take episode.
I don't want to actually really even know what that term means.
I just see it on the internet.
I see cool kids using it and I want to be cool too.
We're going to go over a couple of my personal conspiracies.
Some of them I actually do believe in and some of them I think may be possible.
But we'll get into it.
We'll get into it here.
But I did have a great vacation.
I'm going to get back to responding to all YouTube comments and stuff like that.
Guys have been great while I know the schedule was kind of wonky the past couple weeks, but
I appreciate that you guys are sticking around.
But let's go ahead and get started here.
Now, I don't talk about politics on this show.
It's one of the rules of Dead Rapper Radio.
No politics and never ever fall in love.
Two main rules of Dead Rapper Radio.
But if you don't want to hear anything about politics, skip ahead maybe 10 minutes.
But before you do, let me tell you my first...
Before you jump ahead, you're like, "Great, he's going to talk about income and quality."
Before I get into...
Before you jump ahead, give me a second.
Conspiracy theory number one.
Marianne Williamson is a witch.
Now, yeah, see, I got your attention.
Now this one...
So I know I've done a couple episodes about how I'm not a huge fan of Wiccans.
I think it's...
Okay, that's not being fair.
That's kind of watering it down.
The episode I did was, "Why are Wiccans always fat?"
What's the episode?
I'm not...
I can't pussyfoot around the actual episode.
Hey, welcome new listeners, by the way.
Welcome new listeners to the show, Dead Rapper Radio.
So anyways, but so obviously Marianne Williamson is fairly attractive, thin woman.
So you're like, "Jason, if you went on and on for half hour about why is it that there's
a combination or a correlation between overweight people and the Wiccan religion, but here Marianne
Williamson is 120, I'm assuming.
I don't know.
I'm not her stalker.
I'm all looking through her bushes at her scale.
I think she's a witch.
And so this is the reason why.
Well I don't actually have any proof, but one, she does talk a lot about like mysticism
and magical powers and she talks a lot about like mysticism and like positive thinking,
which you know I'm fine with, definitely I'm a fan of positive thinking.
She talks about Trump bringing a quote, "dark psychic force" into the world and it's almost
to her it's not a battle of policies, it's a battle of like energies.
You know, like Jason, that doesn't make you a witch, huh?
Hold on, hold on.
I also have a like, when you deal with, I've met like witches in real life, not Wiccans,
but like witches, and when you meet people you start to think about it this way.
How many times do you have to get mugged before you're able to pretty, before you're
pretty good at spotting a mugger from like a hundred yards away?
You're walking on the street, well you get the example, so I think that is where I'm
coming from.
I've dealt with real witches in the past, so when I see someone I go, that's a witch,
like burn her, no, no, I'm not saying burn her, I'm not saying that at all, but you know
what I mean, like you see, you pick up on it, you go, that's a witch, that's totally
a witch, and she gives off that witch energy, and I'm not even using that as a pejorative,
I'm just saying that I think she casts, I think she's capable of casting spells.
And not Wiccan, which is different, I think she might be an actual witch.
I also think she probably, here's the thing, people always go, who am I voting for?
I go, who's the funniest candidate?
Who's the candidate that if they won would provide me with the most laughs?
So, I mean, dude, I would love to have a president who believed that crystals healed people.
That would be hilarious.
I probably wouldn't be so good for healthcare in the nation, but wouldn't it be awesome
to have a president who's like, like praying to the moon?
So yeah, I think she's a witch, I don't have any proof of it, I think as the campaign
goes on, I think she's going to be one of the long holdouts of the Democratic Party,
because I think her passion is so into it, and she has magical powers that she can hang
on longer.
I predict she'll be in the top six.
Like when it narrows down to six people, maybe seven people she'll be in there.
So Marianne Williamson is a witch.
I guess I should explain for people who don't know, Marianne Williamson is a Democratic nominee
for president.
I probably should have said that seven minutes ago.
Marianne Williamson is a witch.
That's conspiracy theory number one.
So yes, yes, that is about as political as we get on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Marianne Williamson is a witch, has witch powers.
I'm sure she's also probably the only presidential candidate that's ever used a yawning egg.
Okay, let's go ahead and move on to my next hot take conspiracy.
Bear with me here.
Here's one.
This one I think is fairly true, and I think a lot of people agree with the base of it,
but I'm pushing it a little bit farther.
Fast food restaurants, their food is designed to make you fat.
And I think people go, well, of course, you know, like they have all these ingredients
that, you know, they're big fat burgers, big max.
I'm taking it a step further than that.
I think fast food restaurants in particular use a model basically patterned after drug
dealers.
Because here's the thing.
Before subway, before subway existed, did you ever think, you know what I really need
right now?
A foot of bread in meat in meat.
Like before subway existed, you went to, unless you specifically went to a sub shop, you would
order a sandwich or you would make a sandwich at home.
Maybe you'd have a hoagie if you were feeling particularly ethnic that day.
But subway, and I know the conspiracy theory, and maybe you don't know the conspiracy theory,
but foot long subs are not actually a foot long.
They're like 11 inches.
And I remember there was a big controversy about it years ago, and I'm like, who cares?
Like that's probably one of the dumbest things to get riled up about, that you're getting
one inch less of food.
Anyways.
I think that fast food restaurants use the same model basically that drug dealers use.
You get them hooked on the supply, and you get them hooked on the supply by making the
portions not just full of fat and sugars, but bigger.
Because then what happens is you go to, you know if you go to McDonald's you're going
to get not as good tasting food, but it's going to satisfy you on a primal level more
than going to a sit down restaurant.
Like you can go to McDonald's, and for the same amount of money that you can go to a
sit down restaurant, you can pretty much buy a double the food, or one and a half times
the food.
And you eat it, and it releases all these endorphins because it's full of sugars and
fats.
It's designed to basically make you addicted to it.
And the portions are larger.
You can, let's say you go to a restaurant and you order a bourbon fries.
You really don't give you a lot of fries.
You get a burger, you get a nice juicy delicious burger, Trillium, Great Burgers here on Hood
River, but you never get a lot of fries.
When you go to McDonald's or Burger King or something, you can basically get as many
fries as you want.
Ah, I want a large fry, I want a super sized fry, whatever.
Same thing.
Subway Domino's.
I was looking at ordering Domino's when I got home.
They have that package where it's a p- like you can basically get any two items for $5.99
each.
So you can order like two pizzas for $5.99 each.
The thing, or like two sandwiches or a sandwich and a pizza or whatever, the thing is you
have to order two.
And I'll argue that Domino's knows that most of the people who ordered Domino's live
by themselves.
So basically you're saying, "Eat two pizzas."
You individual person who just flew in from Sacramento, you can't order less than two
pizzas.
We're not going to allow that.
If you want to, well, you can still allow it.
You just have to pay more.
But if you want this deal, you have to order two pizzas.
And I think the logic is, the logic that I'm assigning them is if they order two pizzas,
they'll eat two pizzas.
And then, then nothing less than two pizzas will satisfy them.
It's basically the same thing as drugs.
Okay, I'm realizing that I may not be communicating that logic as much as I, but I think that fast
food restaurants use the same business model as drug dealers.
They're everywhere.
Their food is made to be addictive.
And they give you such outrageous portions that when you think about going somewhere
else, I realize that maybe I'm, this might just be a Jason thing, because I think most
people if they want like a delicious, I don't cook myself.
I hope nobody cooks themselves, but I don't cook for myself that often.
Anyways, I guess that kind of, okay, people are like, no, Jason, you're just fat and
you need to go back on keto.
And I do need to go back on keto.
Okay, onto the, do you guys, I don't like, you guys get that right?
Fast food restaurants are designed to basically be like drug dealers.
Get you addicted to their food.
Get you coming back, all their special sauce and all that stuff.
Think it's suspicious.
Okay, okay, so remaining listeners, thank you.
Thank you for sticking around with this.
Here, we're moving on to our next one.
I think Beyonce is a scam.
I think Beyonce is not, I think she's a real person.
I'm not saying she's a hologram.
I'm not going to go so far to say that she's some sort of tax write-off, but I don't think
she is as big as people say she is.
I think she is propped up by a huge marketing machine and a record label and her albums
aren't as big as they actually are.
You go, Jason, that's easy to prove or disprove because you can look at album sales numbers.
But here's the thing.
We see the same thing with movie tickets to a certain point, but with book, specifically
this happens a lot with book publishers.
A book will come out and a book publisher will buy back tons of their own books so they
can boost their sales up.
What they do is they're basically pre-orders or gifts and stuff like that.
YouTube had an album that they gave away with either a newspaper or an iPod or something
like that.
That counted towards it.
Nowadays, when you buy a ticket to a tour, I know Madonna did this to a tour ago, you
buy a ticket for her tour, you got a free copy of her album.
That counted as an album sale.
There's a lot of ways to artificially boost your sales.
And I think Beyonce, I think that's all she does basically.
There was a huge scandal a couple of years ago.
Jay-Z bought Tidal, which was a music streaming site out of Sweden or Norway.
And it turns out that Kanye West came out with his new album, The Life of Pablo, and
Beyonce came out with her new album, I think it was called Lemonade or something like that.
And they showed that her album had been streamed 320 million times.
And Kanye West's album had been streamed like 300 million times.
And someone started digging through the numbers and they looked and they said, "Everyone who's
subscribed to Tidal would have to listen to Beyonce's album for eight days straight to
get to 300 million downloads in the period of time that it was."
When they looked at the numbers, they actually only got 170 million downloads.
Beyonce's album only got 170 million downloads.
Kanye West's album only got 150 million downloads.
So they were doubled and they showed how all the numbers were rigged and basically there
was duplicate plays going on.
Someone would listen to the album and then behind the scenes it would play again.
So Kanye West and Beyonce got huge payouts from Tidal when actually their albums were
only heard half as many times.
I think that she isn't the huge selling superstar that people make her out to be.
I think she sells albums and I think people really, really like her, but I don't think
they listen to her music.
I don't think they listen to her music and I don't think it is as...
Here's the thing, this could just be because I live up on Hood River, but when's the last
time you heard a Beyonce song on the radio that wasn't crazy in love or Destiny's Child
song?
When's the last time Beyonce has had a crossover hit that would make her sell millions of albums?
The only Beyonce song I ever hear on the radio is, "What was that one song where she's like,
'Oh, you're so beautiful.
You're just a girl or like if girls run the world or something like that?'"
That and Crazy in Love and then Destiny's Child stuff.
You're saying, "Jayson, you're just an old man.
You don't listen to the right radio stations, maybe."
But I don't think she is as popular as...
I think she's an icon.
I personally am not a fan of hers, but I think people know who she is and it's cool to like
Queen B, but it would be interesting to see how many people watched her Netflix special.
It'd be interesting to see how many people actually buy and listen to her albums.
I mean a lot of people are like, "Ooh, I love Queen B.
She's so cool."
But they don't name a couple songs.
Crazy in Love, Lemonade, like it's not...
She doesn't have songs that you can just kick back to and listen.
I don't know, again, maybe I'm just an old man.
But that's one of my conspiracy theories.
Beyonce is a scam.
Beyonce is...
I won't go so far to say she's some sort of tax write off or some sort of malicious scam.
I just think Jay-Z has a hot girlfriend and he wants to keep her happy.
So he lets her record albums.
Oh, Single Ladies, that was a big hit.
But see, all those are like older songs.
Single Ladies was a big hit.
And then she had one or two other ones.
She kind of had this thing in the beginning after she left Destiny's Child when she first
got with Jay-Z.
She had these hits.
Now I think it's just this billionaire husband lets his wife pick songs out of a...
Basically meet up with songwriters and buy songs for her and then she goes in the studio,
sings them, and goes on tour so he can...
I love Jay-Z, by the way.
I'm not trying to throw him under the bus.
But you know, yeah honey, yeah, you're perfect.
Everyone loves your albums.
Queen B, Queen B, why don't you go so I can, you know, go sleep with Becky over here.
So that's...
I love you Jay-Z.
But don't cheat on your wife, dude.
Tacky.
Okay, so...
So...
That's not a conspiracy theory.
I'm actually pretty sure Jay-Z did cheat on his wife.
I think that's kind of public record.
But...
Anyways, so...
Here's an interesting...
I want to go back to the fast food thing for a second.
You remember that documentary Super Size Me?
I remember when that came out...
So before I go on...
There's a documentary called Super Size Me where a guy's like, "I'm going to eat nothing
but McDonald's for 30 days to show how disgusting the food is."
The food isn't good for you.
But he goes, "And if they ask me to Super Size It, I will Super Size It."
And so for 30 days he videotapes himself, Morgan Spurlock walking into McDonald's and
he's like...
By the end of the 30 days he's like, "Oh, I'm so sick."
And the doctor's like, "Oh my God, you're totally going to die."
And then McDonald's stops Super Size Me and their stuff because of the publicity for this.
The bad publicity from the movie.
And Morgan Spurlock was kind of held up as like, "Whoa dude, he's like a new Michael Moore.
He's going out but he's eating stuff and he's showing how bad fast food is for you."
Okay.
When the #MeToo movement was first starting off, Morgan Spurlock got pulled into it because
he was being inappropriate with some female assistant or something like that.
And at that time he came out and he said, "I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
I have an alcohol problem.
I've had alcoholism for years and years and years.
I drink every day."
So sorry.
Now, I'm not making fun.
I kind of chuckled there.
I'm not making fun of people with alcoholism.
Part of the concept of Super Size Me was that he ate and drank nothing except for stuff
that he got at McDonald's.
And he had just admitted in writing that he was an alcoholic during the time they were
shooting Super Size Me.
And I remember reading an article and they said, "McDonald's can sue him now because
that was the whole, he's not feeling well because he's just eating nothing but McDonald's.
But if he was suffering from alcoholism, that will also make your belly be all bloated
and make a doctor go, 'Oh my God, you might die soon.'
And I remember seeing that, I remember reading something too that McDonald's, in the insiders
were saying that McDonald's might try to sue Morgan Spurlock, but they just let it go.
As far as I know, as far as I know, they just kind of let it go because they could have
taken him to court and said, "You committed fraud.
You told everyone you ate nothing but our product for a month and you got sick."
It turns out you were actually drinking four Bloody Marys every morning as well, so you
lied.
And that's the reason why your health was so bad.
Okay, and so next one here, I have just a couple, I had to write these down because
even though I'm not prepared enough to do a normal episode, I had to prepare for something
at least.
Let's see, Mary Ann Williamson is a witch, I did that one.
Here's the, you know, we'll end it on this one, assuming I can keep a linear path in
my thoughts.
I'll end this one.
This is one that is kind of weird.
[laughs]
I mean, that's assuming the other ones were normal to you.
It's going to take us a couple steps together.
So I don't know what happens to you after you die.
Shock, I know, everyone thought I had all the answers, but I don't know what happens
to you after you die.
I believe something, I don't believe you just disappear, I don't believe you just go into
the void.
But people ask me, "Hey, do you believe in reincarnation?"
I go, "I don't know.
I don't know."
That's the exact tone I take with them too.
I go, "I don't know.
I don't know."
I actually have a friend of mine who thinks that her son, like, her son will often mention
stuff about being like in an old war.
She's like, "Really?"
She goes, "I think you might have been reincarnated.
I don't know."
But do I believe in reincarnation?
I don't know.
I think reincarnation is an interesting thought because I like the physical planet Earth.
I like the physical things around us.
So the idea of going into some sort of like spiritual ether or going into a realm not
of this Earth, that actually terrifies me more than like dying.
Like the idea of dying doesn't necessarily scare me.
The idea of moving past the physical realm into a brand new spiritual journey, that's
what scares me.
Like because I like touching stuff and I like seeing stuff and hearing stuff and tasting
stuff.
But we're all based on physical things that are receptors in our body.
I don't think that a little ghost shaped, a little ghost in the shape of Jason is going
to float up into the sky and then be walking on streets.
I don't think that that just doesn't make any sense.
So the idea, I remember I was watching Twin Peaks when I went down to Sacramento.
My brother hadn't seen the last three episodes of Twin Peaks The Return, so I went down there
and we watched him.
And all the stuff with like the giant floating head and the teapot with David Bowie in it.
I'm thinking what if this is what happens when you die?
It's just this weird black and white artistic world.
And it's just like *blah* *psshh* *blah* *psshh* and then David Bowie talks to you.
Like that would not, and it's not where I want to go.
That would be super unsettling.
Killer Bob's floating around in a ball.
No.
So the idea of reincarnation is very intriguing to me.
It's very peaceful to me.
And I will say this, let me do one more little hot take.
Again, I don't know what that means.
The, I think reincarnation may actually be the way you explain to a caveman quantum reality.
Or quantum immortality, where if you die you just shift into another universe and you
don't know you've died, you continue on with your life.
Because you can't experience a world that you can't experience, so you're basically
create a, you move into a world where you can't experience it.
So if you had like shamans or yogis or whatever back in the day experimenting with these vision
quests and they were similar upon the idea of reincarnation, they might have actually
just been realized seeing through the veil and seeing that there's a reality next to us
and when you die you enter that reality.
And they can't really explain that so they go, "Ah, you become a dog."
Like you can't explain to a caveman the way that quantum reality works so you go, "Oh
yeah, if you die you just become a stick."
You become a log.
And like, "That's kind of lame."
Well you should have been better.
If you're a really good log you'll end up becoming a cricket.
"Ah, I can be a good cricket."
And you go on.
And it could just be a way of looking at what may actually be true is that when you die you
shift to a universe where you haven't died and you have no idea that you died.
You know, it's just a quick, "Whoa man, that was close.
I almost got hit by that car."
When in the reality you came from, you actually did get killed instantly when you get hit
by the car.
I don't really even know if I believe in quantum immortality because it raises a lot of questions
like what if you're horribly injured?
Are you horribly injured for the rest of time?
Because you just keep shifting into another reality where you did not succumb to your
wounds but you're like, "Ugh, I'll bust it up."
If you're 99 years old and you die in bed, do you switch into another reality where you're
99 years old dying in bed and then you switch into another reality where you're 99 years
old dying in bed?
And every second you die and go to another reality where you just have one more second
to live, that sounds hellish.
So the idea of quantum immortality, it's kind of a weird one and I don't know how true
it is but let's go back to my main thing which is reincarnation.
Don't worry, this is going somewhere.
I'm supposed to every other segment on this episode.
Reincarnation, the idea that when you die you are reborn into another body.
Most likely humans, sometimes you might become a cricket or a stick or something like that,
but you die and then you become a human baby and you live your life out again and you have
your karmic mission, you live a good life, you become, you get reborn and you do that
so many times you basically fulfill your soul quest or you achieve enlightenment or whatever.
You have to live through a thousand lifetimes or a million lifetimes and if you keep making
the same mistakes in each lifetime, the journey is when you die you start back over as a baby,
but if each time you kind of are more enlightened, you're a better person in each incarnation,
eventually you will ascend out of the physical realm.
I think, so let's assume that's true, because again I don't know, that again there's very
comforting thought to me.
If that's true, I think that this is one of my first incarnations, maybe second or something
like that.
I'm not an old soul, I'm not, if that's true I believe this would be one of my first
times on earth, because everything, I'm 42 years old but everything always seems so new
and fascinating to me and I'm clumsy, kind of clumsy, not super clumsy, I used to be
really clumsy as a kid, so you're like, Jason, just tell me what your conspiracy theory is,
what does any of this have to do?
Here it is, people who are reincarnated just in the beginning, so first, maybe first couple
times that they've been a baby and then died and came back as another baby.
They're still getting used to their physical bodies, their souls are still getting used
to being able to walk around the planet, but people who have lived hundreds if not thousands
of lifetimes before, live a life, grow old, die, live a life, grow old, die, live a life,
grow old, die, over and over and over again, they become so much more comfortable in their
bodies, they know how bodies work intrinsically, they don't understand why, but they've lived
so many lifetimes that they're basically, if you're an RPG character, they've leveled
up their physical attributes over and over and over again, while people who are not,
they have not been reincarnated a lot of times, who are new to the game, they're still kind
of clumsy, they have two left feet, they bump into stuff, scratch their knees, because they're
still getting used, they don't have the expert control of their bodies over the masterclass
people.
Here's my conspiracy theory, here's what I'm getting at.
Dancers, like really really good dancers, are people who have lived millions of years.
Sometimes I'll just watch dance videos on YouTube, I'm fascinated by great dancing, I think it's
amazing, it's a skill I don't have, and I think that I will see kids, I will see these
young men and women pull off moves that I would have thought were impossible, that the human
body should not be able to move that way, but I think it's all, that's because I'm
new to this, I'm new to this planet, my body is still, I'm still getting used to how fingers
curl and how you can move your legs, I'm basically on the cosmic scale, I'm in a baby body, or
I'm an adult body, but I have baby coordination, where you could have a 19 year old kid who's
actually been living and dying since the days of the Romans, who intrinsically knows what
the body's capable of, how it can move, how fast it can move, which way it can bend, and
they are just naturally born gifted dancers.
They're so comfortable with the human form that they can just glide on the floor, do
incredible moves, things like that.
Now of course, obviously they have to train, they have to train themselves as well, but
I think there's a natural, there are people who are just naturally born dancers and with
training they can become great dancers, you have people that are mediocre dancers and
with training can become pretty good dancers, and then there are people like me who I love
to dance, and I'm bad enough at dancing that when I go out, I'm bad enough at dancing that
it's almost charming, like I can keep a rhythm, and people go wow, he's terrible at dancing,
but there's something charming that he's actually just trying and you can tell I'm having fun.
So yeah, it's charming, he's terrible, he's a horrible dancer, but he looks like he's
having fun, that's nice.
That's nice, say something nice for the boy over there in the bar doing my moves, doing
my moves, because I got a baby brain and a baby body, I got a baby brain and an adult
body that I don't know how to use this body to its full potential.
So we look around for proof of reincarnation by finding kids that are like, my wife died
in 1909, I shot her in the head and they're like, what did you say Billy?
He's realizing he confessed to a crime that's over 100 years old, but we look for proof
in reincarnation with like kids saying stuff or people being hypnotized and things like
that, but it might actually just be something more basic than that.
Someone who's lived multiple lifetimes would know their spirit would hop in a baby and
be like, let's do this, I'm ready to go, they're cracking their knuckles and stuff like that,
because they've piloted a human body so many times before.
Where as someone who is new to the scene, they're like, oh what, I got a butthole, what comes
out of this, oh no, that's horrible, it's all new experiences to them, or newer, if
you've only reincarnated two or three times, you'd still be getting used to the whole thing.
So that is my hot take episode.
I'll look that up, I'll look up what the definition of hot take means before I title it.
If the title of the episode is not a hot take, that means that I don't know what I'm talking
about, that I think of the wrong thing.
I think a hot take is just a thing where you just like say stuff off the top of your head,
I don't know.
But that being said, I hope you guys had fun with today's episode, we're moving back to
our normal schedule tomorrow and then next week we'll have five episodes a week, we're
back at home, making moves, doing stuff, and also guys, thanks for promoting the show as
well, we're just seeing a huge amount of listeners joined in.
Everything will be back to normal tomorrow, DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our
email address, you can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast, you don't have to
listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.
[MUSIC]