Two stories that give us an insight into what happens to us after we die
And then we take a look at the story of a Russian town that captured a bigfoot-like creature and held it prisoner
For 40 years today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you're having a great day too man this show just in the last week has really taken off
I'm getting like 800 downloads a day got an extra
110 subscribers on YouTube just over the past five days. It's it's growing and I appreciate that guys
And I'm thankful that you guys are all listening to it
Recommending it to your friends recommending it to strangers. It's really really taking off and I appreciate that I really do I
Also wanted to say I got some more fan art earlier this week from bin via email
We'll post it in the show notes and then it'll be in the YouTube video
apparently he's actually making a
Power of what he called a PowerPoint level animation of the Thomas Dick episode. So yes, Mungo
Mungo is in the episode and so those drawn to there. I appreciate all that fan art. It's amazing guys
Thank you. I never really thought oh
No, no, no, I'll save that till Monday. I'll save that till Monday
I got this other weird piece of information that I'll talk about on Monday involving the show
But we got a lot of stuff to cover today. So I can't thank you bin
But yeah, I just can't keep going on about how awesome you guys are. Sorry
Because people do I gotta I gotta do the other thing we got a lot to cover
so the first thing we're gonna look at is
Conflicting ideas of what happens after you're dead now, obviously, that's something that religion has you either go to
Most religions some of your reincarnated
But you go to a paradise or you go to hell a punishment place now recently
I found this creepypasta and some of you guys may have already heard about this
But I found some interesting details about it and want to give you my own take on it
The photo is a naked man holding a nice block and of what appears to be poop and
Notably a micro corg keyboard in the upper left hand corner now
I can't put the photo on YouTube because they'll just take the video down because the dude's naked
But I'll have it in the show notes, but let me read you this creepypasta here real quick
This isn't a creepypasta channel
But I think it's interesting to dissect to this because there's some weird stuff going on
Clifford Hoyt age 31 suffered serious injuries in an automobile accident in 1999
After he regained consciousness, he told a terrified nurse that he had died and
Visited hell he expounded on the tortures and anguish he experienced in frightening detail
He refused psychological treatment and was released several weeks later
Hoyt's neighbors complained to their landlord that strange music was playing in his apartment at all hours of the night
Upon investigating the building's owner found Clifford in this condition. So the photograph he's naked
He's holding a nice block. There's much a poop and there's a micro corg in the background
He left and contacted mr. Hoyt's family who contacted authorities Clifford claimed that demons from hell
We're still trying to capture him. He explained that his body would burn incessantly unless he played music to scare the demons away
He would only leave the house for short periods of time to get minimal supplies
Including large blocks of ice to soothe the burning he felt as he tried to sleep
Doctors attribute Clifford's actions to brain damage suffered in the accident
He currently resides in a mental rehabilitation facility in Maryland. So I came across this it's it's kind of older creepypasta
But I just came across this pretty recently. I was like, oh, that's creepy, but it's most likely fake
So I immediately
Started tracking where this came from now. Here's the interesting stuff about this again
I don't just want to read creepypasta. I thought that I read that and I was like
I've heard people saying that when they die they've had life after death experiences of going to hell
They're far more rare, but you do see them
But here's the thing the micro so this has apparently happened in 1999 the micro corg was not invented until
2002 so whether or not the story is true the photo isn't
The photo did was not taken in 1999
Secondly, there was really a Clifford Hoyt. His name is actually Gary Clifford Hoyt and he had a car accident in 1999
But he died in that car accident
He was the single fatality of that car accident the other two people in the other car survived
So there really was a guy named Clifford Hoyt full name Gary Clifford Hoyt
And he did have a serious car accident, but he died
This is what this was my take on this that it's most likely just creepypasta that they either they picked that name out at random
And it happened to match or more likely somebody knew of that car accident and created this story
But here's my little take on this. What if this is almost like a carnival of souls type of thing?
Now carnival of souls is that is that movie where spoiler alert
It's like 40 50 years old
But this woman's ride gets in a car accident and then she gets out of the car and she goes to this town
And it's super creepy and there's a bunch of ghosts chasing her around and at the ending it turns out that she really died in the car
Accident all along and but people interacted with her while she was not knowing she was dead
So was it all in her head with the people she was interacting where they real?
Maybe this is a
Example of that. I know that sounds super far-fetched, but it's just the story is weird to me
I don't know. I don't know like I read it my when I was doing my research
I thought I I feel like there's a little bit more to this
Than just the standard creepypasta did he both die in that car accident?
continue to live to have these horrible hallucinations and
End up in a mental institution, but really he died in the car accident
I don't know if I'm making sense
But yeah, like and would we know like could this possibly be a Mandela effect type situation where reality has splintered
And we have a foot in both realities
The one where he died and the one where he's locked up
Probably probably not
Probably not but I thought I think it's an interesting story and again
There's just something still not sitting right with me
But going for I read that and the next day I read this other article about life after death very very fascinating thing going on
So now we're going from wherever this dude died because I didn't write that down in my notes
We're going to New York State the Big Apple the state that never sleeps. We're going to a place called hospice
Buffalo
Which that's the name of it hospice buffalo now
It's not a hospice in the shape of a buffalo which would be where I would want to die
I think it's just a hospice in the city of Buffalo and they just named stuff really badly over there
There's a guy named dr. Kerr and
He sounds like a bad guy
He sounds like he is like an old-timey villain for an old-timey Batman, but dr. Kerr is actually a guy running this hospice and
One time he was sitting there and he's thinking you know what I think I could have let this patient live longer if I
Changed the IV like if I gave them a different IV thing and he's thinking about it
So he went to get the patient and the nurse was with the patient and he goes hey
I think I'm gonna set up this new IV thing and the nurse goes let me get her actual quote here
Because this was a real event dr. Kerr says I walked in and the nurse didn't even look up and she said no no
He's dying and I said why are you saying that and she said well he's seeing his deceased mother and
Dr. Kerr said he just kind of laughed kind of chuckled like you know and the man died shortly after that and
He started to notice a pattern his staff because he was running everything
So he'd see the patients, but he wasn't in that day-to-day scene every patient all the time
His staff knew when people were going to die not in a creepy final destination sort of way
But they had gotten used to
When people start talking about seeing their mom or seeing their sister or seeing people who had passed before them
The nurses all knew he's they're gonna be dead in a short while a couple weeks a couple days maybe
And so dr. Kerr said you know what let's start recording these
Incidents let's see if there's any sort of patterns
So for ten years at hospice Buffalo, they've started recording these incidents
14,000 cases
80% of the people who pass away
Have a dream or a vision where a loved one comes back to them
And they've actually been able to identify certain themes and he said one of the most common themes is travel
They'll have dreams where they're packing their bags
So weird and he goes their breath their body is old and broken, but their brains are still very very active
So they'll start seeing their mom or their brother or their best friend who passed away before them
They'll dream about them. They'll see them in the room sometimes with a vision and then they'll start having dreams where they're packing stuff up
Getting ready for a journey a long journey now these aren't just the people who are having these dreams also say they're incredibly detailed
They're the most incredibly detailed dreams. They've ever had they wake up sobbing because they're seeing someone that they miss and
The person is bringing a sense of peace to them and it's funny because the reporter asked dr. Kerr
So what do you think the scientific explanation for this or do you think it's a religious explanation for this and he his response was
It doesn't really matter like I don't know and it doesn't matter
He says they should just be respected period as far as like these experiences. They're going through
Just respect that these people are actually having them the saddest thing in it because it's very heart. It's very
Heartlifting is that a word? It's very affirming to know that
That you see those people who left before you
Helping you on that journey. I thought this was the saddest part of the story
little kids
Who they're young so they haven't had they haven't had a lot of loss in their life
You know your six your seven and your parents are still around your best friends are still around your grandparents are still around
They dream about their pets
They dream about any pets that they've lost
little puppies
That is so
sad
But again, it's sad to me
But again, it's affirming to that little boy or that little girl who's kind of scared
Because they're passing away, but then they see their little puppy Rover
And they're just dream that they're petting their puppy that they lost two years ago
And they're just they had that makes them at peace
That makes them at peace as their body is failing when they sleep
They're playing with their puppy that they're soon going to be reunited with
The the big question is this and so that those studies are going on and they're not being done in any sort of scientific way
They're just logging these dreams and visions. The big question is this this is what happens to people who are
Dying in a hospice situation
what happen is there something similar to this if your head gets chopped off or
You fall off a bridge or you get riddled with bullets and a drug deal gone wrong like is there a correlation between these two things I
Would think yes, and this is again
Going back to a whole carnival of souls type thing like let's say I'm sitting in my apartment and a bunch of gangbangers raid it and
Just blow my brains out
That event is going to take a total of three minutes
From the point where they knocked down the door to the point that I snapped two of their necks and stab another one in the chest
Do a witty one-liner throw him out the window and then the shotguns to the back of my head and I'm like damn it
As that bullet enters my brain, I almost think that the brain runs into a bullet time mode
And I'm able to have those same affirming experiences
I think at the moment that you die
whether it takes three weeks for you to die or
Three seconds for you to die. I think your brain still
Processes that and they're my backup for that is when you dream dreams seem like they're hours or months or yeah
I've had dreams that have lasted decades
But it really was only three seconds in my brain that was shooting that spark but to me it felt like 70 years in my dream
So I do think that's possible
I think that in the moment of death like the horrible torture you go through will probably be I should say will but let's say that you're
You're you fall into a wheat thresher feet first
That's awful, but I think at the last moment you do find that piece as fleeting as it may seem
Physically mentally it is on par of a little girl holding her puppy
I think at the moment of death you are at peace in your brain. It gives you it gives you a good dream
I don't think anyone ever really dies horribly
But now let's go to the world of cryptids
Yes, yes cryptids because we've talked a lot about cryptids this week
And we talked about zermatism earlier and he was saying
Stanislaw was not Stanislaw Stanislaw was saying that all over the world
There are stories of bigfoot-esque creatures and he named off a couple of them the woodwows in
Britain and a bunch of other ones now one of the ones he named off was the almas of Mongolia the bigfoot-esque creature
I started looking around at a couple of them and there is a story
from the
1870s of an Alma that was actually captured
So let's go back in time to the 1870s. Let's get in the carpenter copter
Actually, no, that'll probably bring too much attention
Let's go ahead and hop in the Jason Jalopy. That'll be a little more
Bit of subterfuge because we don't want to get captured by these people either
We go into the Jason Jalopy we go back in time we're in the 1870s
We're in Russia Far East Russia Mongolian area
So I should have told you to grab your jacket because it's gonna get really cold out here
But it's too late, so you're probably gonna get frostbite. These are the remote forests of
Abcazi
Abcazia Abcazia no it's not a realm from Lord of the Rings. It's actually a real place
Abcazia there's a village there just a normal little Russian village back in time doing villager stuff thatched tuts
fire with a little pot over it a
Metal pot and then you know, they're making stew and little kids are running around with little sticks
hitting each other whatever and so
These two hunters. I don't know how many hunters, but anyways these hunters come out of the woods and they're like
We caught one we caught one and everyone's like what's going on?
hunters start leading a huge
hairy woman
into the camp at
Musket point or arrow point whatever they had
ranged weapon pointed at her
That's that's actually gonna be really bad taste when I reveal this but
She comes walking in they have her captured
She's taller than anyone else there. She's very very strong
They say but they don't say how they know that I don't know if she was like snapping next in the woods
Or knocking over trees, but anyways
these Russian hunters captured an
Alma a large
Bigfoot-esque beast of the Mongolian region now
This is how they're normally listed there can be between five which isn't super tall
But between five to six and a half feet they actually have a lot of Neanderthal like features
pronounced brow
flat nose
Weak chin this one was covered in hair sometimes they're hairy sometimes they're super hairy sometimes they're just normal hairy
Sometimes they're just like Italian hairy, but anyways this one comes in
And then you know they got it at ranged weapon point and they're like what do we do with this thing?
I mean this thing is monstrous. It's one of the almas
We can't really let it go because then it might like just start bashing us in
But we can't really keep a prisoner here because it's so strong, but the village elders go
That we can't let it go at least in this town. We know where it's at at all times
Now there was something about it that they thought
Maybe we can communicate with it
so they tried speaking to it in whatever language I don't think they were speaking Russian that far out in
The in the area, but probably they were speaking something
And they tried speaking something to this creature and it wouldn't say anything it wouldn't say anything it was mute
It would just make noises
So they're like okay well we can't tell it not to kill us if it sees us out in the woods
So our safest bet is to keep it isolated in this village. We'll just keep it prisoner
Now what's bizarre is this is the story we have we have them capturing the Alma they name it Zana and
then we have
40 years later she was prisoner for 40 years and in that time period
One of the tribe members well, I believe one of the elders, but one of the tribe members
fell in love with Zana this massive hairy beast that they they could they considered it a beast they considered it a beast and
he fell in love with it and he wooed it and
Had sex with it. So he's banging this mythical creature
that they have always been leery of in this area and
They have four kids
Four kids two of the sons lived long enough to have children of their own and I believe two of them died fairly early
And after 40 years of captivity now
Married to this dude now raising kids still never said a word the children could talk
Children could totally talk fine
But Zana never said anything but after 40 years eventually love conquers all but death and
Zana passes away
this story has been very popular in
Russian
Mongolian circles
To the point that scientists said, you know what we really need to figure out what Zana was
Let's get DNA from her descendants
Like and then it'll show was she a humanoid?
Was she something else?
So a couple years ago
They did it
They got DNA from her grandson, and I think they actually might have had her tooth. I'm a little iffy on that
They got DNA from some of her grandchildren, and they look at it and they're like hmm, okay
Let me let me run these numbers again because this was not a good story if this is true
And they're looking at the numbers and they're like kind of holding the report upside down and they're like
This is not what we thought now every so often we'll find bigfoot hair and they run it to a laboratory and
It's a dog or they'll find a big footprint and they'll start analyzing it
And it turns out to that like this is obviously a fake
This is the worst example ever ever of you running a test on a bigfoot type creature and it coming back as something else
Because basically the story people have been telling for close to a hundred years about how this Russian town had captured a
Alma
Turns out that when they do that when they did the test on
the grandson and
They ran all the numbers
That the creature who was described as a large hairy creature who couldn't talk and roamed around and was prisoner for 40 years
Was a black woman
That's that's what they caught they caught a black woman in the woods and
they kept your prisoner for 40 years and
They had a bunch of babies and she never said a word they want to let her do nothing except you know run around and
Yeah, that's I mean there's
People generally people who are racist are like yeah, I'm racist. I'm totally cool with it
Be an accidentally racist is the worst like at least the person who's who's just like oh, no, I'm totally racist
I don't like this racist. Okay, but when you're accidentally racist
It's kind of worse because you don't think you're being racist trapping a
Black person for 40 years because you think they're a monster is the worst example of being accidentally racist
I've ever seen so
Apparently what happened was they run around the test and they said she would have been 100% sub-saharan African and
There were a bunch of they had just freed a bunch of slave like slavery ended in Russia. I believe two years prior to this
So there was a bunch of free slaves running around in the in Russia in general
But in that particular area they figure that she must have just gotten lost from like who she was with or was just wandering around
She ran into these hunters who were probably smaller who probably were physically smaller than her
I don't know where the hair thing comes from
Why they kept describing her as super hairy, but they saw this tall black woman and they're like oh
You must be a monster and they captured her they captured her and they held her prisoner for 40 years
And then for decades and a hundred years people are telling the story about this town that caught this bigfoot now
That story in and of itself accidental racism aside the story of the almas
Is even more fascinating than that. There's a reason why
They said this must be an Alma. I'm gonna keep going back to Bigfoot literature here in Bigfoot literature
It is it's the Native American saw it as this spirit creature
And when the Westerners came here, they've seen it as this one off maybe in a group of three or four
Type of creatures that are spotted, but there's no proof ever found
There's there's maybe one video clips and blurry photos stuff like that the almas are amazingly
Documented not in modern times, which is what makes it interesting
Like I said, it was the description of a Neanderthal pronounced brow flat nose weak chin
How would somebody in the Middle Ages
Know what a Neanderthal looked like we know what they look like now because we have
Creations and drawings of them, but they shouldn't have had those back then they didn't have forensic anthropology
They shouldn't have been able to say this creature looks just like this type of human that it used to exist
Unless they were seeing them then there's this book. There's this book. It is a Tibetan
medicinal book
There is a drawing of an Alma and a description of the Alma
everything else in that book is a
Plant or an animal that lives today and can be verified
That book has no mythological creatures in it at all no dragons no
Groot slangs nothing deer and tigers and berries and bananas and whatever
Everything in that book is scientifically verifiable. You can see it today
Except for the Alma so that makes people think why would you write this huge?
It basically be if you picked up Grey's Anatomy and you flip through it and on page 84 was an elf
And then you went to the next page and it was a thorax
That's how this book was set up. It was 100 percent everything we can do while 99 percent we can verify exists
except for this creature and it wasn't the almas warrant a
solitary small group type of thing in
1420 there was a guy named Hans
Schlittberger he was taken prisoners by the Mongols. He's tape brought back being brought back to the con
Here was his quote. He survived long enough to write a book and talk about his journeys
But as her imagine you're in a caravan
coming through a the steps of
Mongolia so your care your your carriage is all bumpy because they can't drive it right it's like one wheels on one step one wheels on the other
You're coming through this and you're this westerner and you look out the window
And this is what you see on the same mountain. There are savages who are not like other people and they live there
They are covered all over the body with hair except the hands and face and run about like other wild beasts in the mountain and
Also eat leaves and grass and anything they can find the Lord of the country sent to Eddy
Gee a man and a woman from among these savages that had been taken in the mountain
So we have another instance of these creatures being captured, but you're he's looking at them
He's seen a
basically a herd a tribe of village whatever words you want to use for these beasts these
Neanderthal like beasts being cited in the year
1420 when Hans was a captive
So did these creatures exist?
I think if anything these probably I mean we don't have photos of them now
But there's it's in a super remote area. It's one thing to be walking through Oregon and see a big foot
It's another thing to have to endure the harshness of the Mongolian
Landscape just to get a photograph and they probably just beat you to death. Actually, it's funny. They keep getting captured
So they're probably really sucky at combat and they eat leaves and grass
So I don't know like how strong they really could be
But they also eat like other animals as well
My main diet wouldn't be leaves and grass if I was a cryptid
It's kind of a you want to you want to have sharp teeth to eat people but anyway, so these creep
I mean these creatures are probably the best bet we have for
Proving that there's some sort of bigfoot-esque creature and one last story to wrap up the Alma mystery
I think probably they did exist at some point. I think the descriptions too accurate to things
We do know existed I eat enough in the andre thals
I do think they existed at some point in very very modern history and at this point
They could have been completely wiped out or gone underground or something like that
But one last interesting tidbit to this in 1941 when Germany invaded Russia the Red Army captured a spy a
Big Harry spy who wouldn't talk won't say anything and the Russians blew his brains out because what else are you gonna do?
You're getting invaded you're you read you see someone that you don't
He's not a local. He's not Russian. He's a big Harry dude
He's not talking to you so they shoot him and there's always been the idea that that also could have been an Alma
Because he was a wild man couldn't speak covered in hair
I know the Germans were pretty savvy on their you know spying, but I don't think they're like hey
Groober over there make sure you don't shave for a while and run around in the woods and maybe you can pick up some intel
They probably caught an Alma
Here's the weird thing really the world is so vast
That you can have entire
Tracks of land that are not explored or
Haven't been visited by humans in a long long time
There are forests and jungles and planes and caves that we know of or might not
But we don't go to them to those to it to those cryptids to the almas
Who are in hiding still having their civilization?
Somewhere we are the cryptids
Every so often they may catch a glimpse of a human or
Look up and see a plane and that's their cryptid. That's their legend. Those are their creatures that keep them up at night us
This kind of plays into the whole missing 411 thing like
When we go when when humans go into the woods, we are now on their turf when we go into these vast planes
We're now on their turf when we move out of civilization. We are on the turf of the cryptids and
It makes you wonder how many humans have been kidnapped and
held prisoner for 40 years in
these dark hidden remote villages
We'd never hear their stories
They would just vanish and in that village
They would tell their children the time that they caught the small person with weak limbs
To prove the stories true that we really existed
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com slash dead rabbit radio
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great weekend guys
*Music*