Did you know that you could get arrested simply by putting the wrong words into a Google search engine?
Maybe that's not exactly true. Maybe I am kind of stretching it a bit, but it's a crazy story.
And then we traveled to Germany to meet a young family who has moved into an apartment building where they are the only tenants.
As the children run from floor to floor hiding in abandoned apartments, they have no idea that a new player has entered the game.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys are having tons of fun.
Doing whatever you're doing. It's still a couple weeks away, but I should announce that now we will be doing a live stream special on Christmas Day.
The day when everyone's busy doing something else. I don't know why I plan it this way.
But you don't have anything to do for the holidays, or maybe if you do.
Come and join us. I will give you more details as the date comes clear.
But someone who never needs more details given about them.
Someone who can be read like a perfect book from a mile away.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our Thanksgiving live stream contributors.
Everyone give it up for A. Sampson. 1, 2, 3.
A. Sampson. Woohoo. Yeah. Come on in.
To Dead Rabbit Command.
Shave his head. Shave his head so he loses all his strength.
A. Sampson. Let's go ahead and toss you the oars to the rabbit robo.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Ro ro ro us all the way out to Denver, Colorado.
Oh splash. Oh splash. He's beating the drum.
We're rowing to the beat. We're slaves to the rhythm.
Actually we're probably just slaves. He's making us row this boat across America.
It's August 5th, 2020.
[Snapping]
Martha. Martha. Call 911. The neighbor's house is on fire.
Actually that's too many numbers for a 911.
911, what's your emergency? The house is on fire.
Can't you see the flames? Can't you see the flames from the fire department?
Oh yeah. Woo woo woo. Fire engine pulls up.
If you guys are home and you're chasing, you're doing a lot of sound effects.
Start of this story. This story is pretty grim.
I figured I can't make it as lighthearted as possible.
There's a Dalmatian running around the house.
Firemen keep dropping pails of water. Charlie Chaplin shows up.
That's pretty much the end of the jokes. Unfortunately, in Denver, Colorado,
on August 5th, 2020, there was an arson in this suburban neighborhood.
There's eight people living in this house. Five people died in this fire.
Someone set the fire deliberately. Five people died.
All members of the same family is absolutely horrific.
Five people died in this fire and the police, they have no idea who did this.
They cannot figure out who would be so inhuman to set a house on fire, kill five people.
Apparently there is some surveillance video footage in the area.
It's probably like a Ring Doorbell type camera. Maybe a traffic light cam somewhere.
They were able to get video footage of three men wearing hoodies and full face masks.
It's like a hockey mask or a purge type mask.
So they have no idea who these people were. They go, "Those three guys are probably the ones who committed this arson."
But why would they do it? What is the motive?
Well, it turns out they did end up arresting three people for this crime.
They were all teenagers. There's like two 16-year-olds and I think the other one was like 14 or 15.
These kids set this house on fire, burned it down and killed five people.
And it was really interesting. At the time, the Denver police chief, Paul Payzen,
gave a comment about this to the media. He was talking about their investigation and he said, "This was as complex of an investigation as I am aware of in my entire career."
They did an amazing job. I cannot give away the details.
This is very sensitive information because successful prosecution is critical in this case.
Now cops always say stuff like that, right? They're always saying, "You know, we can't reveal too much information, blah, blah, blah."
But this statement in this case was 100% true because how they caught these guys is raising a lot of eyebrows across America.
I want to give a shout out to NBC News. This is the only place I really found any information on this.
In the NBC News, there is a journalist named John Schupp.
He wrote an article about what they did to catch these guys. And it's weird because on the one hand, yeah, they caught three teenagers who murdered five people, right?
An arson attack that killed this family. The way they did it was the police went to Google and said, "We want to know everyone who typed this address in to your search engine."
We want a list of everyone who searched for this address. And I think they gave them a time parameter. I think it was within 15 days before the attack.
And they got a judge to sign off on it. The judge sent it to Google and Google says, "Here you go."
Here's a list of everyone who searched for that address before the attack.
Now, it's super interesting because you're just fishing. You're just fishing for information.
Normally, you have a suspect, you have a name, or you have some sort of description, the type of car they have, and you can then go to the DMV and go,
"Give us the addresses of everyone who owns a white Subaru in the area."
You have some DNA, so they go, "Let's start running this DNA. Let's start running these fingerprints through these databases that we have."
That local PD or the federal government has. This is one where they went to Google and says, "Tell us everyone who typed this address into your search engine."
And Google did. Google saw the court order and said, "Yeah, sure. Here's a list of everyone who did it."
Shockingly enough, this is just weird to begin with because we know three people were behind it.
There were 61 people who searched for that address before the fire. Within 15 days before the fire, 61 different people typed in that address.
What were they looking at it for? Well, the police investigated as much as they could and they were able to narrow it down.
They kept going, "Okay, so we think it was this group of people." They narrowed it down to about 12 or 6, and then they kept asking Google for more information.
What's the IP addresses? Where are these people at? Where do they live? Where did they search this from?
And eventually, they found one of the three teenagers. They got his address from the fact that he typed in the address of the house two weeks prior to the house burning down.
So they went and they talked to him and they arrested him. They got all of his social media accounts and then they are able to get the other two guys as well.
Now, the lawyer of the 17-year-old who got arrested for this, he was arguing in court. He goes, "This is violation of the Fourth Amendment.
You just can't walk around the neighborhood and walk into people's houses and hopefully find information on that employee that's against the law.
That's unreasonable search and seizure. You're searching their Google searches.
What's the difference between getting that and getting every phone call made 15 days before an event?
The judge in the murder case, it's still going on. The trial is still going on for these three teenagers.
The judge goes, "I'll allow it. I will allow this Google information. It's allowable in trial."
This is super weird and apparently this isn't the first time. They've used this about four or five other times recently.
And that might have been the first four or five times. John Shoup was kind of listing off the other times and I was reading some of those articles as well.
They used it for a sex trafficking case. They used it in a fraud case where they go, "The fraud case is what happened once this person was being defrauded."
And the police are like, "We don't know how to track them down. Let's find out everyone who searched this victim's name within this time period before the crime."
They were able to get the IP address of the person who put in that name.
Now listen, I'm not pro arson. And what's terrifying about this too is so now that they've been arrested, the police figured out what the motive was.
They burned down the wrong house. Apparently one of their cell phones went missing and they thought it was these people who stole their cell phone.
So they went to set fire to that person's house, but instead they burned this house down and killed five people.
So they weren't even the intended target. It's not like that makes it any better, right? It's still a horrible tragedy.
You're like, "Oh, but they killed the people who stole the phone." That's okay then.
It was petty revenge and it was the wrong house to begin with. It's a super interesting story and I mean...
We all know there's zero privacy online. At least I hope you know that, right? There's zero privacy online.
I don't care how many VPNs you got. I know a lot of people use VPNs and you're like, "Oh, I can watch shows in countries where those shows aren't allowed in my country."
That's all they're good for. If you really think that your VPN is protecting your identity, it's not.
There are a hundred different ways they're going to find you and I don't believe any piece of technology like a VPN would even be allowed on the marketplace if there isn't a backdoor.
Just like whenever I read these articles about the police arresting people and they're like, "They didn't give us the password for the phone so we went to Apple and said, 'Unlock this phone,' and Apple said, 'No, we're not going to do it.'
That's all smoke and marriage. Those police have a hundred different ways into your devices. I don't believe for a second that they can actually add...
They have to ask Apple for access. I think that's all a charade. I really, really do.
So you know there's no privacy online. You know there's no privacy online. That's why no one wants to sponsor this show.
I'm not going to get a Nord VPN sponsorship. There's no privacy online. At the same time, I know when I put it into Google, somebody has access to it, but the fact that the police are just basically doing this huge trawling.
And remember there were 61 other people typing this address in. Who knows what reason? Innocently. They had nothing to do with any of that.
But they were also getting trawled through and then so all of the stuff they did online had to be looked at. So the police could rule them out as a suspect.
I don't want the government looking at my stuff. I mean, I know what they do, right? It's just, it's this weird thing. I know that they do. I know that they have access to all of that stuff.
But at the same time, like, so there's a thing called geofencing where the police have said, we see this all the time in true crime, in true crime articles.
What happens is generally someone gets caught for murder and they go, I wasn't in that area and the police can go. Well, that's funny because we have your cell phone pinging in this area and we can show that her cell phone was pinging in that area too.
But only your cell phone left that area. Like, we can track all that. That's when they actually have the suspect already. They can prove that he's lying.
They also do this thing called geofencing. I mean, there's a shooting in Baltimore and the police will say, we want the electronic device signature. We want the cell phone pings of everyone who was in that area before, during and after that shooting.
We want to know everyone who was there because we all have these tracking devices on us. That's been ruled illegal in Virginia. That's the only place where you can't do that. Every other state right now, you can do that. The cops can say, we want to know everyone who was in this area.
I mean, again, I'm not pro arson. I'm glad that these guys got arrested. It's just the way that they do it. It's so interesting and it opens up a whole bunch of legal issues. It really, really does.
Because at what point, I mean, at what point should we just be mailing, just printing out mailing in our searches to the cops? Just, I mean, just to skip a step, right?
Because as long as a judge signs off on it, Google's going to comply. Now, Google will not say how many of these they get on a regular basis. Like, we know about four or five cases.
This could happen all the time. We are not privy to, like, Google's like, we're not even going to tell you how many times we get these calls in a week.
But I mean, from a law enforcement thing, it makes sense, right? They want to do it. They want to find out who's there.
And I thought about this. I thought about this. There is a YouTube video. I'll put a link in the show notes. I've really thought about just having the last 10 minutes of the podcast be this video.
It is, I mean, listen, the worst thing, think of the worst thing you could possibly put into a search engine, right?
So Nicholas Cruz, that guy who shot up Stoneman Douglas High School down in Florida.
There is a YouTube video. It's about 10 minutes long, and it's a prosecutor reading off all of Nicholas Cruz's search requests. Everything he typed into Google.
And it is so explicit. I would not sleep at night. I'll put it in the show notes. I'll put the link in the show notes. I'll let someone else sleep at night.
I could not, I thought, dude, I should just take this audio and put it at the end of an episode, because it's so insane.
The stuff that this guy, it's not safe for work. I'll tell you that. Don't start blasting on the loudspeakers.
It's some of the grossest stuff you could ever imagine. It is, I haven't been able to make it. I have not been able to make it the full 10 minutes.
And this isn't a challenge either. I'm not going to be like, hey, you told me how long you lasted. They had all of us. I don't know what the timeline was. I don't really care.
I don't care if it was across 10 years or one week. It is some of the most disgusting things you could ever think of.
My thing was, why didn't he arrest him when he typed in the first five things?
The stuff he was putting in was so illegal. These are things he was looking for. It wasn't that he was just making a shopping list.
Well, he wasn't making a shopping list. He wanted this stuff. He was typing this into Google.
But it's not like he was just writing it down in his dream journal, which, trust me, he would have been worrisome enough there.
If it's his internal thoughts, you can't arrest someone for pre-crime. It's so bizarre that you can't investigate someone for looking into what he looked into.
And I'm glad the arsonist got arrested. I'm glad the sex traffickers got arrested and the person who got defrauded found justice.
I'm glad for all that stuff, but it's just so interesting that they're literally, I mean, it is no different than walking into everyone's house in that area and saying, do you have any gasoline here?
That's really what they did, which would have been illegal. But since they used Google, they was legal. It's super interesting.
And it will be happening way more. It will be happening way, way more. A. Sampson123.
Quit going on to show notes. He's like, I don't think it's that. I doubt that YouTube video is going to be that bad, Jason.
No, don't, don't, don't. Hey, let me give you the keys to the carpenter copter. Take us away from Denver, Colorado. We are headed all the way out to Germany.
(imitates carpenters)
This is a really cool story. I got sent by one of you guys, a longtime Patreon supporter of the show BS is his name.
Very, very fascinating and terrifying story coming out of a small town in Germany.
And it's not his story. He said he was actually him and his coworker were driving around late one night. His coworker told him this story.
We're in northern Germany at an unnamed small harbour town, which I understand. He was one of Doc's coworker.
This story took place in the past though. I don't think this is... I know this guy still doesn't live in this apartment complex.
Apparently in this German town, there's an apartment complex that had caught on fire. The firefighters came in, they stopped the fire, they saved the building, but nobody wanted to live there.
Nobody wanted to live in an apartment building. They just got entorged and had a bunch of water damage everywhere.
But when BS's friend, we're going to go ahead and call him Billy, he's 16 years old. His family moved into this apartment complex.
And it was Bill, his mom, his dad, and his little brother, we're going to call him Joey, who's only six.
Bill's 16, Joey's 6 years old. They move into this apartment complex and they said, you know, it was actually kind of cool.
It was actually kind of cool. You had the whole complex to yourself and none of the apartment doors were locked.
So you really had the whole complex to yourself. Now, I don't know if they got their stuff out of there. I don't know if they were running around like, oh, this house has a Nintendo 64.
Take it at home. I don't know. I don't think they were thieves, but you definitely had all of these rooms.
And behind each door, a mystery, right? Around the corner of each hallway, an undiscovered path.
And these kids, they made good use of this apartment complex. When their cousins would come over, they'd play hide and go seek.
Can you imagine playing hide and go seek in an entire apartment complex? I don't know how big this was.
I don't know if it was like three stories or if it was one of those like multi-wrapper round units with 100 units, but still.
You would have to set some series parameters with that hide and go seek game.
You'd have to be like, okay, okay, Joey, today, please, only the fifth and sixth floor.
I don't want to have to run up and down all these floors looking for you. There's under departments here.
You would have to set some parameters. But if you're playing hide and go seek in an apartment complex, it's going to be a pretty involved game.
But Billy said one thing when you were playing hide and go seek, if you didn't get found right away, right, you're the hider, not the seeker.
You didn't get found for a while. You could start to feel the loneliness.
You're hiding in an apartment that no one's been in for months. You're just curled up in the corner all alone.
The longer you went without being found, the more a sense of true isolation would set in.
Now, despite the fact that they had an entire apartment complex to play hide and go seek, everything wasn't great at this apartment complex
because that doesn't help the adults at all. I guess if they don't want to hang out with their kids, they're like, hey, shouldn't you go play hide and go seek?
He's like, I'm home by myself. Oh yeah, go find yourself. Consider it a spiritual journey.
The parents, I mean, they liked the apartment as well, but the problem was, was in their apartment, the ceiling was black.
Not like painted black. It was like blackened, which they figured had obviously had something to do with the fire,
but probably more to do with water damage in the apartment above them and their apartment themselves.
So they go, you know, that's kind of gross. That's kind of gross. Having a black ceiling. Let's paint it.
Let's get rid of it. Let's paint over it. So one day they did, they painted the ceiling to match the walls,
but over time, the ceiling would turn black again as if they had never painted it.
And not only that, they could actually see that the ceiling would once again become damp.
Billy's mom starts to find trash in the apartment.
She's like, what's that piece of garbage doing over there? Old banana peel, saran wrap,
just sitting behind the couch, like, what in the world? Now she does have two sons, right?
And you could probably chalk it up to kids just being messy. So she throws the banana peel away, throws away the saran wrap.
But she starts to notice more and more just miscellaneous pieces of trash popping up around the apartment.
But she also, when she sees these, and she does apparently question the boys, they go, we have nothing to do with it.
What are you talking about? Billy said my mom would not only find trash strewn about the apartment,
it would be trash that she personally put in the garbage can. It was stuff that she knew should have been in the garbage can.
Later she would find that same piece of trash somewhere else in the apartment.
Now again, two boys could be them. Most likely them right kids love trash.
The family would be hanging out in the living room debating what color of paint they're going to do the ceiling next time.
They'd be sitting in the living room hanging out and they would hear coming from the apartment above them.
[MUMBLING]
That's the sound of somebody walking above them.
If you didn't know what that was, you're like, what? Someone's using a thightmaster up there?
They would hear what sounded like someone in the apartment above them.
Now anyone who's ever lived in an apartment, we're familiar with those sounds. They pretty much grew up in apartments.
You're used to that. The problem was, is they were the only people in the entire complex,
but every so often they'd hear someone walking around upstairs.
Then the family begins to suffer issues with their electronics.
One night Billy wakes up in the middle of the night to find his television on in his bedroom.
[MUMBLING]
I don't know if it was on Spooky, Spooky Snow Channel. It could have been showing rug rats for all I know.
The point is, it's a television. It doesn't matter what it is, right? It doesn't matter what it is.
You're dead asleep, your television turns on, and it shouldn't be on.
It's terrifying. It doesn't matter if it's a rerun of Doug. It's still awful.
His television turned on in the middle of the night. We'll come up one night.
The other members of the household also started to experience things like that.
Electronics would turn on when they shouldn't be on.
When no one turned them on, they would go, "Ding!" Turn on.
Billy said, "Around this point, it stopped being fun. It stopped being fun to live there."
Because the whole family is experiencing weird stuff right now.
What's interesting, because I read this a couple of times and looking over my notes,
it's interesting that Billy never mentions what his dad experienced.
We know the mom was finding the trash everywhere, and the two brothers,
well, I don't want to give it away, Joey has an experience coming up.
I'm curious. There could be one or two things going on.
Even though I said there's a dad in the house, there may not be a dad.
I think there is, because at one point he mentions his parents.
What I'm getting at is I'm wondering if the dad was also experiencing stuff,
and he wasn't telling anybody. He wasn't telling anybody.
Because he was just like, "My family's going to freak out if I told them this."
Because this story took place years and years ago.
Actually, I can play it at least 12 years ago. I know that for a fact.
But yeah, I'm wondering if the dad, because we have experience from the mom,
experience from both brothers, but the dad, there's no interesting, right?
The dad could just be like, "I'm not telling my family about that."
But whether or not the dad was experiencing anything, or whether or not the dad existed in the first place,
he was the ghost all along.
The fact is that it stopped being fun to live here.
Now, there was no more running up and down the hallways, no more hiding in the apartments.
Billy said, "We pretty much just locked the front door and watched movies."
That was our fun. Because the creep factor just kept getting worse and worse and worse.
Well, one night Billy and Joey were home alone.
And then all of a sudden, boom!
Power goes out.
Billy and Joey are home alone in an abandoned, burned-out apartment complex with no electricity.
And it's terrifying, right? You'd obviously, you've already heard all of these weird noises.
The unpaintable ceiling, the unpaintable ceiling of doom.
Like, Tronics have been turning themselves on and off.
You've had some weird things going on here. Now the power goes out, and it's terrifying.
But Billy's sitting there in the dark, and he goes, "Wait a second. Wait a second.
I can't chalk this up to being paranormal. It is quite likely that all that has happened is a fuse has burned out."
I mean, after all this place was engulfed in flames, the fuse box may have suffered some damage.
So I just need to walk down the hallway of this abandoned, burned-out apartment complex and change the fuse.
Now in America we have our circuit breaker boxes, right? They just go, "Click." You walk and you flip them.
Apparently, in the rest of the world, it's like dying light, where you have to find fuses and carry them from point A to point B and plug them in.
I had to look this up because I was like, "What in the world is a fuse box?"
So Billy, apparently he has a fuse in the drawer or something like that.
He takes a fuse and he leaves his little brother in the apartment, because it really is Joe.
What's Joey's choices are? Walk through the darkness of this apartment, and who knows what is out there, or be comfortable on your couch.
I mean, you're shrouded in darkness either way. Maybe they have flashlight, but...
Joey stays behind and Billy takes the fuse and he walks through the fuse box.
Easy peasy, right? He's going to get this electricity back on.
He says right when he's getting ready to put the fuse back in, he hears the most blood-curdling scream he's ever heard in his life.
And he recognizes it as his little brother's voice.
He runs back through the hallway, bone-chilling scream coming from the apartment.
He runs in the door and his little brother is curled up on the couch.
And he is sobbing so heavily and screaming so loud.
His six-year-old brother is just hysterical.
Billy's like, "What's wrong? What's wrong?" And he can't even catch a breath.
Joey can't even take a moment to say what happened.
He's just curled up in a ball on the couch screaming and crying and sobbing.
To Billy, it looks like he's almost going into some sort of catatonic state.
Like he's going into shock.
He just can't control his breathing. He's just freaking out.
And Billy just wants to know what's happening because if he doesn't know what's happening, how's he going to help?
Joey, curled up on his couch, reaches an arm out and extends his finger and begins pointing.
Into the darkness.
And Joey finally in between sobs is able to get out one word.
"Girl!"
And Billy turns and looks and sees where Joey is pointing at.
His arm shaking as he tries to keep it steady, but his heaving body won't allow it.
He's pointing out into the darkness of the living room.
Joey was pointing at where he saw the girl.
A girl who appeared out of the darkness.
A girl who stood there in front of his little brother.
A girl who waited until Billy left the room before she appeared.
When the parents get home, Billy tells them, "Hey, I just... I don't know how your guys' evening went, but here's what happened while you were gone."
And at that point, the family made a decision, "It's time to leave. We're out of here. This is just too much."
But the issue is, they had signed the housing contract, a lease, right?
You can't get out of a lease by claiming the place is haunted.
However, they were able to say, "This has nothing to do with the ghosts! It has nothing to do with anything spooky!"
Our ceiling is black. Our ceiling is black. No matter how many times we've tried painting over it, the black stuff returns.
And we don't think it's healthy for our kids to be in a living room full of whatever is causing that blackness on our ceiling.
So they were able to break their lease. They were actually able to get out of that housing contract and move earlier than they were supposed to.
They had signed up for more months.
All in all, from beginning to end, they only lived there for six months. They were the only tenants there, and their stay only lasted six months.
And as they were wrapping up the whole process of moving out and signing all the paperwork,
Billy's parents kind of discreetly began asking questions about the apartment complex before the fire and how it all may have started.
You should have asked in the beginning, right? They're like, "It was a mysterious fire!" Nobody knows!
They should have asked all that stuff upfront, but it was probably a great deal.
They began asking a little bit about the fire and what had happened, and they were told that a little girl had died in the fire.
And to the family, that made a lot of sense. That explained a lot.
I mean, obviously the ghost girl in the living room, but also, you know, other people walking around.
You could hear there's people walking around in their apartment. When you'd play hide-and-go-seek, you would feel just lonely.
Missed, but not "ha-ha! I've gone away with hiding the best."
You felt trapped. You felt solitude. Involuntary solitude.
They're in an average game of hide-and-go-seek.
It's interesting because we see this a lot in paranormal investigations.
I've personally experienced it on both sides.
Joey completely forgot that this ever happened. He had no idea. He had no memory of the night he was curled up in a ball on the couch going,
"Girl, girl, he doesn't remember any of that."
And no one reminded him, no one reminded him until he turned 18.
Sounds like a great gift. What do you give the person who has everything? Trauma.
On his 18th birthday, I actually don't know if it was on the birthday. They're like, "Oh, here's your present. It's like a photo album. It's a photo album of ghost girls."
Billy said after he turned 18, and not specifically on his 18th birthday, a ghost girl blows out the candles and goes, "Boom."
Everyone else disappears.
He goes, "We told him about it. We told him about..." Well, we asked him, "Hey, remember that time we were in that old abandoned apartment complex?"
I think he probably remembered that. He probably remembered that, but he was told about the time he was curled up into the ball,
shouting, "Girl," in between moans. And Joey's like, "I don't remember any of that. I don't remember any of that."
Billy's like, "Yeah, and you peed your pants too, you big baby Joe." I was like, "No, I didn't. He's all making up extra details."
Well, no, I feel like I'm kind of cutting off the legs of the story. He didn't do that, but Joey didn't remember it.
I've done ghost investigations with people. I've been out with Josh, my buddy Josh, and something crazy would happen.
And then years later, I was like, "Hey, dude, remember when we were down at that park and that spooky thing happened? You peed your pants, Josh? Remember when you peed your pants?"
He's like, "No." He wouldn't remember the ghost. He wouldn't remember the ghost thing. I've done that with a couple people.
I had a buddy named Chris, too, who had this really weird experience with a shadow man.
And then years later, he's like, "Dude, what are you talking about?" I go, "Dude, there were 15 witnesses, man. You don't remember that?"
But then it was so weird because I'd be like, "Maybe you just can't handle the truth. Maybe that movie's real."
And you can't handle the truth, and your brain actually has a circuit breaker built into it. I do believe that.
And something so outside the norm happens and you experience it in that moment, but as time goes by, you just forget it.
It's not forgotten. It's blocked out. You block it out because it's so terrifying.
Imagine if a six-year-old had to come to grips with the fact that the dead still walk the earth in spirit form.
And he's being confronted with a child possibly close to his age, her spirit, her soul, trapped in the darkness of a burned-out apartment.
Like for a six-year-old to really kind of comprehend that, it's terrifying to us if we saw it.
But to a six-year-old, he's closer to the age range. He's having to grapple with all sorts of stuff all of a sudden as this girl's walking out of the darkness towards him.
So it's a terrifying story BS. Thank you so much for sharing it with me.
And there's a lot of stuff we can talk about, but the main thing that I want to talk about here as we wrap this episode up, it's super interesting to me.
We have an apartment. There's almost like a scientific experiment because we can have a lot of controls going on here.
We have an apartment complex that burned down and a little girl died in it.
And as far as we know, nobody lived in it until this family. They were the first family back in.
And what we had was an escalation of power. We had an escalation of abilities.
So first it was just a feeling of loneliness when you were alone.
More than you would normally feel when you were alone, right?
An uneasy sense of isolation.
Then physical matter begins to move around.
You know, the trash that is known to be thrown away appears in other places.
The electronic devices are going on and off at, let's be honest, creepy moments, right?
Ghosts aren't idiots. They used to be alive. They know it's creepy and what's not creepy.
Middle of the day your television set turns on. You're like, "What? Did I sit on the remote? Is there short?"
Middle of the night when you're sleeping your television turns on, it's creepier.
And it's like everything is being set up. Oh, and the footprints upstairs, right? The sound of the walking.
Those are all pretty normal ghostly activity. Actually the trash coming in and out of the trash can,
you know, something that was thrown away, appears back in the house.
That's a fairly high power level already, but to then appear, and not just appear in the darkness,
but to wait until Joey was alone.
Like actually cause the power, wait till the two boys are home alone, cause the power outage.
So Billy would leave and then take a form, become an image of a girl standing in the darkness in front of the youngest member of the family.
It was an escalation. It wasn't a moment where she's already there and people go, "Yeah, so we're late at night.
I swear that I can hear the sound of a little girl crying in the apartment next to us."
And then when you're playing "How to Go Seek," you would hear like a giggle and you'd see like a sunflower dress kind of whip by at the end of the hallway as you're catching glimpses of her.
They didn't get that. It was almost like this ghost had to feed off of them and was slowly ramping things up.
And what's interesting is, I think she's gathered enough energy that the next family that came into that apartment complex, which I'd love to know if it was still there.
The next family that moved into that apartment complex would be facing a ghost who while she may pull those same type of stunts,
she may still want to feed off of that fear energy and that energy of discontent.
She's fully formed. She would come in more powerful than she was before she fed off this family.
I don't think this is a good spirit. This story, there's something about this girl that seemed menacing.
There's something about this specter that seemed dangerous.
And whatever happened in this apartment complex after this family moved out, the ghost was more powerful when they left than it was before they arrived.
So it would make me wonder if this building is still there. If they were renting out apartments after a fire, I can't imagine it was like on the verge of collapse.
They may have just fixed it, you know, gave it a new paint job, tore out the carpets, put a new one, did a full renovation.
Now it's a fully stocked apartment complex with people living in every apartment.
But one of those apartments may have an extra tenant, the ghost of a girl who died in a fire or a demon pretending to be such a victim.
I do think this entity was feeding off the uncertainty and the fear and the confusion of this family.
And I do think that the darker elements in the world can do that. I think they can do that quite easily.
So the next time you're feeling a little down, you're depressed, you don't like your job, you're a fireman caught on fire, you're in a hotel room.
Next time you're feeling a little down, the next time you're feeling a little...solid, there could be something nearby, some unseen spirit gaining power from your emotions.
The next time you're confused, you're doing a Sudoku puzzle and you're like, "What? Why am I doing a Sudoku puzzle?" And you throw it to the ground.
There could be a spirit behind you drinking in all that delicious lush, that emotional energy made of pain and misery.
You're like, "Sudoku's not that bad, Chase. It doesn't make demons appear just because you hate math. It doesn't mean that a demon's like, "Oh, yes. I'm going to go work for The New York Times as their Sudoku editor."
The next time you're feeling a little out of sorts, confused, lonely, depressed, don't do those things.
I don't know where I'm going with this. Don't do those things, because you may be feeding a demonic spirit nearby.
And you're like, "That's it. I'm going to bed. I've had such a depressing and confusing day. I don't even know where my bed's at."
And you lay down in bed, you're just like, "Man, what a horrible day." And I had a horrible yesterday and I'll probably have a horrible tomorrow and you're just slowly going to sleep.
You can't even fall asleep fast. You're so depressed, you're serotonin. It's like, "No, we're going to hang out here for a while. Melatonin, you stay. You stay down there. You stay down there."
You're slowly falling asleep. You could be feeding the spirit of a little girl standing at the foot of your bed.
She's like, "Finally! Finally! I finally have enough energy to fully manifest." And then she does that. So basically the moral of the story is don't be depressed, I guess.
I don't know. I was thinking, I was thinking it was going to be super creepy. And then I was like, "How can you not be depressed?"
Well, don't. Because when you're depressed, you may be feeding a dark spirit. I guess if it did take the form of a little girl at the end of your bed, you could be like, "Do chores and stuff. Young lady, if you're under my roof, you're going to fall in my rules."
She's like, "Oh, just don't have her take out the trash because she's really bad at that job."
Okay, that's it. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Tiktok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day. And I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great day, guys.
[Music]
[BLANK_AUDIO]