Did the Vatican try hiding proof that holy icons can be possessed by the devil?
And then we take a look at the story of a man who almost dies and has a vision of his death today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a bunch of stuff to get started with.
Coming into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our legacy Patreon supporters. Give it up for Joe S.
Everyone give a round of applause to Joe S. He's walking on in. He's tumbling into Dead Rabbit Command.
Joe, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode. If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show. You guys have no idea how much that means. Word of mouth is king
with podcasts. So I need you guys telling people about it. Talk about it online. Talk about it to your friends.
It really, really is important to spread the word about the show. Joe S. I'm going to go ahead and tash the oars to the Dead Rabbit
Robo. We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. We are sailing all the way out to Milan, Italy.
Splishity splash. Splishity splash. Those are the oars in the water. I realized the other day
I don't really have a sound effect for the Dead Rabbit Robo. That's the sound of the oars hitting the water. Splishity splash.
And as we're sailing out there, first off, let's go ahead. I want to issue a
update. A Dead Rabbit Radio update. Breaking update. Episode 676. I had an episode called "He Tested His Time Machine On Himself."
It was the story of Mike Madman Markham. It was a great episode. It's one of my
favorite recent episodes. I really, really love that one. But in that episode, I made a claim
that a Minecraft game was haunted by a third player. And it was about how open world games themselves
are kind of spooky and who knows what's going on in the programming. And what happened was I was watching
"Fruitberries vs. Illumina." I know your eyes are glazing over. Just like whenever your nephew talks to you about Minecraft.
But "Fruitberries vs. Illumina" are two of the best Minecraft players in the world. They're fighting each other.
And I saw a third player in there. Even one of them, I think it was Illumina, turned and looked and go,
"Hey, are you over there?" Like it tricked him. And I had this segment about who knows what's going on in the background of these open world.
And I still stand by that. We don't know what goes on in the open worlds. But this mystery has been solved thanks to Corey NJ.
I thought it was a third player in Enchanted Armor jumping into a lake.
It turns out it was a dolphin.
You're like, "Jason, Jason, how did you... how did you confuse a dolphin with a man in whatever armor you said?"
Well, it's easy to confuse. Like even Corey NJ, they said they'd been playing the game since beta.
They said they slowed it down and they magnified it and they were able to see it. And once Corey NJ said that,
I went back and rewatched it and yes. So I wanted to make that correction. I wanted to make that update.
That was a claim I was making specifically. Every show often I'll cover stories and the episode will be out.
Sometimes there might be a slight alteration to the news.
Like Church Going Mule. I covered a story recently about a guy banging a donkey in El Salvador and he gave birth to another donkey.
Church Going Mule did some more research on it and he goes,
"This seems to be a story that's floating around in Spanish-speaking countries." He goes, "When I looked for it in Spanish newspapers,
there was like a story that said it happened in Argentina. There was a story that said it happened in Mexico,
I believe it, and people were saying it was a hoax and stuff like that. That was a story.
I wasn't going to stop the press as an announcement. The story about the half human half donkey
may not have happened in El Salvador. It seems the photos are real, but we don't know the origin of the photos.
But when I make a claim,
when I make a claim and that was my conspiracy theory, I definitely wanted to come forward and go,
there's new evidence and that particular instance
is not,
it's a dolphin. It is a dolphin. If we can make a shirt that just says it's a dolphin
and that'll be in the Ted Rabbit store soon enough,
we have to own our mistakes. I don't really know if I would say this was, I guess it was a mistake.
I did think it was a man in armor and it was a dolphin, but I think it's so important
for Paranormal and also I'd recently talked about the Dibbock box and Zach Baggins and you have to come forward and say,
you have to come forward and go, I had a belief
this is a mild one. That's the great thing about putting out a daily podcast, honestly.
If I spent weeks and weeks and weeks putting together shows
and I had a 30 minute video that was super slick and then someone goes, oh, excuse me, no, that's not real,
it'd be much harder for you to back down because you spent so much time making that for me.
I'm putting together daily content. So when people go, that's not real, which doesn't happen that often, honestly.
I mean, people may quibble. Like, I have this guy telling me that I should drink my own pee.
He's doing it right now. He's knocking on my door trying to give me drink pee. On an episode I did a long time ago about Ormus.
He keeps messaging.
I wouldn't say keeps. He's left like two or three comments, but he's like, you don't know what you're talking about.
Pee's good for you and all that. I'll put that episode in the show notes, but
if you're watching this and have no idea what you're talking about, but
I'll get people will try calling me out on stuff like that, but if and they're wrong, but I'm not going to drink my pee.
But on a situation like this where I make the claim, I need to come forward and say
I was wrong and I wish more paranormal people would do this.
When you're putting out an episode once a day, it does help because I don't have a horse in this.
I don't have a dolphin in this fight. But again, thank you, Corey and Jay for
checking that out and church going mule as well for doing more research.
But El Salvador will always have the donkey boy in my heart.
We're rolling on out to Milan. We're specifically headed to Portonari Chapel.
That's in the Basilica of Saint Eustegorio in Milan.
Now everyone shh, quit laughing at my mispronunciations. We're walking into the tomb
of a saint. This story was sent to me by Dead Rabbit Radio Listener, Sad Paperclip. This was great.
It's funny. This is actually a good segue. It's a follow-up to an episode I did
called "Can Demons Disguise Themselves as Holy Icons?" It was the end of season 14.
But you don't have to listen to that episode to get the context of this. It's exactly what it sounds
like. The question was, is can demons or dark forces disguise themselves as holy figures?
And just a quick overview, that one had three, if I remember correctly, three girls in Russia,
Eastern Europe, running away from the Virgin Mary who seemed a little menacing and she was
like floating after them and then she was like standing, just standing creepily at their neighbor's
house, just watching them from the distance. And the question was, is could a demon disguise itself
as a virgin Mary? And Sad Paperclip sent me this article and basically said, "Yeah, I think it could."
I've actually got a lot of really good feedback on that episode. That's another one of my recent
favorite episodes. But he sent me this story. We're in the Tomb of the Saint. And this is the tomb
of Saint Peter Martyr. That's setting your kid up. Like, why would your last name be Martyr?
Right? Then you're just asking him, that'd be like me having a kid and being like,
you're now Johnny Suicide Bomber. He's like, why can't I do something else? Like, no. Hang out with
your sister Suzy Patient Zero. Like, you're setting them up, you know how they're gonna die. They're
gonna be martyred. So Peter Martyr, this is the 13th century. He's an Italian Catholic priest.
And he's actually like super controversial. Well, the Catholics love him. The Catholics love him
today. He's a saint. But back then, the people around town are like, we don't know about you,
bro. Because what? Your name's Martyr. So we assume you're gonna die super violently. No one wants
to hang out with him. He's like, hey, what's hanging out in my house and play some cards? You're like,
uh, I don't know. Today might be the day you like burst into flames or someone ties you to a catapult.
You're gonna get martyred, bro. He was controversial because you have this breakaway set of Christianity
called the Cathars. Basically Catholics are like, you guys, we'd rather hang out with witches
than you guys. Now 13th century is the Inquisition time. So they are hanging out with the witches
because they're torturing them. But the Cathars were up on the Inquisition list as well because the
Cathars believe, and I know history majors are pulling their hair out every time I mispronounce
something. But the Cathars believe in the duality of God, as in there's two of them. It's not this
monotheism, the Catholicism's practicing. They believe that the God of the New Testament is
different than the God of the Old Testament. The God of the New Testament is a good guy because
he's like, yeah, it doesn't matter what you do. It doesn't matter if you're a Jew or a Gentile,
if you're a sinner, like I still got love for you, homie. Like all this stuff in Jesus represents
that. He's like, yeah, I don't care about what you did. I mean, like quit sitting right now in front
of me. But I love you. I love you. You too. You're selling stuff in the synagogue. I'm going to beat
you up. But at the end of the day, I love you, bros. The God of the Old Testament does seem like
a different guy because he's like, your hair, you cut your hair, and you're going to hell. Oh,
you got that tattoo on your arm. Sorry, bro. Like he's pretty, pretty brutal. Now, it is different
time periods. It is totally different time periods, but he does have a character. God
does have an interesting character arc through the Bible. But the Cathars believe that the God of
the Old Testament is a totally different guy. It's not a character arc. It's not someone who grows.
It's a dude named Rex Mundy, which means king of the world. It's actually like a separate individual.
And they also believe like Jesus was not corporeal, that he was like a ghost floating around. He's like
caspering it all over the Holy Land. They were basically saying stuff specifically to mess with
the Catholics, but they believed it. The Catholics were getting so mad at them. They're like, you
know what? We've perfected all this torture with these witches. Why don't we use this on these Cathars?
And first, first way we'll torture them is by mispronouncing their name. They're like,
so, so Peter Martyr was this Italian Catholic priest and he was constantly in conflict with
these Cathars in this area. And the Cathars are like, dude, this dude totally sucks. Let's take
care of him. Let's make his last name finally mean something. So one day he's walking down the street
and a dude runs up behind him with an axe and hits him on the head so hard. This is the thing. Okay,
let me pause it right here. A little bit of dramatic pause. I used to work in a morgue. And one of the
first things you realize when you're around a lot of dead bodies is that people do not die in movie
type ways. Like when people get shot in movies, they go, oh, and they kind of fall down. There's
an awful lot of gurgling. There's an awful lot of gurgling involved when people die. A lot of
noises, a lot of smells. And it's not like when you hit someone with an axe on the head, it doesn't
get stuck in the, I mean, these things can happen. You get stuck in the head or the head goes flying
off and then winks at a sexy lady is it rolling along the ground? No, there's a, the human head is
a, is a ball, right? It's like a oval type thing and an axe comes to a point. So if you're running
up behind someone and you're going to chop their head off or put an axe in your head, there's a
lot of things that can go wrong or right. The assailant takes the axe and hits Peter's head and
cuts off just a piece of his brain. I mean, there's no, it's 13th century Italy. That's a, you're dead.
But not immediately. Like it's not so dramatic that he's able to, he chops off a chunk of skull
and a bit of brain go fly. You're like, Jason, damn it. Dude, that's so gross. I know, I know.
The, the axe just chops off. Imagine if all of a sudden you lost one tenth of your brain.
Like you look and it's laying on the ground. You'd probably freak out. I'd probably freak out. I
think anyone freak out. But Peter martyr, he takes his blow to his head, probably about 10,
20% of his brain goes flying out and he immediately begins this thing called the Apostles Creed,
which is the Bible version of Assassin's Creed. It's that lame game, the one you played at
vacation Bible school. He begins saying, I believe in God, the Father Almighty, creator of heaven and
earth. And as he's doing the Apostles Creed, the other guys like, damn it, dude, why'd you have to
just chop off part of his brain and he gets stabbed and it still takes some like four or five days to
die. So this point, Peter martyr is actually the fastest person to go from death to sainthood. It's
11 months from the time he died to the time he became a saint. And when you look, I didn't know
this. So I guess this kind of makes sense. When you look at pictures of Jesus, he's crucified,
not all the time. Sometimes he's like walking around talking to people, but a lot of times,
especially in Catholicism, he's on the cross. I didn't know this was a thing, but apparently
in Catholicism, the saints are drawn with the martyr, you know, the martyred saints are drawn
with the way they're dead. I didn't know this was a thing, because if you look at a pain,
it's horrifying. This is so horrifying. If you look at paintings of Saint now Saint Peter martyr,
there's an axe in his head and a knife through his chest. And he's like talking to baby Jesus.
It's so bizarre. I mean, I'm not trying, I mean, I guess I know I know I've lost every Catholic
listener. I'm not trying to be insulting. I just didn't know there was a thing. Like it's super
disturbing. And because he died, because this article said because he died of two different
ways, they're both included. And it's almost, it doesn't look like an axe. It looks like if you
had a paper cutter at work, and then you took the bolt off, and then you stuck that in someone's
head, that it's like this giant cleaver. And then he has a knife in them. There's a painting of him
talking to Jesus. But that's not why we're here. That's not why that's all incredibly fascinating.
That's not why we're here. So Portanari Chapel is the tomb of Saint Peter martyr. And they have
all these frescoes and all these paintings. And you can go there, you pay a couple lira,
and you walk around. It's a great little experience. But in 1952, they were doing some sort of
renovation, and they were working on something, and they began to chip away at the plaster on this
wall. And they found a painting, a fresco, from 1468 that had been covered up. They didn't know
who knew it was there. It had been covered up for hundreds of years at this point.
And they take all the plaster off, and they do restoration of the painting. And it was painted
by Renaissance master. Wasn't just some Guy Graffiti artist there. Vincenzo Fappa painted this.
And it's the painting of Saint Peter that he did no acts in his head at this point. And he's
standing around a bunch of other people. And in front of him is the Virgin Mary and baby Jesus,
both of them with devil horns. So that's what the sat paper clip sent me. He goes,
you know, there's a story about Saint Peter. He exercised the devil from a statue of Mary.
And the name of this painting is Saint Peter martyr, exercising a demon possessed statue of
the Virgin and child. But there was no info on like the articles I was reading about it. They
said we know when it was painted or around the time period, we know it was covered up. But we
don't really know what event this was relating to. And whenever I searched for this, it kept bringing
up stories about the plaster and this painting. But I couldn't find any event of when he showed
up and when he exercised the devil from the statue. I was looking, I'm looking, I'm looking,
I'm looking, I was about to give up. I came across an Atlas Obscura article. It wasn't a statue.
Check this out. This is this is the story. Saint Peter finds out that this man who was previously
Catholic had joined the Cathars. And he's like, dang it, dude, now I got to go and reconvert them
or deconvert them. However it is. He goes, listen, you got to be a Catholic again. This is no good
news. Why are why are you even toying with this idea of being a cathar? And the friend of his goes,
dude, you won't believe it. I went and I was hanging out with these other cathar people.
And the Virgin Mary and baby Jesus showed up. Like I go to your church all the time. I never
seen none of that stuff, but I saw her and little baby Jesus. So who, what would you do? Now Saint
Peter goes, this has to be a setup, right? This can't be real because I know that the Blessed
Virgin Mary and baby Jesus is on our side. So he goes, you know, I'll go with you. I want to see
this vision for myself. So he goes and he's hanging out with his buddy and all these other cathars
are standing around in this area and the Virgin Mary and baby Jesus show up. And Saint Peter's
looking at him and it goes, you guys, this is it? This is what they're like, yeah, that's, that's,
you can see that, right? He's like, oh no, I totally see it. That's, that's the Virgin Mary and
and little baby Jesus. But you guys see the other thing, right? And what Saint Peter realized,
no one else could see this, both Mary and Jesus had devil horns. So he knows this is not the
real Blessed Virgin Mary, but the cathars are like, no, no, no, they don't see the horns. No, no,
no, this is actual vision. So what he does is he has some sacramental bread on him and he asks the
Virgin Mary, well, this is his quote, if you're the mother of God, adore your son, unquote. He
wanted her to take the sacrament, which is the bread supposed to symbolize the flesh of Jesus
and you eat it and gives her the piece of bread to eat to take that sacrament and she won't because
it's the devil and she runs away. And all of the cathars there realize that this not, this was not
the Blessed Virgin Mary, it was actually the devil and they all immediately become Catholic again.
It's an interesting story. I was only able to find one source of it that when I was reading
articles about the painting, it would refer me to a book that was like $50. The ebook version was
$50. It's normally like $150. It was talking about the life of Saint Peter. So it's possible
that Atlas Obscura got this from the book, but I couldn't afford the book to verify it.
But it's more information than what we were getting with everything else, which was basically like,
I don't know. There's this painting that they found that had the Virgin Mary and it would make
sense if the context of it was lost over time. If this story became limited over time, I'm not
saying they had to buy the ebook back in the 1500s, but if over time, if the story was so rare,
I could only find one source of it and everyone else just said it's a painting. We think it's this.
It would make sense that when people are going to visit the tomb, out of context, the picture of
the Blessed Virgin Mary and baby Jesus with devil horns would make no sense. And it's possible that
there were probably people working in that chapel who were completely unfamiliar with this story.
And if they couldn't explain it, it just became the story of, I don't know, and then eventually
they just said, "Paint it over. I'm tired of not being able to answer questions." And then over
the centuries, people just forgot about it altogether. But a fascinating story and one more
piece of the puzzle, it does seem like the forces of evil can disguise themselves as
holy icons. Not only can they, it seems like they do it quite often. So then you have to sit back
and wonder how many visions from God are actually visions from the devil. I remember one thing I
heard really early on. I was probably in middle school and my dad was a minister before he owned
a morgue. But I remember one thing I learned really early on, middle school when I was going to church,
the devil hears your prayers too. I thought it was really spooky because you may really want
something, you may really want something to happen, and the devil may give it to you, knowing
that is not the path you should be going down. So thank you so much for that story,
sad paperclip. Again, it's very, very cool and creepy addition to the saga of Canary religious
icons really be devils in disguise. Joe S, I'm going to go ahead and touch you the keys of the
Carbinder Coptor. We are leaving behind Italy. We are headed on out to Jolly Old England.
Joe's flying us over the quaint little households of England. This is one of those stories where we
don't have a name. This is anonymous story. So we're going to call this guy Paul. And we don't
really have a time period for when the story starts as well. Mid 80s maybe. So we have some real
wiggly stuff in the beginning, but I think the story builds to a point that it's definitely
worth telling and examining. We're in England and there's a little eight year old boy we're going
to call him Paul. He has a terrible fever. And he's rolling around in his bed. His parents are
like, we don't know what to do. We tried everything. And his parents are super worried. I mean,
this kid is burning up and they call 999. That's the emergency phone line over in England and
Wales and stuff like that. And they're like, listen, here's what you need to do. Get a bathtub,
get the coldest water possible, throw some ice cubes in it and dunk your kid in the bathtub.
I don't know if that's the best advice. I don't know if they just going to send an ambulance out
there, but that's their first advice. So the parents draw the really cold bathtub, fill a full
ice, pick up a little Paul and submerge him into this ice cold water. And Paul says, I remember
originally I just felt freezing cold, freezing cold. But when they submerged my body into the water,
I was engulfed in flames. I felt just every pore of my body was just burning hot.
And I instantly went unconscious. He says I felt a pop in the center of my brain.
And then my eyes open, but not his physical eyes. He's floating above his body. He can
feel himself completely disconnected from his little tiny body submerged in the ice cold bath.
And he's looking up at what should be the ceiling of the bathroom. But what he really sees as a
vast unending desert. And he's looking at this landscape and he goes, it looked like Mars.
So the only thing his little eight year old brain could compare it to. I thought I was on Mars.
He's looking at this unending horizon and then he hears a click. And not too far off in the distance,
he sees an explosion. And he's just watching flame and smoke dance in the middle of this desert.
And he's watching it for what seems like hours. He feels another pop. And the next thing he knows,
he's back in his body. He's still in the bathtub. And he has then rushed to the hospital. He said
he had a really bad flu. He had the worst fever. They took him to the emergency room.
Jump ahead to the year 2006, Afghanistan.
Paul is in a Humvee along with fellow soldiers. They're driving down a pre designated road.
This is a road that the military has said this is as safe as it's going to get.
This place is swept for IEDs. There's none out here. You can travel down this road with relatives.
He says we're driving down this road. And I can't explain it. But I tell the driver, stop.
Driver looks at him, stops. What's going on? What's going on, Paul? Paul sits there and he looks out
at this landscape. He goes, there's a bomb on that road right in front of us. There's a bomb over there.
It's an interesting thing. I imagine soldiers would be extremely superstitious people.
You'd have those rituals that you did on that certain day. You tied your shoes
first left foot, then your right foot, and that's the day that the bullet hit your helmet.
It should have killed you. But it was a miracle that it didn't. So you always put your shoes on that
way. I imagine that soldiers are very, very superstitious people. So you're driving on this
road that you know is constantly swept for IEDs. There's not an IED on this road. This is a
pre designated road. It's always swept. And if any places this should be the safest. But when
someone says, stop the car. I have a funny feeling about this road. You're going to stop the car.
He goes, there's an IED up there. And he says they got out, cautiously approached the area.
There they see a freshly placed improvised explosive device.
He said it was big enough that it would have completely vaporized the vehicle. They would
have all been dead. And when they discover the IED, they call it in to get it diffused.
He's sitting in that Humvee and he remembers that night floating out of his body as a child.
He can't explain what happened or how it happened. But he knows that vision
he had as a child was his death as an adult. Fascinating, fascinating story. This is one
of those stories where you just kind of sit back and go, what happened? Like the connection between
the two events almost dying and seeing his death. And so it's just to me, it's one of those stories.
I read it and I immediately was like, I got to tell you guys about this story. I got to tell you
guys about this story because it makes no sense and it makes all the sense. Makes no sense as to
how it could have happened. But it makes sense that what if when we're at the edge of death,
where we're about to push through that veil, we see all deaths. I don't know. I mean, I could
almost hypothesize about it just over and over again. But it's like, he was, because he saw his
own death. It's not like he saw himself get warned. He's almost dying as a kid. He sees his death in
the future. But he's able to prevent that from his vision as a kid. If he didn't have that fever,
they would have driven right over that IED. Not only did he save his own life,
but he saved the lives of the other men. Did the other men in that vehicle have dreams when
they were children? Maybe not the extreme fever, but maybe just a normal dream that they forgot.
They woke up and they never remembered. How was he warned? Did the fever
spark something in his brain that allowed him to see through time? And this story has,
I mean, what if the driver wasn't superstitious or Paul didn't speak up? He's thinking, I don't
want to be a weirdo. Like, maybe I'm just, or maybe he was distracted that day.
And he wasn't thinking back to that childhood memory. How many times have we not followed our
gut instinct? Now, a lot of times I have a gut instinct to not fly on a plane. Every time I get
on a plane, I don't like, oh man, this is the time that plane's going to go down. And I start to get
a little panicked and then I just go out, screw it. And I just put on my headphones and start
listening to letters to Cleo or something and then just ignore it all. But, and it's never happened,
right? So, I mean, his gut instinct must have been far stronger than that. But what if he ignored it?
And they got vaporized. He still would have seen his death, but he wouldn't have been alive to tell
us about it. It's just so fascinating to think the difference between a Humvee full of soldiers
safely making it back to base or ending up as twisted steel and dead bodies. The only difference
between those two outcomes was the fever dream of an eight-year-old boy, barely clinging to life
as he saw a vision. And more importantly, listening to that vision.
[Music]
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also
do this up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio. TikTok is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day. And I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]