Anti-cosmic Satanism, the misanthropic Luciferian order can't get more of a
try-hard name than that. And zombies, zombies, zombies today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm
having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. It's October 1st. It's the
beginning of Halloween month. We got a lot of good stuff this month. Today
we're gonna talk about, like I said before, anti-cosmic Satanism. And I want
to give you a brief overview of Satanism in general. Because there's basically
like two big segments of it. One, you have the Church of Satan. So the Church of
Satan was founded by Anton Leves and it doesn't really worship Satan as a person
or as a creature. It's more of a humanist religion. It's more about, "I'm gonna do
what makes me feel good." They do have, they're not like, "Don't go out and do
heroin and, you know, molest a ton of kids." Like, if that makes you feel good,
then there's some deeper problems. It's more about, "Don't deny yourself the
pleasures of the flesh within reason." I've had friends who were that type of
Satan worshiper. Not many, but I've run into a couple of them over the years. And
they're just normal people. It's just they've chosen that as a religion. And
that's kind of on par with things like Christianity or Mormonism or Buddhism or
Islam or Judaism. It's just kind of a religious sect. And then just how when
you have a group like the Christians, or the Catholic Church in particular, and
then they have that, you know, that breakaway sect that was the movement for
the Restoration of the Ten Commandments. We did a episode on them a while back.
They were basically a death cult. Or you had, we did an episode on this as well,
you have Islam as a major religion. And then you had the breakaway cult in New
Mexico, I believe, where they tried exercising the four-year-old disabled
kid. And then he died and they said he'd come back as Jesus and teach all the
other kids how to shoot up schools. Like, the Church of Satan would be kind of
that mainstream, you know, they have tax exempt status, they have buildings, they
have a structure, things like that. And what happens is then you have smaller
groups of people, basically where you get into the cult level, and their beliefs
tend to be just a little more extreme. And when I say a little more, I mean
they're nuts. They're absolutely nuts. Because basically it goes from having
like a structure of a religion, and then five guys in their basement like just
playing deathcore music and writing down their commandments or whatever they want
to do. It's edgelord stuff. It really is edgelord stuff. Now if a bunch of kids
want to get together and they're like, dude, let's come up with like a breakaway
of Judaism. If a bunch of like Orthodox Jews are shitting in the basement,
listening to, I don't know, what type of music Jewish people listen to, but you
know, and they come up with their own, that's fine. Because generally their 10
commandments or their new like little cult they're forming doesn't talk about
just like murdering people. So that's kind of the group we're gonna be talking
about today. We're gonna be talking about anti-cosmic Satanism in general. And
then the MLO, which is the Misanthropic Luciferian Order. And again, you know, like
I get it. And you know, the Church of Satan, the name is shocking. When you look
into their beliefs, they're like, yeah, Satan's just the other, it's just an
Abrahamic idea. It's this old religion. It's almost like a shock value name. They
don't actually worship Satan as a person. So anti-cosmic Satanism is a breakaway
of a breakaway of a breakaway. And I think it's important for the story we're
gonna follow this up with. To take a look at kind of the overview of anti-cosmic
Satanism, and I'm gonna be totally honest up front too, it's complete nonsense. Now
I'll probably have a bunch of Satanists, or not Satanists in general, but well maybe
them too, but a bunch of anti-cosmic Satanists flooding the comments or
trying to murder me, I don't know. But let's go ahead and take a look at what
these guys believe in. So let's take a look at what actually is anti-cosmic
Satanism. This is from the Satanic International Network's website,
SatanicInternationalNetwork.com, actually. In the beginning there was nothing but
the energy of chaos. Abso and Tiamat slept and dreamed their darkest dreams. And
all was good until the dark dreams began to spawn the cosmic gods. And then it's
just nonsense from then on out. Like that was pretty ridiculous to begin with. And
I know what you're thinking, you're going, "Jason, how is that any more nonsensical
than in the beginning God created the heaven and the earth, or anything like
that, any creation myth?" Here's my pushback on that. The Abrahamic religions,
which would be Christianity, Judaism, Islam, their stories, whether or not you
accept that they're true, their creation myths, their stories, have lasted longer
than any empire ever on the planet. They're thousands of years old. And we will
even look at things like Buddhism or Taoism. These things have stood the test
of time. They have watched cultures rise and fall and rise again under the
teachings of these people. Anti-cosmic Satanism was written by some people in
their basement in a three-ring binder. That's the difference. You can use the
names that you pick and choose from this ancient, "Oh, let's take this Tiamet.
That's a cool sound of name. Oh, well, you set. Oh, that's a cool name." Well, it's,
there are myths that stand the test of time that billions of people believe
around the world that were carved in stone. And now you can read them on the
internet. They've just spanned the breadth of human knowledge and human
advancement. And then there's this nonsense. That's my pushback on that. So
basically, these ancient gods were having the darkest dreams. Nothing's ever
nice in these anti-cosmic sanism. It's always so dark and dreary. It's always so
edgelord. Anyway, so they're having these horrible dreams and, or I guess, well,
yeah, see, darkest dreams. That sounds bad. Anyways, so all these other gods pop up
and then one god pops up among them all. We know him as Yahweh or God or Ra or
whatever. Any of the good gods that we've ever heard about in religions was
actually the evil god whose goal was to subjugate mankind and turn us into
slaves. But see, the anti-cosmic Satanism, they've seen through the lies. They're
pushing back against the demiurge. I believe that's how you pronounce it. So
let's take a look here. These are their, here's some guidelines. They have, okay,
"While there are no strict laws, a Satanist must follow." There are some
guidelines that will lead you to a better life on earth. So let me, I'm gonna
read these to you. Tell me if you think this would make, you know what, actually,
no. I want you, I want to read these to you and I want you to imagine a 15-year-
old kid writing these on a rainy, rainy day. "Do unto others as they do unto you."
Okay, fair enough. That's it. That sounds familiar. This is one. "Do unto others as
they do unto you." If a man strikes you on the cheek, destroy him. What? That seems
like a bit of an escalation. Man strikes me on the cheek. That's not doing what
they do unto you. That's, you're killing them. And then it says, "If a person shows
you love, show them love." That'll be important for our next story. Number two,
mercy is for the weak masses. Show no mercy towards your enemies. May your
hatred towards them burn as bright as a thousand suns. I'm not, this, look at the
show notes. This is totally sincere. Ridiculous. Okay, four, the strong,
mischievous terror to make themselves heard over the wailing of the inferior
majority. Again, guys, come on. This is try hard bullshit. This is so, I mean, again,
like, I could write this stuff when I was 15 years old. The sheeple will all bow
down when the strong man, it's garbage. It's garbage. Seven, the weak masses are
trapped by morality. The satanist is beyond such constructs. That's gonna be
important in our next story. See if there's any other gold ones here. Oh, what?
Okay, this is bizarre. So they're talking about strong overcoming the weak and no
morality. Like, we're above that. They're above that. I've already got Stockholm
Syndrome. This is point eight. It's quite odd. This kind of stood out to me. The
satanist should strive to create a fascist society in which the strong rule
over the weak. That kind of fits in. But then we got communism and socialism must
be fought as they seek to have everyone wallow in mediocrity. Might is right. I
think the big problem, I think my main problem with communism and socialism is
the fact that they are all headed by strong men. If we had a
communist or socialist government that was like Star Trek, I'd be fine. And
that's actually interesting to side because the Star Trek goes on. We start
to see the dark side of the Starfleet. But if it is a truly like
gallitarian utopian society, I don't need to own anything if we're in
like this post-scarcity world. And I knew there was no Politburo or no Fidel
Castro or Paul Pot or Joseph Stalin or Chairman Ma... or any of the hundreds of
other examples we have of communism and socialism being run by corrupt, corrupt
strong people. The satanist, nine, the satanist should be... you like that little
rant there. Nine, the satanist should be prepared to sacrifice his own life if
necessary to hasten the return of the dark gods. That's ridiculous. Ten,
weakness must never be tolerated and annihilate the weak. And then there's
some other stupid ones after that. If someone is bothering you, oh yes, point
13. If someone is bothering you, ask them to stop. If they persist, annihilate them.
Again, guys, the escalation here is completely out of control. Someone's
like, "I'm not touching you. I'm not touching you. Will you please stop? I'm
not touching you. I'm not... you burn their family's farm down and you scatter
their ashes, right?" It's just that there's no in-between with these guys. And why even
put in, ask them to stop? Because you're gonna annihilate them anyways.
Whoever stops doing something when you say, "Please stop." Okay, and then let's do
this real quick. These are the satanic statements. This is... Jesus. This is
there. What you just heard were the guidelines. You know, you don't have to
follow them, but they're just guidelines. They're very, very polite,
anti-cosmic satanists. These are the satanic statements. One violent action
speaks louder than 1,000 words. Not 900 words. It's actually 1,000 words. Do not
say, "Do." I'm a fan of that one. "Do what you must to get your point across." Okay.
So again, the escalation. Whatever. "Only the inferior submit to social norms and
the status quo." You know, I always think it's funny when I meet people who say
that and yet they're wearing clothes. Because isn't that a social norm? Jeans.
A t-shirt. I'll have someone in front of me talking to someone, debating someone,
and they'll be like, "I don't follow any social norms." But you're wearing clothes,
which is a social norm. Why do these guys care? They're anti-cosmic satanists.
They're actually fighting to bring back the dark gods. Why do they have proper
footwear? I don't understand it. "Your enemies do not deserve mercy. Showing them
forgiveness will only lead to them taking advantage of you and eventually
destroying you." I think there might be some... especially if they're enemies. I
mean, they're showing mercy, but showing someone forgiveness and them taking
advantage of you. Yeah, people go through that. Next sentence. "Kill them before they
kill you." "Make yourself a terror to your adversary." This stuff is the most,
again, most ridiculous, edgy, 15-year-old, try-hard nonsense. They're only... here,
we'll cover this one last. "If given a blow..." Bad choice of words. "If given a blow..."
I should have just said, "If you're punched or if somebody hits you." But if... if given a
blow, retaliate a hundredfold. Okay. "Make the aggressor sorry that they ever
bothered you." Again, I think you're supposed to ask them to stop first, but
maybe that doesn't come with getting blown. "If somebody blows you, blow them back and
99 of their friends." Anti-cosmic satanism. Now, you're like Jason. Okay, you just made
fun of a ridiculous religion for way longer than you were supposed to. The
episode's run a little long. But it's because it's setting up the myth...
mythanthropic Luciferian order. So these guys don't really exist anymore. And
again, that should be a bit of a spoiler alert. This group was established in
Norway. It was set to the backdrop of the Norwegian, like, black metal music. They
have a... it's really popular over there. Black metal. And they had a rash of
incidents like in the 90s where like churches were getting burnt down and
this one member of this black metal band blew his brains out and his band
member took a picture of the crime scene and put it on the album cover and they
had a little chunks of his skull in their... you know, whatever. I mean, that's
gross, but... and it's sad that he killed himself. But anyway, so the
mythanthropic Luciferian order grew out of this and one of the main founders of
it actually was in a band called Dissection. I don't know if that's how
you pronounce it. I know how to pronounce dissection, but I don't know if it's
pronounced differently in Norwegian. And I actually listened to one of their songs,
one of the like, the big songs, and it... I mean, musically it was really well done.
It's not the type of music I listen to in general, but I can appreciate it. I used
to listen to like, tamer stuff, like Metallica and Guns N' Roses, like, more
like just heavy... I don't even know if it's classified as heavy metal, but it was
actually pretty good. And I was like, "Oh, that sucks to that." You know, this whole
story played out. But anyways, so the mythanthropic Luciferian order, we'll
call them MLO. We'll... from here on out. But I do love saying that name because
it's just so ridiculous. They have on their website, and again, this goes to
show that the mentality of the people we're dealing with, these people believe
that the Dark Gods are fighting against the God that most people know and that
the anti-cosmic, the cosmic world we live in, is controlled by the evil God, but
we're tricked into thinking he's a good God, and we have to, if we're given a blow,
strike back with a thousand blows, or a hundred blows, or whatever it was, and
don't be afraid to, like, kill our enemies and die for the Dark Gods. So this is
from an interview that a couple of the leaders gave quite a while back. "What
does it take for someone to become a member of MLO?" So Noxifer is the one
answering this. "For a candidate to become a member of MLO, he/she must wholeheartedly
sympathize with the misanthropic and anti-cosmic values of our order, and also
be over 18 years of age." Again, why do you care how old they are? I mean, I get
legally you have to care, but if you're like, "Oh, the whole universe is against
us and the real Dark Gods are the ones in control," why do you follow any rules at
all? Why don't they go, we get them when they're three, and we just like pound
heavy metal music into their ears and really get it? Because why do you care?
Why do you, following any laws, or wearing any clothes, or speaking any
language, you should just be like, "I reject everything. Everything comes from an
evil God and an evil society. I reject it all. I'm gonna walk around bucknakin and
recruit 15 year olds." Like, what do you care? Why do you care? And why are you
saying he/she? Why are you being so polite and gender-neutral? I don't understand
the mentality of these guys. At one point they want to be like these feared
rebels, and on the other side they're being like, "But first we must follow the
laws." And they there them, like, "What is going on with these dudes?" So MLO was this
anti-cosmic Satanist group, and they were basically in this big black metal band.
They had a bunch of members, I think probably like less than 50 at the
time, but it was enough they sat around, they did whatever drugs they do. I don't
that's probably stereotype, but... And they sacrificed cats. So if you're a cat
lover, you automatically hate these people. And two of the leaders, the guy who
was in the band, his name was John, I can't say his last name, Nadhvit, and then
he says his accomplice, Vlaad. I don't have the last name for the Vlaad written
down here, but Vlaad, I'm sure I'll remember that. They start saying, "We're
sacrificing cats and that's cool and all." But you know what the dark gods really
want us to do? They want us to kill somebody, a human. They want us to make a
human sacrifice. So this is the tipping point for any cult. Someone says we got
to step it up a notch. Let's fight the government, or let's, you know, kill, do a
human sacrifice or whatever. In very uncult-like fashion, and I am happily
surprised, the rest of the members of the cult left. They're like, "Nope, we didn't
sign up for this. Killing cats, that's one thing. We're not gonna kill a human."
They left. So the only people left in the cult at that time in the misanthropic
Luciferian order was Vlaad, John, and Vlaad's girlfriend. And so this is a
summer of 1997. And John and Vlaad are out walking around kind of like bar hop and
stuff like that. They meet this young man named Joseph Ben Meador. He was a, I
think he was a Nigerian immigrant. They're in Norway. So they're hanging out,
they're talking, and Joseph goes, "Hey, you guys kind of look like Satanists. Like,
would you tell me more about your beliefs?" And they're like, "Yeah, sure." Again,
like, you know, Joseph's just kind of asking some questions. They're walking
along and eventually John and Vlaad kind of get the impression that Joseph is gay.
And that angers them so much. They hate gay people. They hate them more than they
hate the cosmic God. And again, this goes against your own beliefs. Why do you care
about someone's morality? And he's just showing you love and he didn't give you
a blow. He didn't strike you down. He didn't do anything. And they're just so
angry with him that they make the decision then to kill him. So they walk
back. They spend quite a long time walking around. It's dark now. And they
invite him into their house. And Joseph, when they got to the house, Joseph decided
not to go in for whatever reason. He probably got his little spider-sense
tingling. And they're like, "Okay." And then John says, "Okay, let me go grab some."
And he goes in, he grabs a taser and a pistol, and he goes, "Let's walk to the
park and we'll discuss Satanism a little more." Now, that is an offer I
would not accept. You want to go to Starbucks and talk about it? Fine. But I'm
not gonna go to a park with you at three in the morning. But Joseph went and
they're walking along and they shot him with a taser. There's a
debate over who shot who. But they shot him with a taser and it didn't take. He
didn't get taste. So he takes off running and then one of the two used the gun and
shot him twice and killed him. Eventually the cops caught up to him. It was this big
thing because they couldn't identify the body. Then the gay man's lover was
arrested but he got let free because he didn't do it. And they caught these two
guys and then they eventually confessed because even though they're like hardcore
waging war against God, you know, a cop, a beat cop can break it out of him. The
police can never figure out if he was killed as a satanic worship or as a
hate crime. They couldn't, but they just knew that they killed him. These guys got
ten years in prison for killing this dude. And then John, John Notavet, after he got
out of jail he hung himself or I think he, I know, no, he shot himself. He was
surrounded by candles and he had like this satanic grimoire in front of him.
And what is, what a way to go. I just think that that's just so grim and sad.
And you know you die and you're like, oh man, that was all made up. Should have
figured it was made up because I wrote it in a three-ring binder with a big like
mega death sticker on the cover. Like I really kind of botched that one. But
anyway, so I'm trying not to make light of his death. I think that's tragic. I
don't think that. I wish he hadn't killed himself even though he had killed
somebody, but so that, you know, to put a pin on it, that's really, I think the,
that's where if your religious commandments are, blow everything up.
You're going to, your religion is going to blow up. If your religion is, you know,
everything sucks. We were descended from demons and the one person that's supposed
to take care of you, that invisible man in the sky, is the bad guy. And now we have
to side with these dark, dark creatures, the dark ones. You call them the dark
ones. Spoiler alert, your religion is going to explode and it's going to
explode in blood and violence. And I do have to say this too, killing people is
super tacky, super tacky. I've talked about that before. Oh, big deal. You killed a
guy. Oh, he's blood sacrificed. Whatever, dude. You want to be, you want to be like a
true agent of chaos? You could ravage for five dollars. You could destroy entire
ecosystems. You could buy like kudzu vines or creeping vines or that, that horrible
stuff. Those, you could buy plants from around the world and they just throw
seeds out of your window as you're driving through Idaho. And then in five years
they're going to be like, why the fuck are all of our crops being choked out by
these horrible vines? Where did these come from? Go buy some fresh water
crocodiles and just like throw babies into the river, not human babies.
Throw a bunch of baby crocodiles into a river as you're driving down the road.
You only need two guys and it'll start populating. It'll completely, that's
Satanism. That's completely like destroying an area for generations and
generations. Salt the earth. Oh, dude, you know what? Slipping in the bathtub will
kill somebody. That's lame. I just get so fed up where they're like, yeah, do
sacrifice. Oh, don't get me started on serial killers. Serial killers are the
most overrated of all the killers easily and they're just so fucking tacky.
I'm getting worked up. I'm getting worked up because this young dude died because
these two people wanted to prove how badass they were because they were
believing that nonsense. And yes, people believe all sorts of nonsense in
religions. They do all sorts of horrible things. But this, I mean, come on, dark
ones and blowing dudes and then you got to blow them 100 times. It's just, it's
all nonsense. It's all nonsense. So the next story is going to be, I figure,
we're kicking off Halloween, Halloween month. I think you guys know, if you
listen to the podcast regularly, which some of you do and some of you don't, I
really, you know, happy that anyone listens to it, even if it's just for an
episode. But you know, I'm a fan of zombies. I'm a fan of zombie books and
zombie movies. Pretty much zombies, anything. I still watch The Walking Dead.
And the question always is, is how realistic are zombies? There's stuff like
The Living Dead, which I think is the least realistic that usually would
require some sort of like magic or some sort of apocalyptic bib.
Nope. Stop. Stop. Okay. So this is Jason from the future. Now, if you're listening
to this podcast in the archives, like if you've, if you've just started finding
Dead Rabbit, you've been listening through, or if you're listening to it
again after the first time, I did re- so originally there was a song here that I
performed called Dead World. Spoiler alert, Dead World part one was in this
episode. Now it was a mixtape, so I was rapping over somebody else's beat.
Now, you know, in the world of rap or whatever, that's really not a big deal,
but once you get into things like podcasting, if you fall into, I didn't
get a copyright claim against me, but I wanted to get in front of it before it
happened. I didn't want to be three, four hundred episodes in, and then someone
goes, "Hey, my instrumental is used on that song." And to be fair, the producer of that
beat, you know, deserves to get the credit. I don't even remember who made it, but
all the other music on the podcast, I are their own completely, like the intro and
the outro song, or it's free stock music, but the two rap songs that I
ended up performing on the podcast, I just, it wasn't worth the hassle, but just
let you know they have not disappeared into the ether. Dead World part one,
there's going to be a YouTube link below, I guess below, you're on a podcast,
so there's no below, but in your show notes, if you are so inclined, you can
listen to the rap song that I did take out of here. But I'm in the future.
This episode was recorded the first of October, I believe. Now it's November
11th, 12th, I think my brother's birthday was yesterday. But yeah, so I will see
you when you catch up to the present day. Whoa, disappearing now, how...