A performance artist so daring, so shocking, he either committed a horrifying crime or
he made the whole thing up.
And then we take a look at a young man who is traveling on his way to school when he
finds out that he is in the middle of a glitch in reality.
As he tries to navigate his way through a time loop he and his friends are caught in,
we have to ask the bigger question.
Are we ourselves currently trapped in a never ending cycle of beginnings and beginnings?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Corviner, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too and hope you guys have some great plans for the
weekend.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our newest Patreon supporters, I
think, I'll explain that in a second.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command, everyone give a round of applause for Gregory Fader.
Yeah, come on in Gregory, come on in buddy.
He's like, "It's weird, I think I've been here before he thinks he's trapped in a time
loop."
I might have given Gregory Fader a shout out on an earlier episode, but I'm not entirely
for sure.
His name's still sitting here in my notes and I would rather err on the side of caution
and definitely give him a shout out today than to just assume that I had done it before.
But again, could be a time loop, could be a time loop, I could have done that.
Gregory, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't support the
Patreon, I totally get it, I really do.
Just help spread the word about the show, that really really helps out a lot.
And to you guys who do support the Patreon, I wanna tell you how much that means to me.
That's like grocery money for me, okay?
That's like rent money and keeping the lights on.
It means a lot that you guys are giving me donations, like it really does.
I count on this money, so to those of you who do support the Patreon, hats off to you.
You guys are feeding me and keeping me comfortable, so really really appreciate that.
Oh, and before we get started, take a look at this fan art we have for Fan Art Friday.
This was sent to me by Mountain Man Leroy on Reddit, has a picture of the Carburetor
Coptor hovering overhead and then it shows two people having a nice day on the beach.
And it says, "Random people thinking nothing tragic weird is going to happen to them."
So the Carburetor Coptor, when you do see that coming, you've probably been trapped
in some nightmarish reality or a victim of a true crime.
And hopefully that never happens to any of us, but who knows where we're currently at
in the time stream.
Let's go ahead and toss you the Hair Hanglider.
We're going to jump off the highest point of Dead Rabbit Command.
We're going to fly all the way out to Italy.
Specifically, we're headed to Bologna, Italy.
I think it might be pronounced "Bologna."
Probably not.
It looks like it.
It looks like it's pronounced that way, which would actually make sense because I think
this artist, allegedly, allegedly is full of it.
Baloney.
I don't believe that this artist is doing what they're saying.
I'm putting all my cards on the table right now, but let's take a look at it.
I will say this, when I started doing this podcast, I always thought we'd cover a lot
of ghost stuff, a lot of UFO stuff, some Bigfoot stuff.
We've covered a lot of Bigfoot stuff, not covering a lot of ghosts, because the stories
are really hard to find, but I'm doing my best.
We got a lot of good ghost stuff recently.
One thing that I never expected to ever do, like multiple shows on, I've covered a lot
of these guys over the years, performance artists.
Performance artists.
We covered that guy who rolled an egg through London with his nose to protest wheat prices
or something like that.
And we talked about Marina Abramovich.
She's very popular in the conspiracy theory community and her connections to the Clinton
administration and her connections to witchcraft and all of this stuff.
We talked about that.
We also talked about she's a crazy performance artist.
Sometimes she took a car into the Metropolitan Museum of Modern Art and was doing donuts,
spraying black oil everywhere.
So she's definitely, she definitely has some controversy surrounding her, but her performance
art is just weird.
We've covered a lot of these guys.
I recently came across this guy named John Duncan.
That was the sound of a couple of you shutting off the podcast or finding the fast forward
button.
You're like, nope, I'm going to pull over in my car and just figure out where the time
loop story is.
Cause if you know the name John Duncan, you know exactly what the main thing we're going
to talk about on this story.
John Duncan.
Back in the 1970s, he's in the performance art scene in Los Angeles and performance art
is basically people sitting around going, I have an idea.
I'm going to do something weird.
And then I'm going to attribute some sort of deeper meaning to it.
And one of his was this.
I don't think there's really any deeper meaning to this one.
One of his artworks was called scare.
Scare.
He wears a disguise in this one.
It's not really scary if he walked into the room.
It actually does turn out because the, the already does, it would make you scared if
he walked into the room.
If he's telling the truth again, who knows.
But this one, there were witnesses to this one.
He put on a disguise and he walked into an art exhibit or he walked in where all these
people were.
They're all sitting around there and we're John Duncan.
He's supposed to scare us.
And he was wearing his disguise and he jumped out with a gun.
He goes, "Ahhhhh!"
He's waving the gun in his fuel's faces and they're like, "Ahh!
Who are you?"
That was, that was it.
That was the whole art exhibit that only works once.
Like you can imagine the people like waiting to go visit that one.
They see a guy jump out and he's waving a gun and they're like, "Uhhh."
I can imagine what is going to scare me, that guy with the gun.
And it's probably John Duncan.
So that really happened.
He also apparently was a Los Angeles city bus driver for a while.
Either that or he pretended to be one of the more bus driver uniform and just gotten a
bus and started driving around.
Because a couple of his artworks, quote unquote artwork, has to do with driving a bus, driving
a city bus.
In 1976 he had one called Bus Ride.
This first one's funny.
This first one's pretty funny.
That's the reason why I like performance artists and sometimes they're wacky.
He, I don't know if he arranges.
I'm assuming this was some sort of skit that was going on on a bus.
But the bus would be going down the street and he would have a pregnant woman on board.
I'm sure I wish she was part of this.
I wish she was in on it.
Otherwise, actually it's probably more hilarious if she wasn't.
There's a pregnant woman on the bus.
There's a bunch of random passengers.
This is, nowadays we would call this a social experiment on YouTube.
But back then this was high art.
He would drive around a bus.
He's wearing a sky suit.
He's dressed up like a burglar.
He has his gun ready to scare people in case he needs another artwork real quick.
This one isn't paying out.
There's a pregnant woman and then there's a stranger on there as well.
I mean, it's a bus.
Everyone's a stranger but there's a pregnant woman and not a stranger to John Duncan.
Someone John Duncan knows.
And this dude kicks the pregnant woman off the seat.
Like they're sitting next to each other and he kicks her off and then props his feet up
on the seat.
So he was doing it just to have more leg room.
He wasn't doing it because he needed to get there.
He wasn't doing it because she was Sarah Connor and he was the terminator.
He kicks her off the seat and then a fight breaks out among the other passengers and
half of them take the stranger's side.
Half of them go, "Hey, man, you shouldn't kick a pregnant lady off of the seat."
And the other half is like, "Well, we don't know the whole story.
We don't know the whole story.
Maybe he's from the future and he's trying to terminate John Connor."
He did that twice.
He did that artwork twice, 30 days apart.
And then he did this other one which I had to go.
I ended up finding his website and really had to dig into some of this stuff because
this made no sense, but this is a quote, this is from Wikipedia.
His other version of bus ride was, "Bus ride sexually stimulated unsuspecting passengers."
This would be a crime nowadays.
It's a crime back then too, but "Bus ride sexually stimulated unsuspecting passengers
on a city bus with a liquid poured into the ventilation system in order to observe the
results."
I'm like, "What?
What in the possible?"
Like, I can understand like if he was driving, he's driving by sexy billboards over and over
and people are like, "Ooh, that sure is a sexy picture of Bo Derek or whoever was hot
back in 1976."
No, he put a liquid in and I was like, "What?
That's not enough information.
I'm not going to figure out what this liquid is."
It was, this is gross.
This is so gross.
Who would get turned on by this?
Imagine you're on a city bus in Los Angeles, the home of smog, the birthplace of smog.
It didn't exist until Los Angeles was built.
It's 1976.
It's the smoggiest of smogs.
You're driving in this hot city bus.
You're like hoping you can see a rainbow and we kicked off a seat.
You're like, "That's my fetish because I'm a weird sicko."
But instead, instead you don't get to see that delight.
Instead he dropped fish extract into the ventilation system.
I mean, that's the grossest smell.
Fish extract into the ventilation system.
I've done that as a prank.
It's actually a crime, but I've done that.
I've taken fish oils or other smelly things and put it in people's ventilation systems
in their cars.
It was a long time ago, officers, you can't prosecute me for that, for that misdemeanor.
He would put fish extract in the ventilation system of an LA bus and also the windows he
made so the windows don't open up.
So now it's not a social experiment.
Now he's basically just the joker.
He's trying to drive people mad.
And that's not sexually stimulating.
I've never been walking by dudes fishing and they're like checking me out.
They're like, "Woohoo, woohoo!"
And they're like cat calling me.
Fish aren't sexy.
I don't understand why he thought that he could put fish extract in a dirty city bus's
ventilation system with all the other smells that are contained in that bus.
Lock the windows, which I'm pretty sure is fire hazard, and just drive around in circles.
We were like, "Sir, that was my stop.
That was my stop."
And he's like, "Do you have a boner yet?"
And they're like, "No, of course not.
I don't want a disgusting city bus."
He's like, "We're just going to keep driving around until you do."
He's most famous, though.
Not for this hilarious practice.
That's pretty funny, right?
Both of those are kind of funny.
He's not famous for those.
He's famous for...and piece of art he did on May 14th, 1980.
This one had no witnesses.
You could argue it had one, but as far as I know, they've never come forward.
This was a performance art that he did called Blind Date.
And you can find it on YouTube, shockingly.
Well, I mean, again, if it's fake, it's probably about as real as the Batman.
You can watch a video of Robert Pattinson beating up some thug.
You're not like Colin the cop.
You're like, "I just saw Robert Pattinson beat up this dude."
He has this audio only.
There's no video footage or film footage of this at all.
We have to take his word for this.
And if you listen to the audio track on YouTube, it explains, "On May 14th, 1980, John Duncan
had sex with a dead body."
Apparently, he went to Mexico and bribed a coroner down there to have sex with a body.
He walks in with a pocket full of cash and he goes, "Do you have any suggestions, good
sir?
Can I have your hottest corpse?"
And I don't know if he cared how hot it was.
It was a dead woman, right?
I don't know.
And here's the thing.
I don't believe this.
I don't believe this happened.
If you guys are getting angry at me laughing, I think it's made up.
But he says he went to a coroner down in Mexico and bribed one of them to have sex with a
dead body and he was going to record it on audio tape.
So there's no proof he did any of this.
And he had sex to completion and then he went and had a vasectomy on audio tape.
So he went, I don't know if they were all in the same room.
I don't know if there was a doctor sitting there and he's like, "Oh, come on.
Hurry up, dude.
I got another appointment.
I got another appointment with another sicko."
It rides down.
Apparently, he had sex with this corpse and recorded the audio of it and then had a vasectomy
and recorded the audio of that.
And the point was to have put the last of his living viable seed, his sperm, into a dead
body, to a corpse that can never get pregnant.
I don't believe this happened.
I don't believe this happened because basically I listened to the audio track.
Again, it's on YouTube.
I had to go to some crazy website and I wouldn't have if I had to.
I'd been like, "Ah, whatever."
I went to YouTube and I listened to this and it's about, imagine what you, imagine
the sounds of two people having sex but one of them can't.
It's that.
It's nothing.
I mean, I don't know if I expected like Barry White music in the background and him like
talking to it.
This is getting really, really dark and really gross.
But again, I didn't, I'm not saying that he did this.
He's saying that he did this and I don't believe him.
It's the sound, it's like nothing.
It's like 10 minutes of like a guy unzipping his pants and then nothing.
And then about 10 minutes, an unreasonably long amount of time, I don't know how long
the sectomies take.
I'm like, "What?
Come on.
I have an appointment on the other side of town.
Hurry up, duck."
It's the sound of two blocks of wood scraping against each other.
That's really what it sounds like.
I don't know if he was trying to simulate like someone sawing through his testicles to
give him a, the vasectomy.
I don't know what he was trying to do, but it's basically like 10 minutes of nothing.
And then 10 minutes of, "Ugh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,