It's been one day, so of course now we have more conspiracies about the death of a young
rapper.
Why listening to an anonymous poster on 4chan could ruin your life?
And US fighter pilots have a close encounter of the churned kind today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Oh you have no idea how many times I recorded that intro.
My name is Jason Carpenter, this is Dead Rabbit Radio.
You know this is one of those days where it's like "hey what do you want to do for a hobby?"
"Oh I'm gonna do a podcast."
"When do you want to start it?"
"June."
You know you can't run any fans or have any sort of air conditioning units while you're
recording.
Oh yeah yeah and I know, I know.
It's 91 degrees.
It's 10 o'clock at night.
I'm sweating.
It's like recording in a swamp.
But you know, what are you gonna do?
It could be worse.
I could still be in California.
I'm up in the ever so docile yet stunningly dark town of Hood River.
It's very creepy here.
I think I might have to dedicate a whole week to episodes about Hood River.
It's something off here.
You can always tell there's something bad in a neighborhood or in a town when there's
a lot of churches.
There's a lot of churches in Hood River.
We have a population of about 10,000 people and just off the top of my head there's maybe
10 churches.
And there was a pause there because it's just, I mean that's a church for every thousand
people.
I lived in Sacramento when I was in California.
Millions of people live there.
There was a ton of churches but when you have millions of people you're gonna have tons
of churches.
Some churches are going to have 10 members.
10 churches are going to have, you know, five, six hundred members.
I think Crystal Cathedral was down there, something like that.
Hood River has, I'd say about 10 churches and you have like the Latter-day Saints and
you have the Jehovah's Witness Temple and then you have, you know, the Protestant breakaways,
the Seventh-day Adventists and the Baptist and so on and so on.
We have three Mason lodges all within about two blocks of each other.
That's weird.
So yeah, it's just weird.
I always say that if you have, if you go to a town there's a lot of churches there.
That means people have a need to repent more.
I don't know, I'm rambling now.
The heat's getting to me.
So we're gonna try to get this going quickly.
So let's go ahead and start off with the story about, again, a young rapper whose name I'm
sure I mispronouncing, extension on.
Of course, it's only been a little bit over 24 hours.
We're already getting more conspiracy theories about the death of extension.
It's coming out, you know, of course the Drake theory seems to be the leading one.
That photo I talked about the last episode with Drake engaged in a homosexual act, oral
copulation with another man, that picture has been getting more traction and when I
saw it, it was cropped kind of a, kind of suggestively when extension put it on his
Twitter, it was kind of cropped and now I've seen kind of the full photo and there is a
dick in this young man's mouth.
I don't know if it's Drake or what, but it looks like Drake.
Anyways, so this is the other, and this is the thing I've always found that's interesting
with conspiracy theories.
You'll have an event, an event that happens.
And some people, a weird thing with conspiracy theories is now people have started debating
whether or not the event has happened in the first place.
Or an event happens and then you have an initial conspiracy theory come out about it and then
the conspiracy theories get odder and odder as time goes on.
So for example JFK gets shot, that's an incident that has actually absolutely happened.
The first conspiracy theories were things like it was Russia who was behind it.
And then as you start to bring, as you start to pull back through time, you start to get
stuff where no, it was the mafia.
That wasn't an initial, that wasn't one of the initial big theories.
You had to give it a little bit of a distance there.
And as time has gone on even further, even further, you start having stuff like, "Oh
no, he got killed because he was going to reveal the existence of aliens."
So the conspiracy theories tend to start off fairly close to home.
And then as time goes on, they spread out.
9/11, the initial conspiracy theories was, it was an inside job.
It was controlled demolition because of the way that the towers fell.
And then give it, and about six months a year after that, it became hologram, the planes
are holograms and they were destroyed by a laser from space.
If that was the first conspiracy theory that had gained traction with 9/11, people would
have dismissed it outright.
It's almost like the slippery slope of arguments for conspiracy theories.
The first ones are always relatively plausible.
So let's say that it is plausible that X, I'm just going to call him X now, X tweeted
that thing about Drake and then Drake killed him.
That's a plausible conspiracy.
It's still a conspiracy, but that's a plausible one.
It's been one day.
And you know, to go back to my thing, the cycle has sped up because conspiracy theories have
become so mainstream now.
The cycle has sped up.
When it used to take months or years for the conspiracy theories to get wacky, they've
definitely sped up.
I came across this post today.
The headline is "Extension was killed by demons."
I'm almost certain, this is not my words, this is what he's saying, I'm almost certain
Extension was killed by the Grand Pontiff of Hell, Balbarath, or Ba-- I don't think it's
Balbarath, Ba-- Barath or Bulfry.
And then it says, "Barath is a demon who grants material success, turns base metals
into gold, and enhances musical performance, but is also a notorious liar and trickster.
He also shapeshifts."
No, no, no citation for this.
I don't know why I'm surprised there's no citation for this, that I can't actually look
this up.
He grants material success, turns base metals into gold.
That's kind of redundant.
But anyways, and here's his evidence.
He actually entitles this next passage some evidence.
"Barath appears wearing red.
Exes killers were alleged to have been wearing red masks.
On a horse, the killing was a drive-by.
Barath is the most powerful Monday evening at night.
Ex was killed on a Monday afternoon."
I don't know how that plays because he's the most powerful evening at night.
"During the month of June, according to Christian lore, Barath is associated with murder and
blasphemy."
I-- We're past the looking glass, people.
We have entered a reality where some people are going to take this seriously.
And I guess we've always been there.
But because of the internet, this stuff's going to fly around incredibly fast.
I believe that this post here-- This is the way conspiracy theories didn't really work.
This post is going to go up.
It's going to disappear probably in the next 24 or 48 hours.
And then maybe two, three weeks from now, you're going to start seeing more and more
people talking about this.
He was killed by the occult.
He was killed by a demon.
It's almost like you throw the seed out there and then it just kind of disappears at first
and then other people take root because here's the thing.
When you post it, people are going to look at it and go, "That's in it.
That doesn't make any sense."
So it disappears and then people start talking about it.
And they-- Every time-- Every time you talk about it, the details change a bit.
So then what will happen is six weeks from now, someone will go, "Oh, yeah, you know,
I think-- I read this thing a while back that said that X was killed by a demon because
this demon only operates during the June afternoons."
And he was killed during June afternoon.
People go, "Oh, man, that is a weird coincidence."
Like the same demon who's known for being-- bringing about rap success only operates
in June afternoons.
And they're like, "Oh, yeah, that-- See how the information changes?"
He-- The information this person norm-- norm first puts off enhanced musical performance
during the nights, during June.
All that stuff will get changed.
And I've seen it with almost every conspiracy theory.
I've seen it with almost every conspiracy theory.
The initial conspiracy is put out and then the information is changed.
So generally that's what happens.
Someone spouts off a conspiracy theory that's half-assed and over time it becomes even more
half-assed when people start adding into leading things that coa-- you know, work better with
the theory.
That's generally how these things work.
They grow over time.
They're fairly organic because they don't rely on a core set of facts.
The core set of facts is X got killed on June 18th.
That's the fact.
Everything else you can kind of throw in there.
"Oh, they're wearing--" You know, okay, here's one.
They said it was a car and it was like riding a horse watch.
The car will turn into a Mustang or the car will have some sort of Mustang decal or it
will tie it in closer to that horse imagery.
We'll see these conspiracies grow over-- around this.
So I mean, that's one of the things that I think is fascinating about conspiracy theories.
It is very like-- you can watch them evolve over time.
I think they're fairly dangerous.
And that's what's going to lead us into our next segment.
Now I did an episode a couple-- I know we're on episode nine, but it was, I think episode
five or six where I was talking about the anti-Trump resistance rap with the little
girls and was garbage.
Now in the sake of fairness-- and I blasted them because they were using it so merchandise--
in the sake of fairness, I came across this article the other day and this is an unfortunate
story and it shows the problem and this happens on both sides of the divide.
But it's particularly interesting with this.
So there, if you're familiar with 4chan at all, there is currently a poster on 4chan
called Q or QAnon, but it's Q is what he goes by, or she.
This to be a top level-- actually doesn't really claim much, just kind of leaks out
information.
Q is a top secret, like a really high-secret security clearance.
People have postulated that Q is Baron Trump or Jared Kushner or Steve Bannon or Trump
himself, but whoever this person is has dropped hints and basically said that Robert Moller
is working with Donald Trump to drain the swamp, that this whole investigation is a
way for him to get into the FBI's files and root out all of this stuff because if Trump
tried investigating Hillary Clinton and Locker up and all of that stuff, he'd be stymied.
So what they do is they created this controlled opposition.
So Robert Moller is like, "I'm going to get you Trump.
FBI, give me all your files so I can pin Trump."
And they're like, "Yeah, sure."
And then he's going through them and he's like, "Hillary Clinton did this wrong, Obama
did this wrong, Loretta Lynch did this wrong, Comey did this wrong."
And then there's these mass arrests.
I go back to what I said yesterday.
Sometimes it's nice to live in this world.
Yesterday I was talking about sci-fi world, but you live in this world where it's good
versus evil and there's clear battle lines and the bad guys live in a smoking volcano.
They're good guys wear shining armor and in the end the good guys win and the bad guys
are punished.
That's not really the way the world works.
The bad guys don't live in a smoking volcano.
Everyone is on a sliding scale.
But these people want to believe this Q story because it just, one, it takes away the fear
of, "Oh crap, Robert Moller is digging hard on Trump."
And if you dig hard enough on anyone, you're going to find something.
And then someone goes, "Don't be afraid though.
Robert Moller's on our side.
See, don't be afraid.
He's with us."
So it takes away that stress of reading the newspaper, assuming they read the newspaper,
but reading the newspaper and being like, "Oh man, you know, Manafort got caught and, you
know, all this stuff."
So it gives a nice narrative.
It's basically saying, "Shh, you know, don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid."
It's a nice narrative.
It's a nice narrative to think that the people who you perceive are the bad guys will be
thrown in jail and the good guys will be thrown in jail.
Disregarding what an absolute chaos that would send America into if a bunch of political
opponents were jailed, it wouldn't work out.
I almost think that even if Hillary Clinton and Obama had done a bunch of illegal stuff,
it wouldn't be worth it to throw them in jail.
But anyways, I'm getting off topic because Q has been going on saying this, and it's
gone to the point where the inspector general had a report coming out, and Trump was of
course chiming in, and he's like, "Do you better not water down that report."
And you know, the worry was that Q was right, that this inspector general's report was
going to come out, and it was going to prove that Hillary Clinton and Barack Obama were
totally crooked and all of this stuff was going on.
So why is this, why am I talking about this obviously super political issue on this podcast?
It's because what happens is when people post stuff online, just like the resistance movement,
but both of them, but I'm talking specifically about the resistance of light one, the one
we were talking about yesterday, sucks people in, it sucks people in, and people do stupid
stuff when they think they're on the right side.
So this young man, and I'm saying young, he's 30, he's younger than me.
He goes to the Hoover Dam, he's driving an armored vehicle, he parks sideways, so completely
blocks traffic.
He holds up a sign that says, "Release the OIG report," which is the office of the inspector
general.
He's holding the sign up, he's doing that for about an hour, and what's odd is that
the report was already released.
So this person was most likely under the belief that it was the watered down report, that
the one that Q had predicted.
The true report was still out here.
And this man was going to do the right thing.
I'm sure as he was planning this, he was daydreaming.
He was daydreaming the fact that he's going to block traffic and he's going to hold the
sign up, and America's going to look and go, "What's the OIG report?"
There's going to be FBI agents rubbing their hands together going, "How do we defeat him?
How we can't let the sheep will know about the OIG report, but here is this American
hero, and he's out there for days, and celebrities are like, "Yes, yes, yes," like they're chanting
his name.
He's daydreaming all of this.
All of the people now recognizing this young man finally as the hero that he knows he is.
And the report is released.
And Obama and Clinton and all of the rest are thrown in jail because he got the true
OIG report released.
He's a celebrity now.
No.
He's a national hero.
And so you get those thoughts spinning in your head.
First you kind of get the seed in your head, and then you start daydreaming about it, and
then you go do it.
He's sitting in jail right now.
He was charged with terrorist acts, which is 10 years, just right off the bat if he
gets found guilty.
Terrorist acts, unlawful flight from law enforcement, because what happened was after
about an hour he took off.
He crossed state lines.
That's not good.
Hoover Dam, I believe, is federally controlled, so that he's going to get federal charges
with that.
But anyways, unlawful flight from law enforcement, carrying a weapon in the commission of a felony.
He had a gun and a shotgun, and misconduct involving weapons.
He also faces a misdemeanor charge of blocking a highway.
That's the least of his worries.
This young man is the way I always say, he's taken off the game board.
He's taken off the game board.
You have people who are politically active on both sides.
They get riled up by their leaders who care nothing for them.
Their only motive is making profit and perpetuating their own power.
We see this on both sides.
Some of them, sure.
Some of them feel, some of them are like, "Yeah, no, I'm doing the right thing."
And most of them, this is just a way for them to make a buck.
But anyways, so this young man, he's taken off the game board.
And when politics, when I say taken off the game board, what you do is you vote.
You can run for office.
You can be political.
You can be active in the political process.
That's done for him.
And you have that on the other side, too.
People who are very, very political, getting in fights, and a member of Antifa gets in
a fight, gets charged with a felony, loses their right to vote.
They're taken off the game board.
They're not going to be able to engage in the political process anymore.
Because this changed nothing.
Punching someone in the face, it changes nothing.
I think this is tragic, though, because this young man was going to 4chan or wherever he
was reading it, most likely 4chan, he's getting his head filled with these ideas from somebody
who nobody knows if Q is even real, if Q is even one person.
What we do know is what Q predicted has not come true.
So my advice to you in that, and I think this is kind of advice going forward, there's very
few conspiracy theories that I actually believe are true.
That I'm like, nope, that one's absolutely true.
I've researched it.
That one's true.
But even the ones I think are true, I'm not like, and now I have to take action.
Because you can take, you don't have to block a freeway.
You know, it's done.
This guy's done.
And honestly, he'll get persecuted for the fullest extent of the law.
And 30 years old, he'll probably be in jail for about 10, 12 years.
Going to have a hard life getting out, getting readjusted.
For what?
Because he thought he was right.
He thought he was right.
He didn't have all the information.
Sucks.
Quickly, I think I've gone on too long, but I didn't want to talk about this.
So I know the other day I was kind of poo-pooing the idea of UFOs.
And again, I do believe there's unidentified flying objects.
I do believe there's quote, unquote, alien space vehicles.
My idea is that I don't think they're from another planet.
I think they're either from Earth or they're from another dimension.
So I'm not like, oh no, I'm totally sceptic.
I have to see everything and believe it and blah, blah, blah.
I think they're either from Earth and they're a more advanced species than us.
I think they're either from Earth and they are humans, but they have just a certain level
of technology above us.
Or that it's from something so remotely alien as in another dimension that we can't interact
with them in any sort of meaningful way.
I think those three scenarios are far more likely than something on another planet that
has none of our similar DNA that is completely alien to us in both biology and chemistry
and mental capacity, building something that we could even recognize as a vehicle.
Building a box, putting things in that box and moving that box from point A to point B
is an earthly concept.
We do it.
That is something that is done on Earth.
The only reason we do it is because we had massive oceans.
If you lived on a planet that was mostly rivers that you could bridge across, the idea of
building a box and sending it from point A to point B over a vast distance, that's a
very, very human thing.
We do it and do it.
It's an Earth concept.
So the fact that you are expecting something that has evolved along a totally different
evolutionary platform to have that same concept, to me, is more ridiculous than something on
this planet from under the ocean or in the cave system or something like that, who is
connected to our DNA, is connected to our planet going, "Hey, you know what we need
to do?
We need to build a box and move it from point A to point B."
That's far more realistic to me.
So I was reading these articles the other day and it's not super old.
It's from May.
I found it interesting because we're starting to get these disclosure incidents from the
-- what was it?
The U.S. Navy.
We're finding -- it was the Tic Tac UFO.
And I'm going to include the link because the video is amazing.
And generally, when people talk about UFO sightings, we tend to give more credibility
to Air Force pilots, military personnel, police officers for a reason.
And they tend to, one, be out in weird areas.
They generally aren't allowed to drink on the job, so a lot of times -- especially airline
pilots, hopefully not, but -- so their sightings are more credible because they have no substances
in their system and they're flying all the time.
They're looking up all the time.
They're patrolling all the time, so when they see something out of the ordinary and they
can't explain it, it's more than me going into the woods for the first time in eight
years and seeing a big thing move by and me going, "Oh, it's a big foot, and it's really
just a black bear."
Because I never see him.
Anyways, so we're starting to get these videos of these fighter pilots chasing these little
Tic Tac shapes, which is cool enough.
But when I was reading the article -- and this is where the churned -- time -- the close
encounters of the churned kind, it took me a while to come up with that.
So this one fighter pilot is chasing this Tic Tac and flying over the ocean.
And what I thought was amazing was that the fighter pilot's flying over the ocean, he's
chasing the Tic Tac.
He starts to lose visual on the Tic Tac, and he looks down and he sees in the ocean.
So the ocean underneath him, the water is churning.
It's just this massive -- it was described as, "Okay, so pilots reported a large disturbance
just under the surface of the ocean, round and hundred yards across.
It appears if the Tic Tac was rendezvous with the underwater object."
And then it said, "So it's just like this huge churning of water, like the size of a
football field, just moving through the water."
And when the pilot came back around, it was -- because it looked like something was submerging,
the way the water kind of just turns white and bubbles up.
And the pilot says, "You know, I fly over the ocean all the time."
It was also similar to how shoals, like coral may look, is water -- like, you know, it's
kind of sticking up in the water and the water's in it.
He goes, "But when I came back around, there was nothing there."
Like he expected to come back around and see that same whiteness and go, "Well, it must
just be the shoals, but they were gone."
And our submarine said, "There's nothing there."
So yeah, and you know, our submarines weren't picking up anything.
The term "cloaking" was used a couple times in the article.
So it was just kind of an interesting idea.
I guess this footage is from back in 2009, and they were saying, "Yeah, in 2009."
And of course, it was seven F-18 pilots who were part of the statements, as well as radar
operators on the ships.
And then it said, "Despite the seriousness of the encounter, the pilots faced ridicule
after their encounters.
The Navy's initial report was buried, but not forwarded to command.
It was decided the AAV, which is the Anonymous Aerial Vehicle, was not a threat."
So it's another term they're using instead of UFO because it has such a bad meaning to
it.
So that's the thing.
It's like, "Oh man, I was flying, and I saw this tic-tac, and people are going to make
fun of you, and then they watch the footage, and they're just like, 'Ah, let's just bury
it.'
It sucks."
You know, because people do see this stuff, and it makes people not want to come forward,
and that's always been the big thing, is the government is trying to hide that information
from us all.
But again, I think this points more to my theory that if something's underwater, if
the tic-tac is going to meet up with something underwater, that what's here is from this planet.
I think that's more likely, and I think the interdimensional thing is second.
I don't think it's less likely, but it's definitely more likely than, again, aliens coming from
another planet that's just ridiculous.
It all can be considered ridiculous, but the distances are so great, the idea of them
building to even have ships, they would need to have propulsion systems to develop propulsion
systems.
They would have some sort of state of warfare to develop dynamite and explosives, and so
those are all things that humans have done, and to assume that the same pattern would
take place on a planet even within the spitting distance of us.
I mean, of course, across the universe, sure, I'm sure there's aliens on another planet,
I'm denying that.
The idea of them building ships and flying here, and ever getting here and being even
in our same galaxy are so infinitesimally small.
It's nice to think about, incredibly unlikely.
Before I go, I did watch a movie, it's kind of the same vein called The Alien Code, it
came out this year.
I'm going to give it a half-hearted recommendation.
I had a great concept, a lot of great visuals, the acting was really good.
It just, the second act got real rough for me.
A character shows up out of the blue and does an info dump for about 15 minutes, and then
the movie kind of carries on from that, but it really lost me.
It's funny because you can watch a movie, you can be totally into it, and then all it
takes is a chunk to take you out.
One scene won't take me out of the movie, one line or one bad special effect won't
take me out of a movie, but I think that they had three leads in the movie.
One of the leads disappeared and another person showed up and just was sipping tea and gave
all this exposition, and I totally took me out of the movie.
It was a super boring scene, and I was thinking the whole time, why didn't they just have
the third lead deliver this information?
It would have been much more cohesive.
It could actually be done quicker because you didn't have to introduce that person.
You could have that third person go, "These are the files."
The concept is that a young man is hired by this private corporation saying, "We found
a U.S. satellite in orbit, and it's broadcasting a code that we can't break.
This kid's a cryptographer."
We found this U.S. satellite in orbit.
It's broadcasting a code that we can't break.
We need someone to break the code and tell us what it is.
The young man goes, "Well, why don't you just ask the U.S. government?"
They sent it up, and she goes, "Well, they didn't send it up."
The young man goes, "What do you mean they didn't send it up?
You said it was U.S. satellite."
She said, "Yeah, it is a U.S. satellite.
We haven't sent it up yet.
We believe it's from the future."
That's a cool way to start a movie off.
The mystery is ready to go.
I'm like, "Okay."
There's actually another mystery that starts a movie off.
I'm like, "Okay, that's cool.
We're watching this young man trying to decode this transmission, and the mystery goes on
from there.
Who sent it up?
Why they sent it up?
What's happening to the young man?
What's happening to the other people in the world around them?"
Very well done movie.
Just that scene.
You'll know it because it's kind of the color tone changes.
The feel of the entire movie changes in the 15 minutes.
When I had to get back on board for the last act, for the last 20, 30 minutes, actually
it took me a bit to get on.
The ending was good.
I'll take away my half-hearted recommendation.
I'd recommend watching this movie if you're a fan of sci-fi.
Maybe you'll watch it and you won't have that same criticism as I did.
I will have to say it was nice watching a good science fiction movie lately.
I've been watching a lot of garbage.
That is going to be it for tonight.
I have to turn this fan on so bad I am just dripping sweat.
Dripping dripping sweat.
Do I have anything I do?
I have some more Diodepepsi.
Here's a sponsored drink for you.
I wish I could say brought to you today by Diodepepsi, the choice of a generation.
But I can't, because it didn't sponsor me.
But I did carry home a 24 pack by myself today.
And those are heavier than you think.
I'm going to finish off this Diodepepsi.
You have a great day.
Thanks for listening to Dead Ravver.
Bye.
[MUSIC]