We've all heard of "Boy Meets Girl", but today we take a look at "Girl Bleets Boy".
And then we finish off season 16 by taking a trip in an elevator.
After you, sir.
Ding!
The doors open up.
You step inside and I just wave.
I'm not getting on this elevator.
You are.
You're getting on this elevator.
And you're about to come face to face with unspeakable madness.
Today on the season finale of Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Season 16 comes to an end.
Episode 801.
That basically is 16 years worth of podcasts.
If I did this as a weekly podcast, like a sane person.
Like every other podcast out there only comes out at once a week.
801 episodes.