Does a massive entertainment franchise have a connection to one of the worst crimes possible?
And then we continue Halloween month with the spooky tale of the Ellen Austin.
When this ship set sail from London to New York in 1880, it was supposed to be a routine
journey and the journey was normal until they ran into a ship that devoured all hope today
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover today so we're gonna get started with the Patreon.
I got a new Patreon just this morning.
Matthew McKenzie.
Matthew McKenzie hit me up right as I was getting ready to record this episode.
I really appreciate the support from all of you guys.
It really really means a lot.
It means a lot.
You guys remember Spuds McKenzie?
You remember that?
Did he talk or was it just a dog with spuds?
I don't know how old you are Matthew, but if you were my age you probably would have
gotten called Spuds in school.
But anyways, let's go ahead and move on with our first story of the day.
So for our first story, we're going to go to Canada.
Put on your parkas and your hiking boots.
We're walking there.
We're just gonna go on a big old nature hike.
We're gonna be chasing butterflies and like punching squirrels, collecting cactus and
then taking it back to the desert.
It shouldn't be in the forest dude.
Stay where you belong Mr. Cactus.
And as we move through the forest, why are we in the forest?
We're on, okay.
We walk along the highways.
The point is is that we get to Toronto.
So we go into Toronto, we're catching the sights, we're putting cactuses down in funny
places, putting them under park benches.
It's not funny.
No one's gonna sit on a cactus under a park bench.
We're putting them where we're putting them in locker rooms.
So why are we doing anything with you?
The point is is that we're in Toronto, Canada.
And so we're in Toronto to meet the law enforcement officers of the child exploitation section.
So this story is a little rough guys.
But anyways, has a weird twist to it.
And as we're walking around, we're, "Hey, oi, matey, I'm from Canada.
Thank you.
I'm shaking your hands guys."
And then the cop leads us away.
Not to a jail cell leads us to give us a tour of his facility.
And we're looking around and we're like, "Oh, you know, it's mostly computers because they
have to deal with a lot of horrible stuff on the internet."
But you go into one room and there's a giant poster.
And it's a picture of the original cast of the Star Trek television show.
So Kirk, Spock, Bones, Uhura, Scotty, and the Russian dude, Vlad.
And so we go, "Hey, that's kind of weird.
Like why do you have..."
Oh, no, I didn't finish describing the poster.
So it's not just a poster of the Star Trek crew.
That would just be kind of out of place for the child exploitation section.
They're like, "Oh, we're huge fans."
No, I didn't finish describing the poster.
The poster then has the faces of each cast member replaced with a photograph of the officers
working in the child exploitation section.
So this actually happened.
There was a reporter who was covering this group saw the poster and goes, "Why do you
have that poster there with your faces on those people?"
And the cop goes, "This was huge news when this came out.
I don't remember how many of you people...
I remember this being really big news."
Now, this happened back in 2005.
So the nerd sphere of the internet wasn't super entrenched.
You didn't have gizmodo or all those other websites that are just fueled by geek culture.
That's all they do.
It's like 24/7 about Dick Grayson is dead or something like that.
I get these alerts all the time because once I clicked on a link and now they think that
I always want to know about what's happening in Batman comic books, which to be fair, I
do.
But I get stuff for all sorts of stupid geek nonsense, Game of Thrones and those bobblehead
toys.
I've never bought one of those.
Why am I getting alerts that there's a new one of those?
Anyways, geek culture 24/7.
So this was before all that.
So it kind of popped up in traditional newspapers.
It was a bit online and then it kind of died.
And then it popped back up a little bit later, but let me get...
I'm building it up.
So what happened was the law enforcement officer goes, "It's really weird.
We've kicked down the doors of a lot of child molesters and child pornographers to be specific.
We've arrested over 100 offenders in four years.
And only one of them did not have a bunch of Star Trek the original series merchandise
all over their house."
And the reporter's like, "What?"
And the dude's like, "It's weird.
Trust me, it's weird.
And I can't figure out why it is, but it's not the next generation.
It's none of the other series.
It's the original series and there'll be like toys and posters and stuff like that.
It's such a bizarre connection, but it's there.
We don't know what causes it."
One of the quotes was, "This was Detective Constable Warren Bulmer.
It has something to do with a fantasy world where mutants have power and where the usual
rules don't apply.
But beyond that, I can't really explain it."
And that doesn't...
That's not a kind of not a good description of Star Trek.
I have my own theories of what could cause it, but one of the...
This was from the Huffington Post article I read about it.
They said, "The characters in Star Trek as sexual as like Captain Kirk is, he never forms
real connections with any of the adults around him.
Like he has a connection with Spock and Bones, but like a romantic relationship.
It only lasts an episode and then he's gone.
There's no long-term relationship goal for him."
And they said, "That appeals to a pedophile.
They're not looking for a long-term goal.
They're looking for a short-term fix.
And they're seeing people who's just moving from conquest to conquest to conquest."
They also said the show is fairly sexually sterile as well.
There's a lot of like shirt ripping and kind of making out, but there's not a lot of like
real sexuality in it.
I mean, the show was from 1960s, what do you expect?
Another thing was that any sort of fantasy world has generally a world with no rules,
where there's no boundaries, where people are kind of making things up as they go.
And as a reader, you're going on this journey where you know the next episode there is a
brand new thing happening.
So there's no rules, there's nothing going on.
But the thing is, is that because people go, "Well, did they find other fantasy stuff there?
Was there other sci-fi stuff?"
Because people started asking after this article came out, originally came out in the LA Times
back in 2005, got a lot of phone calls to this section.
And at first they started saying, "Well, I was kind of misquoted, but it's true.
Like yes, I didn't say exactly what I said, but there is a connection."
And so that caused even more phone calls and like, "Well, what about Battle Circle Act?
What about this?"
And they said, "Listen, we don't know why this is.
We have no idea."
And yes, you would go to a house where they would have a bunch of Tron action figures,
but they would still have the Star Trek stuff.
Like, that was the one constant across all things.
It really is a bizarre connection.
What is there, the first thing is, is there a connection between the two?
100, arrest, only one person wasn't a Star Trek fan.
That seems a little, like, that seems like a connection.
And what's intra, and you will see these things with people in crime.
There's an, I've had, I've read this book called The Collector.
And if you're a serial killer in the 70s or 80s, if cops were, like, doing a case and
they're like, "Oh, this guy's killed three women, da-da-da-da-da."
They're on the hunt for these serial killers.
They would turn to their partner and go, "What do you want to bet?
He has a copy of The Collector."
Other officers like, "I'm not taking that bet."
Because every serial killer has a copy of The Collector.
And that was another common theme.
You would run into these serial killers.
You'd finally break their door down with a sledgehammer, put a gun to the back of their
head and they're under arrest.
And then when you're combing the scene for evidence, you find a copy of the book, The
Collector.
The Collector, so of course I was like, "I gotta read this book."
I had read a lot of true crime novels that talked about The Collector.
It being in someone's collection.
And so I went and got the book and it's, I recommend reading it.
It's a really fascinating book.
It's a story of a man who caneps a woman, he's a butterfly collector, and then he wants
to collect a woman.
So he caneps this woman and puts her in his basement.
This came out like in like mid-70s, maybe late 60s.
Caneps a woman puts her in the basement.
The book is broken up into two parts.
The first part is the killer trying to, it's a first person narrative, the killer trying
to break the woman.
The second part is a first person narrative from her point of view, how she's dealing
with being quote unquote broken.
It's a fascinating book and I can almost guarantee anyone who reads that book and then inspires
to become a serial killer doesn't finish the book.
Because the second part is extremely powerful.
Because you read the first book and you're like, "Whoa, what a horrible situation this
woman's in."
You're reading the second part and you're like, "Whoa, what a horrible situation this woman's
in."
But all of the stuff that she's going through and the tricks she's playing in the mental
is really, really good book.
It's like 90 pages long.
I would check out The Collector, but let's go ahead and actually move on to my Dead Rabbit.
That was my book recommendation.
I want to do 31 Dead Rabbit Recommends this month.
I want to give you something to watch each spooky day of spooky, spooky Halloween.
Today's movie that I want to talk about very briefly, I actually was recommended to me
by Carson.
He's a listener of the show.
He supports the Patreon as well.
He's a friend of mine in real life.
I should have said that first.
A young starlet, she's not even a starlet.
A young woman is in LA.
She wants to be a star more than anything.
She wants to make it in Hollywood.
She's living at a house with like five of her friends.
They're all young, beautiful people.
And she just can't land the right role.
No matter what she does, she just can't get a break until she meets a casting director
and everything spins out of control.
The movie's called Starry Eyes.
Now right there you're like, "What is this?
You're recommending me to watch some drama?"
This movie is about Illuminati, Satan worshippers controlling the movie industry, dark forces
behind your favorite actors.
It's a really, really good horror movie.
Again, fairly low budget.
It looks beautiful.
It's beautifully shot.
Fairly low budget, messes with your head a couple times.
You start to wonder, is she really hallucinating all this stuff and she's gotten too far into
the internet and believes all these stupid conspiracy theories or are these things actually
going on?
Starry Eyes, that's my recommendation for today.
Check it out.
Really, really good movie.
Okay, let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
Just like how I want to have a Dead Rabbit recommend every day, I want to have one spooky
story for you every day.
The pedophile story is just disgusting, but this story is actually spooky.
So we're leaving Toronto.
We walk to the ocean and then we just walk into the water.
And now I'm swimming in my scuba set.
Oh, you don't have your Dead Rabbit license scuba set?
Sorry, bro.
And you're splashing around and I'm like, "Ah, fine.
I'll go swim back."
You're going to share my oxygen tank.
I'm going to take a couple extra breaths though.
I'm going to be like, "Ah."
And then I'll give it to you and you go, "Ah."
And I just take it back and go, "Ah."
Because you know, I got to survive longer, right?
So anyways, we're swimming in our Dead Rabbit diving suit, Dead Rabbit diving suit.
I don't think you want to name a diving suit after dining.
I don't think you want to name any of our vehicles after stuff like a Dead Rabbit dirgible.
You don't want the word "dead" in your vehicle.
But anyways, Dead Rabbit diving bell, isn't that like that giant?
We're not even under water in this story.
Okay, so anyways, we get onto the Dead Rabbit robot.
Well, I'll help you onboard.
I don't know why we're going deeper into the ocean.
Dead Rabbit robot, we're rowing to the year 1856.
But we're just rowing to New York.
So we're just kind of doing a loop.
And we go into New York City.
We grab a newspaper.
We're reading this article.
This was printed in 1856.
This was in the New York Tribune.
This was printed in the February 19th edition of New York Tribune 1857.
Reading this article, right?
And there we tell the story about this boat called the Ellen Austin.
And this guy says, "Okay, here's what happened.
I worked on the Ellen Austin and I slept past the breakfast bell, the morning meal bell.
And the crew member slept past it.
So I heard you slept past the morning meal bell.
And he's like, "I did, but is that a big deal?"
And he's like, "Yeah, that's a big deal on my boat."
They throw a blanket over his head so no one can hear him scream, begin hitting him with
a giant metal rope.
And then the captain goes, "Sick 'em, boys.
And attack dogs.
Attack this guy on a boat and bite his legs up."
He's like, "Oh, next time we'll hear the bell, I promise."
And they just bite his legs up.
Captain's like, "Good.
As you can see on my boat, the punishment fits the crime."
He may go and he's like, "Uh, he hobbles out of the ship."
And then he's instructed to show all the other crew members his legs.
Now, it's 1856.
This isn't 1492.
One.
There are passengers on this boat.
This boat, the Ellen Austin was called a "package ship."
So it would have a regular route.
It would go from London to New York, London to New York.
And it would move passengers, material, mail, stuff like that.
So other people are like, "Oh, man, that was a really good breath fix.
I really like it.
I mean, that was a really good morning meal.
Sorry, Jason."
And I really like those eggs.
And then you see some guy with like bloody legs come out and goes, "This is what happens
when you don't come to the morning meal bell."
12 days later.
Okay?
His same dude is jumping down off of like a mast or something.
He's like, "Whoopie!"
He's like, "Oh, playing arrow fling."
He's jumping off of this mast and he lands on the boat's swaying foot and falls down.
And the boat's swaying goes to the captain and says, "I was just doing my boat's swaying.
This guy jumped on top of me and hurt me."
The captain goes, "Bring him to me."
So the dude hobbles in.
Legs are all still messed up.
Captain goes, "So I heard you attack this guy."
He's like, "I didn't attack this guy.
I didn't attack the carpet."
So they throw a carpet over him, beat him with the wire again, end up like bashing up
his head.
And then the captain goes, "Sick of him, boys."
And he gets attacked by dogs again.
Eventually the boat docks in New York.
He jumps out.
Not literally.
He has to crawl out.
He said after this, the only job he could do was steering the boat.
That's because he couldn't move.
And he reports a story.
And the Ellen Austin, there was this quote from the New York Times.
It says, "The officers of the Ellen Austin have a very unenviable notoriety for alleged
cruelty to their men, and that the vessel has scarcely ever entered port without complaints
being made in our police courts against them for cruel and inhuman treatment."
And people still worked for this boat and wrote it because they're like, "Oh, I really
need to get back to London."
And you think, "Okay, it's the crews getting attacked by dogs."
1859, this passenger lands in New York and says, "You won't believe what happened to
me."
And they're like, "Let me guess, you were on the Ellen Austin passenger."
Just like, "How did you know?"
So this passenger, not a crew member, is on the boat.
Some officers on the boat, they tie his arms and his legs down.
So basically they rope him up.
And then they began, quote, "Rolling him along the deck like a bale of goods."
A passenger.
They just rope up and they're like, "Weee, they're playing shuffleboard with a life
human being on the boat."
And then they just untie him and he goes and complains.
So the reason why I'm telling you that stuff is, one, the Ellen Austin had a long history
of just bizarre and cruel behavior.
And two, because the comings and goings of the Ellen Austin are actually very, very detailed.
Loids of London had to insure all these goods so we know when the boat was leaving London
ahead of New York and vice versa.
So every time this ship docked, there's a record of it.
And every time the ship docked, someone jumped off and said, "Hey, I was just on that boat
and they punched me in both eyes and it had dogs chase me around for like 10 minutes."
That's what makes this following story even more intriguing.
December 5th, 1880.
The Ellen Austin leaves London, headed towards New York like it normally does.
At this time it's being captained by AJ Griffin, who's a different captain than the dude who
was doing all that stuff.
But it still had a really bad reputation as far as a boat goes.
People still didn't really like working on the boat.
They had to pay people more.
December 5th, 1880, it leaves London.
And as they're coming across the ocean, they see an unidentified schooner, schooner, schooner
boat.
It's another boat.
They see another boat drifting listlessly in the sea in front of them and they go, "Pirates."
That ship doesn't look damaged at all.
Has to be a trap.
So the captain ordered that the Ellen Austin just kind of keep distance for a while and
watch it.
And then after two days they watched this boat.
No sign of life on board, just drifting there.
After two days the captain goes, "Okay, let's go and see what's going on with this boat."
So they come up alongside the boat, put down their gangplank.
I don't know if that's what it's called.
And they walk over.
Actually no, they didn't do that.
They got on a rowboat.
Now they remember it and they rode over to it and they started inspecting it.
No crew, no bodies, no sign of violence.
The captain's log was missing.
The name plates off the bow were missing.
But inside the hold was a giant shipment of mahogany.
So at that point the captain's eyes are like, "A-roo-ga, a-roo-ga."
He's like, "The ship alone is worth a lot of salvage, but this mahogany, this is worth
so much money."
Salvation rights.
We've got to get this ship.
He says, "Let's get my best crew over to that ship and we're going to take them both
to New York."
One of the articles, I got a lot of this information from an awesome website called Something
Interesting.
And they said, "To be fair, the best crew would still be on the Ellen Austin."
So it was probably his B team.
But still, you got a good crew over there, send some people over there, and they're just
going to take both ships back.
And for about two days, both ships are sailing, everything's fine.
And then out of nowhere, which is really how everything happens in the ocean, massive
storm hits.
You're getting tossed around.
Their human shuffleboard game gets interrupted.
They're like, "Oh no, we have to go inside."
The dude's like, "Are you going to untie me?
Are you going to untie me?"
Captain's like, "Sick 'em boys, dogs are on, tie in the ropes."
The passenger goes back.
Storm lasts for two days.
So there's no communication between the ships at that time.
But after two days, storm clears.
The other ship is gone.
They don't see it anywhere.
They're like, "Did they get..."
They must have got blown away by the storm.
It'll come back.
But they go, "We got to find that ship.
We got to find our crew.
We got to find all that sweet, sweet mahogany."
And so, and they're doing this search for a while, and eventually they see like right
over by the horizon, the tip of the ship.
They're like, "There they are.
It takes them eight hours to..."
Now that they found them, it takes them eight hours to get to the boat.
When they get there, it's just drifting.
Captain's like, "Okay, he wants a volunteer to go on board this time."
But they do need to go on board.
They need to find out what happened.
They need to find out if their crewmen are okay.
So they hop in a blue rowboat, row over, climb on board.
Ships completely empty.
The bunk beds haven't even been slept in.
The captain's log that was put there to replace the one that was missing is now also gone.
But it's still full of that sweet mahogany wood.
So Captain's like, "We got to get a new crew over here."
Nobody wanted to do it.
They go, "That ship's cursed."
He's like, "We need that stuff.
This ship is salvageable.
We can do this."
Took him quite a few hours to convince another crew to go over there.
And he said to tell you what, you guys can bring whatever you want.
Bring your weapons.
Bring that dude over.
He plays a little shuffleboard.
Totally cool.
What you need, whatever you need to feel safe, you can go over.
And also he must have promised them a lot of money because eventually he did get another
crew of people to go over there, which at this point we're probably at his sea team.
Not definitely not the best of the best.
So this other crew goes over there and the captain says, "We will stay within 10 boat
lengths of you.
We're not going to lose sight of you.
We're not going to be popping wheelies.
We're not going to be doing anything fun.
We're going to take two boats.
We're just going to sail them straight.
We'll be right behind you."
The other guys are like, "Fine."
Day passes.
No storm.
And then one day when the sea is perfectly calm, because they're over this place called
the Sargosa Sea.
It's in the Atlantic Ocean where the seaweed is so thick the wind doesn't make the water
break.
It's just a flat area.
They said the only breaks that you see in the water at the Sargosa Sea is derelict ships
because the ship will sink there and there's no current or anything to move it away.
So it just sits there.
You've reached this graveyard of boats, but you've got to go through it.
You're leaving from London to New York, New York to London.
So they're within 10 boat lengths.
The sea is perfectly calm and then fog.
Thick is peace, Sue.
Captain.
I see that matey.
Apparently, it's pirate day on my ship.
Let's talk like normal humans.
We're not pirates.
I forgot that for a second.
Thick fog moves in and neither ship can see each other at this point.
Just everyone on the Elan Austin is very, very nervous at this point.
But eventually the thick fog dissipates.
And the guy working the lookout for the Elan Austin goes, "She's gone, Captain."
And all around them is just calm sea.
The boat was never seen again.
Now this story was reported in 1906.
The first time it was reported was in 1906 in the Daily Deadwood Pioneer Times.
Tell me that doesn't sound like a rootin toot newspaper.
It comes with bullet holes shot through each issue.
But really that story had been going around for the previous 15 years from sailor to sailor.
It was already an old story that sailors told each other about the Elan Austin.
The ship was very famous for its infamous activities.
So sailors knew the name of the boat.
But they would tell this story about this missing ship that swallowed up two crews.
It was after that article in the newspaper, and that was a newspaper, after that article
it would come in and out.
It was published in a couple other accounts and then it was really made famous in the 1940s.
There was a radio show that was like weird news.
It was like the original art bell from the 1940s.
Imagine ragtime music or jazz music or whatever garbage they listened to back then.
And a dude named Lieutenant Colonel Rupert T. Gold.
Talk about weird news.
He told this story on his radio show too and that made it extremely popular at the time.
That whole time period from after the boat docked in 1881.
Because see we have the records.
I'll get to that in a second.
But after the boat docked in 1881 till really today, I'm sure sailors still talk about this
story, but definitely they were talking about it long before it became part of the public
consciousness.
So there's a lot of interesting facts to this story and there's some myths.
Obviously one of the biggest, the first thing you want to know is we have all these documents
about this boat.
Are there any reports of crew missing from this boat during that journey?
No, there aren't.
If you have a boat and people die in your boat, you have to list it.
Lost sea, you have to list it.
It's all for insurance purposes.
But we do know that the boat left on December 5th, 1880 and it arrived in New York in February
11th, 1881.
Which is apparently back then an unusually long amount of time.
It shouldn't have taken that long for that boat to reach New York.
So the idea is the boat was delayed in some way.
Not just a storm, not just a two or three day storm.
But the conclusion is that if a boat was constantly chasing another boat trying to find it, then
that could take a while.
As you say, it was just eight hours for them to go from where they were out to find the
boat the second time.
Well they took two days off to wait for the boat.
And it took them a good period of time to even see the boat off the horizon the first
time it disappeared.
It took them eight hours to get over there, but it took them a while.
They were just sailing around hoping to find it.
So the idea is the reason why the journey took longer is because of that.
Why there are no casualties listed in this report.
If I think about four men were sent over each time, four to six men were sent over each
time.
If you lost eight to twelve dudes, why isn't that reported?
A little bit of a hole in the story.
Also as the story kept getting reported later on when the radio show popped up, he changed
the name of the captain and he changed.
Boat was renamed from the Ellen Austin to the Metta.
And on the radio show he kept talking about the Metta and people think that was just a
research error because before the radio show was always known as the Ellen Austin during
the story.
So there are some discrepancies.
Some people say it was on its way to Newfoundland.
So there are some discrepancies, but when you look at the very first reported incident
of it, a little news article in the Daily Deadwood Pioneer Times, it matches pretty much all
the details that we know today.
They've said, "Oh, the radio show kind of made some mistakes."
This is one of those stories that is almost too good to be true, but when you deal with
paranormal stuff, you run into that all the time.
We've had alien invaders making kids disappear and we've had all sorts of Mormon Bigfoot.
We've had all sorts of bizarre stuff over the course of the show that we come across
stuff that's just so wacky and fun to look at that you want it to be true more than anything.
And this to me is one of those stories.
So that's the story of Ellen Austin.
You know, I read a lot of stuff about ghost ships and mostly it's just like, "Oh, there's
a boat that's abandoned," or "There's a boat that appears.
It's a literal ghost ship.
It just kind of floats around and then disappears."
But I don't think I've ever come across one that's eaten two crews.
Well, three basically, because it ate the first crew as well, if the story is true.
They find a boat, everyone's gone.
You put another crew on it, they disappear.
You put another crew on it and the boat disappears.
It's funny because we always think of ghost ships as like a derelict, a mystery, like
why did these people leave the boat or like I said, a literal ghost ship.
But what if in this case, it's a cryptid?
It's a life form that's a perfect mimic.
It adapted to a way to get people onto it.
Now you're saying Jason, that's kind of ridiculous.
Evolutionary, why would it evolve to eat people and then mimic to become a wooden boat so
people would get on it.
There's much other stuff.
Does the cryptid not like logbooks?
Is it like vulnerable to paper and leather so it has to just throw those out?
But I mean, I think we always try to say like, this is a ghost ship, this is a big foot,
this is that, but why can't there be some intersection between those things?
Are there ghost cryptids?
Are there ghosts of Mothman?
Are there aliens who are also cult leaders?
And are there ghost ships that are actually living creatures that feed off of us?
If that is true, it would have to change its hunting techniques as our boats changed.
So if you're ever offered a free ride on a Carnival Cruise Line, you might want to think
about it.
Because you don't know if you're actually getting on the funnest boat experience of
your life, this episode sponsored by Carnival Cruise Lines, or you're walking into the
belly of a beast that will disappear and you will become nothing but a footnote in stories
of those lost at sea.
DeadRavverRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRavverRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRavverRadio.
DeadRavverRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)