One swamp. One name. But two terrifying origin stories.
And then we take a look at a man who's done the one thing we all want to do. He peed on
a spaceship today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. This week's
been kind of dark. Some dark stories yesterday. I was about to shoot his mom. So I figured,
you know what? We're going to do some lighthearted stories today. So we got more tales of human
troubles but they're not, they don't involve people shooting their own mothers. So you
know, there you go. That's a bonus.
Speaking of bonuses, here comes in our newest Patreon supporter, Liam Boucher. Liam Boucher,
everybody give a round of applause to him as he's walking in. Apparently Boucher is
butcher in French or Quebec Wheeze. So he's already turning around walking out. He's
refunding his money. No, no, no, no, come back. Liam is juggling cleavers. He's going to be
our captain or pilot this episode. If anything needs to get chopped up, he's going to do
it. That's our guy.
He's saying, he's saying, he's saying, it's just my last name, bro. Are you an actual
carpenter? Well, I don't know. Maybe. I never tried. Whether or not you're a carpenter or
a Boucher. If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. Just help get the word about
the show. Really, really helps out a lot. Liam, toss me one of those cleavers. I'm going
to toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible. We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed out too.
Durgible is flying out to Florida. While we're going out there, I wanted to talk to you guys
a little bit about yesterday's episode, not the whole shoot in the mall thing. I did that
new Prophecy Watch segment where I want to start highlighting these prophecies that get
people really worried in the conspiracy community and notate them because otherwise they just
disappear. And Dark Outpost, yesterday we covered DarkOutpost.com, the best piece of
entertainment that I have found since Hans. And I didn't find it. Dr. Hare recommended
it to me. I don't think he even realized the deep, the deep, deep well of entertainment
value out of this website. DarkOutpost.com, they made this claim that the National Guard
was going to arrest Joe Biden. And, but Joe Biden's like a clone now, so they weren't
even arresting the original Joe Biden. He's already in Guantanamo Bay. They were arresting
his clone for some reason. I actually dug more into it after I recorded that episode.
And Obama's in Guantanamo Bay, but his clone was there. So they were going to put the clone
on trial. Poor clones, right? They just got cloned. They don't know what's going on.
They didn't do any of this stuff. And then Mike Pence's clone and all this stuff. So
they were going to arrest all these clones, which seems like just a waste of energy, right?
You already have the original people in Guantanamo Bay. National Guard is going to take over.
Trump was never going to leave the presidency, all this stuff. To their credit, to DarkOutpost's
credit, they did not remove the article. I kind of thought that they might because
we knew it wasn't going to happen. But for weeks, people had been talking about this.
They didn't remove the article. So that was very interesting. They did move it from their
front page. You now have to search for it, but I'm still going to give a little tip
of my hat for them not removing the article wholesale. That's all the tip of the hat they
get. I have to say this. Yesterday I listened to their episode about that, about the 10
Days of Darkness. I listened to it twice because I couldn't believe what they were
saying and not in the sense that I couldn't believe the conspiracy theories because I
hear that stuff all the time. About five minutes into the podcast or video. It's like a video,
but you just listen to people. You don't have to watch it. It's one guy named David Zyblek.
About five minutes into the video, he says, "Hey, guys, so before I tell you about this
whole clone thing, you know the thing you clicked on, the thing you want to listen to?"
Let me tell you, do you have Parkinson's or cancer or methylthemioma or Parkinson's?
Do you have dementia? I might because I mentioned those twice. Do you have any of these horrible
illnesses that we wouldn't wish on our worst enemy? Well, if you do, I have the not cure,
not cure, but something that will make it better. Something that will make all your
cancer worries go away. I'm listening to this and I'm like, seriously, of course I know
you're going to talk about clones and doppelgangers and things like that, but now you're also
selling snake oil. I don't know why I was surprised. I guess I wasn't surprised, but
I was shocked by this. As he's talking about this, did you have cancer or does a loved
one have cancer, which is such a horrible pitch, right? But anyways, he goes, "You can
call Jeanette. Jeanette will tailor a plant and I kind of caught my attention. I'm like,
call somebody. What are you talking about? This is a video broadcast on the web." What
I would assume, really, you have a worldwide audience. I honestly think Dark Outpost is
going to become one of the biggest conspiracy theory channels out there. It's been around
for a long time. I think it's in a position to outmaneuver Alex Jones. That's my prophecy
that Dark Outpost is going to blow up, but he's doing this video. He's releasing this
video and he goes, "Call Jeanette." I look over at the bottom of the screen is Jeanette's
phone number, her full phone number. It's like, "Call her." Then he says it out loud
just in case you're driving. "Call Jeanette." I'm like, "What? Why are you asking people
on the internet to call this woman to cure their cancer?" Now, to be fair, he's not
saying it'll cure their cancer for obvious legal reasons, but it will make things better.
She can tailor a health plan for your cancer. I'm looking at this and her phone number is
flashing on the screen. It's not like a 976 number. It doesn't even exist. It's not like
a toll-free number. It looks like her home or business line. I'm thinking, "How is this
woman not..." I'm not encouraging this, but I'm thinking, "How has this woman not got
10 calls a day asking to cure dick cancer?" How is this not happening? His audience may
have less weirdos than the internet as a whole, but I don't think so. Then he begrudgingly.
This is so fascinating. He hasn't even gotten to the clone stuff. He tells you to call her.
He's like, "Just call her if she doesn't pick up the phone." She's watching TV and
the phone rings. She's like, "No, I do not have to cure for dick cancer." Click. Not
only does he say, and again, I'm not encouraging that at all, but I'm just shocked that it doesn't
really happen. He goes, "If you don't want to call her and you should," he keeps pushing.
He might be doxing this woman. He might be his ex-wife or something. He goes, "If you
don't want to call her and you should, that's the best way to get hold of her. She may not
pick up the phone. She may be ironing a shirt or something like that." You can email her,
and he's super down on the fact that some people want to use email. Then he gives her
email address out, letter by letter, like the oldest man in the world, like Dorfwood.
The no joke, the email account for Dark Outpost or maybe for him, I didn't get it. I just
listened to the episode twice. They use an AOL email account, which is just so quaint.
It's so adorable. It's like thetruthseekers@aol.com that gave me a chuckle. Like I said though,
they've been around for a long time. And then, before he even gets to the clone, at this
point we're half hour into the episode. If I chase him to this point, we're half hour
into this episode. You haven't gotten to the swamp yet. We may be half hour into DarkOutpost.com.
And again, I'm working. I'm doing dead rabbit stuff. I'm filling out forms and trying to
make the website look better. I'm listening to this, and I realized that for the past
five minutes he said nothing. But, so this is how you unzip a file. So I'm going to
send you a file, and it's called a zip file. Now with a Mac, it's going to be called a
stuffed file. But you're going to take this zipped file, the Z-I-P-P-E-D file, and then
you're going to have to download a program to unzip it. Now I use 7-zip. That's the
number 7 Z-I-P. And then you get this and you will extract. I'm like, here's the thing.
He knows his audience. He knows his audience. He has no idea what a zip file is. And what
they're trying to unzip. Apparently if you're like a DarkOutpost+ member or something like
that, you can get a list of everyone in Guantanamo Bay. Now you're going, oh, so like everyone
who was arrested from 2001 to war on terror, all the prisoners of war we got from, no.
No, it's just a bunch of celebrities and politicians. So if you want to know a list of, he can't
put it on his website. He makes a zip file and then has to wait for 10 minutes in his
broadcast how to unzip it. What type of program to use. I'm thinking to put this in the email.
Put this in the truesecrets@aol.com email when people order it. Because I didn't order
it. I don't need to hear this. Send in the clones. Send in the clones. And he got to
the clone stuff and it was funny. It was nothing that I hadn't heard before and I was actually
more amused by the fact that one, you think it's a good idea to give out a woman of all
people a woman's number on the internet and a lot of pissed off calls from people who didn't
get their dementia cured or their cancer cured or whatever. And then just the fact that it
became a tech podcast, it basically became CNET.com's podcast telling you how to unzip
a file. Fascinating stuff. My prediction that Dark Out Post is going to be huge. Huge. I
really think it's going to blow up. I will say this. Dark Out Post TV makes Alex Jones
look like this show. Like it is just so, so off the chain. Is that a term the kids are
still using? That's what Dave Zblix is like. If you order my thing, you'll be off the chain.
Now I'm the boomer. But yeah, it's bizarre. Alex Jones, he makes Alex Jones look like
a very nuanced thinker. And again, I've always said this. I think Alex Jones puts on an act.
And this guy may be putting on an act too. Dave also might be putting on an act. But
just the stuff he says is far more inflammatory than Alex Jones. So that should give you an
idea of where we're dealing with. But if you need to have dementia cured, call that number.
If you don't know how to unzip a file, you're taking notes during my segment. You're like,
Jason, slow down. I have all these files that my grandson sent me. They're all zipped. So
we'll dip our toes in the Outpost.com waters from time to time. It's just so much political
stuff. And I like to stay away from that. But when you talk about clones, you got me.
Is it really a political story when the clones show up? Liam, by now we have reached the
jungles, not those. By now, he was like struggling to shoulder. He's like, what jungles? Liam,
by now we've reached the swamps of Florida. Did rabbit dirgeables float in overhead? Let's
get our ropes and scale down into the sticky green swamps of Florida. We're in Tate's
Hell, State Forest. Which is a lie, it's a swamp. Talking about tricking the tourists,
they're like, can we camp in the forest? And the park rangers are like, eyes are going
from side to side. They're like, yeah. You totally camp in the forest. This story was
recommended to me by a Patreon. Kim So Raw. Thank you very much, Kim, for sending this
over. I had actually had this one prepped and ready to go for like, I don't know, 8
months. And never covered it. And then Kim So Raw reached out and goes, hey, you should
cover this story. And I was like, I will. And another 4 months passed. Kim sent this
to me a while ago and then I was ready to do it. Because I wanted some lighthearted stuff.
But it's still kind of spooky. But not, you know, dance on your mom's dead body spooky.
Tate's Hell, State Forest. It's a swamp. Don't let them lie to you. And there is a notable
feature to it. Like in the middle of it, there's a grove of dwarf cypress trees that are over
300 years old. That's older than America. You hear that question work in my voice?
It's older than the founding of America, I believe. 17th, yeah, yeah.
That's the sound. That's the sound of history lessons going in one ear and out the other.
And it's the sound of the grove trees moving. They're an endangered species. So now it used
to be private land, but nowadays they're trying to restore it to nature. They're trying to make it
more natural. So I just imagine they're like, getting swamped from other places is full of
bunch of invasive species. They're like, no, no, no, don't do that. Helicopters are dropping
big buckets of swamp water from Okie-Fanokie. But they're making it more and more natural.
They want to preserve this area so future generations can know how disgusting Florida was.
They're like, oh, this is a swamp. I always wondered what these were. But how did it get the
name Tate's Hell? That's the story, right? That's a spooky, the word Tate's not incredibly scary,
but hell. So there has to be an origin story of why this is called Tate's Hell. So we have our
waders on. We're walking through the swamp, pushing around alligators and stuff like that.
With sticks, we have long sticks. You brought one, right? You brought your anti-alligator stick.
The year is 1871. You got old timey bluegrass, bluegrass swamp music playing. And there we're
going to meet Jebediah Tate and his son, Siba Tate. They're like, oh, wake up one morning. Hey,
son, how's it going? And it seems like it's going fine. They're dressed me up every morning and it's
a little, again, a little annoying. Jebediah goes, look at all of this land we have. It's all swamp
water at Supergross. There's 160 acres of swamp, a pristine swamp land that Jebediah Tate bought.
He only paid $5 for it. So that's a deal, right? For the guy who got the $5. But he's going to
turn this swamp land into a business. So he starts like tapping trees for pine oil, and he's raising
cattle and pigs. Now, I see that in my notes. So I don't think this is like swamp things, swamp.
I don't think the cows, the cows are up to their udders and slime, and they don't even know where
the pigs are. I think there is dry land. Everyone's not in there. Like, yes, Jason, there is dry land
in swamps. I was imagining like adventures of Bayou Billy or something like that. So apparently,
the 160 acres was usable farmland. There's pine trees, there's cows walking around, there's a
bunch of pigs. It's a really hard life living on the swamp. So eventually, Jebediah makes a deal
with the, not the devil, but a local medicine man. A couple rungs down on the diabolical level.
And he goes to the medicine man, he goes, "Listen, I want a better life." And the medicine man is
like grinding up some herbs and spices. It's girl sanders. It's girl sanders in the swamp.
The medicine man goes, "You know what? I can do that for you. I can totally do that for you,
but you need to make a sacrifice to me." And Jebediah looks at his son. He's like,
"Whatever, I don't like that guy anyways." The medicine man goes, "No, no, no. What I need you
to do is, one, you need to stay out of the cypress forest." So that grove of trees,
at that point, would only be about 200 years old. Stay away from them. Jebediah's like,
"Fine, I don't like dwarf trees anyways." And then the medicine man goes, "And every year,
you gotta bring me a pig." Jebediah looks at his son. He's like, "No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, not your son again. You gotta bring me a succulent pig. I want to eat it up."
So that happened in 1871. All of that stuff happened in that year. 1874, Jebediah wakes up
one morning. He's like, "Hey son, how you doing?" The son's like, "I'm fine, Dad." What askin' me that?
Jebediah, for whatever reason this year, decides to break off the deal. So that year, medicine
man's sitting there and he's like, finishing off the pig from last year. He's like, "Eating pig,
jerky, baking all that stuff." And he's like, "Okay, now it's time for my new pig." And he's just
sitting there and the sun comes up and the sun goes down and the medicine man's waiting.
Nah, maybe they forgot. Maybe they got waylaid by crocodiles and they just didn't bring it to me.
Or they're all devoured by crocodiles. A couple days past, the medicine man realizes that they
not doing the deal anymore. The deal's broken. So the medicine man goes to the Tate farm and says,
"Listen, deal's off. I don't know if you forgot on purpose, but it really broke my heart.
I'm also hungry." So from now on, your life is going to be hard. Like it was before.
Actually, no, it's going to be worse, the medicine man says. You're going to go through hell.
There's no mention of lightning strikes in the story or my notes, but I felt it was dramatic.
I felt it was needed. What happened shortly after this? The dad dies of malaria.
So he is journey. I mean, that would be a sucky way to die. You're living in a swamp,
you kind of expect it. But is that a hellish way to die? It might be. I'm looking into it
and checking out my notes. I know it's not the best. Like in the top 10 ways to die,
it's probably not even in the top 50. But he didn't really go through hell, right? The curse
was actually going to focus on the sun Seb or CB, however I pronounced it earlier.
Seb, we'll call him, is now walking out to the trees to check the pine oil. And he's like cranking
the thing. He's like twisting these, twisting the trees. He's like Paul Bunning trying to squeeze
out the oil. Nothing's coming out. Huh? Oh man, my life is hell now. And he's like, hopefully,
hopefully this is as bad as it gets. One day he wakes up and all the cows are gone.
Now not like UFO abduction mysteriously disappeared into the mist. He kind of figured out that from
all the guts, from all the guts that were littering the ground, that something was predating them.
What's the term? What's a predator does it? Not eat. Predating them, right? Predate,
predate, it doesn't matter. He knew, he pronounced it, the pronunciation was right in his head,
he's just going to say it. They're being predated. He says as he looks around, make sure,
did I say that right? Did I say that right? He knows. They didn't all disappear in one day.
They're going one by one. He finds a bunch of guts everywhere. He knows something in the jungle
is coming and getting them. And to make matters worse, like for some reason this is part of the
hellish curse. Pigs everywhere. The pigs are out breeding. Well the cows are dying, but now he is
way too many pigs. That is hell. If you live in a swamp and you have too many pigs, apparently that
is hell. 1875 comes around. So that is all going on for a year. And he's like, okay, I gotta figure
out what's killing the cows. But in the meantime, I'm kind of lonely. So he actually orders a male
order bride. So one day he's sitting there and basically the mailman shows up with this huge
crate with holes drilled into it. How do they ship? I know they don't actually ship them in
crates, but how do you ship a male order bride? Like I'm assuming just on a plane or a boat. I don't
think they're actually taken by the post office, but how do you know that's your male order bride
that shows up? Like you're like, no one's going to impersonate a male order bride, but do they have
some sort of identification? Do you mean track workers have some sort of way to keep track of
these people? Like how would you know? Like you ordered, especially back then you didn't have the
internet. Like did you just go through a catalog and there was like a description where there are
photographs? I don't know. Maybe I should look up the history of male order bride and end up on
eight FBI watch lists. 1875 he gets a male order bride and he's like, this will be awesome. I won't
be lonely at all. They open up the crate and that was the sound of the crate door. Oh, that was
the sound of the woman coming out of it. That was the crate door heading the ground. He meets this
woman. So he's like, listen, I have this great life for you here in the swamp. She's like,
this is horrible. Why can I have been sold to a sultan or something like that? He goes, listen,
we have the swamp and I really hope you love bacon and pig jerky. Apparently that's a thing. Jason
just made a pig jerky and we got ham hocks and he's going. He's like this. There's like a sea of pigs.
There's just 160 acres of pigs and he's like, look at all this. Maybe with the two of us,
we can actually eat all these pigs and he kind of chuckles. He rubs his tummy. He's like, I've been
doing my best. I've been doing my best. I think I have several parasites and I think I'm very,
very sick. And the woman looks at him and she looks around the swamp. She looks at the house and
she goes, I can make a life here, but I'm Jewish. And then at that point, at that point, seven turns
of the camera and goes, a gulp. And then we move on to part two of this Odyssey. So it is actually
not part two. It's a continuation, but anyways, it's the next thing. She can't eat pork and she
goes, I need, if I'm going to eat anything, I can eat, well, I can eat anything but pork. I can
eat that pork. I can eat this house, but I can't eat pork. So he has to now buy some cows and protect
them. And he figures, okay, I love this woman. I just ordered her, but she came from the heart.
She can't eat pigs. That's against her religion. So what I'm going to do is I'm going to buy some
more cows and then I'm going to find out what's killing them. I'm going to straight up Nancy Drew
this and figure this out. So he gets some more cows and of course their guts get ripped out.
He looks at his wife. She's like, did you do that? And she's like, no, I'm not that hungry.
He realizes there's a panther in the swamp. Big old panther noise. Insert there. Insert there,
editor. He goes out to hunt this panther down. Probably could have done this a while ago, but
you know, he was fine just eating pigs. He brings his dogs with them and he's loading up his gun and
he's looking. He hears this incredibly loud panther. It's not very stealthy at all. Walking
through the jungle and the panther is stalking them and they're stalking the panther and the
dogs are like this socks dude. We've seen what it's done to these cows. I mean, we may have killed one
or two. We were hungry, but we let the panther take the blame for it, but we're not going to have
anything to do with this. So his dogs run away. So now he's in the swamp all alone with his rifle
looking for this panther. And then somehow it's not specified really in the story, but
he drops his gun, splashes, and he watches it sink into the murky depths of the swamp. And he's like,
oh no, if only I could pin it over and pick it up, but I can't. I've eaten too much pig.
So now he's walking through the swamp. He's unarmed. Panther is still stalking him.
And then a snake shows up. There's sound effects here. I didn't even get to do a gunshot sound effect.
He drops the gun into the swamp. It goes off. That goes through the swamp. Now this snake,
now fast forward back to the snake. The snake bites him. He falls down. He's laying against the tree
and he has this swamp bite on him. He's like, oh this sucks. And then they're still a panther.
They're still a panther walking around. I hope it doesn't go back to my house and get my cows or
my new wife. It can eat all the pigs that it wants. And then a bunch of bugs show up. Because
in the swamp they were there the whole time. But now that he's laying on the swamp with this snake
bite, he has no gun and no dogs, the insects are putting little napkins around their necks. They're
running up with forks and knives. They start biting him and he's like, oh this sucks. This sucks. This
truly is hell. And he runs and he's running through the swamps and he sees that grove of dwarf cypress
trees. He runs into the trees and apparently the bugs don't follow him or the panther or the snake.
He's just laying in the grove of trees. And he's like, okay now I'm not getting eaten anymore,
but I'm super thirsty. There's nothing around me but dirty dirty swamp water. So he begins to drink
a swamp water. Seven days later people are wondering where this dude's at. They're like, hey whatever
your husband, he's like, I don't know we just got married. Honestly do you have like a hamburger or
something I can eat? And they're like, yeah sure. This figure comes crawling out of the swamp. He's
like, uh, and he crawls out and he falls in front of a dude. There's just some guy walking through
the swamp and he falls in front of him, Seb falls in front of him and he's like, uh, and he looks up
at this man and he goes, my name is Seb. I'm assuming he pronounced it correctly. The guy's
like, well that's not your name. This guy goes, my name is Seb Tate and I just came through hell.
Now some versions of the story I believe immediately dies after that, which doesn't make
sense because how did he tell people about the snake? It's not like they'd bring out a forensic
expert. He's like, hmm, from what I can tell he was first scared and dropped his gun from
the way that his fingers were frozen and it appears that he somehow dropped his gun into the swamp.
And then from the snake bite it seems that the insect showed and no one would know any of that
stuff. He has seven days of swamp water in his stomach. I've heard a version that he died. I think
the other most likely version, if this is true at all, is that he lived and then they just took
him and they gave him a couple, you know, pork loins and he's like, throw those up. He's like,
please no more pig. They give him some fruits and veggies and he tells this story. That's more
likely because otherwise no one would know. That's why it's called Tate's Hell, but we don't even know
if any of that is true. We don't know. I believe that that family existed there. Obviously,
I don't think the state of Florida was like, and then a magical man showed up and placed a curse
on the family. There's elements of it that are probably true. I.e. there's a Tate family there,
but as far as like the magic being cast or the snake bite, I'm sure again, the snake probably
did bite him. I don't know why that's the most fantastical element, but you have this story.
Now, but people don't even know if that's the reason. This is why there's a dispute because
some people say that's not the reason why it's called Tate's Hell. So it could just be a story
that's made up to match the name Tate's Hell because there's actually another version of this.
There's another version of this story. There's no year for this one, but we'll just assume it's
old timey again, 1871. This is on the other side of the swamp as Jebediah and Seb are waking up
and saying good morning on the other side of the swamp. There's a fisherman named Tate. This is
his only name. He's like Prince or Madonna. His name's Tate, and he goes missing in the swamp,
and people are like, oh man, what happened to Tate? Dude, that guy was super dope. He also owed me like
five bucks. I was going to go buy all this swamp land, but these other people bought it instead.
Dang it. And then after a couple days, Tate, the fisherman, shows up out of the swamp, and he's
like, guys, you won't believe what just happened to me. So I was fishing in the swamp. Really bad
fishermen. I don't know why. I thought I'd catch some toads that day. And then I got to the middle
of the swamp, and I saw her. And they're like, what? I saw her, and he's like, yes. It was a giant.
I saw a giant woman walking through the swamp. But now at this point, all the men put down their
newspapers, and they're like, tell me more. Was this woman clean and bathed? He's like, no,
because she lived in a swamp. But she may not have been clean and bathed, but she was hot and
bothered. And people are like, ooh, they're fanning their self with their newspapers. And
all the ladies have been dismissed from the bar, which I'm assuming is where this story is being
told. Tate says, guys, listen, so I was fishing in the swamp. I saw this giant lady in the middle
of the swamp, and she saw me, and I feared for my life. Plus, my pants got a little tight. And
sure enough, that giant woman plucked me out of the boat, tore my clothes off, and banged me
for the past couple weeks. Right? I've been missing this whole time, right? I've been having sex with
a giant. People are like, first off, people are like, where exactly did you see this again? We
want to mount an expedition and get mounted ourselves. He says, yeah, that seems great and
all. And I did have the best sex ever for a week or two. But look at me, and he's like,
now everyone's noticing he's super thin. He's all emaciated. He's like, the sex wouldn't stop.
Like, sure, I could grab a handful of swamp water here and there. And if a tadpole was in it,
I'd get a little protein. But she wouldn't stop banging me to the point where she sucked all the
energy out of me. Now, apparently, in that swamp, there was a legend of the Timucan tribe. And they
were native to that area. And they said that these natives were seven feet tall, that they were giants.
But even that's up for dispute, because apparently that's based on skeletons
that were like five foot three. And they go, well, this is, this must be a toddler. This five foot
three one must be a toddler. So we're like a, you know, second grade or whatever. So they extrapolated
these giant natives. But there's never been really, there's never been any conclusive proof
of giants in the, in the world. There's lots of legends and there's lots of fake photographs
that are going around in the 1800s. We've covered it multiple times on the show. I'll put an episode
in the show notes about the Smithsonian destroying giants. I don't want to get too way late on that
one. We've covered it multiple times on the show, but that was the story. So people were thinking,
well, maybe it was true. Maybe there is a lost member of this tribe who was looking for some love.
And here is this lucky, lucky fisherman. He's shaking his head. He's like, I was not lucky. I
was starving. I was starving the whole time. And the other people were like, we will take
our, they'll just bring back that. So just bring granola bars with them. And they'll just lay back
and they'll have like one of those hats on with the two soda cans sucking it through the straw.
And they're like, take me baby. So that's the story of Tate's hell. That's also the end of the
episode. I'm not going to be able to get to the UFO story. This episode went on really long.
I want to give these stories time to breathe. So we'll do the UFO story on Monday. So Liam,
let's trudge out of this swamp in the middle of this, in the middle of the grove of dwarf cypress
trees. There is the carpenter copter, Spick and span. Liam, go ahead and climb into the cockpit
and get us up, up and away from this army of pigs and slowly advancing on our position. Go,
go, go, go, go. Helicopters flying off. We each got a pig though. So we each got a little pet pig
from this episode. And we each got a mail order bride. She's not a want a mail order ride,
but you got one. Now we're not just flying away for any good reason, then we'll escape from the pig
army. Liam, take us out of this stratosphere. I want to get this carpenter copter as high as it
can. It has the anti frost coating on it. We're now floating over the earth in the carpenter
copter. And I want to end the episode like this. You know, on earth we always talk about these
special locations. Sometimes they're blessed locations, holy locations. Sometimes they're
cursed locations like a haunted house or spooky cemetery. The grove of dwarf cypress trees actually
could exist in between those two. It seemed to be the source of the medicine man's powers.
It was the one place where he didn't want any visitors to go. It could also be the
font of eternal banging by a giant woman, but again she doesn't let you eat, so you know,
you gotta pick your poison on that one. Is it worth it? Who knows. But I was saying about this the
other day. We have these locations on earth that are mystical, that can give you power or curse you
to hell. What if earth itself is one of those locations? Hear me out. Whenever we look at
the lore involving aliens, they're always here for some reason. Either they're here to keep an eye
over us so we can join the galactic brotherhood, which I'd rather not. That sounds super lame.
Or they're here to sap our resources, take our water, take our minerals. That one never really
held much sway with me other than being a big fan of the miniseries V. I always thought there's more
water or you could easily go to a planet that has ice caps and melt the ice caps fairly easy with
nukes and things like that, instead of going to a planet that's populated by a bunch of monkey
barbarian warlords who want to use their weapon who make movies about killing people from other
planets. Like what would be easier? Drop a couple nukes on a planet like Mars that has massive
ice caps, or come down and engage with the species. As much as I love us, we are quite brutal species.
No one is the human race. Then these are the idea of them using us as cattle they're here to enslave
us or eat us. Again, the best thing is to not have a food source that can kill you. That's why
we grow wheat and domesticated cows. That's why we're not a species that lives on tiger and bear
meat. So none of those really held sway with me, none of those really made much sense to me.
But what if the earth is special? It's just not a rock, it's just not the third rock from the sun.
It's a mystical location and an otherwise mystically dead universe. Just like you can have
the entire swamp surrounding this area, but this grove of trees is special compared to the rest of
it. What if the earth itself is a mystical location? When we look at very rarely when we look at
stories of aliens, very rarely do they mention religion. And I don't think I've ever come across
the story of aliens practicing magic. Of course there are stories where it seems like they're
engaged in magic, but it always goes back to their technologies just so advanced. I don't think I've
ever come across a story where an alien is actually like "oh no, let me pull a rabbit, let me pull a
rabbit out of this space calculator." They never talk about magic, they very very rarely talk about
religion. How many holy leaders have we had visit this planet in just the past 2000 years? Maybe
this planet is the anomaly in the universe, maybe life is abundant, but we're the only planet in the
universe that has this mystical connection to something beyond the physical. Earth may be,
universally speaking, a grove of dwarf cypress trees in the middle of a swamp.
It's just an interesting theory, and yet another reason why earth is the most amazing place in
the universe. I'm a little biased because I live here, I exist here, but I truly think it is.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address,
so you can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio Twitter. You're like "what's the wrong with
joining the Galactic Brotherhood?" It's lame. DeadRabbitRadio at DeadRabbitRadio is the Twitter
thing. I always lose track of this. DeadRabbitRadio is your daily paranormal conspiracy and true
kind of podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great weekend guys!
[Music]