Did Russian cosmonauts see angels flying in space? The truth may shake up the
paranormal community forever. And then we travel to New York City to take a look
at a bizarre crime spree that happened in the 1930s. Who is 3x and what is the
red diamond of Russia today on Dead Rabbit Radio? Hey everyone welcome back to
another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a
great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Let's give a shout out to
our newest Patreon supporter Caleb. Caleb thank you so much for supporting
the show that really really helps out a lot. You are awesome, really really
appreciate it. Everyone all the other patrons are like you never called me
awesome. You're all awesome. Caleb's awesome but all of you guys are awesome.
Thank you so much for your support. Still sending out those Dead Rabbit Radio
stickers. I'm gonna be revealing the design soon. You guys are gonna be like
"Oh I got a support Patreon" because these stickers are dope. These stickers are dope.
Caleb, but Caleb we are actually going to take a new vehicle. I don't think we've
used this before. I think I just made it up now. We're gonna do a slow motion walk
or in our spacesuits and there's like NASA voices. You know NASA voices they're
like 10, 9, 8, because you know normal people don't count. Only NASA people.
We're in the rabbit rocket. We're like "Uhhh" it's like G-forces and stuff. We're
leaving behind the Earth's atmosphere. We're blasting off into space. We're gonna
go to a Russian space station known as "Salute 7" dead rabbit rocket. You
don't want a vehicle that has the word dead in it. I just realized that the
rabbit rocket though it breaks away of the coil of the planet Earth. The planet
Earth is shaking its fist at us. I'll get you one of these days. I'll get you on
reentry. We're like gulp. We're floating around space. We're back in the year 1985
and Soviet space station "Salute 7" it's in low orbit. Low Earth orbit. Now up
there there's six cosmonauts just chilling, running scientific experiments,
doing wedgies on each other. I do... that'd be actually so funny. Now that I
thought about that you should have a movie where there's a bully on a space
station. So you have like this guy who's so muscular his suit. You know the suit?
Space suits are all baggy. His muscles are bulging out of his space suit. He's
just beating up nerds. James Wan make that happen. I know you listen to this
podcast. I know you do. If I was one of... if I was an astronaut I'd totally be a
bully ruining all their experiments. They're like what? I didn't know that
Space Mold had mustaches. I'm gonna draw on it with the Sharpie. There's a reason
why I'm not a scientist. So anyways, but now we are. We're docking with this
"Salute" space station. There's six cosmonauts up there. One of them is Oleg
Atkov. Just floating around and then they see like this orange gas floating
outside of the space station. At first they think they're all going to die.
What's going on out here? We shouldn't be seeing orange mist outside the space
station, but then suddenly the mist forms into shapes. Each shape is about 80 feet
long. These massive shapes. They end up seeing seven angels. Hold on. Don't
shut the podcast off yet. Caleb's trying to hotwire the rocket to get out of here.
He's like this story's lame. Hold on. Hold on. I know it's completely
unbelievable, but let's just keep going with it. And actually I'm sure a lot of
you guys are like, "Oh, Jason's covering this. I've seen this story on
ancient aliens. This is a real popular story." That's weird. He normally does
weirder, more obscure stuff. Hold on guys. Do not panic. Do not panic in the space
station. There's a reason why I'm doing this story. So anyways, as lame as it
sounds, these angels are floating in space and the Russian cosmonauts are like,
"Oh!" They reported back to Earth. They call up the Soviet Union on their rotary
phone in space because it's Russian technology. It's not the most advanced
stuff. There's a wire going all the way from the space station to the
Kremlin. We just saw some angels up here and they go, "Nyet! Do not tell anyone
else about these things of the phone." That's pretty good impression, right? You
guys like that one? Another group of cosmonauts ended up coming up to the
space station and the Oleg and his buddies are like, "Hey, yeah, it's pretty cool. You
can float around and give people wedgies. It's hard to do a noogie in a space
helmet." But we found a way. They have a little mechanical arm that doesn't...
But there's also a bunch of angels. There's lots and
bunch of angels that will show up and the cosmonauts are like, "What? We weren't
briefed on that." And then soon enough with the new cosmonauts up there, there's
this orange glow outside the space station. Angels show up. And NASA had
intercepted this communication. They had their own phone line going right to the
White House. NASA had intercepted this communication and their thing was like,
"It must be some sort of mass hallucination. There must be some sort of
oxygen deprivation going on in the space station." Something, because that's
impossible. So NASA was looking into this and then some NASA astronauts have also
said they've seen some weird things up there. The story is extremely popular. I
found it originally on a non-alien. A non-alien is a website I go to all the
time. I also, Mysterious Universe, covered it. Ancient aliens did a segment on it. So
it's been covered a lot. I normally don't cover stories that are that wide known.
The reason why I'm covering it now, because it is an interesting story. Angels in
space, it does sound super cheesy. But the reason why I'm covering it is all these
other sources have covered it. I tried to be more obscure. I was able to track down
where this story came from. The earliest mention that I could find in
print was a book from April 1st. April 1st, 1996. This book, that was when it was
published. I don't think it was published on that date on purpose, but there's a
book called Moments with Angels. Spectacular encounters with heavenly
heavenly messengers. And you'll see the book in the show notes. Not the book
itself, but the link to buy the book. And in this book contains this passage, quote,
"According to the Weekly World News," and then it tells the story that I just told
you. If you don't know what Weekly World News-- half of you guys, I think I heard the
face palm. If you don't know what Weekly World News is, imagine the-- here's some
other headlines from Weekly World News. Idaho Man stricken with potato feet.
They covered the Bat Boy, Bat Boy saga. Bat Boy was found in a cave. Bat Boy joined
the military. I think Bat Boy ran for president at some point. I was Bigfoot's
love slave. That's a famous Weekly World News. It's fictional news. Fictional news.
So it's made up. It's made up, dude. And this story's been going around for years.
This is what's so funny about this. I've heard about this story years ago.
Ancient aliens, they had got all their experts together. They did reenactments.
It would be the equivalent of ancient aliens doing an episode and they'd be
like, "And some people still believe that this school houses both witches and
wizards to this very day." Then you have like some reenactment of some fourth
rate Harry Potter wannabe flying around and then you cut to a talking head and
he's like, "Well, you know, magic and mysticism go long back into England's
history. It's fake. It's so fake. I don't know if I'm frustrated or having a ball
with this." Because I've heard this-- I cover a lot of obscure stories. I'm sure a
good portion of you knew this story before I even talked about it. It's fake.
It's 100% fake. 100% fake. And it took me 20 minutes to find. You know what the
key was? It was like on one of the articles they had a photograph or like an
illustration I looked at it and I go, "That looks like that was from the Weekly
World News." I read the Weekly World News growing up. I thought it was hilarious.
That's from the Weekly World News. So I did a reverse image search. It wasn't
pulling up anything. So I had to do the typical thing where I just go back to
find the farthest back reference to it. And I found that book and it said-- I did
a little Google book search for the inside of the book and it said, "According to the
Week--" No! Because of course you want it to be true, right? As cheesy as it is.
First off, I'd be like, "How come the Soviets get to see the angels and not the
Americans?" Because come on guys, right? We don't have telephone wires going from
Earth to the space station. But that aside, that ethnocentrism aside, the
story's fake anyway. So I'm actually glad it was so, you know. It wasn't John Glenn
or Neil Armstrong. It's in this Oleg dude. It's on his Wikipedia page. Like, it's
like-- he actually invented all of this. Like, he has all these patents for like
these devices that allow open-heart surgeries to go by much easier. On his
Wikipedia page, it says that he saw angels. That's ridiculous. It's hilarious.
It's hilarious. But guys, really, Mysterious Universe, Anomalien-- I get it.
When you put out a ton of content, you're gonna make mistakes.
Mysterious Universe and Anomalien-- I get a lot of stuff from them. A lot of their
stuff is good. Neither of those articles had an author's byline on it. So I'm
wondering if the author figured out, "Oh, wait a second. This isn't true." And then
had their name removed. That's possible. The Anomalien article was-- a couple points
said, "This does sound ridiculous," but they kept going with it. I get it.
Both of those websites post stuff daily. I get you have to churn stuff out. I've
done stories that turned out not to be true as well, like Lone Pine Devils,
Civil War of the Worlds. I've done stuff that turned out not to be true, but I'll
correct it when it's brought to my attention. But I'm not gonna say, "Oh,
Mysterious Universe, you suck." Anomalien, you suck. When you're throwing a hundred
darts at a dartboard, you're gonna miss from time to time. They might want to
run corrections on it now. They don't have to pull the article down, but they
can say, "Hey, we found this out. Ancient Aliens. Ancient Aliens has a dedicated
team of writers and editors. I hope. Maybe I'm wrong, but they have a dedicated
team of people that-- that to me is more inexcusable. Mysterious Universe
website, they have a couple writers. They're always looking for content. They
put out a lot of good stuff. You're gonna make mistakes from time to time. An
Anomalien, it's the same thing. You're just looking for content. You're gonna
get hoodwinked. But they're not these multi-- I mean, come on, dude. By the time, at
some point when the guy playing Oleg, when the-- when the guy doing the
reenactment for the Russian cosmonaut, he should have been like, "Wait a second.
This story sounds really, really dumb." But then again, Ancient Aliens, the
producer of Ancient Aliens, may have turned him up and go, "Have you ever seen this show?
It's all dumb." I always rag on Ancient Aliens and just to back it up, you guys
might be a huge fan of the show and that's totally fine if you enjoy that
show. It's totally fine. There is a YouTube video. I'll have to put it in the
show notes. There's a YouTube video I refer to all the time called "Ancient
Aliens Debunked." It's three hours long, but it has timestamps so you can click to
the stuff that you want, like goblitepke or whatever you say, pyramids, like the
Nazca lines. You click on what you want and the guy has done his research and he
goes, "This is what really happened." In fact, it was from a guy who loved Ancient
Aliens. It was his favorite show. He had a little penant that said "Ancient Aliens."
And then one day, he realized that they told him a lie. They said, "Yeah, we'll pick
you up at five." And he's out there and it's raining and it's 6.45 and there's
still no car. He's like, "Ancient Aliens." He realized they said something that wasn't
true and he started researching a lot of their claims and realized that wasn't
true so he made this three-hour long YouTube video. Check it out. If you enjoy
the show, whatever, like I'm not a snob. I definitely think it's
interesting, but this story, I don't believe it, but this story is 100%
fake. It's from the Weekly World News, so I feel bad for Oleg. I feel bad for Oleg.
It's on his Wikipedia page. If one of you guys wants to go change it, I'm sure he
would appreciate it. His ghost or if he's still alive, but while you are
changing Wikipedia, we're gonna take this rocket back down to earth. We're gonna
sneak in though because the earth still wants to beat us up. We're gonna come
around to Australia. We're gonna fly nice and low. We're actually taking the
long way around the world because apparently that's how that works. Now
this story, I never ever heard of this story and you guys know I always like to
give credit where credit's due. Or bash on people when they get something horribly
wrong. This is from a Reddit user called Trailwentcold. Trailwentcold is
actually also the name of this user's podcast. It's a true crime podcast called
Trailwentcold. I haven't listened to the podcast, but this is a really good write-up.
Wanted to give them credit for this. Okay, Lib, let's hop out of the rabbit
rocket. We are taking off in the carpenter copter again, flying nice and
low over the ocean. The earth is still looking for us. We're flying low over
the ocean. We're headed to College Point, New York. It's June 11th, 1930, and we're
flying to a Lovers Point. You know what they call it? Like Lookout Hill or
Lovers Point or Makeout Mountain or whatever. You know where people, Lovers
Lane. That's what I was looking for. It's the place where you go to like make out and
stuff, kiss people. Not because you can't do that at home. Well they couldn't. This group
of people couldn't. Joseph Mosinski. He's 39 years old. He owned a grocery store.
And he's married, but she's not in the car with him at Lovers Lane. No, instead
we have Catherine May, a 19 year old girl. He's been having an affair with her.
So the sun has set, the earth is asleep, we're able to evade detection, the moon
is high, they're just sitting there in the dark. Because I don't think they had car
radios back then, right? I think you still have to have the giant piece of wood,
wooden radio in your living room. So they're just sitting in a car having to
talk to each other. They're not even talking to each other. They're in the back
seat, they're making out. And then outside the car, it's not a guy's sandpapering
some wood down. It's a stranger walking up alongside the car and he knocks on the
car door and Joseph jumps up. Totally scared. This wasn't supposed to happen.
He was supposed to make it out with his 19 year old lover. Instead there's a guy
standing there and he tells Joe, "Get in the front seat." But in a German accent, I
can't do a German accent. In a German accent, he tells Joseph to get in the front
seat. Joseph gets in the front seat, Catherine stays in the back. Joseph is
waiting for the next command, "Pop! Pop!" Two bullets enter his head. He falls.
Now Catherine's in the back seat. She's completely panicking, but before she can
even take in that her lover had been shot, the back door opens up, the man
climbs into the back seat and rapes Catherine. After he's done, he orders her
out of the car and says, "I will take you to the bus stop." So they walk to the bus
stop, they get on the bus together. So now the bus is driving through New York.
A murderer, a rapist sitting next to a young woman driving through the city
streets. Eventually they get to the bus station and the man gives her an envelope
and says, "Do not read this until tomorrow." She gets on another bus like they
took him to a bus terminal, a main bus terminal. She had to take another bus
home and once they separate, she opens up the letter and it says, "Joseph
Moisinski 3x3x097." Now while she's riding the bus, she remembers something.
Catherine remembers something because she just looked over at her notes.
Like I just did and I forgot this detail. When she had a flashback, when she was on
the bus, she looks over and she sees the man, the stranger, go through Joseph's
pockets after he killed him. He pulls some pieces of paper out of Joseph's
pocket. He's kind of looking at him. He's kind of like, "Ugh." Then he crumbles him up,
sets him on fire, throws him on the ground, and then we come back to the present
day. Now she's all alone. The dude dropped her off at the bus station
and just walked away and she's taking the bus home. She doesn't go to the police.
She doesn't go to the police because she's honestly, and this is the way
sometimes people act, yeah she just saw a murder and she was just a victim of a
horrible crime herself, but she didn't want her parents to know she was with a
married man. She figured, "Well, if I go to the cops, that will come out, so I'm
just gonna keep my mouth shut." But that's not really how crime works, right? You
don't always need the testimony of someone because what happens is the next
day people are up at Lever's Lane and they see a car parked and they're like,
"Whoa, he's here early," and his brains are all over the car and they're like, "Ugh."
So they call the cops. The cops go out there and they're checking in on them. It
doesn't take long for the cops to trace him back to Catherine May. So they pull
her in for questioning and they're like, "What happened?" She starts telling the
story, she shows them the note, and they don't believe her. The very most they
think she might have set him up and this note is supposed to misdirect him from
the crime, but they don't believe her. They don't believe her story at all. It
does seem very far-fetched. Now, they hold her for a long period of time. They're
constantly interrogating her trying to get her to break, but while they're
interrogating her across town, the New York Evening Journal, it's a local
newspaper, they get a letter. And the letter starts off with this quote,
"Kindly print this letter in your paper for Moyzinski's friends." Then there's a
bunch of coded letters and numbers. It goes on by saying, "By doing this you may
save their lives." And the women may know where the missing papers are and who has
them since they were given to Moyzinski. We do not want any more shootings unless
we have to. Signed 3x, the man behind the gun. The letter was actually postmarked
before the body was found. So the police know that the letter, whoever wrote the
letter, knew about it, but it doesn't totally absolve Catherine, right? Because
this could just be part of her scheme to kill somebody and get away with it. So
they're still questioning her. The New York Evening Journal does not publish the
letter though, so they get another letter. And the other letter explains, "Listen,
Catherine May had nothing to do with this," which would actually make the police
more suspicious because why is this guy saying, "Oh yeah, I killed and it may kill
again, but she's innocent." Again, I think the cops are still thinking, "Catherine May
has something to do with this." But the second letter says, "Listen, she had
nothing to do with it. Not only did she have nothing to do with it, Joseph
Moyzinski was super gross. He was banging six other women and two teenage
girls, a 14-year-old and a 15-year-old." He goes, "Catherine May is innocent and this
dude is no saint to begin with, so quit trying to act like he's some victim." He
is a victim, a murder victim, but he basically deserved it. It's kind of what
3X is saying, and now he's making his case. He actually has, in this second
letter, he goes into really what's going on here. He says, "I am an agent of a
secret international order, and when I met Moyzinski that night, it was to get
from him certain documents, but unfortunately they were not in his
possession at the time." And then he goes on to have this coded message, and he's
saying, "If anyone knows where these documents are, we're going to need them."
And then eventually the note ends with, "These papers must be returned to us at
once, or 14 of Moyzinski's friends will join him. Moyzinski's relatives and
friends have up to Monday, 12 p.m., to bring these documents to us or to have
someone get in touch with us and tell them where to find them. If no answer is
received by that time, we will start merry hell for all of them." And then he has
his normal signature 3X, the man behind the gun, and then there's an inverted V
and a regular V. All that stuff happened within a five-day period, because by the
time June 16th 1930th rolls around, we have Noel, Noel in OEL, Noel, Noel
Soutley, 26-year-old radio mechanic, and his girl, his main squeeze, Betty Ring, 18
years old. They're on a floral park neighborhood in New York. They're making
out. It's big news about this guy getting killed, because you're getting letters
written to the newspaper, everyone, it's super intriguing, it's sexy, they
don't know about the rape, it's not reported in the newspaper, but like, "Ooh,
who's this man behind the gun? Who's this mystery man?" So Noel and Betty must have
known about this, but what are you gonna do? You're gonna go to Lever's Lane,
footprints up alongside the car. Guy pulls out a gun, 3X, as he'll be named
from now on, pulls the gun out, points it at Noel, and asks him for his driver's
license. So Noel pulls out his driver's license, and at that point 3X is looking
at the driver's license, puts it down, and pulls a flashlight out and kind of
clicks it, shining the light off into the tree line, and then he turns back to
Noel and he goes, "I'm letting my friends know I can do this one alone."
Odd detail. 3X asks Noel, "Do you know who John Moisinski is?" And Noel says, "No."
And before he can continue to deny that he knows this guy, 3X shoots him in the
mouth. Noel says, "Plades with them, I'm not the man you're looking for." 3X
shoots him again, killing him. He begins going through Noel's pockets just like
before, and he pulls out a piece of paper and he looks at it and he goes, "I have it!"
Puts it in his own pocket and then sees Betty sitting on the other side of the
car. He begins to walk around the car and he approaches Betty. Now the rape was not
reported. Betty doesn't know what may happen, but she probably didn't have to
read on the newspaper to gather the intent of this guy. Plus he just murdered
someone. I think she kind of knew what was coming. As he's getting closer to
her, she actually has on this religious necklace and she kind of holds it up,
almost like warding off a vampire. And 3X changes his mind, leaves her alone, but
does escort her to a local bus stop and they both take a bus to the bus station
and they go their separate ways. He does give her a letter as well, and on the
letter it says, "Sowley 3X." Again, a total targeted kill. He just pulls out the
letter and hands it to her. She goes directly to the police. She goes directly
to the police. And the police are looking at all this stuff and they're like,
"There's no way that a 39 year old grocery owner and a 26 year old radio
mechanic are part of some sort of international intrigue, spiring. It's a
super ridiculous. Like this guy is either picking people at random and then
it's some sort of magician. He can just pull stuff out of his pocket that has
someone's name on it. Or these are targeted killings like mob hits and
this is a cover story. At this point they've let Catherine to make go, but
they're like, "There has to be something else going on here." When they go to the
crime scene and they find Noel, the police go through his pockets and they
find an article about Joseph's murder. On that article the name Moisinski is
stamped on it and in the margin someone wrote, "Here's how." The police are
looking at each other and they're like, "Are you serious?" So these guys did know
each other somehow enough that what it looked like was something, this is just
supposition that somebody sent Noel a news article warning him, which is
interesting to think of because then what Noel's like, "Well, yeah, I don't know. I'm
gonna go to Lovers Lane anyways. I don't care. No one's gonna keep me from
smooching my sweet thing." Someone sent you an article about someone getting shot
playing a pick-up game of basketball. I would just suggest not to play
basketball for a while, but anyways he went to Lovers Lane. He was killed as
well. Even in journals it gets another letter and it basically says, "3x is
starting to detail." It's a lot of coded messages. Like all these people have
different coded words and numbers, but it's basically saying, "Hey, thanks for
publishing my paper. One of these people came forward and gave me some of the
paperwork I'm looking for and I got $37,000 in money that had been blackmailed
from people and I'm gonna keep doing this stuff and it looks like we're getting
this all taken care of." And then on June 21st they got one more letter. Even in
journal got one more letter. It said, "The last document, NJ 4344, returned to us
on the 19th at 9 p.m. My mission is ended. There is no further cause for worry."
And then in a theatrical gesture it decides to let everyone know exactly what
was going on. He goes on to explain that he does indeed work for a secret
international order. This time he names it. It's called the Red Diamond of Russia.
And he said, "Part of his signature with the inverted V and the regular V," he goes,
"Those were symbols in and of themselves. The inverted V symbolized the
supreme tribunal of the order and then the regular V was the secret agent. You
put them together, it forms the form of a diamond. They didn't have emojis back
there. This is about as complicated as you could get. Upside down V, regular V."
He says that Joseph and Noel both were members of the Red Diamond, not just
affiliated, not just owing a money or stumbled across them and this was their
way to keep them quiet. They were actually members of the Red Diamond of
Russia and they committed treason against the group. They'd actually sold top
secret documents and were blackmailing people with them. And they started their
own little ring. It was them two and fourteen other people who were blackmailing
people with this information. And so they had drawn lots and 3x had gotten the
winning lot to go to America and retrieve these documents. He says, "My job's done
though. My job's completely done. Any other letters signed 3x are fake. I'm
going back home. I'm done." And it was true. They actually did get letters after
that, but the police in the evening journal were like, "No, these aren't from the
original 3x." No one was ever caught and the police have always still been
scratching their heads over how real this story is. Because, I mean, first off, they
interviewed the families and families are like, "No, they had no ties to any
sort of international crime ring or spy ring or nothing. That doesn't make any
sense." I could understand a 39 year old grocery store owner. Maybe at some time in
his past had gotten involved in something and then retired and tried, you
know, doing something else and maybe took some documents with him for his
extra payday. By the time he's 39, you've usually lived a pretty full life.
You've pretty lived a pretty diverse life. At 26, so that'd be really hard to
pull off. To join, to find, join and then leave a spy organization within a short
amount of time. Like the FBI, the CIA, they don't, I mean, other than a
specialized agent, they really don't even want to talk to you until you're out of
college. They want you to get a lot of life learning under your belt. It's not
like they're scouting out high schools. Now, of course, CIA, FBI agents, do they
have underage agents? Absolutely. The FBI actually now they say that. They may not,
but I'm sure the CIA has had agents that were 14, 15 years old. I would be shocked
if they didn't have those. But, I think the FBI seems more investigative stuff.
CIA does a lot of more undercover stuff. So you would need someone who was 14
years old sometimes, or maybe they can just get an adult. It's not like doovy
houses are working for the CIA or Webster. Let's go on an adventure, but first,
clack, clack, my gun ready. Just in case we run into any weirdos. It would be weird
that, and it's also like, if they were in the Red Diamond of Russia, that they had
come up with this plan together. They just, the age and the skill level
difference, you know, grocery store owner versus a radio mechanic. They just seem so
vast. So the police have always been kind of scratching their heads, and they go on
one hand, he could have just been this guy wanted to murder these two people, and
created this elaborate backstory. They could have been highly targeted
killings, and this was the backstory the guy went with. Maybe it was a thrill killer.
Is this really any different than the Zodiac? This is basically just the
Zodiac killings with extra steps, right? This is having that writing the code and
messages, but this guy's built up his own mythology, his own world behind it.
The Zodiac wasn't popping out letters with people's names on it, so that's a
different thing, but the idea of writing the letters and building up the myth
behind the man. Otherwise, it's just two people who got shot at Lovers Lane. But it
could actually be that the Red Diamond of Russia is a real organization, and I
say is and not was, because if a group like this existed, I would imagine they're
still around today. I would imagine they're still around today. So I think it's a
pretty clear thing. If you're working for a secret organization that has no
problems sending killers out to take care of business, don't steal from them or
try to blackmail them or any of that stuff. First off, I want to get involved
with them in the first place, but secondly, if you decided to, when there is an
opt-out clause, take it and don't walk out with a filing cabinet. Just be like,
"See you guys later. I will go now work at my grocery store. I will blackmail
none of you. Bye guys." And that's the conspiracy story, but also I think it's
interesting on a meta level, just as a story level. And so I want to take a note
here real quick to explain this part of the thing. So because other people have
probably heard of this story and or you could follow the show notes. If you
read the articles of the time, it never mentions the rape. It never mentions the
rape of Catherine at all. I only saw it in the Reddit post by Trail went Cold, and
I was doing my research and I was looking this and I go, "That's weird because it's
only in this one Reddit post." So I actually messaged Trail went Cold, because
this is how you do research, ancient aliens. This is how you do this, okay? When
you come across things that seem off, you have to track down the source. I go, I
need some clarification on the rape issue. I'm not seeing that anywhere else.
And Trail went Cold said, "The detail was so scandalous that the
newspapers didn't report it." And I was like, "Okay, that's interesting." And then I
verified that as well. I found a book from the 1940s written about this case,
and it also said that she, you know, enough time had passed they had said that
Catherine had been raped. So it's an interesting side note, and it also
tinges the story a bit. Because as we get more into the story, you're gonna be
like, "That's it! Like this guy seems quite noble. He seems like he might act..." Oh
yeah, but he raped a woman. Like it's really weird. If you read the story
without the rape, it actually has a more of a...
a noble revenge type of thing. A man on a mission type of thing. But the
rape really tinges. It's really weird. I mean, I'm not saying that the killing's
okay, but it's just a weird detail. And I think that part of the mystique, I think
at the time, even the mystique that this killer builds up, wouldn't have been so
endearing if it was... if that detail was readily available. So is the Red Diamond
Arrest just still in operation? Are they still out there just minding their own
business until someone crosses their path? Or is it a group that has more lofty
goals? I always say a lot of times people claim the Illuminati's running the
world, or this ethnic group is running the world, or this political party's running
the world, or whatever boogeyman you have. I always think the more realistic
thing is you have thousands of small groups constantly vying for control, and
there's allegiances, and betrayals, and things like that. And these groups are
constantly trying to take over from other groups, and eventually conquer the
world themselves, but no one's even come close yet. I think that's far more
realistic, and I honestly far more frightening, because when you have a
thousand groups fighting for control, that's just unmitigated chaos. It's kind
of what it always feels like. But when things feel crazy today, things have
always felt crazy. There's always been these groups fighting for control. So if
the Red Diamond of Russia still exists, and they most likely do, they're
still out there making moves. They're still out there sending agents. And again, if you
work for one of these groups, the last thing you want to do is piss them off,
because not only can they take you out, because that's kind of what they're
known for, they can do it in a way that you will never find justice. Your killer
will never be caught. If this guy wasn't sending letters, it would just be too
random murders and a rape on a police blotter. No one would have thought twice
about it. But the Red Diamond of Russia wanted to send a message. He tried to
blackmail us. We will do whatever it takes to silence you. And that message was
heard, and it's still being heard 70 years later. People are still talking
about this story. Whether or not the group ever existed, or whether or not it
exists today, it's definitely become a legend in the true crime community.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up
at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio. Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime
podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it
today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]