Honey that was once used as a weapon of war and we take a look at UFO sightings interfering
With our military maneuvers today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I
Hope you're having a great day. I'm having pretty good day. It's 98 degrees. I'm recording during the day again
But I have a sore back so I have a heating pad on my back. So my back is probably closer to like 105 110
I think I told you before that I made my own back ointment with the
It took a I think it's called a dragon pepper or devil's tongue or something like that. It's one of the top two hottest peppers
Scorpion maybe
anyways, I
Took one of those and I squished it into a bucket of been gay and just like mushed it around
And so I've been used I've only used it a couple times because it's pretty intense obviously what's interesting about it
Is you rub it on your back? You don't feel anything like normally when you put on an ointment on your back you feel stuff immediately
This one you rub on your back. You don't feel anything and then you rub it on your back a little more and you still don't feel anything
And what happens is you get to a point where well I did I put it on my back
I woke up. I didn't get much sleep last night. My back was hurting
Because I'm sleeping on the couch, but that's another story
and so
I'm walking to work. I have this ointment all over my back
I need to come up with a name for it, but I'm walking to work and I begin sweating and my back's on fire
It really has to be water activated for it to work. So it's kind of an interesting
Interesting little little thing little thing going on, but yeah, I just got some muscle pain in general
I think I'm just not sleeping well or whatever
So we got some really good stories for you today
One of them is actually off of that conspiracy list I often reference and it's one of the ones that people have always kind of laughed at
And just the name of it. They're like what that's stupid. That's totally made up and I went and looked it up and it's real
It's actually real
There it's made today. It still exists today. So a lot of stuff on the conspiracy list
I think is word salad just a couple words put together
But some of it I found some documentation for some of it what happens is it gets a life of its own so
Someone will throw something on the list and then people will then work backwards to try to find a conspiracy for it
And that's always interesting too because whether or not the story is true sometimes is irrelevant
It's the fact that the story exists in any way the cylinder man is not a true story
But it's an interesting fun story and the fact that it has become a
Quote-unquote true story. It's become a myth of our times the story behind slender man is more fascinating than slender man
himself
And so I think when we go deeper into some of these conspiracies, we're gonna run into those things
I'm going to
Make a quick plug for a product. It's not I'm not getting sponsored by this, but I use it all the time
And it's something everyone uses all the time, but this is phenomenal
So deodorant and here's the thing I think a lot of people get this mixed up
You don't just need deodorant you need deodorant anti-perspirant because they're two completely different things
I think a lot of people get them mixed up deodorant just coverage up any sort of smell you're gonna have any perspirant
I don't know if I'm saying that right, but any perspirant keeps you from sweating
And I get that you know some people don't like to use anti-perspirant because it
Blocks the pores in your armpit and so you can't secrete
The the you know toxins you're supposed to but I like to use both. I don't like to just buy a deodorant or an anti-perspirant
Why would you buy an anti-perspirant and not a deodorant? I can understand if someone just got the deodorant, but anyways
Old spice wolf thorn
Is the best deodorant I have ever had it's a little it's probably about 380 of
For just one bar of it. I think it's called the bar
It smells great. It works great. I've never had any trouble with it
Doesn't stain any of my shirts old spice wolf thorn if you're looking for a good smelling
Effective deodorant that's the one and I've tried and I think everybody has and I've tried all sorts of stuff
And sometimes I want to save some money
So I'll buy like the two pack of arm and hammer deodorant, which is okay, but it's just doesn't I don't really like the smell as much
It's effective in what it does, but and it kind of stains my shirts, but old spice wolf thorn
I know that totally sounds like an ad and it kind of is I'm not getting paid for it, but it's like my favorite deodorant
I love the smell of it. It's just super efficient. I kind of gone on for that for a bit now. Okay, so
We'll go ahead and get started on this episode here
Sponsored by wolf thorn deodorant. No, I'm joking. I'm joking
So I came across some interesting stories and the food based one is actually
The conspiracy the one that's on the conspiracy list
It's one that a lot of people have requested a lot of people have questions its existence
They thought it was just something funny that someone put in the board and that is mad honey
So mad honey is actually a real thing and it's manufactured today
It comes from turkey
now
Mad honey kind of got its reputation
Because of an event back in 67 bc
I wasn't able to find any sourcing for this story
This is from an article that you all post below and I was hoping to get some more detail on this actual battle
But I wasn't able to so in 1960. I'm sorry 1967 in 67 bc these roman soldiers were invading
the black sea area
and
The king the the king in that area king. Let's see how much I butcher this king myth right dates myth redates
Knew that these roman soldiers are just going to plow over his troops
This is the turkey region region what wasn't called turkey back then. I don't believe but anyways
The he sees that these roman soldiers are coming through and he's like how am I going to take these guys on they're very well trained
You know, we got a good army too, but
We've got to take care of this. You don't want to have to fight them in an open field
So he ordered his men
Hey
Go get some of that mad honey, and I want you to break off huge honeycombs of mad honey
And it's actual honey, and I want you to just drop it
In the area leave it around so as the troops are marching they'll run into it. They'll find it
Now you're a soldier. It's 67 bc. You're not you know an army marches on its stomach
There's no snicker bars back then you're getting a little hangry
You want to kill some turks, but you're also just kind of hungry right now
And you look down and you see a big red honeycomb laying on the ground
Looks delicious looks kind of like a pomegranate. Maybe you're hoping maybe it tastes like one so you pick it up
Take a big bite of it. Hmm. Dude. This is this is like honey
This this tastes delicious and the other roman soldier goes oh man here. Let me see that glass devias or whatever
Oh, you know what I found out too
that the
roman word for sheath
Means vagina
So if you back and if you traveled so basically a vagina is just the latin form of saying the word sheath because it makes sense
You're kind of like putting
Your your your quote-unquote sword into a sheath
So you're gladius into a vagina
So if you traveled back in time you would hear a bunch of roman soldiers being like oh man, where's my vagina?
I left it at home
I got to go because otherwise I can't carry the sword all the time. No here borrow my vagina. It's a little worn out
But it'll fit your sword. Oh, thank you. Thank you
favius
anyways, so
I'm sure that ruins the narrative
The narrative immersion of my well crafted story here, but anyway
So these the roman soldiers with vaginas at hand taped to their waist
Are walking through they're marching through this
path to invade to take on the turks
And they keep finding chunks of this red honeycomb and oh man. This is delicious
Eatin it
having a good time
And then the side effects kick in
First a couple of the soldiers
Get a little nauseous
A little sick
Some of them are complaining about blurred vision. You can't see anything really well
Then the hallucinations kick in they see the god Saturn fly across the sky
Throwing out rose petals at their feet. They see two squirrels
Playing ping pong or the roman equivalent of ping pong back then
Their vaginas begin to talk to them. Hey put a sword in me
And in the midst of the nausea blurred vision and general unwellness not to mention the
Crippling hallucinations the turks showed up and slaughtered
slaughtered the romans
So what is mad honey?
Mad honey is actually
Honey create obviously, but it's some honey created by bees
that
Are let loose in an area that has
A bunch of uh rojijeron
So it's these flowers. So what happens is even today the turkish beekeepers in the area
They'll create their regular honey
And then they'll load up their big boxes of
Bees and they have to hike them up this huge hill where that's where all the rojijeron things are all the rojijeron
I know i'm not saying that right, but
rojido
den drawn anyways, so they take them up there and
Bees can pollinate those type of flowers really anywhere, but up there. There's no other flowers around
So every bit of pollination the bee gets it's from those flowers. They go back to their beehive
And they the one of the chemicals in those type of flowers is a hallucinogenic
So the bees basically are making hallucinogenic honey
In turkey it's considered to have a lot of health benefits and that's why people still still make it
It's very expensive too. I think it's like 120 dollars a bottle
And you can order it online if you're so inclined. However before you do that
We'll get to the health warnings soon enough if the nausea and hallucinations didn't
Didn't get you
But in turkey it's kind of a cultural thing where oh you're sick. Just take a scoop of mad honey
Oh, you're you know lethargic take a scoop of mad honey a little depressed. It's a scoop of mad honey
If you just take a scoop you're fine, but it's very easy to overdose on it can actually kill you if you take too much of it
So it starts off and it low blood pressure irregularities on the heartbeat
Nausea numbness blurred vision fainting potent hallucination seizures and death in rare cases
So it's nothing to be toyed with
and this article
It was a very interesting article this reporter goes to turkey and kind of talking to different people and a couple of them
Are like oh a couple of other people from the west are like, yeah, I really want to get some mad honey
I can order it online, but you never know what's going to be in it could be fake
This is kind of like the holy grail of honey
I wonder if bees pollinate marijuana. It doesn't have to be a flower. I wonder if they could cross breed a flower
and marijuana
And then bees would pollinate marijuana. I don't know how does marijuana grow its seeds, right?
Seeds fall off. So maybe that's different, but do bees pollinate sunflowers because those have seeds too
anyways anyways
So they're making this honey over there
And you can buy it and it's you can buy it from a shop there
But they don't really advertise it because again if you're in turkey, you know where to get it
They don't want a bunch of westerners coming over taking three scoops
Flipping out and calling themselves the messiah as they run down the street naked and on fire
And it basically causing the government to regulate their business
They keep it on the download they keep it under the shelves
Every so often some you have to have a friend who will introduce you to the right shopkeeper
And they usually keep it under their counter
Fascinating and again, you can order it online, but you don't know what you're getting
So mad honey
Very simple
Um, it is a it's such a lesser known conspiracy that it shows up on the conspiracy list
It's actually fairly easy to find I just googled mad honey
A lot of people are like, what is mad honey? This is fake and it maybe maybe it was a little more than googling it
I think it it took me maybe like five ten minutes, but it wasn't hard at all
And I thought it was fascinating that it was it's basically a
Biological weapon
You can use it against an invading force and they don't know what they're into it takes very specialized
It's like only can grown a certain area like you can't have a bunch of other flowers around
And I always think that's interesting. So like how did they first discover this like who was the first guy?
Who saw a cow and goes, you know what?
Yeah, I'm drinking out of that udder
Who at what point in human history because I mean someone had to sit there and go man, you know what my sons
Drinking from my wife's boob
And that calf is drinking from that cow's boob
Ergo, I should be able to drink from that cow's boob
Like you you had to have a chain of events a chain of decisions to get there
And the same thing with this, you know
That there are beekeepers in the valley for a thousand years
And they're like making honey and stuff like that and since they're like
Some guy shows up
Charles Charles the Turk shows up and they're like get out of here, Charles. You can't put your beehives here
This whole area is taken. He's like fun. I'm gonna go somewhere else
So he climbs up the hill to get away from all the bullies and he puts down his beehive and he's like, okay
I think I'll put him up here
And then he starts noticing his honey's red and he's like, oh, that's a waste
It throws it out and then more bees they make more honey and it's red and he's like, what am I going to do with this red honey?
I'll taste it and he takes a bite and he's like
Oh
Oh, this actually isn't that bad even though it's red. It tastes pretty good
What do you think bee goddess and the bee goddess is talking to him because he's having horrible hallucinations
And then from that point on somebody said, you know what I bet you this has some health benefits
Lowering blood pressure is a health benefit. I don't see really see how blurred vision is a health benefit, but
It's that that chain of events had to happen
I mean, maybe they found a red just beehive one day and they're like, hey, let's take a bite out of that and see what happens
But even then that's weird to get to the point where they're manufacturing
Mad honey and they know enough about it that they can use it effectively against an invading force
It wasn't just a fluke. Nothing's ever a fluke and I think that a lot of times when we look at society or world history
we jump from
We jump to like point
12 the point 12 was being mad honey exists. We don't know who found it. We don't know why they found it
You know same thing with shaman
Who are like take this bean and put it in your ear and then blow out your left nose while chewing on an onion root
And it'll get how do they know all that stuff?
More importantly, how do they know which stuff in the
Forest is not poisonous
Shamans are like, hey drink this but don't drink too much or you're gonna die. Like how do you figure that out?
ayahuasca things like that the
You think evolutionary wise someone would have found it eaten it died and then everyone else would have been like no not doing that anymore
That's what animals do
Animals eat plants and they keep dying and then they go they evolve to where they're stop eating that plant
So it's weird how we just jump we skip whole parts of human history and it's just like oh this exists
humans drink milk
And who was the first guy was like, mmm that white mucus coming out of that udder that dirt covered mud covered udder
Yeah, i'm putting that in my mouth
Fascinating because somebody had to do it
somebody had to do it
Our next story
We're gonna go in the completely opposite direction
from
I can't think of a pun
From bees in a box
To ufo's
Yeah, I got nothing. Okay, so I always saw this was an interesting story. I it's one of those stories that
It's one of those stories that you have to take a lot of stuff on faith like mad honey can be tested
So there are some stories like dovelyn wisconsin, which they really has no backing information the town that disappeared
And we we run into those fairly often then there's stories that have some backing information
And that's eyewitness testimony first person eyewitness testimony. I was there
And then you get stories where it's like third person then you get stories that are like
Very well documented this story kind of falls into that area of the first person. So we have to
Assume these people are telling the truth if we're going to believe in this story
If you don't believe that they're telling the truth the story completely falls apart
Because the government has said now it's not happening
But you know again when you ever you're building a conspiracy you have a group
You have a factor in it as a group that people don't normally trust which is the military
so
This is the idea and this kind of plays into a couple of theories. I have with aliens in general
And I've heard this story. I don't think this story will come as a surprise to anybody
Maybe some people I guess if it didn't come to a surprise to anyone I wouldn't cover it
But we've been having a problem
With our nuclear bases
United States nuclear bases now they're scattered across the United States when I was a kid
I actually was told that there were certain skyscrapers in New York that had no nothing in them
They were just a nuclear missile and they built a building around it to hide it
And I don't really think I believed that I think it's an interesting
scenario
But I would be the point of having one nuclear missile in New York ready to launch and
Hidden in a building
New York's getting nuked anyways. It's not like it would be a total shock
It's not like you'd like be able to save it for after the war or something like that
Anyways, that was an old urban legend and there's at least one or two buildings in New York City that have a nuke in them
It's a kind of an empty shell of a building
so
We have what we do have nuclear bases across the United States
back in the 60s
They were having reports the u.s. Air Force was getting reports from servicemen
saying
There's bright lights in the sky
And our nuclear weapons deactivated
Air Force command is like what are you talking? What are you talking about?
Oh
Servicemen there's bright lights in the sky. We see them
They come through the perimeter
And our missiles just get deactivated. So of course Air Force. It's like you guys are nuts. That's not happening
And these kept popping up these stories kept popping up
One of the stories we have a witness. It is Air Force captain robert salis c a l as
He was at maelstrom air force base in montana
And
He hears
So this that basically the security the base security tells him
That we have a problem. There's some bright lights very high up and they're moving into our perimeter
So everyone's freaking out. They don't know what's going on
This is you know, not necessary. I guess it's like the height of the cold war 67 1967
You see these bright lights moving overhead
And what are you going to do you're going to open fire on them? You don't know what they are
You don't know if they're us. You don't know if they're russian
You don't know if it's uh
Even if it's us if it's some sort of shadowy group, you know, who knows they don't know so they're not going to just open fire
and what happens is
10 of the icbms that
captain salis
Had control over
Just all deactivated
They all shut down now this testimony. He didn't give this in a smoke filled apartment while he's sitting in his recliner
And you know with an iron lung counting these days down
This is part of the disclosure project where he was at the national press club
And they had a bunch of people coming out. I think the number was over a hundred of
previous soldiers previous airmen
A military personnel who were coming out. So this wasn't just him saying this
Yeah, well, he taught okay, so here's an interesting
This is funny
So what I just said I just said 120 airmen and servicemen were testifying about this
and then
I the reason why i'm leaving this part in because I think this is important when we're talking about any stories like this
I stated that as a fact. I read it on this website earlier. This is the actual this is the actual information
so
Okay, so here's here's what it said. So from what it looks like salis was at the
National press club and I have watched footage of this and i'm going to post it up as well some other servicemen
But originally I said there was 120 servicemen part of this
That's not true. So hastens the ufo researcher robert hastens said he has talked to more than 120 former service members
Who have seen ufo's near where nuclear weapons are stored and and tested
Some of these incidents involved ufo's deactivating nuclear missiles
So now we're talking third party again 120 people did not join the disclosure
pro
120 people did not
Join the disclosure program a man who makes his living
Researching ufo's has talked to 120 people and they confirmed his story now. I'm not throwing
I'm not saying he's a liar or anything like that, but
The amount of proof the amount of evidence changes drastically versus 120 people coming forward
Versus one person saying i've talked to 120 people because at best
He's telling the truth and he did talk to them, but at worst he's making it up
He's misinformed
He's exaggerating and all of those things and i'm not going to say which one is which because I don't know
But I think it's interesting because and it chalk it up to my ignorance
But I think it's important when we talk about conspiracy theories and paranormal stuff
That too I watch a lot of these conspiracy videos and I listen to these podcasts and they will make blank and statements
A very very common one is no one can go to antarctica. I've heard that multiple times
No one can go to antarctica
Nobody can go to antarctica and I heard that on maybe two different podcasts in maybe the span of three or four days
I went home and googled that that is 100 not true
There's like no only seven nations can go to antarctica and there's this treaty that bans anyone from going to antarctica. That's not true
There are restrictions to going to antarctica. They don't want you to go in there and drilling for oil
But if zanzibar
Decided if they got their act together and had a good gdp
And got all their finances in order and began to explore and they said hey, we want to go to antarctica
There is no law preventing them from going to antarctica
If you have the money you can charge a complaint to antarctica
They may say hey, don't go super far inland because your plane is going to crash
But you're not going to get shot down by f-18s
It's flat out not true and I've heard multiple podcasts say you can't go to antarctica and and
They got their facts wrong just like I got my facts wrong and I almost just kept going and if you're listening to this podcast
And you never checked it out. You're like whoa 120 servicemen went to this one meeting and they all stood there and told their stories
And that's just not true. But anyways, let's get back on topic
I again, I'm going to call it out when I make mistakes too because again, it's important and then you know
They also quote a retired air force lieutenant colonel dwin amazon and again. This is important
He comes out and says oh I in 1967 I was in montana and I saw a
A message come over the wire saying nuclear weapons were disabled
Well, you know, again, that's third party. I get it that you're in the military and he may have seen that message
I'm not disputing
Some of the facts here. It's funny because as I'm reading this story and this kind of happened with
Um, and uh, what was the other consp- oh the titanic conspiracy is I'm reading this article
I've heard about this story for a long time and as I'm reading this article
I can feel like my skeptical
Vibes picking up. So we have this article
I read it over a few times. I'm very familiar with the story of
UFOs being spotted over military bases and UFOs shutting down nuclear missiles
But according to this story that story that I've been hearing for five to six years come really can be verified by only one person
And that is captain salas
Uh, lieutenant colonel aimson
arnson
Said that he saw wire message that it came through and then hastens is saying he talked to other men who have the story
But they've never come forward. So the story I've been hearing for five years really
Can only be verified by one person who says he was there when it happened
Is it possible that he saw bright lights come overhead? Yes. Is it possible that the nuclear missiles were deactivated? Yes
Is it possible that?
The air force obviously saying this isn't a threat. This isn't a problem now
I was kind of reading the story and I again I've heard about it. It's a fairly famous incident that they're doing this
And it's not only happened in america. There's reports of it happening in
britain and in
russia
But again, it's real sparse information. It's kind of the same level of evidence
But I was hoping to do this story about UFOs, you know
Flying over military bases and people were like, what is that and all of a sudden ring
Like a light comes down like I imagine like this is 1960s light
So the special effect is just a light fading on and off and people were like call the captain
Should we shoot it down? No, sir. Ba da da da. They're just kind of like looking at stuff
Their their vaginas are hanging off of their waist. The soldiers just still have swords in 1967 and they're looking up
and then all of a sudden like
Their Icbm's what's going on here get the
President on the line. We got to figure out what's going on
That's the story I wanted to tell
And maybe it happened. Maybe it happened just like my 1960
sci-fi movie brain wanted to have happened
Do okay here. Let's do this. Let's get this let's get this episode back into
Hopefully conspiracy land. Do I think this happened?
Man, I really just can't do I think this happened based on the information that I've read about
and this article
Well, you know here let's end it like this. I'm not going to worry so much about debunking it
I think everyone should go out and do their own own own information on this
The resistance of light. I don't have any problem debunking
There's some stuff that you just on the on the face of it is fake. It's fake. See, I think that's the difference
I don't think this is necessarily fake. There's some of the details could be mismatched and we only have like one real eyewitness
About this, but I do think this is interesting because when they talked to
um lieutenant colonel Arneson
He said
He he they the article ends like this. He has many questions about these sightings. He goes
Are they extraterrestrial? Who knows? Are they from other dimensions? Who knows? Are they from underneath the earth? Who knows?
Your guess is as good as mine
And I think that's how we're gonna have to wrap that story up because I can't come out and say this is 100 fake
I don't have
Then full knowledge based on that. I've done reading on this, but I
Don't have a full knowledge based on this story or on really anything
So i'm not gonna come out and debunk it. There will be other like the anthony bordain thing
I think that that was just a tragic event
And I'll debunk that
I don't believe that he was murdered
this story i'm going to put in the
I'm going to put it in the possible category honestly, and I think that when you have someone going, I don't know what it is either when you have a
Uh retired air force colonel lieutenant colonel going height
I don't know they could be from another dimension. They could be from underwater. Who knows your guess is as good as mine
Sometimes stories have to end like that
Sometimes stories aren't going to have conclusive evidence and they're going to have an alien footprint or a bigfoot hair
You're just going to have to go from that that might be true
Again like I was saying it depends on how much trust you you put into your source in the beginning
And I'll trust these gentlemen unless i'm given information that says otherwise
So I think we came back around on that. I was if I when I was going on there for a while
I was like, oh
Yeah, this story's a buzzkill, but no, I think it actually is hopeful because I think sometimes you can find
You do have to just say it might be your guess is as good as mine
It might sound like a cop-out answer, but I think saying if I had gone and said this is not true
That's being ignorant and if I said, you know what despite all my misgivings, this is 100 true
That's just being ignorant as well. They're just opposite sides of the scale
We're going to go ahead and end
This episode of dead rabbit radio right now
My name is jason carpenter you can hit me up at dead rabbit radio at gmail.com. That's a preferred method of
Communicating with me. You can also hit me up at twitter at jason o carpenter
We have our facebook group that is facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
Thinking about getting an instagram going on we have our youtube channel. That's under dead rabbit radio as well
And we're basically taking these episodes and cutting them into smaller little portions
So that's always nice to get a different audience
A different audience there and tomorrow we'll be continuing
Our food based conspiracy theories with a tasty yet tricky
story
Hope to see you guys back tomorrow. Have a great day
Yeah
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]