I'm gone for one week and you guys decide to blow up the planet.
One week. Was Kobe Bryant murdered by the Illuminati and the Illuminati used a Comedy Central cartoon
to warn us of the coming tragedy? Did that happen? Is a virus about to tear humanity apart?
At the very best killing all of us. At the very worst turning us into zombies.
And then both of those stories are quite tragic but in probably the most bizarre turn
in Dead Rabbit Radio history. Hawn's Warm Hat. A man, a friend of the shell. A man we have covered
multiple times. A man who believes that platypuses are actually CGI. That all monkeys are either humans
in suits or hand puppets. A man who believes that all except for a few, except for him,
a few others, that all men are women and all women are men. Hawn's Warm Hat. Actually,
his most insane conspiracy theory, kind of proven, in court. What happened this week guys?
What did you do? We'll explore all of that on this extra special current events episode of
Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a lot of stuff to cover so
we're gonna jump right in. I know we're really gonna get going with this. Now, the first story
we're gonna talk about here is the story of Kobe Bryant. Now, if you have been living under a rock,
if you said, you know what, Jason's not putting out any new episodes this week. I'm not going to
interact with any humans whatsoever until I hear Jason's sweet, sweet voice. Well, it's back and
you can come out of that rock to download this podcast. And let me tell you what happened to
Kobe Bryant. Because apparently you're like, "Wait, ooh." Yawning. You're like, "Oh man, I wonder what
Kobe Bryant's up to." That's the first thing you think of. Well, he's dead and not trying to make
light of it, even though I kind of chuckled. It's tragic. It's absolutely tragic. He's passed away.
A bunch of kids died. You're like, "Jesus, Jason, you could have let me get a little stretch and I
didn't know any of this. It was terrible." I remember one day my mom came to like, I was, when I first
moved up to Hood River, I was staying with my mom and my aunt. And because I was trying, when I was
like getting everything organized, like getting a place and stuff like that. And my mom comes downstairs
and I go, "Oh dude, did you hear? Some dude walked into elementary school and shot like a bunch of kids."
And she's like, "What?" And I was like, "Yeah, did you not?" It's like she was wearing her pajamas.
And she was coming down to get her morning coffee and I was like, "Oh dude, I think she woke up late
that day." The point, that's not the point of when she woke up. The point is I have a tendency to
deliver bad news as casual conversation. So, Kobe Bryant and his daughter and some other young girls
died. They were on their way to play in a youth girls basketball team. There was another basketball
coach on the helicopter. It was a big helicopter pilot. There's total of nine people who died in
this crash. They died flying through the fog. Horrible tragedy. So of course, horrible tragedy
famous person within minutes. Conspiracy theories started. Let's get into this Kobe Bryant thing.
Most likely what happened, helicopter crashed. Well, obviously that happened, but most likely
it was an accident. But I kind of want to like, I like going into this stuff and looking at
why the conspiracy theories start, why they become popular. And we're also, we're also going to do
this. We're going to look at these and we're going to offer our own conspiracy theories.
Because I, and not because I think they're true, because I like seeing how the, the putting is
made. Is that a phrase? I like seeing, it's just milk, it's just milk curdling, put a little chocolate
in it. I like seeing, there you go. You know how putting them in. I like to see how this stuff
works. So conspiracy theories start off immediately. One of the big things, of course, whenever this
type of stuff happens, it's the media making mistakes fuels the conspiracy theory. Up until
recently, if you typed into Google, when did, this is true. This was reported by USA Today.
Bastion of all media have to accept what they say because it's today. USA Today reports,
if you typed in when did Kobe Bryant die, Google lists January 26th, 2020, which is the exact day
he died, but they listed January 26th, 2020, date of assassination. So that's creepy. Now they blamed
it on Wikipedia. They said, we're pulling the information from Wikipedia and Wikipedia says,
you didn't get it from us. Glitch. So that's a legit, that I think I, I will put my cards on
the table. I think Kobe Bryant died in a helicopter accident. Now, now some of you guys are full
tentos deep into the Illuminati stuff, but I'm just getting out there. I think it was,
they were flying through fog. Every other helicopter was grounded. This helicopter got
special permission and it crashed. And that's why the other helicopters were grounded. If you want
it, if I was the Illuminati and I wanted to assassinate somebody, I would do it super publicly.
I'd have Kobe Bryant ready to make a shot and then he has a heart attack. And then you don't mess
with the Illuminati cause you might suffer from the leading cause of death in the United States. But
there's also the whole thing, the predictive programming, cause you knew it. You knew this
was going to happen. Apparently in 2012, there was a cartoon on Comedy Central that nobody remembers
that these little fat kids, not South Park. And in the cartoon, a helicopter crashed. Well, okay,
let me rephrase this. In the YouTube clip being sent around the internet, a helicopter crashes in
front of these three kids. Kobe Bryant is in the helicopter and he pops out holding two awards.
I don't know where they are. He goes, "Help me, help me. I'm about to die in a helicopter
helicopter explosion." They're like, "Give us the awards." And he goes, "What?"
Helicopter blows up. Predictive programming. The Illuminati predicted Kobe Bryant would die
back in 2012. They predicted he would die eight years before he actually died.
Years after he left basketball, he retired. He was going to die in a helicopter crash. Jason, how,
how can you dispute this evidence? Well, a couple different ways. One, the media is like chicken
bones at this point. There's so much of it. There is going to be stuff that matches. But here's my
question. This is what you have to look at when we look at it. This is really going to be the bulk
of this episode. We're really going to be ripping this stuff apart, ripping these conspiracy theories
apart. If you believe in predictive programming, that is the idea that the Illuminati or whatever
Satanic group of the week is controlling the world, before they do something, they have to tell us
they're going to do it. Stupid theory based on the idea that you can find clues in stuff.
Stuff has to happen first and then you can go backwards. My question, one, go through,
this is your homework, if you believe in this, go through all media involving Kobe Bryant and see
if there are any other jokes about him dying in any other way. If there is, your argument is an
ol' void. Absolutely. Two, what's the context of the joke in the cartoon? Three, was Kobe Bryant
famously known for taking helicopters? Now I'm not saying in the middle of the game, he's like
"see you later losers" and jumped in a helicopter and fly away. But, traffic sucks in LA. Apparently
that is a normal thing for people who are wealthy enough to fly helicopters around LA. It's not
like his first time ever flying in a helicopter. Let me say this too, this might sound kind of cruel,
but because Kobe Bryant had a lot of other people in the helicopter who died, but who was more famous?
Kobe Bryant or Michael Jackson? Now, Michael Jackson's death by the Illuminati, Michael Jackson being
an enemy of the Illuminati is long in story. They've actually thought about doing an episode on it,
because there's this whole conspiracy theory that Michael Jackson was fighting against the Illuminati
as much as he could in all the chivalrous station allegations was them pushing back against his war
against the Illuminati. That it was all made up and he was fighting the elites and they were
hitting him where it hurt the most, which is being accused of being a chivalrous. So, that's
it's a whole own episode, maybe, but that's a long, long conspiracy theory that's gone on for a long
time. Is there any predictive programming involving his death? Was there a cartoon on Comedy Central
where he's like, "He he, I'm gonna die in my sleep!" As a morally bankrupt doctor is pumping
him full of opioids? Was that, is that a thing that you can find? Is there like a predictive
programming thing where they show Michael Jackson just slowly falling asleep and then choking on
his own vomit? Just stop breathing and then there's a laugh track? No. Not that I know of. And his
Michael Jackson's career lasted longer than Kobe Bryant was alive. Michael Jackson's far more famous
than Kobe Bryant always been linked to fighting the Illuminati, been linked to being murdered by
the Illuminati before his comeback tour. His first comeback tour, like he was a, he, after the first
set of chivalrous station allegations, he was like, "Okay, that's done." He had this huge comeback
tour ready. He did a, his big show in Madison Square Garden. It was considered equal to Elvis'
comeback tour. His Elvis was just a pop star. He went off for a while. He came back, gave this
live performance, and then he became the legend. This Madison Square Garden show for Michael Jackson
was considered, they're like, "He's back. He's back." That show at Madison Square Garden,
September 10th, 2001. So his story has been closely linked to fighting against the elites
and the elites fighting back. Do I believe any of that? You'll have to wait for the episode that I
might eventually do. But my point is, is that celebrities die all the time and it's unfortunate.
Absolutely unfortunate. I'm not trying to make light of any of this stuff. But if predictive
programming is a thing, we should see it all the time. But Jason, The Simpsons, and 9/11, we should
see it all the time. But Family Guy and the Boston Bunk, we should see it all the time. Three or four
or 10 or 15 events spread across 20 years is not all the time. If the Illuminati is as powerful
as people make them out to be and are taking out these people one by one and that they have to show
what they're going to do before they do it, if you believe that, all media should be
predictive programming. That every piece of media should be a warning of a terrorist attack,
a celebrity death. It all should be that, but it's not because predictive programming is false. But
let's look at some of these things that people are saying specifically about the death of Kobe
Ryan. Kobe Ryan? I don't believe this, but some people, apparently people on 4chan, some of them,
some of them, pretty rational people, some of them are nuts, is Kobe Ryan a saint worshiper. Now,
apparently he's covered in tattoos. Can you believe that? A NBA basketball player covered in tattoos.
I know I was shocked as well, but apparently some of these tattoos may look satanic, they're not,
by the way. So, but apparently the person who posted this thread on the paranormal board of 4chan
goes, "Oh, does this guy look like a saint worshiper? Look at these tattoos." Now, he didn't have
like a giant pentagram on his stomach, on the back of it and say, "Goat" with a picture of an
actual goat. Just a bunch of tattoos. He's a basketball player. This is how the post started
off. Looking at his tattoos gives you the impression that Kobe Ryan sold his soul to Satan
in order to achieve all that wealth and success in sports. And then some guy, it goes on for a
while, and then some guy comments this, "Co- I love this. Kobe woke up at 3am every day to get as far
as he did. Don't try to diminish his achievements just because you're an impotent dolt." Which
makes me think that this guy is actually an officer in the Empire. He's currently serving
aboard a Star Destroyer. You dolt- People don't use that word enough. Just because you're an impotent
dolt, whose biggest accomplishment is jacking off four times in one day. First off, five times, sir.
Secondly, if I sold my soul to- This is a good point, right? Because if I sold my soul to the
devil, which I never would, it's not a good deal. But if I did, I would hope that I get all of the
fame and success with none of the work or very minimal work. Maybe I wake up every once in a
while to go to the set of my talk show that's streaming on Netflix. Now watch me get a talk
show streaming on Netflix. Everyone's going to think I sold my soul to the devil. But let's say
that I just, "Woooh, wake up. Go do a monologue. Talk to some people." If I got a talk show on Netflix
the world, definitely we're living in a simulation at that point. It would be a terrible show,
but you'd watch it. I would watch it. But anyways, the point is, is that I just interviewed-
I just interviewed Britney Spears every episode. The point is, is that I think it's implied by
selling your soul to the devil. You don't have to do any work, right? That would suck to sell your
soul to the devil. And you have to like work 80 hours a week to get anything done. You know,
you already have my soul at least give me some vacation time. But this guy says, "Listen,
dude. Kobe Bryant woke up at 3 a.m. every day shooting hoops, practicing, building up his body
and his mind to be a sports legend." And because he has tattoos, you think he's saying worship.
Now, reading that comment- I laughed because I knew exactly what was going to come
after reading that comment. I knew it. You might know it too. But if you don't, there's two ways
that this could go. People would go, "You're right. That doesn't make sense." He played basketball
and played it well, played it hard, practiced hard, probably didn't sell his soul to Satan.
That's what a rational person would say. A rational person wouldn't be reading this thread in the
first place, but that's what a rational person would think. An irrational person and the way that
this thread went after this guy's comment was 3 a.m. Well, that's the witch's hour. That's when
Satan's is most powerful. So the fact that he woke up at 3 a.m. every morning actually proves
he's a Saint-Worshipper. So thank you. You're the impotent adult for not believing, for not seeing
that connection. Why, I got a Comedy Central cartoon clip that I can show you that'll prove
everything to you. The thread then became, "He's definitely Saint-Worshipper because he wakes up
at 3 a.m." You know why people believe 3 a.m. is the witch's hour? It's because apparently Jesus
died at 3 p.m. So that makes that God's hour. As if God is relic. He's like, "Whoop, no miracles,
no miracles until 3 p.m." As if the Holy Trinity has to wait. It's like 359. It's like, "Oh, no,
time's running out. Better do this miracle. Better do this world peat." Ah, sorry, guys. Better
like tomorrow. Apparently, so Jesus died at 3 p.m., which again, there's no reference to that in
any sort of biblical text. Jesus was crucified at 3 p.m. or died at 3 p.m. That makes that God's hour.
So the opposite of 3 p.m. is 3 a.m. That's where the witch's hour thing comes from.
It's completely ridiculous. On multiple levels, one, it would all, if that was true, it would only
be the opposite hour in Calgary where Jesus was crucified. So in America, it would be like one in
the afternoon. There'd be witches flying around, goblins jumping out of manholes and all sorts
of stuff. Kobe Bryant practiced in there like, "Hey, that's weird. Why are you practicing at 1 p.m.?
You'll see." This is eyes glow, red. It's just stupid on its face. The idea of there's an opposite
hour. Like, why would God even... Why would God set up a system of time where he's like,
"Yes, I will create a 24-hour day, but I will create one hour where I'm incredibly weak
and the forces of darkness will rise up. It'll also be the spookiest time. It'll be when there's
no sunup and Kobe Bryant will practice that as well." Like, why would you engineer something where
you have a weakness? So the whole thing is ridiculous, but apparently Kobe Bryant practicing at 3 a.m.
is proof not that he's a dedicated or was a dedicated basketball player,
fact that he was actually a Saint-Worshiper. Also, here's this conspiracy theory. And this
is going on right now. Super Bowl is going on right now. I'm going to take a huge assumption and
nothing dramatic has happened because nothing dramatic ever happens with this type of nonsense.
But today, I'm recording this on February 2nd, 2020, there's a big thing that this is a paladrome
number. It only happens once every 900 years. No matter what country you're in, it's a paladrome
number. So whatever. Yeah, it's a math. A lot of this stuff relies on math trickery. The lowest form
of magic. You're like, "Oh, yeah, I picked a number and you guessed it to be 42 and you made me add
and subtract and multiply stuff. And then you made me subtract everything from my number, leave
me with zero and then add 42." Yay. Anyways, 2-2-2020. A Super Bowl 54 happens on 2-2-2020. It's the 33rd
day of the year. 333 days left in the year because it's a leap year. Kobe Bryant was
ritually sacrificed, not my words, ritually sacrificed seven days before 2-2-2020. And then
they also start talking about that Comedy Central cartoon. This is on 4chan as well.
Whenever people throw these numbers out about this type of stuff, "Oh, it's 33 days in the year and
33 days." It's always the numbers they don't include. How many years have the 49ers been playing?
How many years have the Kansas Chiefs been playing? Playing? They're ripping the full...
They're like, "I don't want to play them. They're ripping our flesh off." How many years have they
been playing? What are all the numbers on the teams added up divided by 33? Does it get 33?
All the number... If they include the number, it fits them. But if they don't include the number,
it doesn't. How many miles away from San Francisco 49ers training camp to where the Super Bowl is
being held at? You know what? All of these numbers that they just disregard, disregard. How old was
Kobe Bryant? Times? How long has Trump been in office? If it matched, they'd be like, "Bam."
So when people throw out numbers, you just go, "Well, whatever. Do these numbers match or
do these numbers match?" And so on and so forth. But anyways, so I do think Kobe Bryant was killed
by the Illuminati. No. Do I think that they predicted it on a Comedy Central cartoon? A
coincidence? Sure. But again, I'd have to wonder if there are any other jokes ever made in the history
of Kobe Bryant's career. Oh, and there was a tweet where it said, "Kobe Bryant's going to die in a
helicopter crash." Again, that tweet came out like in 2012, around the same time as the cartoon. So
I'm going to assume that Kobe Bryant has a history of flying in helicopters. If I died in helicopter
crash, it would be weird because other than the carpenter copter, a fictional vehicle, I never
get in helicopters. So it would be weird if the media started making predictions that they're like,
"And before we end the nightly news, podcast host Jason Carpenter will die in a helicopter crash.
See you tomorrow." That would be weird if I did. And I never flew in a helicopter. And the one time
I did it, crash. That would be odd. But someone has a history of taking helicopters all the time
and saying, "Hey, I got to get there in time. Fly through this fog bank. We'll get special permission
to go through this fog bank." People are going to say, "Dude, that guy's going to die in a helicopter
crash." Just like people say, "Dude, something Jason's going to die in a car accident." Or I get this.
Jason, one of these days you're going to get hit by a car walking on the street. I get that all the
time because I walk all the time at night. And people can say that all the time. If I get hit by a car,
they'll say, "I told them. I told them. If I don't get hit by a car and I live a long life and I end
up 80 years old dying in my sleep as I'm fighting two werewolves, I wake up just in time to shoot
them in the brain and they fall on top of me and smother me." People will never remember predicting.
I almost said in a car crash, always saying I was going to have to die in a car crash. So it's just
selective. But all that being said, I said people want to believe in this. People don't like to
believe in accidents. People don't like to think about it. So they're going with this Illuminati
killed Kobe Bryant. There's also been references to killing him was a way to divert attention from
the coronavirus. We'll get into that in a second. But let's build an actual conspiracy theory that
I don't believe, but again, shows how conspiracy theories work. Now, all this is about Kobe Bryant
being a Saint-Worshiver, Kobe Bryant being killed by the Illuminati. And I know I won over this briefly,
but Kobe Bryant killed by the elite because they want to cover up the coronavirus because that
worked, right? No one's talking about that. That was another conspiracy theory that was
going around. Those are sexy conspiracy theories. They involve Saint-Warsherpene. They involve a
faceless elite that's trying to destroy the world. It involves predictive programming. Here's a
conspiracy theory for you. I don't believe it, but here's a conspiracy theory for you. Killed by the mob.
Killed by the mob. Kobe Bryant either was supposed to fix a game,
not like recently he was supposed to be involved. He's supposed to talk to same young sports
athlete to try and get him to fix a game. Or maybe years ago he's supposed to do something and the
mob just checked their day planner and they're like, "Oh, we never got back of this guy." Mob killed him.
Organized crime. There you go. That's a conspiracy theory. But you know, it's not sexy.
That's the weird thing about it. Like when you hear that, you're like, "That's it." But wouldn't
that be a thousand times more believable than a Saint-Warsherpene elite group killed him seven
days before the Super Bowl for reasons and announced it in a cartoon, a Comedy Central cartoon,
or someone on the helicopter owed a lot of money to the mob or Kobe Bryant turned down something.
They're like, "Hey, we want you to do this criminal act." And he's like, "No way. I'm Kobe Bryant."
And I don't commit any criminal acts whatsoever. As I shift from side to side, the mob's like,
"We'll get you." Isn't that more believable conspiracy theory? But again, it's funny. It's
not sexy. I was talking about the conspiracy theory about Hillary Clinton eating babies.
To me, it's the funniest conspiracy theory. And I was thinking about it today. I thought,
it almost seems like controlled opposition. It's so ridiculous. It's so ridiculous on its face
that it almost makes you disregard every other conspiracy theory involving Hillary Clinton.
I heard the funniest thing today, the absolutely funniest thing today. I don't like to talk politics
on the show, but I have stated in the past, I vote for whoever makes me laugh the most. Like,
whatever can, whatever, when I wake up, because I think it's all, I think it's all phony. I think
local government is perfectly fine, but like national government, I think it's all phony.
And each time the other side goes, "We would never do that." And they had done that at the
previous administration. I've been seeing that since I started following politics back in the
80s. I love politics, but to me it's like professional wrestling. So I tend to vote for the person who
will entertain me the most when I wake up every morning. I found out that, so here's the thing,
let me back up here. So Hillary Clinton, there's a conspiracy theory that she eats babies, right?
Her and Huma Abedin eat children. Now, that's just, that's just probably one of my favorite
conspiracy theories out there right now. But it's totally, it's totally just so nonsensical. It's
almost like controlled opposition. Back in the 90s, they started the conspiracy theory of the
Hillary Clinton body count, where there have been, I think, like 47, 48 people connected to the
Clintons who have died under, to say the least, suspicious circumstances. Playing crashes,
suicides with multiple bullet wounds in the head. Epstein has now become part of the Clinton body
count. I think Trevor Noah asked her, "So how did you kill Jeffrey Epstein?" And she laughed,
because it's such a common conspiracy theory, the Hillary Clinton body count, right? The
Clintons, and Hillary Clinton specifically, will kill anyone who gets in her way. Now that, again,
the eating babies thing, that's a ridiculous conspiracy theory. The Clinton body count
is much more down to earth. It's not sexy. It's not super mysterious. It doesn't involve reptilians,
taking over the White House. It just involves someone who may or may not be so ruthless
and a quest for power that she's willing to assassinate anyone who comes anywhere near
destroying her. Seth Rich is part of the Clinton body count. Okay, I heard this news the other day
that, and now, and I don't attack politics, but I do have to say this honestly, this, okay,
I may vote just out of, based on my whole thing of voting on who would be the most entertaining for
me, I almost can't pass this up. If this is true, if this is true. Hillary Clinton apparently
might run for vice president. She might, she might, she might become someone's vice president. Now,
here's the thing. Here's the, somebody who has 48 bodies, possibly has 48 bodies under their
belt, right? Jim Wunders recently, Jeffrey Epstein, okay, I, I, do you know how big your balls would
have to be to have her as your vice president? Like, just out of print, every morning you would
wake up and wonder what Looney Tunes, Tom and Jerry type contraption Hillary Clinton had built
in the White House that day to kill the sitting president. Could you imagine being the Secret
Service agent assigned to protect the president, knowing that the biggest, possibly the biggest
threat to the president is the vice president? I just imagine every single day would be an episode
of Tom and Jerry, where she's just constantly running around with a giant mallet and acts,
sticks of dynamite, whatever it would take. I don't, I don't have the, I honestly commend anyone
who would have the balls to be, to be the president when Hillary Clinton is a vice president.
Because again, her eating babies completely ridiculous conspiracy theory, her being,
basically eliminating opposition, that's far more believable. That's far more believable. And
I would wake up every single day, like it was Christmas. And the first thing I would do is run
to the newspaper, run online, look it up, just to see what contraption she had built that failed.
They're like, today, today the president went into the Rose Garden and slipped on a bunch of marbles,
and nobody knows, and she's like in the bushes. That, that would be ballsy. That would be absolutely
ballsy. So hopefully she, hopefully she's somebody's vice president, because I would just, again,
I'm not saying I would vote for, I'm not saying I would vote for anyone who picked her to be
vice president, but I, I don't, I think, I think there would be a collective gasp in America,
and they'd be like, oh my, oh my, and she's just like, her shadow is, that whole, even the campaign,
you'd be like, oh dude, is she going to kill him? Is she going to kill him before they even have the
election? That would actually be pretty entertaining. Let's go ahead and move on to our next topic here.
Our next topic now, we're leaving behind the story of Kobe Bryant, we're leaving behind all of
those conspiracy theories. Right now, we are going to get into the coronavirus. Now, Sheenanigans,
Sheenanigans has hit me up before. I don't remember what specifically the story was. Let me look it up.
You know, you know, here's the thing. I just, I've, I'll be honest with you guys, I've recorded
multiple versions of this episode now. I've probably been at it for probably about an hour
and a half, honestly. I'm going to have to break this up into three episodes. I know you guys
really want me to get, you're like, no, no, I'm afraid the coronavirus is going to kill me.
Don't worry, we'll talk about that tomorrow and we'll do the Hans thing tomorrow as well. The
Kobe Bryant thing went on a lot longer than I thought it was going to. You know, but I, so I
apologize for that. Me, you know, it's funny when I listen to podcasts, I don't mind that they continue
onto the next day. What I don't like personally is bone, like, paid Patreon and you'll get to
hear the rest of the story. So I'm going to make an oath to you. I'm never going to do that. I'm
never going to do that. That bugs me. But that being said, you don't, you can't pay money,
but you can if you want. I do have a Patreon, but even if you don't, you'll have to wait till
tomorrow or even if you do, you'll have to wait till tomorrow because I've tried cramming everything
into one episode. It just doesn't work. So you got your Kobe Bryant stuff. I know that's what
you were all clamoring for. You got your Kobe Bryant stuff. And then tomorrow we'll talk about
coronavirus and Hans. Hans Wormhat is back. And before you guys ask, I have no idea why he goes
by the name Hans Wormhat now. I can't even begin to comprehend how that name, but Hans is back.
Hans is back. He's better than ever. And again, it's easier for tomorrow, dude. He, he, he,
he took the W. He got the win. I still don't believe in his conspiracy theories.
But he definitely does now because when it came down to a in court, in court, he got one of his
most bizarre conspiracy theories verified. At least, now I'm really teasing, at least this court drama
gave him so much ammunition that now I cannot wait for the next Hans Wormhat video.
But anyway, so if you don't know who Hans Wormhat is, you can check out episode, what is it,
think it was in the 60s. It was a recent classics episode, "Monkey Don't Exist." "Monkeys Don't Exist."
I recommend listening to that episode. If you do know who Hans Wormhat is, we'll have to wait for
tomorrow to explore that more. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also
hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day. But I'm
glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys. I'll see you tomorrow. Sorry for the tease.
Sorry for the tease, but it's just it didn't work all this one episode. Have a great one guys.
[Music]
[MUSIC]