A mysterious videotape is delivered to the US Department of Defense, and after they watch
it, they know the truth.
And then we take a look at a new conspiracy theory that's just popped up in the last
few months, who is taking children's movie trailers and editing in acts of violence.
And then we meet a farmer who's been dealing with a rash of cattle mutilations.
He is intent on finding the culprit and punishing them, but nothing could prepare him when he
comes face to face with the beast responsible today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having lots of fun doing whatever you're doing.
I hope you guys are on the right path making the right decisions.
First off, let's go ahead and meet today's legacy Patreon, a man who always makes the
best decisions.
Everyone give a round of applause to Nathan, he's all walking in that braggart.
He's talking about all his good decisions.
Nathan, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it, it's fine.
Just help spread the word about the show really, really helps out a lot.
Now Nathan, you heard that we have a slam, bam and episode today.
Nathan, I'm going to go and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command, we are headed all the way out to the 38th
parallel.
In 1996, the US Department of Defense is presented with a VHS tape.
They're looking at this and they go, who wants to put it in?
Now the ring wasn't invented, right?
Nobody knew about spooky video cassettes, so they actually had no problem.
They weren't finding some intern to watch this video tape.
They're looking at this video tape and it's written in Korean unsung heroes.
I'm like, what?
I didn't order this.
This wasn't part of my Netflix queue.
What's this doing here?
And the guy who brought it in goes, oh no, no, no, no, no, I probably should have introduced
it.
I probably shouldn't have brought in this tape and just sat down and just go, guess,
he goes unsung heroes is a North Korean crime drama, spy thriller.
And the department of defense is like, okay, I mean, it doesn't, it still doesn't give
us any remation.
We know the genre now and the guy's like, oh yeah, I don't know why I paused there.
I was, I was distracted.
I should have, he's a really bad agent.
They're getting ready to fire him.
He goes, this tape, oh, you know what, watch it.
I don't even think I can figure out the best way to say it.
Obviously, I can tell you guys are about to fire me.
So they put in the VHS tape and it's this 20 hour long soap opera slash spy thriller.
They're watching it.
He's all eating popcorn.
He's like, oh, this is my favorite part.
No, no, no.
And the department of defense is like, oh my God, 20 hours.
This is taking so long.
Wait what?
Willis, Willis, get the president on the phone.
We found them.
Now let's go back in time, May 28th, 1962.
We're at the 38th parallel.
The Korean War had been over since, well, it's not over, but basically the conflict
ceased in 1953.
So it had been nine years since anything had really popped off.
On May 28th, 1962, private first class Larry Abshire, he's a 19 year old kid.
He's getting corn marshals for smoke and weed and you're not supposed to be able to do that,
right?
So he's thinking, oh man, what, I'm probably going to get thrown in the brig and get kicked
out of the military and they'll probably wag their fingers at me.
Or, I mean, all that stuff, I can do all that stuff, slap on the wrist.
Or, and he looks across the 38th parallel.
Larry is stationed in South Korea.
He's very close to the 38th parallel and he looks wistfully across this landmine-struin
area or it could defect to North Korea.
I mean, how bad could they be?
So he runs through the minefield.
No one chased him.
No Americans chased him.
They were shocked.
They just let him go.
What are you going to do?
You're like, no, stop, wait for me.
I want to be thrown into that totalitarian hellhole.
You just let him go.
Well, not even that.
They probably knew he was going to step on a landmine at any given point.
They watch him run across the DMZ and he disappeared.
He was the first US soldier to defect to North Korea since the end of the war, which
is interesting.
He kept seeing that sentence and I thought, well, who was doing it during the war?
I mean, I get it.
A lot of times your government will run propaganda against the enemy, but I think now, 60 years
later, we still have a pretty clear picture of how North Korea is.
It's not a very fun place to be.
He was the first soldier to defect after the end of the war, but he wasn't the last.
Three other dudes did it.
One of them was worried about their father-in-law beating them up.
So again, I'm going to run across the minefield.
One of them was in trouble for forging documents.
These weren't huge issues, but for whatever reason, they thought, I'm going to try my
luck in North Korea.
Now they do get across all four of these guys.
You had James Dresnok, Jerry Wayne Parrish, Charles Robert Jenkins, and then we had Larry,
the first one to do it.
They all successfully get across the minefield.
What happens is, after a couple days, they start broadcasting on the live speakers.
"Hey guys, it's me.
It's me.
Good old Jerry Parrish.
And you know what?
I know that I was your favorite.
People are like, "Who the hell's Jerry Parrish?
We don't know this guy.
We used to hang out all the time.
You guys should come over here too and hang out more, man."
It's dope.
They got like Orange Fanta over here, and they got like, he turns over to his North Korean
handlers.
He's like, "What else do you have?"
And they're like, "We have cars.
They have cars.
You like cars, right?"
They got beautiful babes from all over the world.
They might be slaves.
They might be kidnapped victims, but they're from all over the world.
Why don't you come across this minefield and join us?
And these broadcasts are constantly being done.
And of course, no one knows.
This is like the dumbest thing, right?
Everyone knows that this is pure propaganda.
No one falls for this.
These broadcasts keep going on for a while, right?
They're on and they're being used in North Korea to be like, "Look it.
That's how bad America is.
These Yankees were willing to run across these landmines to get here."
That shows how awful it was.
They're like these celebrities in North Korea.
They're on magazine covers and all this stuff.
And that's all true, but after like the glamorous shoot, after they're like, "Jee, jee, jee,"
the guy's taking pictures and stuff like that.
And they're like, "Okay, get in your limo."
And then they walk out and the limo is just a guy with a machine gun and he's pushing
them down the street.
They're like, "Ah, this is the worst limo I've never been in."
They all four had to live in a shack.
And when they weren't having their pictures taken or at the DMZ doing like recruitment
tapes, which actually they probably just recorded them, right?
They probably got super bored, they had to sit in a shack, all four of them.
They didn't know each other before they came over.
They did not like each other.
They're constantly fighting.
Which is not something you should do if you're prisoners of war, right?
You should try to assemble together, maybe.
Because the guards are also beating them up and they're like, "Oh man, I haven't gone
beat up that much since this morning when one of my fellow countrymen beat me up."
When they weren't getting beaten or doing magazine covers or both at the same time,
they're like five fashions to wear when you're brutally bruised.
When they weren't doing that stuff, they had to constantly study the writings of Kim Il-sung,
the country's founder.
They had to do the struggle sessions, which is where they confessed their wrongs.
And all this stuff, the stuff that we see come out of these dystopian communist governments.
This captivity goes on and on.
And the government doesn't really know what to do with these guys because they are prisoners
and they are propaganda tools and maybe they'll be useful in the future.
So they're trying to keep them happy.
They're supplying them with women and then they steal women from other countries and
supply them with them.
It's a pretty horrible story overall when you have women getting kidnapped from Morocco,
kidnapped from Japan just to be these dudes' wives.
But what happened is in 1978, North Korea, we talked about this before, we did a whole
week on North Korea, they loved their film industry.
And in 1978, the government decided to make this 20-hour long series about spies in Korea
called Unsung Heroes.
And they go, "Well, we have all these great actors to be the North Koreans and the South
Koreans because it's about who started the war and the ideas the Americans did.
We have all these great actors, but we need some bad guys."
Just happen to be any Americans around.
And they got two of these POWs to be in the movie.
Charles Jenkins played a devious American who actually masterminded the Korean War.
And then James Dresnok played a guy named Arthur Cockstudd.
This is not a forno.
I don't know why they chose that name.
They had to have known what it meant.
Or maybe they didn't.
Arthur's like, "Oh no, this means bad guy."
And they're like, "Oh, that's cool."
He plays a POW camp commander.
And his role is so popular, like people love the character of Arthur Cockstudd so much
that when he's walking around town, because he is allowed at this point, like what, 15
years have passed, he knows all the stuff about Kim O Sung's philosophies.
They totally believe he's one of them.
They're allowed to walk around town.
People just call him Arthur.
People just call him Arthur, which happens over here.
I mean, I'm sure Dustin Diamond got called Screech at his funeral.
Like at a certain point, everyone's just going to know you by the name of your character.
But from the time that they escaped over the border, and those broadcasts started being
done, which were recorded at a certain point, the US government figured these dudes were
dead.
No idea that they were alive at all.
North Korea is a really, really hard country to spy on.
They had no way to know until 1996 a VHS copy of Unsung Heroes is smuggled out of North
Korea and the US Department of Defense goes, "Oh, at least two of these guys are still
alive."
The story ends depending on your point of view in a pretty depressing way.
I mean, if you're a North Korean, it's a happy ending.
In 1983, Larry Abshir, he dies of a heart attack.
And he was buried in North Korea and his tombstone says he was born in Yongyang, which is the
capital of North Korea.
In 1998, Jerry Parish dies and he had a wife and kids.
They are still in North Korea.
They weren't allowed to leave.
In 2016, James Dresnok died.
He also had kids that are in North Korea.
And this is brilliant, right?
Jerry Dresnok died.
Arthur Kochstead, I wonder if that's on his gravestone.
Arthur Kochstead died.
His children also entered the film industry to play villainous Americans.
So keeping in the family, Charles Robert Jenkins had the most interesting ending.
He died in 2017, but before that, his wife was one of the kidnapped Japanese women.
The North Koreans were constantly kidnapping Japanese women for usually sexual purposes.
His wife was one of them.
And the Japanese government found out about this.
The North Korea denied it, denied it, denied it.
But in 2002, they confirmed that they had done it and that they said, okay, we'll give
you the Japanese citizens back.
And because he was married to a Japanese citizen, he actually also got to leave.
He was the only person who died outside of the country.
The reason why I want to talk about that story, it went a little longer than I wanted to,
but I love the idea of lost media.
It's what this is.
You don't even know this show existed.
And it was proof that these men were still alive.
And how often, when you talk about lost media, a lot of times you're like, oh, Nickelodeon
produced a scary show and everyone who watched it that night thought it was too spooky.
So they never aired it again.
I mean, that's interesting.
We're not discounting that.
That's very interesting.
But imagine Nickelodeon made a show, Nickelodeon made a show and had four real life missing
kids in it.
The casting director turned out to be a big old pervo who was kidnapping kids off the
street and making them be Nickelodeon shows.
That would be, you know what I mean?
It's a different level.
It's a different level of things.
It's a different, so I really like that.
You have the lost media thing and you have the real world impact.
And we know if we ever have to go undercover as spies in North Korea, you know what our
codename is going to be?
Cock stud.
And that is enough to get the episode with an explicit tag.
And it's also the end of that segment.
Nathan, I'm going to go ahead and give you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're leaving behind a 30H parallel.
We're driving all the way out to an internet cafe.
Oh, it's South Korea.
We'll just go down South Korea.
The place is wired for all internet.
This second one's really short.
It's one of those mysteries I don't even really know what is going on.
Is it a mystery?
I don't know.
But it was brought to my attention again recently and I was like, I got to cover this
because it is really weird.
First off, I did a segment a long time ago.
It was episode 594.
Is IMDb a gateway to a parallel universe?
And we talked about stuff being found on IMDb.
That just doesn't make sense.
Now, I know that it's user driven and a lot of you guys emailed me.
I was like, oh, you know, people can put in whatever they want.
And apparently there's a joke where you put in the angry video game nerd as mass murderers
and psychopaths into movies.
So it'll be like a movie.
It'll be the peanut butter solution about the guy who eats too much peanut butter and
he can grow hair forever.
It's a real movie.
I saw as a kid.
You'll be looking at the cast list and it'll say angry video game nerd, whatever the guy's
name is, as Benito Mussolini.
And you're like, well, he wasn't in that movie.
So that's like a running joke.
And that was explained to me after the fact.
And I know what's user generated, but sometimes there's just these weird tidbits that you...
Who does this?
So there was a Reddit post from a deleted name.
I hate it.
Reddit is constantly just deleting stuff.
I have to archive all this stuff.
Basically they were saying there's this mysterious show in Mexico and I don't know what it could
be.
And they said I was watching this movie called The Frame.
I wanted to know more about it.
So went time to be and this popped up.
This television show called The Frame.
And the description of it is, quote, a haunted picture frame that show this stuff.
Okay.
This is where grammar is super important.
Quote, a haunted picture frame that shows all your inner sexual fantasies in 1876.
Unquote.
That's the synopsis for the show.
And you go, so does it show your fantasies?
If they were in 1876?
Like, is it your creepy sexual fantasies but everyone's wearing like old timey clothes?
Does it project whatever your sexual fantasies are back in time?
So someone in 1876 is walking by a picture frame and they're like, oh, not this again.
Ah, they're looking at some horribly disgusting thing.
I'm not accusing you of having disgusting fetishes.
Let me be clear.
But this other person, the other listener, not you, the person sitting next to you, they
have disgusting fetishes.
Like, is it your fantasies being projected into 1876?
Is it your fantasies turning into 1876 fantasies?
So if I had a fantasy for blondes, right, would it be a blonde in like 1876 dress?
I don't know.
So anyways, and also my sexual fantasies are pretty bland, surprisingly.
So when you look into it a little bit more, it appears to be, there appears to be a Mexican
television show called The Frame and it's hosted by Sofia Alvarado and it's a, like,
entertainment program.
Like if you look at it, they like did an episode on The Matrix and they did an episode on like
horror movies and one on superheroes and one about Lost and so on and so forth.
So who, what is that?
Like, I get it.
It's user generated and someone probably, but even like putting that together as a joke,
what's the joke?
I don't get it.
So I think just because I don't get the joke doesn't mean it's a mystery, but it is quite
bizarre.
But I had that locked and loaded ready to go and I never covered it because I just thought,
it's just kind of a weird thing, whatever.
But I wanted to package it with this one because this is another one I had ready to go months
ago and I thought, well, it's just kind of a weird quirky thing.
I don't know where to go with it, but it's popped back into my field of view.
There is a YouTube channel called New Trailers and a long time ago I watched this movie called
A Christmas Cancellation and I almost did a Dead Rabbit Recommends on it with a hard
asterisk because A Christmas Cancellation is an almost good movie.
It's not a bad movie, but you watch the movie and you're like, oh, it's such a good idea.
If they had a bigger budget, if the actors had more rehearsal time, if they had a better
set, they had all this other stuff would have been really good.
Really been super interesting movie.
I've seen a lot of movies like that.
Miranda Vale is the same way.
Miranda Vale, amazing concept and if they had just had some more time to work on it,
they could have got it.
Miranda Vale is about a woman who finds out she's immortal after a serial killer puts a
knife in her heart.
It's really, Miranda Vale is a really, really good movie, but it's raw.
Like you're just like, if you only had an extra $50,000, you could only afford a little
more rehearsal.
The actors work, but Miranda Vale, it was a super interesting movie.
She can't die and it's about the serial killer and this victim trying to figure out why.
I love stuff like that.
Very, very small sets.
I love that.
Christmas cancellations about a group of characters, one by one television characters
who find out their show's about to be canceled and when it's canceled, they'll cease to exist.
Very, very interesting premise and no one believes the other person until they bring
them into the bathroom because they go, you've never seen the bathroom, right?
And they're like, no, because bathrooms don't appear on sitcoms.
They go in the bathroom and the lighting changes and they're like, oh my God, you're right.
What is reality?
Really, really interesting movie, but it just wasn't there yet.
But anyways, I was prepping it for a Dead Rabbit Recommends.
I was really debating on whether or not to cover it.
So I went to go get the trailer like I normally do.
When I looked through the Christmas cancellation trailer, it starts off with a news report
about a guilty plea in a Westfield double murder.
And it talks about a mother and a daughter being murdered during home robbery and you're
like, what?
And then it shows the trailer completely uninterrupted.
And then at the very ending, it cuts to a segment from True Crime Daily, which talks
about an eight month old pregnant woman who's murdered, shot or something like that.
And then the emergency C-section, the baby dies and they cut to a shot of a baby in a
coffin.
And then that's the end of the YouTube video.
And I was like, what?
Now those incidents really did happen.
Like I looked them up, those incidents are real and I go, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
that's weird.
That in and of itself is weird.
And I thought, the movie is not, I don't think there's even any cussing in the movie, if
I remember correctly, because it's supposed to be a sitcom.
But I had a hunch.
I went to another video on that same channel, a baby reindeer's first Christmas.
It came out the same year, 2020 as Christmas cancellation.
And you go to start the video and the first thing you see is a man kicking a kitten, full,
full, you know, full, the kitten's flying, animal abuse, punting it across the parking
line.
Then it shows the trailer and then ends with the report of a man shoplifting a bird.
It's interesting because I saw that and it was shocking.
Obviously, no one likes to see animals getting abused or really anyone getting abused.
And I just go, that's weird.
I thought it wasn't a bot.
Like did something get messed up in the algorithm?
Was someone, someone couldn't be doing this intentionally?
What would be the purpose of that?
I built my notes on it though and then just never covered it and went into my maybe folder.
A couple of days ago, again on Reddit, a username Axelflunk popped up and they go, hey, I just
found this super weird YouTube channel.
This is deleted as well.
Stupid.
I hate Reddit.
They just delete stuff for no reason.
But anyways, this guy posted and he goes, I found this really weird YouTube channel
and his idea, and I didn't think about this, his idea was to be racist.
You go to watch these trailers and you're hit with these images.
He said that the images were black people committing crimes against white people.
I don't remember who was, I don't remember those details.
I do remember the guy who was kicking the kitten was black.
I do remember that.
I don't remember if the victims were white or black.
I don't remember that.
The kitten was just a cat.
The kitten was neither.
But the point is, I couldn't say who the perpetrators were, who the victims were, how racial it
was, so I don't know about that.
But, and I guess I could have went and double checked before I started doing the segment.
I didn't think about that until just now.
It's possible, right?
It's possible.
Maybe a racist influence behind this to show these crimes and then intersperse them with
children.
But it seems like when he posted that, I thought, it reminded me of a Christmas cancellation,
but I thought, what a small target, right?
Like, how, what a small, I mean, hey honey, let's go watch a Christmas cancellation trailer.
And I'm also, I'm also borderline racist.
I haven't gone all the way yet, but maybe one or two more news segments will push me
over the edge.
Like, it's such a weird target.
I think the video, the children's video and the dude kicking the cat, that's the most
egregious that I saw.
Like, because that's the most shocking.
There's no context, there's no like news report context on that if I recall.
It's just a guy kicking a cat.
And paired up with a children's video, that's horrifying.
So it's just so weird, I have no answer for it.
Or is it bots?
Is it someone picking these news stories to inflame racial tensions?
What?
It's, again, they're not putting them on Shang-Chi and the Ten Rings trailers.
They're not putting them on trailers that anyone actually wants to watch.
They're putting them on, if I had never seen a Christmas cancellation and had wanted to
recommend it, I would have never checked that trailer out.
It's just to my new target audience, that if it's a troll, it's really bizarre.
It could be the lead up to something.
It could be building up to something bigger, but for right now, it's just a bizarre internet
mystery.
Nathan, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Carbonercopter.
We are leaving behind South Korea.
We are headed all the way out to the Saga Prefecture in Japan.
It's January 4th, 1992, and it's late at night.
There's a farmer here, we don't have his name so we'll call him Toby.
Toby has been having an issue with some cattle mutilations.
Cattle mutilations are super interesting because it is the one paranormal phenomenon that everyone
believes happens.
The question is what causes it.
I guess crop circles kind of falls into it, but cattle mutilations, there's not anyone
going no, there's no such thing as cattle with their blood missing in their eye.
Even people who don't believe in the aliens or the satanic cult or anything like that,
they just think it's natural predation.
But with ghosts people go "no that's just people being crazy, there are no ghosts."
Or UFOs "oh no it's just swampcasts."
Cattle mutilations is one of those things that you agree that it's happening.
The question is what is going on.
What is something that physically is happening, but what is causing it.
But to Toby, he doesn't really care about the big picture right?
Cows are his livelihood.
A cattle mutilation would be the equivalent of someone wasting thousands of dollars of
food at your local restaurant.
Like it's very very impactful.
So he is looking for the perpetrator and he's going to take care of it.
So one night he hears his dog barking.
So he heads out into the darkness to investigate and he enters his cow shed and he sees inside
the cow shed.
A jellyfish.
Long tentacles coming out of its jellyfish body.
Now if you walked into your cow shed and there was just a jellyfish laying on the ground,
that would be a mystery.
You'd wonder how did that jellyfish get here.
But this jellyfish, I should have said this earlier, this jellyfish is floating.
You're like "why is he making the sound effects?"
There's just a dead jellyfish on some hay.
This jellyfish is floating.
So the tentacles are like hanging down and it's this jellyfish thing just kind of floating
through the shed.
And he's freaking out as you would.
This jellyfish is floating around your shed and he looks and his cow.
His leg is broken.
That poor little cow is a broken leg and the jellyfish is just kind of floating there.
And Toby is watching this bizarre scene.
And all of a sudden the jellyfish continues to float and just floats outside the shed
window and then vanishes.
That's the end of the story, right?
That's the end of the story.
And it's interesting because obviously, we don't know for sure, but obviously the idea
is that the jellyfish was killing the cows, was causing the catamethylation.
Now this story, I got it from ThinkAbout@Docs.com.
They got it from Jenny Randalls and Peter Ho in the book "World's Best True UFO Stories."
And Jenny Randalls, we've covered her a lot.
I have a lot of respect for her.
I haven't come across anything that's been out and out, fraudful.
And ThinkAbout@Docs.com has treated us very well.
As absurd as this story is, you kind of have to look at the pedigree of it.
Because catamethylation is something that happens wherever there's cattle.
And that's the big question, what is doing it?
I've always leaned towards the idea that it's humans doing it.
If it's not natural, because we've talked about that before, predation will attack the
soft parts of the body.
And I'll tell you right now, there is a big difference between completely devoid of blood,
completely suck drain of blood, or having nearly all its blood sucked out.
There's a huge difference between that, and really there's no scientific difference between
that.
What's nearly all their blood?
More than half?
Yeah, technically.
Whenever you look at these stories, a lot of times they'll say nearly all the blood is
removed.
And then when the story is repeated, it will be said "devoid of all blood."
There's a huge difference between the two.
But predation makes sense.
But outside of that, I don't see a reason why aliens would be doing it.
I think it's human action.
I think it's cultists.
Now, it could be all three, or really all four.
Could be the jellyfish scenario as well.
I don't think you can ever really say all of it is one thing when you're looking at the
paranormal, but the thing I love about the jellyfish is it adds such an interesting wrinkle.
And it would be something you're not looking for.
We're looking up in the sky for spaceships, or we're looking up in the sky for black helicopters,
or we're looking for the candles, the monks, and the robes walking around with their sacrificial
daggers and things like that.
But a jellyfish floating through a farm?
I mean, unless it was a super well-lit area, would you be able to see a translucent jellyfish?
This guy was kind of a white, a whitish color.
We've talked about creatures in the sky as well, sky beans, giant jellyfishes in the
sky.
So would it make sense that some of them are smaller and feed on cows, or are just animals
in general?
It just, again, adds another level to the mystery.
There's nothing we can definitively say that this story is true, or that this is the cause
of more than just this guy's catamethylations.
But why not?
And that's one thing that I love about the paranormal community, but also kind of bugs
me and we'll finish it up like this.
Some people always want to say, like, let's take Missing 411, for example, the idea that
people go missing in the national parks.
People will try to give one paranormal answer to all of it, being like, oh, it's secret
agents, super soldiers in the woods who can cloak themselves that accounts for all of
it.
But maybe not all of them.
Maybe some of them are natural, maybe some of them are super soldiers, maybe some of
them are bigfoot.
We seem to get locked into these categories.
And it's no fun.
Couldn't some crop circles be made by UFOs, some crop circles made by pranksters, but
some crop circles made by ghosts?
Why not?
Couldn't some catamethylations be done by these?
See these creatures, like honestly, if you went to a skeptic, they would think this was
the most unbelievable out of all of them, because you're introducing this new creature
into the food chain.
They'd go, yeah, maybe UFOs, probably not, maybe cultists, that's a little more likely,
but what?
They've got floating jellyfish that's even dumber than aliens.
But why not?
And this to me is scarier.
This to me honestly can be a little bit scarier than the cultists going after the cows or
the UFOs abducting the cows and skinning them and then dropping them back off.
That just doesn't make any sense to me.
Why would they, they just dropped them in the middle of the ocean.
Why would they drop them back off?
Why would they want?
Something that kind of makes, the cultists want to breed fear, right?
They worship the dark ones, they love fear, but aliens, you know, whatever, they may not
even believe in God.
We've had a lot of different discussions about aliens on the issue, but they just get rid
of it or vaporize it or dump it in the ocean or whatever, you would never find it, you
would just find cattle missing.
The jellyfish wouldn't have any motive, it would just kill it there, drink its blood
and eat its eyeballs there.
It's just like most animals don't try to hide their prey, they just kill it and eat
it and then leave.
And if this thing exists, would it ever stop at cows?
Like when I read this story, I thought, dude, could you imagine being attacked by something
like this?
Being attacked by something that you didn't even know existed before its tendrils wrapped
around your neck.
You had no idea that this was part of the ecosystem until you felt acid against your
skin and you're trying to struggle, you're trying to grab at tendrils that just seem
supernaturally strong.
It was designed to hunt and kill large mammals and it's sucking out your blood.
It attaches a suction cup to your left eye socket and before the same thing happens to
your right eye, you see your left eye get sucked up into the tendril, slowly being dissolved.
Soon, both eyeballs are gone, the acid pours through your system as you try to struggle,
as you try to get away and you fail.
You are now a lifeless husk, nearly drained of all your blood, all the soft organs dissolved
away.
If it happened to your house, it would be a huge mystery, but if you were out camping,
out farming, in the middle of nowhere enjoying nature.
And this happened to you and your body wasn't found, maybe they'd think it was natural causes,
because it does appear that you suffered a heart attack and the predators just came
and ate away the softest parts of you until your body was found.
But what the autopsy can't show is that your heart attack was brought on by pure fear.
You always wanted to know the truth, is the world of the paranormal real, do cryptids
exist, is there something more than what the skeptics say, but you always figured you'd
live to tell the tale.
Instead you just became another piece of evidence, in an ever growing mystery.
And that's what you're going to find out.
[Music]
[MUSIC PLAYING]