What happens when a couple ghost hunters go into a cabin looking for a ghost?
Instead they find something oddly unsettling
Other than the ghosts they were there for something else
And it would take a look at the story of a young woman who is visited by an alien one night and
Gives her visions of them having sex
Her worst fear is that she's now pregnant from this alien invader
But is that really the worst thing that could happen today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
*music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a ton of stuff to cover
So we're gonna slide right into this first off. Let's give a shout out to one of our legacy Patreons riding in on a giant haul
Is Steve Jones? He's like what? What? He's like Bill Wilder and he was sitting in my office now
I'm gonna hog but we're gonna clap for him anyways. He's riding this hoggin
Steve you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode on big pilot this episode
If you guys can't support the patreon or don't have pigs to ride that's fine too
Just help spread the word about the show Steve go ahead and hop off that pig here. The reason why the pigs in here
Let's all pet this giant hog. I'm actually recording today and tomorrow's episode back to back because tomorrow
I have an appointment. I talked about this a long time ago. I have to hold down a hog for God knows how long
Well another man saws off its hoofs
No, no, no, no, no that came out wrong
We're not jigsaw protege's he's gonna grind down the toenails of this giant hog
So I'm a little nervous
I'm recording I'm recording the next two episodes in advance because I might get injured not only the pigs gonna eat my face
Or anything that is possibility. I think the pigs gonna eat my face
It's a really old hog and I'm gonna hold it down away from its face
But I might like you know hurt my back or something like that or shatter every bone in my legs
So I'm recording the next two episodes just in case so I can take the days off and recuperate and bones heal in three days
Right guys, so Steve. Thank you for writing this hog in we're gonna leave this big old pig at Dead Rabbit command
And I'm gonna toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy. We are leaving behind Pigville USA
formerly Dead Rabbit headquarters. We're headed out to Illinois
Steve drive us on down there actually this was a story that Nicholas sent me the other day was actually
Part of when we did that tour of Illinois, but it didn't really fit in to that episode
I also got to say got a lot of complaints got a lot of complaints about the people who picked number three and and were suffered
Eternal damnation the other people just got stabbed by a clown or entered a television show full of hobos
If you pick number three spoiler alerts
You were trapped in hell for the rest of eternity, but anyways
I
Appreciated all of those emails and made me laugh a lot at how much you guys were but anyways no numbers to be chosen here
This one didn't really fit into the interactive format, but this is really interesting when you research
Paranormal conspiracy stuff for so long the outliers are very very important
This is something we've been hitting on fairly recently on this show
The outliers are super important because it tells something more about the mythology could be totally made up
That would explain an outlier to Steve stop the Jason Jalopy right here. We're at witches bridge in Clarksdale, Illinois
Now very briefly of course this bridge has a legend with the name like witches bridge
It's not like Johnny which built the bridge
Apparently a witch was hung from the bridge. Who knows if that happened. I'm sure people have been hung from bridges there
Whether or not it was an actual witch it would be kind of hard to to hang someone who can fly away
Honestly, she's like my last wish is to hold my broom as you hang me. They're like, okay. What's the worst thing go wrong?
I don't think anyone was actually hung from the bridge
There is a cabin nearby and here's another story. That's very very typical with these type of things
There was a man he had his family he got mad at him
He murdered them all with an axe probably or a shovel or whore while talking just let it crush all their bones and
Then he hung himself on the bridge now apparently this house is guarded by a zombie dog now all of that stuff is
Very run-of-the-mill. We have the cursed bridge. We have people getting hung from it
That's super super common in the lore in ghost lore family annihilators
Super common in the lore even ghost dogs hellhounds things like that real dogs are part of the lore
This was really interesting the cabins no longer there. It's now been moved to Rochester, Illinois
So they're like we want the zombie dog. That's their mascot in that town the zombie dogs go
So they cracked it down the zombie dogs like oh man. I really miss my view
Apparently though when the cabin was in Clarksdale, Illinois, there was a room in the cabin
Obviously right you're like whoa J. You're waking up your buddy. Do do I don't know why you're sleeping next to your buddy
But you're like dude dude. There's a cabin with a room in it. I haven't gotten to the cool part yet, right?
But but it is cool that you're waking up your buddy to listen to the show
There's a room in this cabin and no matter what the temperature was outside if it was hot
If it was cold if it was moderate you would go into this room and it would always be
Warm
Huh?
See that's the twist we've
Cold spots is one of the main things we're like
Yes, yes, because it's always cold spots
It's all I've never ever in 30 years
Come across a ghostly encounter where you entered a room and no matter what the temperature was the room was warm
It's always oh, it's so much colder in here. Look if we're gonna pull out this thermostat. Look how cold it is
It's a cold spot cold spots are always the signs of ghosts
I have never ever ever heard of a house that had a haunting in it and there was a room that was constantly warm
See to me that's fascinating if this was just a cabin where a guy murdered his entire family and then hung himself and
That story is not real then I wouldn't even mention it
And if it had a cold spot I wouldn't even mention it because we hear that stuff all the time
I've never come across and when you look at outliers like this again
You think oh, maybe some maybe some guy made it up and he wanted to be maybe his name is Johnny Warm
And he wanted to start a reputation. It's possible that it's made up obviously, but it's such an outlier. It's worth investigating
Unfortunately, we can't anymore the cabin's been moved
But that is a place if someone said hey, there's a house on the outskirts of town
It doesn't matter how hot or cold it is outside you go in a student room. It's cold
I would I wouldn't get out of bed to go visit that haunted house honestly and be like boring
There's a demon's floating around there battling angels in the living room. I'm like oh cold spots
They're like no no no there's other stuff going on and getting back in a bed with your buddy
I'm sleeping with your buddy - but if someone said hey, there's a house on the outskirts of town
There's a room that's always warm. I would go that night. It's crazy and it's funny because just something that small
It's such an outlier that to me that means there's definitely something going on there
Assuming that it's true assuming that this is just not someone making this up if that was a verifiable report
There's definitely something going on there. I can explain cold spots drafts with how often are you in a hot room?
And you get like a cold draft. It doesn't happen all the time, but you can explain that windows open
other stuff other stuff but
To be in a room and it's freezing cold and warm comes in or it's always just warm really interesting again
It could be a weather phenomenon. I'm not saying it's definitely paranormal
But when you come across outliers like this, they're very very important to investigate
Because the other ones you're just if you know if you know haunted houses are supposed to have orbs
It's supposed to have cold spots and supposed to have like creaky floorboards
You think someone's walking from behind you you're gonna note
You're gonna notice this you're gonna expect those things you might even in your head make those things happen
So it's possible that that was an actual real house now. It's been moved. There's as far as I can tell no reports
Since then so Nicholas. Thanks for sending that story over. I didn't want to include it in I don't want to give you a number
Just say if you pick number three you're warm
No, I want you to be damned to eternity, but in an alternate universe if you pick number three
How about this you're just warm so there you go and you just go home so Steve
I'm gonna toss you the keys to the carbonar copter. We are leaving behind Illinois. We are gonna fly out to Russia
So as you're flying out to
Russia I wanted to give you guys a dead wrap recommends and this one's kind of a hybrid and I really went back on forth over
Whether or not I wanted to recommend this movie or do a full segment on it
It's not that I don't think the movie is not worth recommending because the movie is definitely worth recommending
But it's so such an interesting story that I almost just did a whole segment on it
I came to the conclusion of the movie so good. I can't do a justice
But I'm gonna do a little teaser for it and then I want you guys to watch this movie
Steve actually let's not go to Russia yet
Turn around we're headed to Monterey County because I forgot I did want to cover a little bit of this story
Specifically we're headed to the Pacific Grove Municipal Golf Course in Pacific Grove, California. It's November 3rd at 2013
We're flying overhead and it's 7 20 in the morning and we're flying super low and people are messing up their their golf shots
It's hilarious and then we see a man over by the restrooms
Running around and he's not just having a good time like playing with a dog or something like that playing with a zombie dog
He's on fire
He's running around he's on fire and we're gonna throw some water on him
But by the time we get there he's already dead. His name was Richard Hafner. He's 56 years old
People at the golf course said that this fire was so intense when they could see this
They actually thought a building was on fire
Like it was such a big fire
It was shocking to them when they found it was just one guy
because what happened is he kind of ran from like this walled area to the men's restroom and
Died against the men's restroom walls, which is a horrible place to go
But it's not like being on fire is a picnic or anything
But it's just a horrible combination of things. He actually he was so hot when he touched the wall
He was like scorching the brick of the bathroom the police fire department. They all show up and they started the investigation
homicide
Suicide
Accident they found what appeared to be accelerant in his car
So it looked like he was sitting in his car caught on fire and then started running around and then died about 20 feet later
Very very intense fire spontaneous human combustion. Well one man has the answer to this
Christo
Apollo of Monterey County
He believes it was a UFO attack. I
Started watching this documentary called curse of the man who sees UFOs
It is awesome. I totally recommend you guys
It was one of those documentaries actually watching on my vacation last summer and I put it in and I was like playing Minecraft or something
And I was half paying attention and that story is kind of towards the beginning and I paused and I rewound it and I go
That's not true. It's not true like what a guy just exploded in flames
I mean considering what I talk about on this show, right? I'm thinking there's no way this is true
And then I kept watching it again and they start showing like local news reports
They're like a man burst into flames today
I stopped the movie shut off Minecraft and started looking it up and a hundred percent this story happened
But the concept of the documentary is you're following a man called Christo Rapolo
Who is an avid UFO hunter and he finds them all the time?
It's a really really interesting documentary and when you start it off you go this guy
He he strikes you as if the big Lebowski and Steven Greer morphed into one
He believes in that whole like I can look him in the sky and I can ask the UFOs to appear and then little dots will appear in
The sky and they're catching all this stuff on video. He's just a man who's just kind of living on the edge
I think like he like his apartment was messy or something like that or his car was messy
Not like that makes you a crackpot, but he just his life was a mess and you're following this man
And he's talking about all these UFO events in Monterey County and then a crop circle appears
And Christo goes nuts. It's I've said this before and I'll say it again the best documentaries
They are there at the right time
cartel land
dig
overnight
Curse of the man who sees UFOs. These are all documentaries the crew just happened to show up at some random point in time and
Capture a one-central. I recommend all of those documentaries. They they just show up at one point in time and capture
History and I remember I was I was on the edge of my seat cuz I was like what is going on with this crop circle
It's dope. I really really and I
Was thinking about doing the whole doing a whole segment on it, but I can't do it justice watch
Curse of the man who sees UFOs. It's a really interesting profile on someone who's like just kind of a wacky UFO
Allogist he's very very lucky or he has some sort of control or connection to these things and
Then the underlying mystery is him trying to figure out this crop circle and it's great
This is a great documentary catch curse of the man who sees UFOs Steve Jones
Let's go ahead and turn around this carbon helicopter or just give us a globe so you can keep flying in the same direction
But we are leaving behind Monterey County. We are headed out to
Northern Russia
We got all of our snow gear on our parkas and our
Like face masks. We all look like Arctic warrior GI Joe's. It's the winter. It's 1989
We're beyond the polar circle, so we're way up there. This is northern Russia
It's one in the morning
Steve Jones expert snow pilot
That was his GI Joe name snow pilot and as Steve is flying us in with this carbon helicopter
We're going to see a young woman sitting at a radio station now not like
105.9 with like lasso in the scooch. It's like it's like a listening station for the Soviet Union
It's 1989 and there's a young woman working at this listening radio station
Turning the knobs and stuff like that. She's just like I don't know what I'm doing. She goes home
She gets off work. She walks through the snow. She gets home. She goes to bed
It is one in the morning after all but when she wakes up she's sleeping next to her husband when she wakes up
There's a beam of light right in her face. Oh man
She's kind of swatting it away. She sees outside what's shining the light in her face. She sees an egg-shaped yellow object
It's interesting she describes it and we've come across this a couple times in ufology
She said it looked like she was egg-shaped, but she said it looked like a cloud, but the edges were diffused
So there wasn't like she was watching an incredible edible egg floating by it was like she could see it was fuzzy
And I like that because it it adds to that whole that other worldliness of it
You've never looked at a jet close up and go man. They sure have perfected that fuzzy technology
Everything's very defined even flying saucers. They have very defined edges
But whatever this was you couldn't even look at it correctly
It was interdimensional or just putting out some sort of weird energy source. She said the edges looked blurry
She sees a whitish shadow again an interesting visual a white shadow
Float out of the object and as it's coming closer. She describes it as what we would describe a gray alien 1989 Russia
That wouldn't have been really well known especially that far away in Russia
That wasn't part of the social consciousness, but she describes big head tiny body giant eyes gray alien
This creature flies through the window just glides through
She's wide awake her husband's just laying there next to her hasn't moved an inch
The alien is now standing next to her in bed and then she has a
This is so weird
I love this story because there's just so many weird elements to it the alien standing next to her in bed
And then she sees a projection of
her and the alien having sex
So is the alien having sex with her in the future? Is she
Astrily traveling out of her body is she looking down at the alien having sex with her?
Is it the only way she can kind of compartmentalize what's going on?
Because in this story she is very very clear. She does not want this to happen
She doesn't want to have sex with this alien and the alien is continuing
To try to have sex with trying to rape her and then the alien gives her a drink and she calms down
But I'm not sure if she sees the alien give her the drink in the vision or in the projection
If she's being shown this event and she's panicking in bed and the alien gives her the drink in bed
It's all very abstract the way the story is laid out, but after the drink she calms down the alien
touches her cheek
In in next to her in the bed, and then the alien floats out the window
Svetlana did I say her name earlier? Her name is Svetlana if I didn't say it earlier Svetlana
She is absolutely paranoid by this now. She doesn't know a lot about UFO ology or aliens or anything like that
They don't have exiles over there. They don't have the book communion that stuff would leak into the culture later
But at this point she knows that she had sex like whether or not she had sex in some alternate reality
Or she was being shown that event or she that was happening to her and she was removed from her body to deal with it
She knows for a fact that in some way she had sex with this alien and
She is petrified
She is pregnant
She believes there is a chance that she has a baby inside of her. She doesn't tell her husband what happened
She's waiting for the signs of pregnancy to appear though, but something else starts to happen to her
She notices that her face the skin on her face is starting to get tighter and a little more supple
She sees moles that she's had for years
slowly
Disappear she gets up she looks in the mirror in the morning
She can tell she's visibly younger than she was the day before
Eventually the time came where she didn't even have to wear glasses anymore
She was
de-aging
somehow
Another odd side effect from this was that according to her her sex drive increased tenfold
She could not get enough sex which the husband is like I don't know what's going on
But you're looking great, honey, and all this sex ten times the sex is amazing
We were already having like sex ten times a day. That's a hundred times a day now. We both have to quit our jobs
at this point a couple months have passed and
She hasn't given birth she has to show no signs of being pregnant and she's actually very relieved by that
Because that was her biggest fear. She looks a lot younger than she used to she's having sex
Oh, she might get pregnant again very very soon, but she's not pregnant with an alien baby
She's finally come to peace with that
But one morning she wakes up and she has a burning desire
To carve wood this was something she never done before she never even thought about before she actually bullied the people in
The wood carving club in high school. She goes out she gets some wood and she just kind of begins whittling it down
She doesn't really know what she's doing, but she has a need to carve wood
Whittle whittle whittle whittle whittle whittle
over time
She ends up getting like a carving knife better pieces of wood
She can really get in there and she finds herself carving a very specific image
It's the image of a gray alien
She's taking these pieces of wood and she's carving away everything all that's left
Is the image of a gray alien that floated into her window, but it's not just the gray alien
It's what we would describe what we know as now of an alien hybrid
It's a human with the giant eyes of a gray alien
She's carving these figures over and over again
Eventually she had such a collection of these really interesting figures
She had an art show in st. Petersburg in 1993
Where she displayed all of these little gray alien hybrid human figurines to the public
That story was I got it from think about a docs.com and they got it from a Russian ufologist
We've covered this gentleman before Leonid somov. That's from a book
He wrote called 100 stories of encounters with the unknown in published in 2004
The story is interesting on a couple different notes. It's funny
I kept wanting to interrupt myself, but I wanted to keep the flow of the story going one a lot of times when women are abducted by
Aliens and they're subjected to these type of hybrid experiments
They don't remember them
We covered one story and this is really common, but once the way that sticks out of my mind was there was a woman
She was abducted. She found herself like paralyzed
There was something covering her lower body and alien was walking towards her her legs are spread open
She wakes up. She's at home
That's common. That's usually common when when men get abducted and they have sexual encounters with aliens
They tend to remember them they remember the experience, but a lot of times when women are having sex with aliens
They don't we did cover a story of a woman who's getting gangbanged on the moon by reptilians, but that was made up
That was I will fully say that story is made up. That's not true
So she can remember whatever she wanted it never happened, but when we look at all these other more believable UFO
Hybrid experiment stories women don't normally remember it. So I this again is an outlier. It's very interesting
Not only did she remember it. She viewed it as a third party
She was watching it happen and again was she watching it in the future was it happening and she had astrally projected from her body
We don't know
But not only does she remember it she remembers it as a third party in there
We also have the interesting thing a lot of times in aliens and counter humans. We'll see them
Remove tumors will see them heal people and this one she was getting younger
Which is an interesting side effect to the whole thing
Because that would that's a huge benefit obviously not just looking good, but you're actually de-aging your prolonging your life
Now we only have the first names Fetlana. I'm sure it's a very very common name
It's not like you just go around and look for all the youngest radio operators in Russia who have incredible sex drives
You look for everyone. He's still horny, but you have those things that happen
I think the most interesting part of the story and it's a very interesting story
And I love all the little different rabbit holes. We can go down on it is the wood carving now there is
Stories of people getting just normal people getting bonked on the head getting a metal pipe through the brain the next thing
They know they're a concert pianist
All of these hidden skills people have that they're magically unlocked not really magically unlocked like parts of the brain are damaged
It's the reverse of magic. That's tragic and
They're able to develop these skills. She didn't really have that type of experience
But something prompted her to start carving wood and I think the most obvious answer to the story is the saddest
There's nothing like a human parents love towards their children
When a father or mother sees that little baby
It just radiates love it should I know it doesn't happen all the time
And I know there's a lot of bastards out there
We can't form that connection, but you know what I mean it needs to that's part of the human condition
Even as I'm doing this segment. I'm kind of holding my arms like I'm creating a little baby person a
humans love for their offspring is
boundless and I believe that
Can translate across the stars
Aside from the reptilian gang bang on the moon
The aliens aren't coming down here and having sex with human women just to have sex with human women
Let's put our conspiracy caps fully on here guys because we're gonna talk about this space alien hybrid program
Which is really common in UFO lore
The great aliens aren't coming down just to have sex with humans
They're coming down to create human alien hybrids and a lot of times the human women don't give birth to the children a lot of
Times they're just used for the sexual act and then the women are deposited back at home
Now there are some human women who claim they've given birth to hybrids, but for the most part the story is
They're in some sort of chamber. They're in some sort of
Breeding pod some sort of surrogate birthing method. So I believe Svetlana while not praying in herself
Did have a alien hybrid child that she never saw that she never held
She never kissed good night
Never took it to its first day of space school
Never got to do any of those things, but her motherly love reached across the stars and
Gave her the vision of her child
And not only gave her the vision of her child, but gave her the ability to see that child
She may never be able to see him in real life
But it gave her the ability to create art of a very specific purpose
The child wanted to visit its mom
The child wanted to make its presence known, but it couldn't all it could do is reach across the stars and
Give its mother a memory of
What it looked like
She turned that subconscious memory into art
The alien hybrid baby gave her a gift and in return that child was loved
Even if the mother didn't know that child existed that child was loved a
Parents love
Can reach across the stars. It's never too far away
To say I love you
Is that a homework card is that it that should be something that should be like a phone commercial dead rubber
Do copyright copyright copyrighted that
Radio gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also set up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]