Was a wind turbine destroyed by an alien?
A bizarre weakness for an otherwise unstoppable cryptid?
And then we take a look at the story of Haditha Dam in Iraq.
It's the opening days of the Iraqi war, and US forces make a quick push to secure the dam.
Were they trying to prevent an ecological disaster, or an energy catastrophe?
Or were they trying to prevent the four horsemen from being unleashed upon the world, today
on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Kirpner, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover, and I'm really sore, because today was my first official day
of Brazilian Jiu Jitsu training.
I'm picking you up, throwing you into the Carvener Copture.
You're like, "Ugh!"
Falling in the Carvener Copture, and then I'm just walking through like smoke towards the
copter.
If you're a new listener, you have no idea what's going on.
That's okay, I pick you up, I throw you in as well.
New and old, you're both getting tossed into the Carvener Copture.
We're all going to be on the Carvener Copture, as you're like, "Oh my neck, ow.
Jason, why'd you do that to me?"
I'm like, "Pain is love, my friend."
Turning on the helicopter, pain is love.
We are flying, first off, to Lincolnshire, UK, the United Kingdom, the kingdom that never
sleeps.
And it's January 2009, so flying the Carvener Copture over the sunny, sunny hills of England,
green grass, as opposed to that yellow grass.
Wait, no, there is yellow grass.
I was going to say it was supposed to be a color that doesn't exist in nature.
There is yellow grass.
I'm sure some countries have it.
Savannah, probably.
They call it Savannah, but the large fields of wheat or whatever is out there.
I don't buy this whole humans or baffin environment thing.
Sure, we might not be the greatest, but if it wasn't for us, there would be pumpkins
everywhere.
Think about it.
The way the plants move about the planet is when it blows them, a little seed pops out
of a wheat thing.
You're like, "Jason, are you really going to go on a tangent about science, the subject
you know the least about?"
Yes, I am.
A little seed pops out of wheat.
It flies all the way from Glauchester, England, the United Kingdom, wherever, to Spain, and
then it lands in some dirt and then some wheat grows.
Now, the only reason why crops are relegated to...
Jason, you really don't know what you're talking about.
The only reason why crops are relegated to certain areas is because we say, "No, pumpkin's
here."
We destroy...
We basically like, if a pumpkin landed in your front yard, a pumpkin seed landed in
your front yard, some passerby is spinning them out, a bird's defecating them.
You then see a little pumpkin start growing and you're like, "No," and you like, "Chop
it up.
Get rid of it."
Or you let it grow and have some delicious pumpkin pie, but we basically go, "No, this
is a lawn.
This is a forest.
This is a pumpkin patch."
And here we go.
Now, if it wasn't for us, if it wasn't for humans, the world would just be a mismatch
of stuff.
And then seeds would be blown from Europe to Russia and they would take over.
The seeds would form a junta and they would be destroying the other seeds in their area.
So yes, and I get it.
Hold on.
Don't start yelling yet.
I get it.
The world's four billion years old and seeds have been blown around forever.
But I'm sure before humans showed up, there were pumpkins everywhere.
Pumpkin might be a bad analogy because it's kind of a resource-heavy fruit or vegetable.
You're like, "Jason, you don't know a pumpkin is a vegetable off the top of your head."
Let's go ahead and move on.
Let's go ahead and continue with our first story here.
2009 is Lincolnshire, United Kingdom.
There's grass fields as far as I can see.
There's also these big old wind turbines.
So they spin faster and faster.
The wind turbines, most people don't know this conspiracy.
They're there to help the earth rotate.
It's like a little propulsion unit for the earth.
That's why they're really pushing on building more wind turbines.
It's not for free energy.
It's not for green energy.
It's because the earth stopped rotating or the earth started to slow down about 50 years
ago and if we don't have more wind turbines, the earth will stop spinning completely.
It's totally made up.
But I want you guys to share that conspiracy theory.
Tell them, "Oh, did you know the world is also slowly stopping to rotate?"
That's the real reason behind wind turbines.
Anyways, I'm in Lincolnshire.
What's going on?
And then one night, people in town or village, however you want to put it, I think they call
it "shires" over there.
Lincolnshire.
We've talked about this before on the show.
The wind turbine goes, "Ahhh, it's not an old man.
It's not waking up in the morning."
And everyone's like, "What in the world?
What?
Intarnation?
Jailbillies out there?"
They wake up and they see, because this happened at night and I missed the key detail, but
anyways, I keep going.
Then I'll explain the key detail.
They wake up and a winter of mine has like the big three fans things.
It's like the giant stick and then three blades that spin around generate electricity.
One is completely knocked off and laying on the ground.
The other one, the other blade is super bent back to form, all mashed up.
And then the one's totally normal.
Now, obviously the sound I made at 10 o'clock at night recording this episode is nothing
compared to the sound that they heard.
It was super, super loud.
It was like, "Ahhh, it's waking up."
Sounded like massive thunder hitting this thing, but there was no lightning strikes
in the area.
The key detail I meant to say early before I started talking about pumpkin staking over
the world is that they saw preceding this, people saw these little orbs flying around,
these little orbs with tentacles flying around and basically UFOs.
So they've been seeing these like things floating around with little tendrils coming off of
them.
And then no one, everyone's like, "Oh, it's unidentified objects.
It's Darby O'Gillus and the little people.
It's a leprechauns, it's fairy magic, but because this is modern times, people are saying they're
UFOs.
Also, not Ireland, so I don't think people in Lincolnshire really believe in leprechauns,
but I don't even know if the Irish still do.
They should though.
Those leprechauns are dope.
Those movies are at least.
Why, how come I've never done an episode about leprechauns and how they think about it?
I bet you wish I had.
So anyways, they're seeing these UFOs floating around and then there's this massive destruction
of this windmill.
Now, a lot of people in the area are like, "Oh, it's the UFOs.
It must have been a UFO spacecraft that crashed into this thing and mashed it up."
So that was the news going around in the area and that's how the news article got out to
us.
This is a headline from the Telegraph News website.
"UFO blamed for destruction of wind turbine.
People in the area were like, "It must have been a UFO."
Now of course, other people came out and said, "UFOs aren't...
Well, UFOs are real, but they're not alien spacecraft.
They're unidentified flying objects, sure, but they're not alien spacecraft."
They said, "This could have happened for a number of reasons.
One, it could have been a manufacturing defect.
Two, it could have been an issue where it wasn't...
This would still be considered a manufacturing defect or it could just be wear and tear, but
a little bit of water gets in between the pieces and it builds up and then one day it
gets particularly cold and it freezes and like freezing cold and metal, it's going to
start smashing stuff and falls apart."
And people are like, "Nnngh, I don't like that.
Those sound awfully mundane or that doesn't sound like the noise I heard that wouldn't
cause this massive destruction."
And really it came down to this quote.
This guy left this quote.
He's being interviewed for this article and he said this and this is something I think
that a lot of people lose sight of.
"Any of these explanations..." and he's talking about the more mundane ones.
He's talking about the water one and then just wear and tear, manufacturing defect,
stuff like that I went over.
"Any of these explanations plus several others appear to me to be much more plausible than
the idea that technologically advanced aliens have traveled light years across space but
then bumped into a wind turbine."
And then that's exactly true.
Like obviously you have to plot a... if you have to plot travel between galaxies and then
you're like, "Wachaurooo!"
I mean like the idea of a UFO even having like a joystick that you steer and it's not
controlled by your brain or some hyper-advanced AI.
I got an argument with someone about AI the other day.
I said, "I don't think it's ever...
We will never ever as a human species see the rise of super advanced AI.
I don't think we will.
I don't think we will."
And you're like, "Jason, didn't you just go on a rant about pumpkins?
Don't go on a rant about AI.
I just don't see it happening."
And maybe I'll do an episode on that too or why I think that at least but I just...
I think it's so far...
People go, "Oh, you know put in a couple numbers and put in a couple more numbers and
then have a quantum computer and put in even more numbers and then all of a sudden Skynet
appears.
It's far more advanced than that.
We're not even close.
I don't even think you could replicate a nematode in a computer as far as the complexity of
it all."
I could be wrong on the nematode thing but I definitely don't think I'm wrong on the
AI thing.
I do not think we will ever have an AI to the level that it will say.
And I'm talking about science fiction level AI where it would be like, "Hmm, what is...
What am I?
Who am I?
What is going on here?
Take over humanity."
I don't think that's ever going to happen.
You may eventually create something that says, "You've built me to defend humans and humans
are the worst enemy therefore if I kill all humans I've succeeded in defending all humans."
That's a flawed program.
That's basically just...
You're being stupid programming something in a computer going to defend all humans at
all costs.
That's just dumb.
And building that into defense software.
I mean if you put that into a toaster nobody cares but I'm talking about an AI that tries
to basically anything resembling human thought is completely impossible in a computer environment
I believe.
Maybe in 4,000 years you might get a semblance of that.
But nothing close to what we have today.
It's something you read about in the news every so often AI taking over and Elon Musk
is super afraid of AI and blah blah blah.
It's sci-fi mumbo jumbo.
It's the same thing when people tell me they're afraid of the anti-Christ or something like
that.
I'm like, "Blech."
Okay.
I mean that's kind of the same way I feel about it.
You're just like...
To be perfectly fair if someone told me they were being haunted if they were being chased
down the street by a demon I would take that more seriously than someone telling me that
AI is going to be something in 10 years.
I think the idea of that is just so far out of the technological realm.
Again, you can create a robot that thinks and it can beat you at chess or beat you at
life or beat you at sorry or any other famous board game by Milton Bradley.
But building a robot that then tries to comprehend what happens to it after you shut it off and
all of these human emotions and feelings, emotions would be the...
Rather than imitating human feelings actually having something to the level of human feelings,
millennia is off from that.
So if you had a UFO fly down across the galaxy and had all these sensors and all of these
drive particle things that it would take, this is a real science-heavy episode.
Well, okay, okay.
It's me using words.
Words likely and correctly that are normally used in scientific arenas.
But to be able to plot a course from Alpha Centauri to Earth, just the mere idea of having
to avoid every micro meteorite that came your way, whether that was some sort of advanced
shielding or some advanced navigational system and honestly it would probably be a little
bit of both, to then get all the way to Earth and then to crash into a giant 65 foot tall
blade, the windmill itself is taller than that, but just the blades are about 65 feet
tall to crash into one of those is so unlikely it points more to the proof that aliens do
not have that type of technology to traverse the galaxy than it does to rain, water, manufacturing
defect, wear and tear, anything like that.
But people saw some UFOs and they want to believe that aliens are flying around despite
the fact that it makes them look incredibly stupid.
Not the people who believe in the aliens, it makes them, you know, you can question their
beliefs but they observed something and then saw something happen afterwards and put, or
put in the two together.
It makes the aliens look stupid because they're the ones flying their ship into a giant windmill.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story here.
Our next story is super short and I actually planned it.
I normally only do short stories when they're super short.
I found this today.
There's a cryptid called Zana, X-A-N-A, it's from Spain.
And it's a super kind of boring cryptid.
I was looking into it.
It's a nature spirit.
It's this beautiful young woman.
You're like, Jason, that's the opposite of boring.
And I'm like, I know, I know.
Normally that would be super exciting.
But when you've read, I read a bunch of weirdo cryptids today.
This was on the, it was just a beautiful woman that appears in the forest, nature spirit,
stuff like that.
She didn't do nothing.
No claws.
She didn't transform into a lizard person or destroy windmills or help pump can take
over the planet.
Just real basic stuff.
She's basic.
Watch she's going to haunt me tonight.
She's like, I'm not basic.
And again, if a beautiful, if a beautiful Spanish cryptid wants to break into my apartment
tonight, go nuts, lady.
This one though, very, very classic.
She also has, I should mention this long, blonde or brown hair.
It's pretty cool.
She combs it with a comb made of sunbeams.
That's beautiful imagery.
But she also steals babies.
She can't raise her own kids.
So she'll sneak into your house like a changeline of typical European descent.
She'll break into your house and then swap babies out.
So she gives you the changeling baby and takes yours and yours presumably is going to pass
away because she can't feed it.
And then you raise this Xana.
You raise this changeling baby as your own.
And as she gets older, she eventually leaves the house and joins her kin in the forest.
That's basic changeling stuff.
Again, nothing's really groundbreaking except for this.
I love this.
I found this, this might be one of my favorite weaknesses ever for a cryptid.
Quote, in order to unmask the Xanon, that's like the singular of it, in order to unmask
the Xanon, one must put some pots and eggshells near the fire.
And if the baby is a changeling, he will exclaim, so here's a baby saying this.
Here's a baby saying this.
It's just not a normal old man.
You got a baby, you think it might be changeling.
You take some pots and put some eggshells near the fire.
And then you take your baby over.
Don't put it too close to the fire.
You just set it down next to the fire.
And it will say that if it's a changeling, it'll say this.
I was born 100 years ago, and since then, I have not seen so many eggshells near the
fire.
And then at that point, you know that your baby is a changeling.
So you have to go out and try to find your own kid before it's too late.
Now, I find this might be one of my favorite weaknesses in a cryptid one, because obviously,
oh, oh, after this section of Wikipedia, it said, citation needed.
I was like, certainly, a citation would be helpful for that part.
My question is this.
Let's say that it's true.
How did they figure it out?
Let's say that there really is this cryptid that's swapping babies out.
Was there one time a harried mother was like, why can't my baby stop crying?
Why does it keep wanting that comb with sunbeams in it?
That doesn't even exist.
Babies like crying.
And the woman's like, oh my god, I can't do this.
And she's like trying to clean up, but instead she just throws as much eggshells in a pot
and puts it down the fire and then she hears her little baby go, I was born 100 years ago.
She turns around.
And since then, I have not seen so many eggshells near the fire.
The mother sitting there in this old shack, little babies just rolling around on the ground,
trying to get closer to the eggshells.
She goes to the priest of town.
You won't believe this, dude.
The baby started talking about eggshells, said he was 100 years old.
The priest was like, what?
That is kind of weird.
Babies obviously not 100 years old.
And then eventually they found her kid in the forest.
How would you, what was the origin story for that belief?
That would have had to have happened to somebody.
But it's most likely, okay, it's not true.
I don't think this cryptid exists.
It could be wrong.
I'll tell you on Monday's episode if she comes over tonight.
It's just such a bizarre, it's such a bizarre and specific weakness.
And you could imagine like mothers in Spain when their babies acting up.
They're like, that's it.
Don't make me get out the eggshells.
And the baby's like, I know you're changeling.
I know you're not one of ours breaking eggs.
The husband's like, dude, aren't you going to be eating those?
Why are you just wasting this?
She's like, shut up.
I'm going to prove this kid's not ours.
And she's throwing eggs away, throwing all the shells in a pot.
She puts it down and she puts the baby next to the fire.
Not too close again.
And the baby's just sitting there crying.
And the mom's like, oh, I guess it isn't a changeling.
And then the dad's like, turns to the camera and his eyes are glowing yellow.
He's the changeling.
He's been the changeling all along.
Why?
How did this come out?
How did people use this?
Was there a real epidemic of people thinking their babies were really 100 year old men
who have never seen so many eggs near the fire?
Just such a bizarre story.
But that was the most interesting thing about the Zanas.
I wish there was more to tell you.
And then, speaking of, I wish I had more to tell you, I think I'm out of time for the
damn story.
I know I should have went off on my ecological rant.
So I don't have time to do the damn story.
Damn it.
But I'm not going to just end it on a story about eggshells and babies.
I'm going to tell you something that is super bizarre.
And I don't really know how to process it.
In the past probably like 6 to 8 months, I've developed a phobia of alcohol.
Now it doesn't mean I haven't drank at all in the past 6 to 8 months because I've gone
out with friends.
I've had a drink.
But I've developed and I used to drink heavily when I was in my 20s, when I used to party
all the time.
I drank and I smoked weed and all sorts of stuff.
And it was no big deal.
And then I stopped because I just got bored of it and never really liked it.
Well I liked it back then, but it was just a social thing and I never drank on my own.
It just wasn't my thing.
It wasn't my bag.
But recently I've developed a phobia of alcohol.
Like just thinking about alcohol.
If I think about alcohol, I'm like, why am I even thinking about what I'm going to drink
tonight at the bar?
Like why am I alcohol is something?
When people ask me do you drink, I go, so rarely it's not even worth noting.
And I've had long term friends who have been like, they'll see me shoot Jack and they'll
be like, what?
I've known you for six years.
I've only seen you drink beer.
And I was like, yeah, I drank Jack every once in a while.
It's so rare that I'm doing this.
I have a theory.
Now we've talked about this before.
Before I started doing the podcast, I was pretty miserable.
What I do is I was trying to be an author.
I was trying to be a writer and I would come home and I'd be like, oh, I can't wait to
get home.
I got all these story ideas.
I know exactly where I'm going to go, what I'm going to do.
But first I need to take a break.
So I'd come home and I'd watch YouTube for about six to seven hours.
And then as I was crawling into bed, I was be completely miserable that I hadn't gotten
anything accomplished and what a failure I was and how awful things were going in my
life.
And then I'd wake up and I can't wait to get home from work as I'm getting ready to go
to work.
I'm going to do all this writing.
Today is going to be different.
And I was going through that for probably about two or three years.
Probably about two.
I want to say was that like it was probably more like a year and a half.
It was when I said I'm going to be a writer and I'm going to make a living writing.
And I would produce stuff.
I would write stuff.
I've been writing all my life, but this was when I was really trying to make a push towards
it.
So, but I would be miserable for a good, good chunk of about a year and a half.
I just, my life wasn't going where I wanted it to.
And then I started doing the podcast.
Now it's not like the podcast is a living, but the podcast has definitely given me a
creative output.
It's given me a ton of fan support from you guys.
It's given me, it hasn't paid for stuff.
It is basically making money now, which is very rare for a podcast.
So things are going great artistically, financially, all of that.
But there was a point in time, very recent point in time last year where I was just completely
miserable.
And I feel like my life is branched off.
And I, this is why I think again, it's totally, I have no proof for any of this.
The reason why all of a sudden a man who's 43 develops a fear of alcohol is that I think
in an alternate timeline, I am an alcoholic.
I think in a very, very close alternate timeline, I am an alcoholic and I'm struggling every
day with drinking and it's bleeding over to this universe.
Very, very weird feeling because I don't even like, like I will sit there and be like, maybe
I should have alcohol at my apartment.
So in case a girl comes over, cause you know, a lot of girls in town, a lot of, I think
a lot of girls in general drink wine.
I was like, I should have a bottle of like red or red and white wine, not together.
That'd be cool.
It was in that rose.
I should have a bottle of red, a bottle of white, some nice wine.
I'll never drink it, but just have it in the house.
So when girls come over, they can have some.
And the idea of having alcohol in my house petrifies me, terrifies me.
Absolutely.
And I've had alcohol.
I've had ever clear at my house.
I had like 190 proof alcohol in my house just a few years ago.
There's no problem.
But now the idea of having it in my house, like, I hate to use the word, but triggers
me to the point where I won't have it.
I remember for some event that had recently passed, I was like, oh, I need to go buy alcohol
before I go there.
So I have something to drink in case they don't have anything to drink there that I drink
and because I'm on keto.
And I was like, why am I even trying to process?
I was actually like getting concerned that I was thinking about buying alcohol.
And there's nothing, there would have been nothing wrong with me buying alcohol to take
to somebody's house.
If all they had was beer and I needed a keto alternative, there's nothing wrong with that.
The idea that I was putting any processing power into alcohol before I got to the party,
really, really concerned me.
It was really weird.
And I had this feeling once before, I remember back when I was in my 20s, I was drinking
all the time, I had one of those big 1.75 liters of vodka sitting in my kitchen.
And I was laying on my couch and I was super depressed and I'm like, I want to drink all
that vodka.
I'm just going to get drunk.
I'm going to drink all that vodka and all I could do all day long was think about drinking
vodka as I was laying on my couch.
And I was talking to my friend Liz and I go, I think I'm an alcoholic and she goes, why
am I not going to go?
All I can do all day long is think about drinking vodka and she goes, are you drinking any
vodka?
And I was like, no, I just think about it and she's like, well, then you're not an alcoholic.
Like if you think all day long about drinking vodka, but you're too lazy to get up on the
couch to even pour a shot, probably not an alcoholic.
And I go, yeah, you're kind of right.
But I was processing it.
I was like thinking about it and just the idea of thinking, it's funny now that I remember
that, even thinking about it back then scared me.
But then that was like when I was 23.
So we go 20 years and I go to a party and have a beer, go out, have a shot of Jack.
Never even really consider it until maybe back then, the two timelines were converging
as well.
But yeah, I feel like I'm in an alternate timeline where the podcast didn't get started
or the podcast started, but I picked the wrong subject.
Like I was going to do like a political podcast or a movie review podcast or whatever it was
and it lasted seven episodes and ended or never did the podcast or whatever.
And I started drinking because that's an easy, that's a very, very easy out.
It's a cheap and legal way to shut down your brain.
And I chose that path.
But now I'm at a point where with my beta blockers, I can't drink anyways.
As long as I'm on this and they're still trying to figure out exactly why my heart went off.
They say, "I can't drink anyways."
And I was talking to my mom on the phone and I said, "I'm very grateful.
I'm very grateful that I don't have any substance abuse problems."
And it's funny because that is another thought that I'll just be sitting, sitting at home
some time or be out somewhere and I'm thinking, "I'm so glad I'm not a drug addict.
I'm so glad I'm not an alcoholic."
But my point is is that one, anyone can fall into these traps at any point in time.
I remember watching a documentary the other day.
I was watching this documentary about homeless people in New York City and I have a rule
generally the reason why I watch YouTube is because it can't get super offensive.
It can't get super gross, right?
So usually if I bring home a subway sandwich or something or I'm eating some burgers, put
on some YouTube, I'll watch, you know, Ohmrecker play Dead by Daylight for a half hour.
Whatever it is, I know things aren't going to get too bad.
And this is the reason why I didn't follow that rule this time.
I go, "Oh, I have a documentary about homeless people in New York City.
I'm going to eat dinner and watch this documentary about homeless people in New York City."
It's like a documentary made from these Swedish filmmakers.
The opening shot was a homeless...
I was like, "Are you kidding me?"
Because I normally don't do this.
I know this is a couple of months ago this happened to me and then I haven't done this
again.
I'm sitting down to eat dinner and the opening shot of this documentary, some of you guys
may know this documentary when I say this, the opening shot of the documentary is a homeless
dude blowing some guy, just full on, not silhouetted, not shadowed, but a homeless guy giving some
other guy a blow job, full on camera frame.
And I was like, I just put my food down and I go, "Seriously, seriously, this is the
opening shot of your movie."
But because it was about homeless people in love and these guys were like, "Yeah, you
know, I'm with my girlfriend, but sometimes you got to blow a dude to get some drug money."
The reason why I'm bringing that up is not just to warn people not to watch this documentary
while eating, it was good documentary.
Just don't eat it.
You're eating hot dog.
You're entering a hot dog eating contest.
You're like, "But first, I want to find out about homeless people in love."
One of the hobos, one of the homeless people says, "I've seen it happen over and over again.
Some guy comes from some other part of the country, comes to New York, hooks up with
a guy."
And then next thing he knows, the guy from New York has the visitor, has the tourist,
smoke and meth, smoke and crack.
Tourist spends all of his money to get home, spends all of it on drugs within a weekend
stuck in the city, can't leave.
That's how easy it is to fall into these traps, right?
And so I feel like, and I'm going to go back to my original point here and start wrapping
this up, but I feel like, you're like, "No, Jason, tell us more about the homeless people
in love documentary."
I feel like there is a very, very close universe where I have a drinking problem and it's bleeding
over to this universe.
And that may just be some weird hangup I've developed over alcohol over the past couple
months, as possibly I could be, I don't know, I don't really know.
Obviously that is a far-fetched sci-fi answer, but I can't really think of something else.
There's been no trigger.
I haven't lost a friend to alcoholism recently.
There's been no big event.
I just feel like when I think about alcohol, it scares me.
I don't want to have it around me.
I'll go to bars and hang out, obviously, because my buddies will hang out there, but I'll go
and I'll drink water for the most part.
And I am not like, "Ooh, I'm not like running away from them when they're drinking their
ciders and stuff like that."
But it makes me uneasy to think of me being drunk or me having alcohol on me.
Both of those feelings make me feel super uneasy, and I don't like thinking about it.
And I think that's the way that a struggling drug addict or a struggling alcoholic would
feel as well.
Like, I don't want to be around it.
It's going to cause bad things.
And I'm not trying to trivialize this stuff either.
I'm not trying to be like, "Well, you know, I know what it's like, guys.
It's my alternate version of myself."
I hope it's not...
I hope it's coming across the way that I wanted to come across, basically, that I've developed
this weird hang...
Basically, that I've developed this weird hang up over alcohol, and I don't know why.
Because I'm not a drinker.
I'm not struggling with it.
I'm not struggling with substance abuse in general, other than nicotine, which I gave
up.
Haven't you...
I don't even think about nicotine anymore.
So some of that sweet, sweet nicotine.
I don't even... I totally forget that I was even using it for as long as I did.
Except when I was having to find alternatives.
I'm sticking tissue paper in my mouth.
But the actual nicotine high, I'm not really thinking about anymore.
But yeah, I just don't know what other way to explain why I'm going through this.
And there may be a...
Someone could go, "Jason, it's a normal reaction as you're getting older.
Your body starts processing sugar."
But again, it's not even like affecting me during an alcohol.
It's the mental process.
The idea of me thinking about drinking alcohol that freaks me out.
So is it possible that my little timelines diverged at a very integral point a couple
months ago, a year ago?
And in one of them, I'm here with you, talking about Dead Rava Radio and all these great
subjects and everything that's going to come.
All the great stories to come.
And then in another one, things didn't have such a happy ending.
And I find myself trying to relive my glory days of my 20s.
Nothing really mattered.
Just wanted a party.
And the easiest way to do that was for me to grab a bottle or hang out at a bar.
If those two timelines are true, if things did diverge right there.
And in one version now, I am an alcoholic that is struggling daily with trying to be
sober.
Or, where I'm at right now, which is very happy and safe and loved.
I feel loved in this timeline.
I hope that when I'm getting some of these negative feelings of wanting to not be around
alcohol and not wanting to have it around me, not wanting to drink, being fearful of
alcohol, I hope that that alternate Jason is getting some of the love and warmth that
I'm getting from this universe.
And feeling that as well.
And knowing that in an alternate timeline, things are better.
In an alternate timeline, the answer is not the drugs or the bottle.
The answer is something else.
I hope it works both ways.
Because everyone can have hope.
Everyone can get better.
Even if they are living in the wrong timeline and things aren't going right, right now.
Hopefully everyone ends up in the timeline that is the healthiest and safest for them.
That's all we can really hope for.
And so, alternate Jason, I wish you the best.
And I hope you find your way.
And your happiness.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend, guys.
[Music]