The deadliest tree in the world that you can't even stand underneath when it rains.
And we take a look at one of the most dangerous men on the planet, according to himaly's
John Storm today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. Just a quick update.
I am going to end up taking a week off of the show. We're going to go ahead and do a couple
more episodes to fill this week out. And then the last and then next week I won't be producing any
episodes. It's not that the reptilians got me or the Illuminati has me in their basement. I'm just
taking a week off for vacation. I've been on vacation for about two weeks now and I've still
been putting out episodes. But that last week I think I'm going to take off. So there's a possibility
that I might release an episode or two during that week. But for right now you're going to get four
more episodes. Then there'll be a week break and then I will be back. Don't know if we're calling
it season two yet. Probably not. Actually I already know I'm not going to do that. But so yeah,
we're going to take a week off. We're going to have about four more episodes take a week off and
we will be back at the beginning of September for a whole new batch of episodes just to give
it a little time. It's actually the hardest part of doing this show on vacation is not the recording
but the research. We're going to go ahead and see how this goes. It's possible that I'll release
episodes but just to heads up if I don't that's why I'm not kidnapped. Okay let's go ahead and get
on with the first story. So you've listened to the show long enough. Maybe you're a first listener.
Thanks for listening to Dead or Ever Radio. And you guys know I mispronounce stuff. This story
involves a tree and I'll probably going to mispronounce it too. It is called the Mancheele Tree.
The Manny Cheele Tree. Whatever it's called it's creepy and I never want to see one. So
okay so the more we'll call it the man the Mancheele Tree because that's the easiest way to pronounce it.
And I think that's actually the way you pronounce it but the Mancheele Tree
is a tree that's found in like the Caribbean. It's actually some in Florida and South America,
the northern part of South America. It is a tree that produces like fruit like trees do.
Delicious looking fruit apparently. So much so that they have to put signs in near the trees.
They'll have signs that say the leaves, bark, and fruits of these trees contain a caustic sap
which may be injurious if touched. Columbus described the small green fruits as death apples.
The trees are common along Caribbean shores. Avoid contact with any part of this tree exclamation
point. When I say signs I don't mean that there's like signs in the tourist lobby. These signs are
nailed up outside like right next to the tree. You're not supposed to go anywhere. The trees are
super toxic to actually almost all living creatures. There's certain lizards that like hang out in them
and eat the fruit and they have no problem with it. But animals stay away from them, humans are
supposed to stay away from them. If you chop them down the sap is toxic, can cause blisters. Eating
the fruit can kill you. It'll definitely blister up your throat and cause severe burning and start
to close up your esophagus. There's actually a researcher went to a beach and was like oh look
I would never just eat random fruit. I'd barely eat fruit at the store. So the fact of someone
walking along the beach and going hey look at here's this thing I've never seen. Let's put it in
our mouths. That's super bizarre. But anyway so this researcher was there with I think it was her
friend and they take these fruit and she gives it to her friend and says hey let's eat these.
Weird enough. 15 minutes later they're coughing and gagging. They poisoned themselves on this tree.
Now I know what you're thinking. This tree is so toxic. Why do we allow them to grow? Like why don't
we chop them all down? Oh and the other thing is even being under the tree while it's raining
can cause the liquid to come you know like the tree chemicals to come off and land on you
and start to burn you. Oh and you're not supposed to burn them either because the smoke will also
cause respiratory problems and skin problems and all that stuff. Super toxic. Super super toxic.
Now so your question is before I so rudely interrupted you earlier Jason if these trees
are so dangerous why do we keep them growing? Well because they're actually supposedly like
really good for the ecosystem and they help like shore up um what's this stuff called erosion. Like
they help prevent erosion on the beach so they do serve a purpose just you know stay away from them.
The legend goes that the explorer famed explorer Pawn Staleon was killed by one of these trees not
like it was an ant and chased them around but that the indigenous people stuck their spears into the
apple juice I guess or the sap and then shot them with one and if that arrow gets in you then you
start blistering from the inside out and you look like you made a bad wish from a wish master
and you killed them. That's a legend though they don't know for sure if that's what happened.
I just think it's interesting there are actually a surprising amount of plants that kill people
right on site not on site but I mean there's a good amount of just like poison that's around.
As I was researching this story I found out there used to be an issue with cow's milk being poisoned
because back in olden times and not like Assyrian olden times but Abraham Lincoln's mom died because
cows were eating this poisonous herb near where the cows were and then they made their milk poisonous
and then the farmers would just sell the milk. Well they didn't know it was poisonous but
you know they would just distribute the milk as normal and his mom died from poison milk
and then eventually the farm and this was a national problem it wasn't just this one farm.
Once the farmers realized what was going on they had to start like destroying the weeds
near the cows but cows are stupid they'll eat anything so yeah I mean there's a lot of poisonous
plants out there. I think it's interesting because hot peppers are technically supposed to be
not necessarily poisonous but the capsaicin is supposed to be a defense mechanism. The pepper
plants are like dude if I evolve them evolve and then they like evolved capsaicin and they're like
I'll do this is awesome no one wants to eat me I can freely just germinate nobody has to you know
I'm just shooting seeds out of me I guess that's how plants work and then they're like I have the
perfect defense mechanism who wants to eat spicy food dogs don't want to do it birds don't want to
do it and then we're like eventually humans are like oh dude this is spicy I'm gonna mass like
I'm gonna create a genocide like I'm going to grow you just for the purpose of cutting you open
when you get top spiciness I'm actually going to breed you to be as spicy as possible so that was
a defense mechanism that actually made us eat them made us go that you're more delicious than
that I don't know st germain root over there I don't think that's real but you get my point
it's a self-defense mechanism that actually encourages us to eat them so sometimes it doesn't
work manchill tree sometimes we we may start finding you delicious I won't know because you
sound terrifying having lesions in my throat would be bad I once I found out about butt herpes you
get a herpes sore in your butt that sounds terrifying as well anything that has to do with
your digestive system having open sores no way because you use it all the time so one thing you
use all the time whether or not you're sick or healthy or bedridden or run up a mountain
you gotta eat and you gotta poop so I don't want anything that has to do with either of those
having open so open sores I can have an open sore in my hand I can have an open sore in my ear but
I don't want one in my esophagus let's talk about john storm john storm actually is going to lead
into another story we're going to do tomorrow but to really I originally tried to do it all in one
story and I thought no because john storm is going to set up some of the major issues I have with the
next story tomorrow so a little bit of a teaser so who is john storm I know what you're thinking
hey isn't he johnny storm the meant for the human torch from fantastic four yes he is but that's not
the one we're talking about we're talking about a guy who calls himself john storm who believes
he is a superhero now not in the sense of stockton's batman we covered him on an earlier show who is a
concerned citizen stopping crime john storm believes that he actually has 100 mutant powers powers that
were given to him by the government so he believes that john storm is probably like 67 at this point
he's in his late 60s so let me tell you his version of events so when he was a baby he was brought into
the he was basically brought into mk ultra which was mk ultra was a secret government program to
test mind control techniques on us citizens for the most part so they introduced lsd into them
and they did all these sort of mind games and a couple of people died and a couple of people went
crazy and it got disclosed and it was quote unquote shut down now in john storm's world that's not
what happened mk ultra was about building super soldiers highly classified mobile units of just
you could drop him into vietnam and he would be snapping necks and killing people and then come
back to the base and smoke a cigar and the highest general general would be thank you john storm for
your service he believes that he believes that he was dropped into the jungles of vietnam by himself
taken out people one on one he believes he has a sonic scream attack that he yells and using
key energy defends you and it's the last sound you'll ever hear he believes he did not age from
20 to 40 did not show any signs of aging whatsoever he looked exactly the same he was the perfect
genetic specimen created by the u.s government and now he's turned against them now he knows
he knows they programmed him to fight and to kill in a dishonest war and all the special
weaponry that they gave him all the special training they gave him the psychic reserves the
just ability to do insane martial art maneuvers jumping off walls flicking people so hard in the
forehead they fly across the room and fracture their skull now he's going to use that those skills
to save us us homo sapiens us normal people he's going to use them when you come across stuff like
this there's always the question because i've read a ton about this guy there's always the question
is he delusional enough to believe that he was created by the u.s government oh oh oh and you're
thinking okay jason there are people who are trained by the u.s government who are dropped into vietnam
and take out people and stuff like that sure enough do they know spider-man because he does
john storm also in vietnam met peter parker a young black man who went by the co-named spider-man
who who is an expert acrobatic martial artist and they'd used to spar and he goes he had this great
move so john storms like six foot five but peter parker aka spider-man could do back flips over
his head and kick him in the back of the head john storms quick to point out he didn't kick me that
hard because he knew better it was just kind of a love tap because john storm knows that he can
actually kill spider-man in real life and then years later john storm is in new york and he went
to a circus and who was there a guy dressed as spider-man jumping around and john storm goes hey
it's you peter parker and he goes it is me and then they went into the dressing room and they
fought some more and they had a couple drinks so i mean there's the yes the military trains people
really really well they don't train people named john storm and peter parker aka spider-man
they don't train you and and he said what they do is they break your bones over and over again to
make your bones stronger that was something he endured as an infant infant that's not how it
works dude you get mic for okay i don't know why i'm quibbling because there's so much to cover
with this guy so yes he makes outrageous claims now let me go back to the thing so he's either
delusional and he actually believes that he knows spider-man and that he has these super he's a
trained ninja who has like 140 missions under his belt he actually believes that or he's ripping
people off and he's telling these stories to young men and women and being like yes i was a super
soldier once there's a picture of him wearing like 1970s clothes because he is actually quite old at
this point and on the picture it says in this photo are two knives eight shirking three chain weapons
and blah blah blah and you're like it's supposed to be like look at what a badass i am i have all
these weapons hidden and i can understand if i was a 16 year old boy being like oh yeah do this
guy's totally awesome this guy's a super soldier and he was trained by the government but now he's
using his powers to help us he constantly asks for money and that's what makes me suspicious
that he doesn't even believe these claims he constantly asks for money because at a certain
point we don't have any proof that he ever served in the military at all he has conveniently photos
of his MRIs that he posts online and it's like look at here that's an implant look at here that black
spot i don't know what that is well why are you circling it then if you don't know what it is but
anyway so he can provide photos of his MRIs but i'm not seeing any he talks about being discharged
or honorably discharged he talks about the the government now needs to stop him they're constantly
trying to kill him and at one point he went to his pharmacy and the pharmacy tried to kill him the
pharmacist tried to kill him and then he leaves the pharmacy he never goes into much detail with
these claims then he leaves the pharmacy and a car almost hits him and he's like yeah luckily then he
almost gets hit by an other car and another story i'm thinking how often is this guy jaywalking i know
this sounds super rambly and it might be but trust me this is going to pay off maybe maybe i should
have included it all in one episode so we have this guy who's a super soldier who was trained by
the US government they're they're out to get him and he's ready to fight them so that's his story
now we're going to jump to what's really going on post youtube videos of him showing crotty tricks
him singing songs and him complaining about the cops coming into his house and he's like
oh and the other thing all he does is talk about how he's diabetic and has an arcolepsy
narcolepsy to the point that he passes out and sleeps through his next next insulin shot
and gets sick how are you a super soldier bro how uh the explanation i'm sure he has one
that the all of the testing in him has started to break down his body and now he needs diabetes
and anti-narcoleptic medicine that's why he's going to the pharmacy all the time so he claims
he was a super soldier now he has our narcolepsy and he needs insulin shots all the time he claims
the government is after him but he gets disability so the government knows where it's at the government
wanted to stop him they could just stop giving him disability checks and say oh it was an error
it was an error or just say you know what john storm yes you are a secret operative that we created
and you've gone rogue guess what you're not getting your seat you're not we're not getting your
disability checks anymore he's created this world where both things can be true he depends on the
government for his medication and his money yet the he's the biggest threat to the government
and they're going to stop him at any cost even to the point of contacting his pharmacist to have him
killed and when that fails to have him slightly hit by a car a block away from the pharmacist
and when that fails have him slightly hit by a car later on you're praying on people one way or
the other you're either delusional and you're bringing people into your delusion or you know it's
all bull you know it's all fake and you're taking their time and their money it's one of the two
the third option of him actually being a secret a super soldier is flat out not true and this is
this is why i would i would believe that the government has a labs where they experiment on
people and turn them into anchoring candidates or super soldiers to me that's not outside the realm
of possibility at all they could be taken willing recruits and say we're going to test these drugs
on you and it's going to turn you into a more effective fighter it's going to give you a faster
ability to heal we're going to train you in the top techniques from around the world and even some
experimental fighting combat skills that we have i believe that's 100 possible do i believe the
government may kidnap people or take prisoners and also say we're going to put you under extreme
conditions to train you and if you fail no one cares because you're dead or you're a runaway
that's possible too a little less likely a little less likely than 100 but i'd still we know they've
experimented on prisoners in the past i'm not saying them experimenting on prisoners is unlikely
i'm saying them capturing you know kidnapping people or taking people out of prison and trying
to turn them into a super soldier but i definitely think that's within the realm of possibility
what i do not believe is possible for one second that you are a super soldier with all that training
who has gone rogue and now talks about taking down this power structure this this mk ultra power
structure and talking to other super soldiers and empowering them to do that and they still
give you disability i don't believe that for one second at all because either the government
wants to shut you up or they don't it's a problem with a lot of these conspiracy groups when i was
looking into super soldiers there was a guy who posted on the super soldier forum i tried sending
this message out once but the cops are already on this site they deleted my last message so i'm
retyping it how often have you been typing a message on like say facebook or a comment board on reddit
or four channel or something like that and it doesn't go through or the message gets deleted
before you were able to post it it's not the cops it's user error or site lag but here's my thing
if the cops deleted it like he thought how was he able to post the next message
don't you think the message saying the cops are on this website is more important than anything he
could have said before because he repeated what he said before and simply added the cops are on
the site they deleted my message while i was typing it delusional delusional delusional people
so either the cops are on your site and no information can get through or they're not
and you made a mistake either you are being hunted by the us government because you are a top
operative who has left the system and is exposing them or you get disability checks from them
so one or the other guys the reason why this is important is that all of this nonsense in a way
led to the death of a young man because he ran with these guys he believed in this conspiracy
and my hypothesis which i will lay out tomorrow so consider this part one my hypothesis
is that max spears the conspiracy theorist who died in 2016 suspiciously i believe that the
delusion that everyone was after him everyone from the highest government level so the doctor
led to this young man's death and that's why i get i'm getting a little irritated talking about
the super soldier culture but we're going to explore more about the death of max spears tomorrow
and i think it'll be a good episode i'm actually now that i've done it i'm glad that i've split it
up into two because i think you kind of have to delve into the insanity of what is a super soldier
and who these people are and then look at how that impacts a young man listening to these fairy
tales and buying into this nonsense dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address
you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio twitter is um @jasonocarpenter i'm trying to be on
twitter more i'm trying to get get doing that more and uh we'll be on instagram and all this stuff
when i come back from vacation we're going to hit up more social marketing and all of that stuff
guys if you love the show just share it that does the best for us we don't need patreon we don't
need any financial backing because the show is so low end we all are looking at getting sponsors
but again i want to put that onus on the sponsors they'll really want to put it on you guys but
if you guys can share the show either online or with people that you know that does wonders for
us that really i appreciate that find it it's very very helpful writing reviews for us helps a lot
as well so there's a lot of ways you can help us out um and it requires no money just a little bit
of time saying hey you know check out this show that does wonders for us and i know a lot of
you guys are already doing that because i can see the growth just keep pushing the show helps us a
lot if you enjoy it just keep pushing it dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but i'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys
you