When a young man is getting ready for bed one night, all of a sudden, he hears someone
outside of his house trying to get in.
But he goes to bed anyways, I don't know if this guy's braver than I am.
When he finally does get to sleep, he finds himself thrust into a world of tiny animals.
Are you going to describe a dream for us?
Hold on.
As he's sleeping, he finds himself in a world of tiny animals, UFO invasions, and a fairy
princess who loves destroying the planet.
And then I stop talking about a dream.
I'm pretty sure it's not a dream, but actually I think it's an encounter, we'll go into
it.
But after that story, we take a look at a simple yet unanswerable question.
I never thought about this before, and it really makes you think, why are there no fat
ghosts today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a
great day too.
I hope you guys had an awesome weekend.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is our newest Patreon supporter.
Everyone get on your feet and give a good Dead Rabbit applause to Spear and Fang.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in Spear and Fang.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command, it might be two people for all, I know maybe it's a
dog named Fang, a man named Spear.
It's just one guy who really likes poking people.
Spear and Fang.
You're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about this show that really, really, really helps out a lot.
Spear, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Drive us all the way out to Garden Grove.
We're headed out to Garden Grove, California.
It's August 1979.
It's a warm summer night.
There's a guy sitting at home alone.
His name is Thomas Puzzo.
He's 27 years old and he's at home.
He's getting ready to go to bed, right?
I swear this is not a dream.
I swear this isn't a dream.
Thomas Puzzo, he's wearing little pajamas, a little hat, a little hat with a little fuzzy
ball on the end of it.
He's getting ready to go to bed and as he's shutting everything down for the night, he
hears something outside his house.
He said it sounded like someone was kind of jiggling the handle of his screen door.
He's like, "What in the world?"
So he goes outside.
He looks around.
There's nothing out there.
Warm, late summer breeze.
But nothing else.
He ends up going upstairs and putting his head to the pillow.
Now he says, "I went to sleep, but it didn't feel like sleep."
This is what it's interesting about.
This is where the story starts.
He goes, "He couldn't really describe how it felt.
He goes, "It felt like a type of sleep that you can't describe."
Not like a fitful sleep or deep sleep or something like that.
Almost a state akin to sleep.
Parasleep, something sleepy yet beyond.
Even I can't really clarify it.
But he's in this state.
He's in this kind of sleepless, sleeping state.
And the next thing he knows, he's in a wheelbarrow.
He's in a wheelbarrow and he's rolling down the steepest street in Garden Grove.
Whoa, whoa, gripping the sides, sweat flying off of his brow.
He's going down this street.
But the entire city is emeshed in darkness.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,