A man visits his neighbor one day, and that's just the beginning of a mystery.
Has China developed a drug that is so addictive you can't live without it?
And then we travel to Roswell, New Mexico, a very famous location if you're a fan of
UFOs and aliens.
But an interesting theory has popped up.
Is it possible the craft wasn't from another planet that it didn't contain grey aliens,
but instead contained the bodies of handicapped Russian children today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a ton of stuff to cover, so much stuff, we're just gonna jump right into it.
Whee!
Let's go, let's get started.
Come on, get up, get up, let's go.
Okay, there you go.
Wanted to see you moving.
First off, let's hop into Jason Jalopy.
We're headed to David, Kentucky, December 23rd, 2019.
Two days before Christmas, one day before Christmas Eve, December 23rd, 2019.
It's a cold wintery day in David, Kentucky.
And a dude wakes up one morning and goes, "I'm gonna go see what my neighbor's up to.
So I'm gonna go walk over there."
His wife's like, "You don't have to announce everything you're gonna do.
I'm getting up out of this chair right now and I'm gonna open the door and leave."
And the wife's like, "Oh my god, why am I still with this guy?"
So our neighbor, we'll just call him David, he doesn't have a name.
David of David, Kentucky, walks out of the house.
I am now stepping off the porch, he yells to his wife as she's filing for divorce.
He begins walking across the yard to visit his neighbor.
Now his neighbor, Jonathan Watkins, Jonathan Watkins, 38 years old.
Not to be confused with Jonathan Winters, which none of you did because not only do
those names not sound alike, most of you don't know who Jonathan Winters is.
But if you do know who Jonathan Winters is, imagine the rest of the story.
And Jonathan Watkins as a 400-pound baby.
Because that's basically who Jonathan Winters was.
Imagine a fatter version of that guy.
Okay, that doesn't work either.
Who is that guy?
Louis Anderson.
Imagine a fatter, older Louis Anderson.
If you want to...
Like I don't even know who Louis Anderson is.
I'm not as old as you are, Jason.
Well, anyways, go look those up.
Pause the podcast.
Go look up a photo of Jonathan Winters dressed as a baby.
Come back and then we'll get started.
Okay, you did that.
I trust you guys did that.
So, David, hey Jonathan, I want to see what's up.
And the door opens up.
And Jonathan Watkins standing there, 400-pound human baby, covered in blood.
David thinks this is odd.
Normally people aren't covered in blood until much later in the day.
It's a mystery is afoot.
And the neighbor asks Jonathan, hey, what have you been up to?
And this is the quote.
This is what Jonathan actually said to his neighbor.
"I've been skinning dogs."
Hmm.
David thinks to himself, interesting.
But that can't be true.
Despite the fact that he's covered in blood, which is oddly suspicious, I don't think
he's been telling the truth.
Because this is actually from the article that I got.
This is from the Courier Journal, an article written in the Courier Journal.
This phrase appears, this might be one of the best sentences that I've seen in a long
time.
This is a quote from the article.
The neighbor told police that he did not believe Watkins because of past mental illnesses.
So basically, David is looking at a blood-covered 400-pound human baby who admits he's been
skinning dogs.
And David goes, hmm, you know, if another rational person had told me that, I would
believe that story and I would call the cops immediately.
But because you have a history of mental illness, I think you're lying to me, sir.
Good day, liar.
You fabricator of facts.
David leaves.
Now as David's leaving the porch, he's like, hmm, so he is covered in blood, but because
of his history of mental illness, I think he's lying.
I don't think he's been skinning dogs.
And as David's leaving the porch, he looks over and he sees on the deck animal skins.
Aha, a clue, he thinks to himself.
Interesting.
Another piece of this puzzle.
Maybe those skins were there when he purchased the house and he just has, he's cut himself
very deeply, right?
David again just goes home at this point.
Doesn't call the police.
Man admits to skinning an animal covered in blood.
Animal skins on his porch goes home and then he's sitting there and he has his feet.
I'm propping my feet up on the chair.
He announces loudly into his living room.
His wife's suitcases are ready to go right out the door.
And then he goes, oh, you know what would make this day even better?
Forget the mystery.
Forget the bloody man next door.
The animal skins, you know what would make this day even better?
Hanging out with my two dogs.
Rusty Coco.
He yells off Rusty Coco.
That's two separate dogs.
And honestly, I don't know.
Not the dog's not name Rusty Coco and I don't know what the actual names of the dogs are.
And I think it's kind of moot at this point because we, you should see what's going on.
I'm sorry to start the episode off with this story, but Rusty starts walking around Coco.
Rusty Coco and his dogs are gone and he goes, hmm, let me get out my pipe.
Let me get out my Sherlock Holmes hat.
So let me put together the clues today.
The blue, the blue's clues.
Let me go back.
Me and Steve are going to go back with these blue's clues.
First off, my neighbor is covered in blood.
Secondly, he said he's been skinning animals, but we have to disregard that because he's
insane.
Hmm.
I found two animal carcasses on his porch and now my dogs are missing.
So he sits there for a while and then he goes, I, you know, I should call the cops.
I really should call the cops.
Cops go over to homeboy's house.
Open up, open up sir.
Jonathan Watkins opens the door, still covered in blood.
This time holding a knife.
Police are like, whoa, whoa, what's going on dude?
And he says, quote, I'm making myself a doggy coat.
They know he has a history of mental illness as well, but they, they arrest him.
And David, the neighbor is looking out the window and he's like, hmm, I wonder why the
police are there.
I wonder what could be going on.
Rusty Coco.
So that is the story of Jonathan Watkins, 400 pound human bloody baby who killed dogs
allegedly.
Again, maybe the dogs had heart attacks at the same time.
Anyways, he was making a doggy coat.
So that's that story.
There you go.
That's a good way to, I realized the other day I go, I build this as a true crime podcast,
paranormal conspiracy and true crime.
And I realized this the other day when I was doing the story about the guy injecting stuff
and it was testicles in the middle of McDonald's.
I thought this isn't what people think of when they think of true crime.
When people think of a true crime podcast, they think of serial killers and, and murderers
and stuff like that.
Not vagrants exposing themselves in public and injecting drugs into their testicles.
Not people making doggy coats.
Not any of the other weird things I've covered.
But honestly, I kind of like this true crime stuff better because the murder stuff just
kind of gets old unless it's super weird.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story though.
Now our next story is actually a request.
So we're leaving behind David, we're leaving behind David Kentucky.
We're going to buy him puppies though.
Here you go.
We're actually going to buy him puppies with the money we get from our Patreon because
this next story is actually a request from a Patreon user.
So Lori sent me this story and Lori, we're going to use our money from Patreon to give
him two little puppies.
Here you go.
And he's like, oh yes, two little coats.
And I'm like, what?
And he was in on it.
And I think he was the mastermind the whole time.
He's like, yes, evil doer.
I know you're making those coats.
He's like, but master, you're the one who sells him online.
And he's like that guy's obviously mentally ill.
Cops are arresting him.
Don't worry officers, all dispose of this evidence.
His eyes shifting from side to side.
He goes down to his basement.
He's sewing it together.
Want something done?
You got to do it yourself.
The entire basement full of dog skins and then in the corner, his wife's skin as well.
Leave me, will you?
Leave me.
Okay, apparently he became the crypt keeper.
Apparently this anonymous man whose neighbor in real life killed and skinned dogs is now
the most evil villain in the story.
The camera pans out of his basement window, goes up into the clouds, credits roll for this
fictional story I just made up.
And anyways, we're headed off to China.
Now this has nothing to do with coronavirus.
I'm not talking about coronavirus.
But this was a request from a Patreon user, Lori.
I just want to make sure that I say that because that kind of might have gotten lost in my
fictional world there.
So really, really thank you for the Patreon support.
If you want to support the Patreon, it's in the show notes.
If you can't support the Patreon, just help get the word out about the show.
That really helps a lot.
Supposedly there's a new drug, right?
So we're in China.
There's a factory.
No one's working there right now.
They're all sick.
This conspiracy has kind of been waylaid by what's going on over there right now.
So we go into a factory and it's completely empty.
The bodies are stacked 10 dead on the factory floor.
But that's not because of coronavirus.
That's just because it was a sweatshop.
But also now they're stacked 12 dead because there's also people dying in the floor.
In this factory, these little vials going down an assembly line.
This chemical is known as DYXJU.
Now the reason why we know about this chemical is from John McAfee, inventor of antivirus
software.
I don't know if he invented it or if he's just the guy behind the marketing dude.
He might be the Pillsbury dough boy of the virus software.
I have no idea.
The only thing I know about John McAfee is that he believes in quantum suicide to the
point that he put a loaded revolver into his brain in front of a reporter pulled the trigger
and he goes in another reality.
My brain's blew out but in this reality I'm still alive.
Whatever.
And he is alleged to have killed a man.
Killed his neighbor actually.
Maybe his neighbor was making too many doggy coats.
But that's not what we're going to talk about here.
You can look all that.
You're like I want to hear about that.
No you don't.
It's kind of lame.
But that's all just he's just a weird guy.
So when he tweets this thing about DYXJU it's kind of par for the course for John.
Good old Johnny.
Here's this tweet that he had.
The Chinese government has created a revolutionary drug called DYXJU.
It is absolutely zero effects on physiology or consciousness.
That's kind of a lame drug.
You're like do let's go and do this drug that does nothing.
Absolutely nothing to us.
Yeah man.
I can't wait to just sit there and think normal thoughts.
It is absolutely zero effects on physiology or consciousness.
Do any drugs have effect on a physiology?
Like do you take a drug and you turn blue?
Like aren't they all consciousness?
I guess like cocaine makes your heart race.
That's not a good one though.
It is absolutely zero effects on physiology or consciousness.
People behave normally.
It has zero side effects except one.
This ingested the urge to re-ingest approximately 24 hours later becomes extreme.
For those who asked what's the point?
Imagine a government that could control a population using drugs.
Been done before.
Those are, that's his asides, his little parentheses.
Let me go back to this.
Imagine a government that could control a population using drugs.
Been done before without having to deal with the side effects or changes in society brought
on by the drugs.
That drug could be the most valuable substance on earth.
So obviously there's a couple different questions here.
One, how did he find out about this?
Now he's supposedly like maybe like more enlightened than the rest of us.
He's definitely richer than a lot of us.
Maybe he has access to this stuff.
Whistleblower sent it to him.
He's getting this info fed to him from somewhere.
He uncovered it himself.
He was on submission.
He was looking for more neighbors to murder.
He's like I think I have some neighbors in China.
Kicks down a door.
And it turns out that there's really making this stuff.
So that was his tweet though, right?
Regardless of where he got the information from, he's definitely revealing this to us
to let us know about DYXJ.
Now I'm looking around and other people are going whoa dude this is like trippy because
those Chinese man they're gonna like take us all over and they will use this drug to
do it.
You know slip it in our water supply or just give it to us willingly and tell us it's
something cool and then we're addicted to it.
Government will control us.
And I was doing my research, I was looking all over for this stuff.
I came across a website called, it was an outdoor website called 24 hour campfire.
It's always weird to me how mainstream conspiracy theories have become.
Because when I was reading them they weren't cool at all back when I was like 12.
And I got into all this stuff a long time ago like in the 1980s.
There's real underground stuff.
And now a website dedicated to like camping gear and backpacks and stuff like that.
It's talking about this.
I guess they probably have a survival contingent on that website but still it's odd.
I've come across ghost stories on motorcycle forums.
We talked about that a long time ago.
It's drifting, drifting forums.
Just everyone kind of loves talking about this stuff.
This website 24 hour campfire has a user named Jeff A. And he broke the code.
He broke through the Chinese conspiracy.
And if you're listening to this at work turn it down or put your headphones on because
I'm going to have to use some profanity, which I rarely do on this show.
Because I listen to podcasts at work and I hate it when...
That's why I don't really use a lot of profanity on this show.
I listen to podcasts at work myself and I like to listen to podcasts that don't necessarily
always need headphones.
So, here we go.
DYXJU.
This is what Jeff A. pointed out.
If you shift to the right for each of those letters.
D is F.
Y is U.
X is C.
J is K.
Fuck you.
And then you can be I, but I think that it...
Then it's just fuck I.
But basically it's fuck you.
And then it's basically revealed to be a troll.
So the people on the campfire forum, like the threads going pretty well and then that
release and people are like, "Oh, yeah.
Look at me.
Look how dumb I am that I thought that this was actually real."
People started then posting that on Twitter.
They're like, "Dude, it's a troll obviously.
John gave you this information.
It's an acronym.
It's a little code.
It's just fuck you.
It's not a big deal."
Now, generally, I've been proven wrong, proven wrong on this show.
People have said what you reported, not disputed.
People have said what you reported was actually an internet hoax.
And here's the article proven in.
And I've issued corrections and go, "Oh, yeah.
It wasn't an internet hoax."
And that's part of the problem.
John McCat, and that's what you should do.
You get caught out.
You just get caught out.
There are 388 episodes.
If 10 of them are provably false, not because I was lying, but because the information I
was giving was wrong.
Who cares?
Or, you know, 20 or 30 or whatever.
Anyways, John McCat gets called out on this, and then this is his tweet.
Of course.
The full name of the drug shifted right one key is fuck you.
Okay, you're admitting to it.
He goes on.
An accident?
I think not.
We don't think it's an accident, John.
We think it's actually a troll.
It's a troll on purpose.
But anyways, he continues.
An accident?
I think not.
The Chinese are coming soon.
Eat no- This is not a joke.
I'm not making this next two sentences he actually wrote in public.
Eat no Chinese food?
Okay, you know, it's fine.
No fortune cookies.
What?
What's wrong?
Fortune cookies aren't- I don't even think they're traditionally Chinese.
No sing-tow beer.
I don't even know- How am I supposed to not drink something I didn't even know existed?
Fine, done and done.
I don't even know what that is.
And then, and no, cunnilingus with Chinese women.
Is that how this is spread?
Like why those particular things?
Like, I can understand they're putting- they may be putting it in their food.
I don't know how they're putting a liquid into a fortune cookie.
It might be the driest thing ever constructed.
Sing-tow beer, sure.
Don't know what it is.
Never even knew it existed.
I promise you I'll never drink it.
Maybe they're putting it in the drinks.
And no cunnilingus with Chinese women.
The only way it could get into the woman's system is if she took it herself.
So are they already on this drug?
And also now that I think about it, okay, but is John saying it's cool to just blow
a bunch of Chinese dudes?
Like, oh no, no, you can totally do that.
Meet Jet Li, take him in the bathroom.
Blow him to your heart's content.
But no, not with those women!
So anyways, he's obviously a lunatic, allegedly.
And a lot of people pointed this out.
There's a lot of substances like DYXJU on the market.
It's called food and water.
Like it has no real effect on you or your consciousness, but you need it every 24 hours.
The need to re-consume food and water every 24 hours is great.
And governments can control you by limiting those.
So I really appreciated the recommendation lawyer.
I thought it was an interesting journey.
Because yeah, at first you're like, "Hmm, this seems like some weirdo conspiracy thing."
And then in the end you're like, "Oh, it's just one weirdo conspiracy guy spouting something
off."
Then probably it may be 10% of the people who read everything still believe that the
Chinese government have created this drug that will turn you into a drug addict zombie?
You're just basically a normal person.
You just want it every day.
Which food, water, and sex.
It's basically that.
But in a water form, apparently one of the transmission vectors of it is going down on
Chinese women.
The whole thing's absolutely bizarre.
So I appreciate the recommendation.
Because I love reading bizarre stuff.
So let's go ahead and move on to our last story here.
And our last story is kind of short.
It's actually interesting because for the implications of it, there's really not a lot
of information to back it up.
It was extremely controversial when it was released.
So there's this author/journalist named Annie Jacobson.
She specializes in writing books about secret groups, not like secret groups like Illuminati,
like actual government funded secret groups.
She's had books about the Operation Paperclip where the US government brought Nazis over,
changed their identities because we wanted them for the rocket program.
That's pretty common knowledge.
She has books about CIA paramilitary armies.
She has a book about the government looking into psychokinesis.
These aren't super unknown conspiracy theories.
But she tends to focus on the government side, DARPA, secret stuff that's going on.
Now she wrote a book called Area 51, An Uncensored History of America's Top Secret Military Base.
Getting the history of this place that supposedly doesn't exist.
For the longest time, the government refused to even acknowledge it existed.
But now they'll acknowledge it exists.
They don't acknowledge what goes on there.
So she's doing this book.
And in the book she's detailing the history of the base, right?
But then the last seven pages of the book is about Roswell.
It was a bombshell when it came out and it almost immediately got swept under the rug.
So let's go ahead and take a look at these last seven pages.
We are actually taking the Carbindercopter.
We are going to land in Roswell, New Mexico.
And we are going to watch the crashing of the alien craft in this desert.
Skipping across the ground.
Smoke pouring out of this disk.
Come on guys, let's go see some grays.
We're running through the desert with our flashlights, our pitchforks.
We have those two just in case they're still alive.
We're going to stab them.
We're going to stab these aliens.
We get there.
We get to the crash disk door.
Trying to open and I use my immense strength.
Pull it open.
You guys are all amazed.
A couple of you are turned on.
I'm like, no time to be attracted to me.
You save that for later.
Let's go and we go into the disk.
And there we see the three famous gray alien corpses.
Just laying there.
And I'm like, no.
I wanted to kill you myself.
Military shows up.
Helicopters.
And they go, they pull the bodies out, take them to the lab.
One of them gets autopsy for Fox's alien autopsy in the future.
So on and so forth.
You know the basic story of Roswell.
Turns out none of that stuff is true, by the way.
I found out while I was--
that's how I always thought the story of Roswell happened.
And it turns out that apparently some dude was just walking by his ranch on June 14th
and saw a bunch of debris and didn't think anything of it.
There was nothing spectacular about all the garbage he saw in this field.
His name was William Brazel.
June 14th, 1947 he sees this.
He goes, he leaves.
It's not until July 4th that he goes back to the area for whatever reason, for work,
and goes, you know what?
I'm going to put some of this stuff as a samba.
He drags some of the debris to be underneath a bush.
And to kind of like hide it, because he's still like, yeah, it's nothing.
He starts hearing stories about flying saucers in the media.
And then either June 6th or June 7th, he calls up the authorities, calls up law enforcement,
says, "I've been reading about them flying saucers and I-- there are some weird debrises
out in Roswell."
So then they go out there.
And then July 9th is when the first article is written about it on the Roswell Daily Record
local newspaper.
And in that article there, like it was a balloon.
It was a balloon.
Like, if you read the Roswell Daily Record article that was written, the closest report
to it was not spectacular in any sort of way.
They really explain in the-- I could read you the quote.
Not going to, but I'll read you this part.
When the debris was gathered up, the tinfoil paper, tape, and sticks made a bundle about
three feet long and seven to eight inches thick while the rubber made a bundle about
18 or 20 inches long and about eight inches thick.
And all he estimated the entire lot would have weighed maybe five pounds.
There was no sign of any metal in the area which might have been used for an engine and
no sign of any propellers of any kind, although at least one paperfin had been glued on to
some sort of tinfoil.
So that is being written on July 9th, 1947.
So I have no idea where all these stories of flying discs and alien bought.
I mean, it seems to be pretty obvious that what was found out there was a bunch of tinfoil
paper and tape.
But whatever, whatever.
Let's assume the traditional thing, because even Annie Jacobson's story assumes it's more
than that initial report in the Roswell Daily Record.
That a disc did crash in Roswell.
But while the story is already out, so now we're back into how people believe Roswell
happened.
The story is out, people have already believed that a flying saucer has crashed.
And actually the story didn't really become famous until the 70s.
Again, there was huge time difference between what had actually happened and when people
actually started paying attention to Roswell as an event.
It was a long period of time.
You might have had one or two people really into it, maybe four or five.
The numbers don't matter.
What I'm saying is, as a national thing, as like a plinch pin in the UFO story, that didn't
start until decades later.
So anyways.
Let's pretend that the myth is the fact that the saucer crashes, the military retrieves
these bodies, and they're autopsying them and they realize, whoa, these are definitely
they don't look human.
They're big old heads and tiny little bodies and all sorts of stuff.
But doing an autopsy, they are definitely, they are definitely, definitely human.
Because this is the theory that's put out in Annie Jacobson's book, in the last seven
pages of a book that other than these last seven pages was just a history book of a base.
Then it goes off into this weird thing.
Stalin did not have a nuclear bomb in 1947.
And Stalin realized that he needed to do something.
He needed to do something now and he needed to do something super, super weird.
He wanted to scare Americans.
So he takes a bunch of deformed Russian kids, right?
Possibly this is, it's so weird that this is all kind of just crowning this conspiracy
theory.
Stalin, Joseph Stalin, leader of the Soviet Union, takes some deformed Russian kids.
Originally designed by Joseph Mengele himself, the angel of death, the Nazi doctor who was
doing all that horrible stuff in the concentration camps.
He was taking Russian kids and deforming them, making them look gross and all grody and stuff
like that.
And then put them in a flying saucer and you're like, wait a second, wait a second, wait a
second.
So Stalin doesn't have nukes but he has flying saucers.
Well, kind of.
Apparently the saucer was remote controlled and you're like, okay, this is even done.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
There was a Russian asset in New Mexico flying a saucer around with remote control full of
three disabled kids, right?
And then they crash it into the ground and then the military shows up and they're like,
oh no, it's aliens, it's an alien invasion.
Now apparently this wasn't the only UFO.
There are other UFOs floating around America.
This one crashed.
They weren't supposed to crash.
They were supposed to just fly around and eventually maybe land and all the kids get
out and like go to McDonald's and then people are like, oh my God, aliens are invading McDonald's.
But this one crashed.
Who knows what happened to the other one?
Who knows if any of this is real, right?
But apparently the CIA was talking to the National Security Council.
The CIA got a lead on something and there was a real fear that the Soviet Union was going
to use Americans obsession and fear of flying saucers.
Because see, flying saucers were big back then.
The Roswell event wasn't connected to them yet on a national scale, but flying saucers
were in vogue and they, free your mind, they, the CIA was afraid that the Soviet Union was
going to use saucers to either make Americans scared or we're going to use flying saucers
to overwhelm early warning systems.
People would be calling up phone lines, servicemen would be seeing all these flying saucers flying
around and when everyone was trying to figure out what to do then, you'd have bombers and
they didn't have nukes, but you'd have like bombers and jets and all that stuff flying
around.
So, she says this in her book and it's immediately lambasted.
They're like, so much of the story doesn't make sense.
I mean, it's all single source.
This part of the story is all single source from someone who worked at Area 51.
But at the end of the, it is ridiculous because I don't know how good remote controls were
back then.
I think it would have been easier to fly a plane and use these things as gliders to
trade like you launch them like you have a glider plane, it just flies for a couple
miles and then crashes somewhere and you would have a bunch of deformed kids bodies hanging
out of stuff.
It would panic people.
The very least you'd be like, Russia really has that deformed kid technology on lock.
They can do that in a heartbeat.
America, we're 50 years behind deforming children.
Get on it, scientists.
You could have done that.
I think that'd be easier, but maybe the Soviet Union, they didn't have nukes so they spent
all their money at Radio Shack buying all of these RC units.
Who knows?
The point is, is that really this scenario is, okay, I know this scenario is more realistic
than a vehicle being built for interstellar travel, passing around meteor showers and
supernovas and galactus trying to eat it, traveling the cosmos more than a solar system
away, Alpha Centauri at the least, and then comes Earthen and they're like, "Wooah!"
and they crash.
Like, that's stupid.
Like that whole scenario is dumb.
I think the most likely scenario, and I've talked about this before, is that aliens are
already here, that they're coming from within the planet or from underwater, that they've
been here as long as we have been, or longer.
That's the most likely scenario.
Or them coming from Mars or Venus is far more likely than them coming from Alpha Centauri
or Sirius or anything like that.
Or they're interdimensional.
But again, an interdimensional craft that can pierce the veil but then can't pierce New
Mexican sand.
That story doesn't wash either.
Anyways, so when you take away, unless the aliens are from here and that ship came out
of the water and then they just had a malfunction and crashed, it would be more likely, and
really if you look at it from a skeptics point of view, the stalling theory is far more likely
because it doesn't evolve any sort of technology that exists in science fiction, or any sort
of species that exists in science fiction.
It's just a cruel, brutal dictator, his country that already had a bunch of economic problems,
trying to build something that could fly and scare people, but they couldn't even do that.
It crashed into the ground and a bunch of bodies fell out of it.
That's far more rational than grey aliens from another reality or planet or solar system
just on its face.
And I'll say this, honestly, I think that's scarier.
I think that's a lot scarier.
Tell me what's more frightening to you.
A species from another solar system that may occasionally show up here, float around, duck
to a couple of people, and go home.
Or the enemy being the people next to you.
David in Kentucky, his enemy was the dog-skinning neighbor.
If the dog-skinning neighbor lived in New Zealand, you would read about it and be like,
"That sucks," but it doesn't affect you.
And maybe that dog-skinning neighbor eventually travels to David, Kentucky, and goes and
buys some popcorn and sees some hot dog walking down the street and takes that dog back to
New Zealand.
Terrifying.
But not as scary as living in the neighborhood.
The idea of governments doing this is scarier than aliens.
And this is why.
One.
Because obviously, the Soviet Union is still, obviously we still have UFO encounters and
abduction encounters, but the Soviet Union's not around anymore.
So you would have other governments doing this, most likely CIA, US government doing
these things.
You would have them not only with this equipment.
I'm not saying they have the ability to fly around super fast in teleports.
I'm saying how UFOs are described.
And so they have this technology that mimics sci-fi, but it's completely understandable.
It's not free energy.
It's not anti-grab.
It's some sort of device that actually is legit, but appears like a magician's trick,
appears to be paranormal.
You have the US government abducting people.
You have the US government taking cows and cutting them up and dropping them up to make
us afraid.
You have CIA operations all over the planet.
They didn't get scared of Stalin.
They didn't let Stalin's plan override our early warning systems.
They learned from this plan.
They perfected this plan.
And so those great aliens that are reported sneaking around in people's bedrooms, those
great aliens that people see when they're abducted aboard these ships, and see three
or four aliens walking around.
A lot of times described as being robotic.
They're deformed children, perfected to a point where they don't just look like three
raggedy old bodies, but children that are taken and reconstructed to look like creatures
from another world.
They've been working on this technology for over 50 years, and it's been perfected now.
That to me is more terrifying than aliens coming from another planet.
With that, when you read these stories about grays, they're actually human children, lobotomized
and transformed into these things.
Far more terrifying.
Because apparently there's a lot of them.
And around the world, every year, a lot of kids go missing and are never found.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
[MUSIC]