What happens when a religious belief inspires a wave of grisly murders?
And then we travel to France to spend the night in a quaint little hotel.
But it turns out that this hotel may finally teach us why.
We would never notice a time traveler walking among us today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvinder, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have some fun plans for the weekend.
We got a lot of stuff to cover here so first off let's go ahead and give a shout out to
one of our Thanksgiving livestream contributors.
Everyone on your feet give it up for Church Going Mule.
Wooo yeah everyone take a ride, take a ride on Church Going Mule.
Hop on his back and kick his ribs.
We're going for a journey.
Church Going Mule you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the show financially, you totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show that really, really, really helps out a lot.
Now let's go ahead, I want to start off with the time slip story.
I know I announced that as the main story and that's going to be the title of the episode
because I want to give you guys a warning.
The story about the crime wave, the grizzly murders, it's really grizzly.
So I'm actually going to save that to the second story so if you don't want to have
this story depress you for the weekend just listen to the time slip story.
Sailor V I'll see you guys on Monday I totally understand but for you perverts, for you totally
disgusting people out there, the grizzly murder story I've been thinking about for weeks.
It's so fascinating, it's so fascinating I can't wait to share it with you but I know
it's not everyone's cup of tea.
So we'll save that story for the second story.
So Church Going Mule let's go ahead and hop aboard the Carpenter Caboose.
Grab a shovel of coal and start scooping it in.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're headed all the way out to France.
Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga
Going all the way in that underwater tunnel that apparently connects America to France.
I want to start off by giving a shout out to a website called UFO Insight.
It's a really really good high strangeness website and this article like many articles
written on the website is by Marcus Loth.
I got most of my information from that website.
Check it out.
We're going back to the year 1979, specifically October 3rd, 1979.
And there's two married couples from England.
They're on their way to Spain.
So as they're driving through France, they see a little hotel and they're like, "Oh,
that place looks like a good place to stay."
I mean, technically it's a professional place to stay.
That's what they were built for.
So they pull up to the hotel and they walk in, ding ding, and then a bell hop walks out
and he's like, "Madame Moselle, yes, you are here.
Why isn't Italian, French accent, Mamma Mia?
You are here to stay the night.
I see ya."
And they're like, "Yes, bell hop."
And then the bell hop goes, "Sorry, we're full."
He teases people all the time.
He's like super courteous and carries your bags upstairs and goes, "No, sorry, no rooms."
And makes some carrying back downstairs.
He goes, "We don't have a room available.
There's no rooms here."
And so they're like, "Aw, man."
But then as they're picking their bags up and they're headed back out to their car,
there's a gentleman in old fashioned clothes standing there and he goes, "You know what?
If you're looking for a room, if you're looking for a hotel, go down the street.
You'll find a small hotel down the road."
So they get back in their car and they're like, "Man, that was a weird place.
Everyone had like eight different accents at once."
They're driving down the road and they follow its directions and they notice that the road
starts to get really narrow.
Another driving between these buildings and they're like, "Okay, can we do this?
It's like a Fast and Furious movie."
All of a sudden they're like driving on the walls.
They're driving through this narrow road and then all of a sudden...
That's the sound.
You don't understand what that sound was.
If you didn't know what that sound was.
That's a car driving over a cobblestone road.
All of a sudden the road became those little rocks.
Those little rocks they put in the mud.
So they're continuing to be like, "Oh dude, we need to get new shocks for this car."
They're driving on the cobblestone road and they see on the side of one of the buildings
a poster for a circus.
But they notice the poster, the circus poster looks really old.
Not just like it's all wrinkly and stuff like that.
It was an old-fashioned looking poster.
They keep on driving and eventually they see a sign that says "Hotel."
Perfect.
That's exactly what we were looking for.
And they all get out of the car and they go walking in and right when they walk into this
hotel it was old-fashioned.
That was the way they described it.
They walked in and it looked like an old hotel.
It had no amenities of the modern age.
They walked in, they didn't see any signs of modern devices.
There are no telephones like the bell hops like "Madame Mazzal, have you seen my cousin?
Have you seen my cousin?
He works down the street."
They see the bell hops standing there and there's no telephone.
There's no elevators either.
It's all staircases.
They check in, they get up to their room and they're like, "This place is so quaint.
This is actually like an old-timey authentic hotel.
It's actually so authentic.
There's no locks on the doors."
They're like, "What?
Where in the world would you possibly want to sleep next to a bunch of strangers and
not be able to lock if not barricade your door?
No locks on the doors."
And then one of the women goes, "Oh, if you think that's insane, look."
And she throws open these wooden shutters.
There's no glass in this window.
It's just wooden shutters.
I'm like, "This is kind of weird, but maybe it is like this new thing.
They're trying to be super rustic.
Get away from the modern age.
It's like super hippy and stuff like that."
No locks on the doors, no telephones, no elevators, no glass.
So they start taking pictures of this incredibly quirky hotel.
The next morning they wake up, they go downstairs and they get breakfast.
They have this really nice dining room.
They're eating ham and eggs.
They doesn't actually say what they ate.
And I'm just listening to stuff that I want to eat.
Sausage with four pancakes covered in syrup.
They're eating my dream meal.
And while they're eating, they see two men walk in and they're wearing these dark blue
uniforms with these little capes.
And one of them goes, "You know what?
They're dressed like old-fashioned French police officers.
Gen d'Arms is what they were called.
These Gen d'Arms are walking around."
And they recognize them as old-fashioned police dudes, but they don't really think anything
of it.
Again, maybe it's part of if you're going to be a police officer in the hotel, you have
to change into this old-timey outfit not to ruin the illusion.
They just continue to go about their business.
And at one point, they get done eating breakfast.
It's time to go.
And they ask someone, "Hey, how do we get to the auto route?"
I guess that's how they call roads over there.
How do we get to the auto route?
We're trying to head down to Spain.
People are like, "What?
What's an auto route?"
And they're like, "You know, it's the thing that you put your car on, you go down the
road."
And they're like, "What?
What are you talking about?"
At this point, you figure they're probably taking the rustic thing a little too far.
They're like, "Okay, buddy, we get it.
You're from the past, but can you just give us directions?"
And they're like, "We don't know what you're talking about."
So they're like, "Fine."
They go to check out.
And after having pain for two rooms and they had dinner that night plus breakfast this
morning, the bill is only 19 francs.
Which they're like, "What?
That's like the best deal ever.
Are you kidding me?
That's no money.
That's basically free."
And the bellhop guy's like, "Well, that's just what we charge here.
There's 19 francs for all that food you ate and the rooms."
So they're like, "This is dope."
So they paid them.
And then they end up getting to Spain.
They stay there for a couple of weeks.
They leave the area.
They find the auto route.
They drive to Spain.
They're there for two weeks.
They have a ball.
Again, it doesn't have that detail.
It doesn't say how much fun they had.
But we'll assume it was a fun vacation.
And as they're headed home, they go, "You know what?
We should stay at that quaint little French hotel that we stayed at.
First off, we don't think they know how to add money because it costs nothing.
But also it was just so nice.
It was so nice."
And then one of them goes, "Yes, you mean that hotel that we took a bunch of pictures
of while they were there?
They took a ton of photos of this really quirky, cool hotel."
So they actually drive back to France and they can't find it.
They drive around the area that they were in.
They can't find the hotel.
They continue to drive down these roads and they see the circus poster.
They're like, "Oh, so we know we're in the right direction so they kept driving on the
road."
But they didn't end up back there.
They're like, "What?"
And they go, "Not only did we not end up back there.
I remember the first time we saw the circus posters, the road was cobblestone, right?"
And they're like, "Yeah, but this is a regular road.
This is a well-maintained road that we're driving down."
And then they find the hotel that they tried to go to first.
That's where the dude said, "I know this place is full, but there's another place down the
road."
They find that hotel and they go, "Hey, can you direct us to the hotel down the street?"
And they're like, "What are you talking about?
I mean, sure, there's other hotels in France, but do you have one in particular?"
And they're like, "Well, it was this old timey one down the Cobblestone Street road."
People were like, "We don't know what you're talking about."
Well, there was an old-fashioned dude.
There was a guy dressed up in a nice suit who was here last time.
Can he tell us where it's at?
And they're describing this guy and people are like, "We have no idea who you're talking
about."
I mean, technically it's a hotel, right?
They don't keep a photograph and a description of everyone who's ever been there, but they
go, "It's not anyone who works here.
We don't know who told you to go down there."
But it wasn't us.
They were never able to find the hotel again.
They weren't even able...
I think you guys can see now this is a time-slip story.
They weren't even able to go down a road and find an old...
They find a version of it.
It's all rusted and there's a big old rat laying in it with a bellhop hat.
Nothing.
They couldn't find like that.
It was burnt down or anything like that.
They can't find the hotels or the remnants of the hotel or the fact that the hotel ever
existed.
When they get home, they have their film developed.
They're not really thinking at this point there's anything paranormal that went on.
They just figured everyone in France doesn't know where other stuff is.
They get their photographs developed from their entire vacation and they're going through
them and they go, "Oh, look, here's the photo.
Here's the photos of us getting in the car.
Here's the photo of us arguing about what the easiest way to get there is."
And then they got to the photographs that they took at the hotel.
There was no photos.
Like they get to like in the timeline of where it was in the film and there was nothing
there.
And at this point they go, "Okay, we know we took photos of the window shutters and
of the room because it was so weird."
And it was quirky.
And Jason keeps using that word but it was so fun.
We wanted to show people about this hotel but there's no photographs here.
And then they would go from their photographs of other places and it would just jump to
further in the journey and then photos of Spain and stuff like that.
So they had no photos and they knew they took photos when they were at the hotel.
Now they're starting to wonder what actually happened because you have four witnesses to
an event where they found this hotel.
No one knows where it's at.
There's no photographic evidence of the hotel.
Through their research they find out that that uniform, those two police officers who
walked in the uniform they wore was an old-timey French uniform, which is what they assumed
that they thought it was a costume.
That uniform hadn't been worn since the year 1905.
And it doesn't even place the story in 1905.
They're saying that was the last time they wore them.
Remember there were no phones or elevators or anything like that so it could have been
anytime 1905.
I mean not caveman times right?
There's a sabertooth tiger in the room.
Probably within you know maybe 1800s to early 1900s.
That would be the time period this would be happening in.
And this story was reported and at the time apparently it became very popular in the world
of the paranormal.
People were really really intrigued by this story.
Time slip stories are really really cool.
And Jeff underwent hypnosis because people were like is there anything else you can remember
about the places or anything else we know.
He underwent hypnosis and when he was in his hypnotic state he did not reveal any more information.
But he didn't reveal any less information.
Like well duh his memory right?
But no if he was faking it you figured maybe the story would change or something would
get left out.
But no it was the exact same story under hypnosis.
And the four of them believed, fully believed that they must have gone back in time somehow.
And this story was brought to us.
Marcus Lowe wrote the article that I got most of the information from.
He got it from a Jenny Randall's book.
Jenny Randall's is a huge paranormal researcher.
She's been in the game for a long time.
She's written a ton of books on it.
So that again is another authoritative source for this story.
And yeah at a time this was a very popular paranormal story.
What's so interesting about this story?
I mean the fact that four people went back in time.
Because time slips are great.
I love covering them.
The idea that at any point you could be traveling from point A to point B and end up in point
eight nine seven four.
It's fascinating to me.
Time slips, portals, all that stuff.
It's scary but cool at the same time.
But this story really raises a lot of interesting questions about what happens during this phenomenon.
The four people, the four travelers from our time, realized things were off.
Realized the police officers were wearing old timey clothes.
There were no phones.
There were no elevators.
There was no windows or locks.
But nobody commented on their clothing.
You have to imagine they had watches.
They had sunglasses.
And they had litigra shirts and slacks.
And no one was like oh what is that stranger doing with those odd clothes on?
That's why the police showed up to have them burned at the stake.
None of the people in the past commented on their clothing or the technology they had
on them.
And they paid their bill, their 19 francs bill with modern money.
They didn't have the Euro back then so they would have had to exchange it for francs of
the 1970s.
And they paid with money from the 1970s and it was accepted.
Now you may say the bellhop or the intaker, whoever is in charge of taking the money,
maybe they weren't that observant.
You would know if money was 200 years in the future.
You would know if someone went back in time from now to the 1980s and tried passing off
money, you'd get arrested as a counterfeiter.
It's so different.
Like you would have to be blind to not realize money had changed in 20 years, let alone in
200 years.
So when they were presented with modern currency, why wasn't it rejected?
Pulled out of a modern wallet by a guy wearing a modern watch.
Now a skeptic could say, skeptic wouldn't believe any of this story, but a skeptic could say,
well maybe when they exchanged their money, they just happened to get money from the 1800s
and maybe they all had classic watches.
So maybe that happened.
Maybe you couldn't tell.
Maybe they were wearing pantaloons and they had big hats with feathers in them.
Yeah, possibly.
Maybe they all just possibly happened to dress up as Renaissance cosplayers.
But I think that aside, this show, this is fascinating to me.
It may be, because a lot of people say, how come if time travel is real, we should see
time travelers.
Maybe we can't.
Maybe our reality.
Our reality is so hard coded into us that if someone slipped from 400 years in the future
or came back with a machine, came back in a time machine, we physically couldn't tell
the difference.
We would see them.
Like think about all those experiments they have where it's like observation, like you
have people playing basketball and then there's an elephant walk spy or a bear walk spy.
I'll put it in the show notes.
If you have no idea what I'm talking about.
But our ability to see absurd things is sometimes, a lot of times, hard to really comprehend if
we're doing something else.
Say working.
You're running a business.
So it could be that our reality, our time period is so hard coded into the way we observe
things we couldn't see someone from the future.
Just like they couldn't.
This is absolutely fascinating.
We have so many stories of time slips where people don't really interact with each other.
They just find themselves in a weird location.
They start to see weird things around them.
I'll try to put a couple episodes about time slips in the show notes, but this is one where
not only, this is an overnight time slip they spent the night here.
They ate two meals.
They paid their bill and a car.
They drove a car.
Don't forget about that.
They drove a car down a cobblestone street.
They parked it outside a hotel in the 1800s, got a room, and no one goes, "What in the
what is that outside?"
It may be when they looked, when the natives to that time period looked, it was a horse
and buggy.
Who know?
I mean, I don't even know what that sounds like when they're like, "What?"
The horse is just perfectly still.
And then when they get in the car and they turn it on, the horse goes, "Whaa, wha, wha,
wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha,
wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha,
wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha
wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha,
wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha,
wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha, wha,
The only out she saw was murdering a child. So a ceremony began to coalesce around these executions. People started to see these executions as very somber events as opposed to, you know, just two guys getting to fight and one guy gets murdered and that guy's being taken to the gallows or killed.
Ah, kill him! Kill him! Yeah, get rid of him! This one, when these women were killing themselves by killing babies, very somber event, people would start to have these costumes they would wear, like the family would show up and they would be wearing these costumes, and there'd be this procession, there'd be like this ceremony as this young woman is being executed.
And the government is getting very, very upset about this. This is supposed to be a deterrent. We're supposed to show, that's why we're making it so bloody, that's why we're burning the corpse. We're not giving it a Christian burial.
This is supposed to prevent people from wanting to do this, but now we got this whole rigmarole around it and we see these people actually venerating the women who are killing these children.
So the government started adding a little bit of torture to it. They're like, "Maybe this will prevent, maybe this will prevent desperate people from finding any way out of earth."
They added a whipping. They're like, "Oh, you've been a naughty girl, we're gonna whip you." They'd whip her with the whip. And I keep saying her because I do think that's predominantly that, but there were men who were doing that as well.
They'd whip them. They're trying to be sexist when it comes to murdering children. This is so horrible. So they'd whip you and you'd have to spend two days on the scaffold and when they executed you, they blindfolded you.
Now that doesn't sound like the worst deterrent in the world. Like no one wants to get whipped, right? But you're like, "Oh no, two days on the scaffold, I want to die. I'm glad that you're killing me."
And so that was the problem. For a while, this was not a... Remember, this was the number two reason for murdering a child in Sweden.
King Gustav III of Sweden was watching this whole thing and he goes, "We gotta do something. This is a societal ill." But people go, "What do you do?"
Like, they're just gonna keep doing this. People are gonna keep doing this. And what King Gustav says, you know what? Let's just change the law. What if if you killed a child, you didn't get sentenced to death?
What if if you killed a child, you were sentenced to life in prison instead? But they didn't do that, right? That would be...
Because there were other reasons why people were killing kids and you didn't want to have these people walking around even if they were in prison. And they ended up just leaving it as, "If you killed a child, you got the death penalty."
It's just an interesting story. As grisly as it is, it's so fascinating because we have that collision of a religious doctrine, which has changed now. Now, suicide is still looked down upon in the Catholic Church.
But that's not doing anyone any favors. When someone who has a mental health struggle and they kill themselves and then you tell the family members, "Oh, dude, yeah, sorry, that dude's in hell.
Sorry." Like now they've worked through that. Now the Catholic Church has changed, I believe. But I think there still are a lot of Catholics who do believe that when you kill yourself, you go to hell.
Or at least you're in purgatory for thousands, if not millions of years and things like that. So... Just fascinating story. I know it's super dark.
I know it's probably not the best way to wrap up the week, but it's been on my mind. It's just this amazing collision of true crime and religion, which we don't see that often. I mean, we see cults and things like this, but that's not what this was.
This wasn't some death cult. This wasn't a Jim Jones/Waco situation. This was an entire society of young women killing children, sometimes not even their own children. I don't even know how many were actually their own children.
I think they were just grabbing random kids and killing them, just so they could have an escape clause off planet Earth.
But don't worry, the babies went to heaven as well. Terrifying. Terrifying story.
You want to injure suffering, but you do nothing but bring unending suffering to the survivors, to the mothers of those children.
Just a dark reminder of what a depraved and depressed human can do what they're capable of. They're capable of the most atrocious crime possible, hurting a child.
But in Christina's mind, she didn't hurt anyone. She spared that baby. That baby went right to heaven. That baby would never fall in love and have her heart broken. No.
Christina was saving that baby as well as saving herself.
At least that's what she was hoping for when she felt that executioner's acts lop off her head.
DeadRabberRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Tiktok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend, guys.
Thank you, Miss.
[Music]