Today we go back in time to meet the very first battle rapper in ancient Greece, huh?
And then what would you do if you were confronted with a UFO who said it could give you anything you wanted and
Then told you to eat poop today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day, too
It's not clickbait. That's what those stories are actually about the weird episode first off
Let's give a shout out to one of our legacy patreon someone who's been supporting the show for a while CJ from the UK
CJ from the UK
CJ in the brain
That's the only way you can have your name pronounced from now on CJ
Thanks for supporting the patreon if you can't support the patreon totally get it
Just help get the word out about the show that also really helps out you can leave reviews
We could always use more reviews just talk about it online, but let's go ahead though and hop in the
Rabbit do we have a hang glider?
Let's hop in the hair glider. Oh, they'll only use this for one episode
CJ's like great. I get the
Experimental thing that we're hopping the hair the hair hang glider
Whatever whatever we'll just catch a cab hang gliders tied up on the top
CJ's like taking down driving a cab
Why my support is patreon?
Fine. We'll take the head wrap hair. We'll take the hair hang glider. We're flying off to Greece CJ's like yippee
We're headed to Greece. We're going back in time as well. We're going back in the year 540 ish
We're gonna meet a man named hippo knacks of a fetius now hippo knacks
We don't have a lot of his poetry not a lot of it
Survived, but he's very well-known at the time. He was well-known as a vulgar poet who hung out with the criminal class
I eat a gangster rapper, right? He would sit there and he was just busting flows writing this poetry down
He's like yo guys. I got a good one for you. Then he sits down with a chisel
And then he holds up the tablet they're like
Like and then he waits for his opponent to respond it's like 15 minutes
He's like oh yeah, he was this battle rapper who just write this vulgar poetry ran with the criminal class
He was super ugly as well. That's really what he was. I mean
That's not a good thing to be known for right being known as a vulgar battle rapper. That's fine
And being ugly, you know on that on your tombstone, but anyway, so people knew him in town. He was pretty famous
He was also a he was also a jerk to people that was another thing that kind of goes along with being a battle rapper
You're not gonna be like battle rapping about how nice the guy's toga is that makes it
He wants to marry this woman so he goes to the father and he's like hey
You might know me for my extreme ugliness and my battle raps. I'd like to marry your daughter
Now the guy he went to his name was buppalus buppalus is like
Have you looked in a mirror lately here? Let me invent a mirror real quick because it's super ancient Greece
He's sitting there. He's polishing something down. Here you go. Look how ugly you are
You're not marrying my daughter. Hipponax leaves now buppalus was not a good guy to mess with either. He was a master sculptor
Not he wasn't a statue himself
Sculptor he was the guy who made the statues
He is far well known in history of his work because it wasn't you know written down on scrolls and stuff
Survived when Rome wanted to decorate their
Colosseums and stuff like that. They were using buppalus statues
Had a little sign a little B at the bottom. They were using his statues. They took him from Greece
His artwork was used to fill temples in Rome. It lasted the ages buppalus decides to go
Not only can you not marry my daughter, but he starts making
sculptures of Hipponax
Who's this ugly guy so he starts making these comically exaggerated
Ugly statues I mean like hey look everyone this guy wanted to marry my daughter and people in town thought it was hilarious
Which it kind of is right? I mean maybe the first time but apparently this guy made multiple ugly statues
His work is celebrated
Hundreds of years later, but he just couldn't stop making the eighth ugly statue of this dude
So Hipponax
Responds the only way that he can he writes a poem
So Hipponax writes this poem about buppalus at the very first
Distract buppalus's mom's name. So you know where this is going
Bopalus's mom's name is artie artie, which means virtue and
Hipponax just drops this
Bopalus the mother effort with artie and
People were like he didn't just say effort. It was the Greek word for someone who?
bangs their mom the audience basically
Basically goes nuts at this point
Bopalus the man who bangs his mother with virtue is really what that line means because his mom's name means virtue
People were like what in the world is going on it continues it talks about his mom
Sorry this episode segment is not for kids
It talks for all the sex acts Bopalus does with his mom talks about him banging his mom talks about the mom
Giving oral sex to Bopalus talks about how such a loser Bopalus is that his mom
Has to have sex with him the audience is losing it
They're like dude. I haven't heard anything this funny since I've read this story of edipus rex
So I'm also like that wasn't a comedy. He's like I know but it was still funny
So this poem he also goes on to say like I'm beat him up
Beat him up which is kind of a mild thing right like you're like oh dude you bang your mom your mom's doing all this stuff
By the way, I'm gonna punch you in the eye
That doesn't matter anymore you some of this horrible stuff about me
There's these ugly statues of hippon acts around town, but everyone in town has heard this poem at this point
It's a viral hit in a time when viruses were wiping out towns. This one was a snappy viral hit
Bopalus killed himself
Because people would not stop laughing the diss track was so
hard
This master sculpture
Sculptor getting not a statue
hung himself
Due to a diss track. We don't really know what happened
We don't know if hippon acts felt bad about it after that or if he did a little b-boy pose
He could have like as Bopalus is being taken into the grave
He's like he invents cardboard puts it over the grave and starts breakdancing
We don't know I would imagine hippon acts was it was a jerk
But you can be a jerk and still feel bad about causing someone to kill themselves
But yeah, is that the very first diss track? I would argue so I don't think anyone was dropping stuff during the odyssey
They're like yo you turn into a pig. That's the only thing I know about the odyssey
Yo, I shot an arrow through hoops. You made some hoops, but a shot and there
I don't even know if that's from the odyssey or from like an episode of duck tails or something like that
But didn't they do that didn't they have a
Like Robinhood you didn't oh Odyssey dude odysseus like come back first a bunch of people turn into pigs
Like his men they're on a boat and they left Troy
We should have a story coming up on Troy. I have to do a bunch of research on it
But he leaves Troy. He's floating on a boat and then they go to an island where Sears sees that and all of his men
Get off and they turn and turn into pigs and then he magically has a supply of hot dogs
Everyone's like he comes back to Greece. They're like what happened to your crew and he's like
Here have a hot dog a bunch of people turn into pigs and then he sails away and then
He goes back to Greece and his wife doesn't recognize him and his dog
Recognizes him and that was like to show how loyal a dog is over your family
And then he's like good dog and then they go you're not Odysseus and he goes
Yeah, I am and then he has to shoot an arrow through a bunch of stuff a bunch of soldiers
But she's all just trying to take him and he shoots arrows through him
No, isn't there like a bunch of hook a bunch of circles and he shoots an arrow through it
This is a very long explanation for a joke
They probably didn't make any sense
But anyways, that is the story of Odysseus if you have a book report to on the Odyssey soon
You have to have read Odyssey just listen to that. I should do a whole audiobook. I should do a whole podcast series
Of me reciting
Books that I've never read. I'm like the story of Beowulf. So Beowulf met Angelina Jolie
I should just do that. That should be a whole podcast
CJ from the UK. Let's leave behind old timey grease. Let's hop on the carpenter copter
We are headed out to new timey grease specifically. We're going to the year 1999. It's June 8th
We're leaving behind old statues and stuff. We got some brand new togas. I got a statue of an ugly dude
I'm hanging on to it. We're flying over grease. We're specifically going to Anno Cortesi Anno Cortesi
It's 2 a.m. In the morning. There's a student named Demetres Helanus
He works at this farm. It's 2 a.m. And he has to go turn off some water valves
He's like, oh, it's time to go to bed at 10 10 p.m. Just like a normal human and then he wakes up at 2
Oh my god, the farm's flooded. I left the water valves on. He obscended his motorcycle
He drives through the pitch black farm to go shut off the water valves and then
He looks up and there is a golden triangle in the night sky
Just this bright golden light like someone cut a triangle out of reality. Yeah, it's 2 a.m. Dude
I'm still getting used to the light and the triangle is just floating there and it says to him
Don't be afraid
I am the Almighty. I will do whatever you ask of me
So you think for a second, right? This is an opening, right?
Whatever you ask this this triangle appears says that it's the Almighty so you're assuming it's God
That'll be wrong assumption. We'll find out soon. You can have anything about it for a second
You can have anything which you could ask for like I mean obviously you could go
I want peace and love for everything in the environment to be
Or you could be like I want to have the number one podcast in the world
Or anything in between right? Maybe you want to help the environment and have the number one podcast
Who knows but you have anything to ask this triangle?
Demetrius thinks about it and goes yeah, I have these horrible migraines have these horrible migraines
Can you get rid of them and let me let me add something else on that? I want to quit smoking and the triangle goes done
Thinking small but those are important things to Demetrius. He the migraines immediately go away
He's like oh, oh, that's so good. Usually when I have those migraines. I'll listen a triangles in the sky
Migraines gone and he pulled out his pack of cigarettes and throws them in the ground
And he feels the bitter taste that's enveloped his mouth for years due to smoking just disappeared
He's never had a cigarette sense as far as we know
So the triangle held up its end of the bargain triangle disappears
That is a great night. You met a triangle
Give you the wish that you wanted you got two wishes and two is that you know you're fast
You got to outthink the triangle. He's out the water valves now. He pulls out his flashlight. He's looking around
Triangle appears above him was a what oh great am I gonna get another wish?
The triangle appears and it goes in reference to his flashlight throw it away. I
Will light your way from now on he's like, oh, okay
I mean you did cure me of an addiction and got rid of my migraines
So he tosses the flashlight and now the triangles just kind of floating there. He's like working on the valves and he's like
Imagine he's thinking this is kind of a weird use for divine power like I had a flashlight
It worked just fine, but then the triangle goes now
I want you to go and tell all of your work buddies about me
The guy's like, I don't really have any friends at work. The triangle's like, yeah, I'm trying to get you to meet
I'm trying to get you to meet other people, but go tell your work mates about me
So to meet you's like, okay, you know the triangle did cure my addiction
So I should go do that so he goes to like the workers shack and he's like hey guys. What's up?
It's 2 a.m. Oh, by the way, remember everyone's asleep except this guy. Hey guys guys wake up wake up
You won't believe it. There's flying triangles out there. It got me to stop smoking and
It replaced my flashlight and what's like dude go to bed. What are you doing? Did you leave the water valves on again?
He's like go to bed dude. It's like 2 a.m. He's like, huh, so he goes back out
No one believes him in the shack goes back out
The triangle appears again. He goes Demetrius pronounce your name differently this time Demetrius
You went and told the workers about us and they didn't believe you now
Go tell your girlfriend about us and he's like what triangle's like go tell your girlfriend about us
And he's like well they did cure my migraines
His girlfriend isn't living a shack on the workplace. He has to get in his car. He drives all the way to his girlfriend's house
He knocks on the door wakes her up. What is it? Maybe two thirty? It's like dude
You won't believe this triangle outside. It's fine triangle outside
Caused me to stop smoking no one will believe me is a girlfriend's like I don't believe you either and it's 2 30 a.m
What are you doing now? What did you leave the water valves on again? It's like listen not about the water valves
Okay, I should have used my wish that everyone forgot about the water valves. No, there's fine triangle out there
The girlfriend doesn't believe him so he gets back in his car
He starts driving back to the farm remember this triangle can easily just appear and show itself to the girlfriend to the workers
It's basically at this point making him sound insane. It's like
Like it's looking in through the window. It's like behind the blinds. It's like dude watch
You know, he's actually telling his girlfriend and you hear what she's saying. No, no, no
But she looks really mad and super tired
The aliens on the other side of this thing are laughing because at this point I think any casual observer would go
This isn't the almighty. This is definitely someone who's just pulling practical jokes at this point
Did cure him of his crippling nicotine addiction and his migraines and replace this flashlight to be fair
But it can obviously like show itself off and it's telling him to go off and tell these people and then it just
Disappears it's like hiding so now he's driving back to the farm and the triangle shows up and says get out of your car
Get out of your car and he's like what?
Well, you did and so he gets out of his car and he's still like miles from the farm and the triangle's like just run
Just run this one. I'd be scared of the triangle gets me out of my car now
It's like you run human he runs and he says he's able to run with superhuman speed
So he actually gets to the farm faster than if he took the car
That's awesome
Except for when he has to go back to the car later and he doesn't have super speed, but we don't know about that part
We just know that he gets this farm super fast the triangle appears above him
He's all alone in the middle of the farm. No one believes him and the triangle goes
You're pretty cool dude, man. You run super fast. He's like really you guys think I'm cool. They're like, yeah
You're so you're super cool, you know, it'd be really cool
You can almost hear the interdimensional creatures laughing on the other side of the void
You know, it'd be really cool if you you got that lighter, right? He's like, yeah, I got a lighter
He's like burn your hand. What what you want me to burn my hand? Yeah, dude
It'd be super like we burn our hands over here all the time
Burn it he goes on, you know
Haven't been steered wrong yet by these guys and he takes this lighter out starts burning his hand
Demetrius says he feels no pain during this but he can see he's holding the lighter on for so long
He can smell his skin cooking this smell
He said actually started to make him sick to his stomach. So he stopped and the triangle goes do it again
It's like what no
He sure it doesn't hurt. It's kind of weird that doesn't hurt, but this do it again. He's like, uh-huh
Get a little nervous now. He's lying
Burn he did it three times
Setting his hand burning his hand. He said never felt any pain, but he could smell the flesh cooking
Then the triangle goes
You know what would be really cool. He's like damn it. You know, it'd be really cool
You got a bunch of dirt in you. He's like what no, I don't they're like, yeah, no trust us
We have this special device that can determine a person's dirt amount in their body
You have a lot of dirt in you Demetrius
burn it out
Swallow the flame and burn it out
This story is interesting because we've talked about this on other stories the level of degrees like the first
Off the triangle shows up and says what do you wish and he gives it to him and then he's like
Replace the flashlight you replace the flashlight tell your workmates tell your old friends stuff like that
It's a matter of degrees if the very first thing the triangle goes. Oh sure. You don't have to smoke anymore
Swallow flame you'd be like no, but it's on a level of degrees
He's already agreed to do so much stuff that this triangle's told him to do with really no ill results
Other than the smell of flesh cooking when the triangle tells him to eat flame
He does it whether or not it actually burns out the dirt in his body because the triangle says you have the dirt in your body
You have to swallow flame to burn it out. I mean, I don't know if that happened at this point when I was reading the storm thing
And these aliens they're just a bunch of frat boy. I assume they're aliens honestly
Imagine two alien frat boys got a hold of a spaceship. They're their spacesuits have popped collars on them
They're flying through the galaxy and they see this dude out in the middle of nowhere and they're like, oh dude
Let's see how far we can push this dude
Because that's really what it seems it seems like just to be this slow escalation because we're not done yet
He's now swallowing flame
And then they go tell you what tell you what okay. That was we just wanted to test you now
We want you to hold that flame and he's probably thinking please no please no more flame related stuff
And they go we want you to sing this
Orthodox him you got to sing it three times while holding the lighter. You're like, oh, I can easily do that
I'm not burning myself. I'm not swallowing flame and he does it and the triangle is like good good a little pitchy a little pitchy
but
decent decent hymnal singing
Then they go. Hey, you see that dirt over there
Yes, yes triangle. Yes triangle. I see the dirt and it's like
Uh, you need to eat it now at this point I would go wait a second
Then I just burned the dirt out of me, but Demetrius
eats the dirt
Just walks over it takes a big old handful of it
Okay, to be fair. I don't know if it was a big handful
He's gonna taking a dirt clot and eating it, but he eats the dirt
And then I imagine at this point on this on this frat controlled UFO. It was a booze cruise
Someone else grabs the microphone at this point and was like dude. You guys are small potatoes, right?
Yeah, sure burning himself eating dirt. Whatever. Let me show you how it's done at kappa kappa gamma
He grabs the microphone and goes hey
Yeah, it's new voice. Uh, it's dimensional thing. Sometimes our voice has changed due to like, uh
Stuff it doesn't matter, but anyways new voice. I want you to get a cup of water
Demetrius like okay. I see where this is going. It's pretty fine. It's a cup of water and then the voice goes
See that fertilizer over there
Mix it with the water and drink it
Now Demetrius may not be the smartest guy on the farm. He's definitely the most gullible
But even he knows that fertilizer mixed with water is a
Extremely toxic poison. It'll create a concoction that will drop you on the spot if it doesn't you're definitely
Gonna be dead soon
But he trusts the aliens is there laughing on the other side. They're like, oh dude. He's really gonna do it
We're totally gonna murder this guy. Come on bleep blorp. Don't go that far. I'll tell you when I'm done
Bleep blorp says to the to the pledges
Tell you when I'm done. We're gonna push this guy as far as you can. He takes his fertilizer and water
Looks up at the triangle. You guys like after I do this, we're gonna be friends, right? You guys are gonna like me after I do this
Uh, yeah, dude, you you'll be like totally awesome. Demetrius is like, okay cool
look look look look
You can taste the fertilization you can taste the manure
But the fact that he can taste it proves that he doesn't die
So despite the fact that he the aliens now made him drink poison
It really he's believed it obviously the whole time he has superhuman powers. He's running fast. He's not being burned
So on his mind, he may be thinking well
They're gonna protect me from the fertilizer poison as well
So he trusts them and they do protect him. It doesn't kill him
We can look back at this and laugh and go man, this guy's so gullible. I would have never drank that
But at the same time I also have never ran a two miles in a minute and a half
So I guess there would be a level of that
But then just to top it all off to prove that these aliens truly are intergalactic frappers
They got this guy to drink what he knew as poison. How do you top that?
How do you end off a night after tricking a guy to drink poisonous manure water?
You get him to drink his own urine at this point as Demetrius is drinking his own urine
I imagine the aliens in the triangle just completely besides themselves laughing it up
Because there is no other reason why you would want someone else to drink their own urine unless you were trying to trick them
I can't think of one right, but Demetrius does drink his own urine
He's like now are we friends now? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're friends the aliens tell him also
I don't know this seems like a weird addition
Like they've been doing all this stuff all night and then they give the standard message like someday all the evil doers will be destroyed
It seems a little like she's a little anti-climatic after I drank poison and survived
But they tell him that and then the aliens leave but they can't leave without doing one last practical joke on this dude on poor Demetrius
Maybe that he's suffering the debilitating effects of drinking poisonous poop water
Maneuver fertilizer mixed together poured in a stew and down his goal. That's possible
But he says that after the triangle left
He heard music for about 10 minutes. He heard music in the air
Now I don't know what type of bands that Demetrius listens to
And I definitely don't know what type of what type of prog rock band bleep lorbs a member of
But this is how he described this music that he heard
He said it resembled quote many birds singing. That's kind of cute, right? Many birds singing and then
animals screaming
live wolves and jackals howling
And it went on for 10 minutes
So it's like
And Demetrius just sitting there belly full of poison
He's like oh this music is so so beautiful. I'm so glad the triangle came to me
Live wolves jackals and what was the birds? I how could even hear the birds over the animal screaming?
This has to be
a joke not in the sense that
This guy's making it up because this it will assume that this encounter is real just for the sake of you know UFO stories, but
This can't be what aliens are actually like. This can't be what the other
intelligences are like in this universe like sure they did get him to quit smoking and cured his migraines
But in return they humiliated him and so that concludes the story of Demetrius
Demetris, did you know that that actually in greek
That means name of a thousand pronunciations you pronounce it however you want. It's totally okay with all the demetrius eyes out there
So that is his story
And I think it's a very revealing look at what may actually happen when aliens do try to invade this planet
We've always been thinking of like flying ships and like blowing stuff up
That stuff will probably happen. Something will probably happen regardless
But maybe it won't be a war between two military superpowers. Maybe it'll be
A haze battle against two fraternities
The fraternity of glip glop glorp out there floating around space
They're out there with like their paddles, but they're lightsabers. Ah, this hurts way more than it should
They're doing all their toilet paper
entire black holes the toilet paper keeps getting sucked in and then you got the real fraternity
The earth fraternity terra terra terra
And you know what we don't put up with any intergalactic shenanigans like if it comes down to a technological war
Sure, they'll probably win. They do have lightsaber. They do have lightsaber technology in their haze paddles
But if it comes down to a haze war
Humanity will destroy these aliens like sure. They got this guy to drink poison. That's pretty funny, right?
But I'm sure we could come up with something way better than that
I think if you got all of the fraternities together you got a great meeting of the mind get out of my way general
I picked on you in high school and now I'm taking over your job. They're just walking into the UN pushing everyone over get out of the way
Popped callers everywhere. You've never seen that many pastel pink polo shirts in your life
And you work at a pastel pink polo shirt factory the fraternities have now taken over the UN
four hours after the big pong party
Four hours after everyone is done drinking they sit there and they go okay now it's time to defeat these aliens
So bring it dude bring it. We have the best
bullies on the planet
Actually, of course because this is only the planet. We have the best bullies in the universe
So aliens if you think you can prank all the demetrias of the planet
Maybe you'll get one or two, but there's no way you'll be able to defeat all of terra terra terra the best fraternity
in the universe
Can I can I start my own fraternity called terra terra terra?
I'm gonna have to look into that because that would be super that would be super dope
We all get like letterman jackets. They just have a picture of the earth on it
And then like a line through the earth were for the earth
We're not saying no earth, but a line wait. No, you'd have a picture of the earth and then like
An alien you'd have to have an alien in there. How about you have a picture of the earth, right?
You're like just just finish the episode hold on you have a picture of the earth on the back of your letterman's jacket
And then and there's like a thumb
There's like a thumbs up
For the earth and then this is a very cluttered letterman's jacket and then kind of underneath the left armpit
There's like an alien sneaking up on the earth and he has like an x through him
And then on the right side of the armpit like I said very very cluttered letterman's jacket
so alien with an x through it earth with a giant thumbs up and then
On the other side like on the right hand side
You have a picture of a super sexy alien space babe and a dude in a super tight pastel pink polo shirt
Popped collars of course with his arm around the space babe
Yeah, there we go. I want that letter. I want that letterman jacket. Are you willing to join terra terra terra today?
I don't know if it exists. I don't know if it exists, but I'll see if I can make it
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day
And I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]