We're gonna talk about ghosts and UFOs and stuff.
It's a couple conspiracies on the special...
The Jason Carpenter is really, really sick.
Special episode.
Episode 403.
The Jason is sick episode.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm sick, but I hope you aren't.
I hope you guys are having a great day.
Now, let me get in front of everything.
It's not corona.
It's not the coronavirus.
It is something that sucks.
Nose has been running all day and pretty gooey feeling.
My bones hurt.
So I did have an episode planned for today, but I'm recording this one pretty late.
I know there's gonna be a lot of times that I'm turning away to cough.
So I'm gonna keep this one easy on me is what I'm saying, but we're not.
This isn't a filler episode because I got some cool stuff to talk about.
It's just not going to be in the format I normally do.
And let me go ahead and say this.
I almost feel like apologizing, but let's give a shout out to today's Patreon supporter.
Today's Patreon supporter is Misty.
Misty specifically requested.
I do not try to pronounce her last name, but I really, really appreciate the support Misty.
I'm gonna use your, your, your particular Patreon donation to go buy some more medicine.
And if you guys can't support the Patreon, you can always support the show by helping
getting the word out about the show.
That helps just as well.
So Misty, let's, let's, um, let's just hang out at my place today.
Come on.
Let's take a seat today.
I want to talk about some conspiracies I believe in.
Now let me say this right off the bat.
I have no proof to back any of this stuff up.
So legally I'm just rambling, right?
With me and you know, with me and you know, I have a couple of weird conspiracy theories
that have been, or insights, not a standup comedian, but here's conspiracy theory number
one.
I believe, okay, so you know when you see like, okay, I, I don't want to use real actors'
names because then that is actual slander.
But let's say there is an actor who's preparing for a role in a superhero movie and they go
from being a normal looking human to 180 pounds of raw muscle.
You guys know this has happened multiple times.
I'm not singling out one particular hero, but it used to be that action heroes were
built genetically built like Arnold Schwarzenegger, Sylvester Stallone, Jean-Claude Van Damme.
These were people who did not look like normal humans, just, just in their normal everyday
life.
But recently though, past 10, 15 years, people started going, let's hire actual actors.
Let's get an actual actor to do this and make them look buff for this particular superhero
movie that begins.
So I think that, and not just that movie, Captain America, pretty much every Marvel movie
started a man, I think outside of the Hulk.
I think my personal conspiracy is, is that when you see an actor put on, this might blow
your mind at first, but you gotta think about it logically.
When you see an actor put on 30 pounds of raw muscle in between shooting movies, they're
doing steroids.
They're mo- they are, they are allegedly on steroids.
Now let me say this, I don't care, steroids is one of those drugs that I don't really
care about.
I think steroids regulated very well outside of a sports competition, I think should be
totally fine.
I think you should be able to go to the doctor and say, hey I want to get more fit, or I
just want to look better.
If we're allowing people to do plastic surgery, if we're allowing people to do surgery to
their body, why can't people do steroids under, under like medical supervision?
I don't have a problem with steroids personally.
Steroids like any drug can lead to harmful things, yes.
But I've always viewed steroids more as something that could be regulated within the medical
system.
If, if people want to take steroids, that's one of those things that I've always thought
should just be regulated and should be legal.
As long as you're not playing sports, because then it's not fair.
The point is, is that I believe that when we see these actors put on all this muscle
weight, because a lot of times steroids may not even make you stronger, it just makes
you look bigger, which is the kind of the connection between that and plastic surgery.
I think they give these actors steroids.
Now, that would be it.
Could you imagine the fallout if that came out?
Because we always see these diet plans, I was watching this YouTube video today and
they're like, "Do you know how so-and-so got into shape for Captain America?"
Intermented fasting and I was like, "Nope, steroids."
That dude obviously did steroids for that franchise, because what happens is then, I mean nowadays
they have the franchises can last a while, but for the most part they, they look normal
their next movie.
Like, "Oh, look at me, I magically lost all that, all that muscle that took me so long
to build up.
It's magically gone.
I can fit in this business suit for this family drama."
Steroids will do that if you stop taking the steroids.
And I bet you anything that they go to these quote-unquote trainers, I'm not, I'm, I don't
know if they're tricking these guys.
They're like, "Look at me, mom, I'm so strong, I'm so strong."
And the guy's like, "You are strong, Billy.
Here, let me give you another injection of strong sauce."
Yay!
I mean, like, they probably sit down with them and say, "Hey, listen, we're gonna have
you eat nothing but fish and you're gonna be lifting much of weight, but you're also
gonna be taking human growth hormones."
And here's, this is why I think this is true.
One, it's my eyeballs work.
I can look at actors who have massive weight fluctuations between movies.
My eyes work.
That's the first part of the conspiracy, too.
If I have a $200 million movie on the horizon and part of it is you looking like a superhero,
I'm not gonna be like, "Hmm, I hope he has good genetics.
I hope he can put on weight, muscle weight really quickly."
Now, norbit, you can throw on a fat suit, right?
And then you're fine.
There's your $200 million investment.
But with this dude, like, with these guys I'm talking about, there's no way they're like
checking their watch and they're like going into the gym each day and they're like, "How's
he doing?"
No, they're injecting them with human growth hormone or steroids or something.
Again, I don't have a problem with it, but it would be a huge scandal if that ever got
out.
And you heard it first, on Dead Rabbit Radio, you know what's funny?
All the stuff I talk about, lizard people taking over the planet, gray aliens, all the
other weird stuff, Mormon Vicput, never worried about him breaking through my door.
It's funny 'cause all the conspiracy theories I do watch, that'll be the one that gets me
shot in some back alley.
I'm shot behind a 24-hour fitness bunch of needles in my back.
So let's go ahead and move on to our next segment.
Our next segment is more of a thought experiment.
So you know how, let me ask you this, guys, and gals, you have, I can almost guarantee,
you have something in your house, your apartment, your dorm room, your shack.
Remember MASH when we were kids, mansion, apartment, shack house?
That has nothing to do with what we're talking about.
That was just a nostalgia thing.
You remember?
Wait, no, no, no, no, no.
Now, I'm starting to lose it.
Now, not remember.
Just descend in the apartment.
She's like, "Dead, why did I have to donate this episode?"
The episode that is the first step in Jason's mental decline.
It's almost sad that he's even recording an episode right now.
So I can guarantee that you guys either have a guitar that is not being played, or some
sort of musical instrument that you bought that you planned on using.
Or maybe you have a program on your computer about how to make a video game.
Maybe you have the first chapter of a book you've written.
Maybe you have the first chapter of a book you've read that you're like, "I always wanted
to read a book, but you've just never finished one."
Maybe you haven't even gone that far.
Maybe you have a story idea that you've totally built out the world, but it's not built out
enough.
You need to have the world building completely done before you start putting pen to paper.
I'm not mocking any of that because I've done that my whole life.
Now I've been blessed that I've done that type of stuff where I'll start a book and
then I'm like, "Oh, I have to do this and I have to do that."
And I'm the same token.
I've also been like, "Oh, here's another idea and I've run with it."
Like this podcast.
Like before I started the podcast, I was trying to be an author.
I was writing all this stuff.
Nothing was really catching fire.
Do this podcast.
It blows up.
So that should be inspirational that what you're trying to do or what you started and
put away.
Maybe that's not the thing for you.
Maybe it needs a second look.
Maybe all that stuff.
Maybe all that inspirational stuff that really sounds better when I feel better.
That's not the point of this segment.
What is, kind of, you should follow your dreams.
But think about this.
Think about this right now.
So back in the 50s and stuff, people had to be...
Okay, so let me say this too.
First off, I apologize for this episode.
Secondly, I'm getting this from a note I wrote to myself called Weird Thoughts.
I found it on my computer when I was like, "What do I want to talk about?
What do I want to talk about this episode?
I want to talk about steroids."
Because I've had that conspiracy theory for a while, actually.
The YouTube ad about intermittent fasting reminded me of it.
Here's this.
This is my note.
I don't know why I thought of this, but here's this note.
People used to want to be married...
Just to show you how my brain works.
This is what I wrote down.
People used to want to be marionette operators or, like, using dummies.
So I was sitting there one day and I thought...
I used to have a guitar in the corner of my room.
Right?
Everyone does.
Everyone has that.
So nothing to be ashamed of.
But I was kind of ashamed of it because it was all dusty.
So I gave it to Veronica who gave it to her daughter and that way if she ever becomes
an ex-Taylor Swift, I'll be the Colonel Tom Parker of that action.
But that's normal, right?
But think about it.
At one point, somebody convinced their wife that they were going to be the next...
I don't even know who was a famous marionette dude.
Somebody...
The reason why I'm thinking this is because it shows how I think familiar the human experiences.
Right?
I'm not going to spend too much time going on this because then I just feel like a stoner.
I'm the worst kind of stoner.
I'm a stoner who doesn't get high.
I'm a stoner who hasn't been high in almost a decade, but I still have stoner thoughts.
We have those dreams and stuff like that and we see, like, guitar people, musicians, they're
normally called, playing guitars and you're like, "Oh, I would like to do that."
Like, I don't see myself as Mr. Maroon 5, but I could see myself as, you know, Jason
Mraz sitting at a coffee shop picking up chicks with my guitar.
But back in, like, the '50s, I mean, they had guitars and stuff like that, but it was
all, like, jazz music and stuff, right?
But you know what was really, you know what was really big was marionettes.
So you had some dude who had an apartment and, like, in the corner of his apartment was
a equilibrous dummy and people would come over and it'd be all dusty and they'd be like,
"Hey, Jason, weren't you trying to get...
Didn't you just talk about trying to get on the Ed Sullivan show with, like, your dummy
and doing that dummy stuff?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I practice on the weekends.
I mean, I don't have a lot of time now, but you know, I still break it out every once
in a while and people are like, "It's kind of dusty."
Have you noticed, too, actually, that joke notwithstanding, when you...
There's almost an unspoken code.
I guess this is a conspiracy.
There's an unspoken code among us.
We all have the dusty guitar.
The half-written book is really hard to see.
A lot of times people at work or people at school talk about a book they're writing
and then there's an unwritten code there where none of us ask the other person how
that's going.
Have you noticed that?
I guess this is kind of a weird standup routine.
I had my dusty guitar in the corner and it was for a couple years.
Multiple people came over.
Sometimes people would pick it up and they'd kind of strum it because they actually knew
how to use it.
But no one ever went, "Man, this guitar is dusty.
You never followed your dreams, did you, Jason?"
You're like, "No."
There's never ever comments on the dusty guitar.
When you say, "Yeah, I'm thinking about writing a book," and you start telling the story and
people are like, "Oh, yeah, it sounds kind of interesting."
They may ask you once or twice, "Hey, how's that book coming?"
But after and you go, "Oh, I'm still working on getting the characterization," after a
while people stop asking and it's not because they're not interested.
It's because we all have that dusty guitar and we don't want to be asked about it, right?
Isn't that weird?
It's kind of like a communal shame.
I believe you have to have the dusty guitar to get the dead rabbit radio.
I believe you do have to have the failures at creativity or whatever you're doing.
Doesn't necessarily have to be created.
You may be trying to rebuild a car.
It's just sitting in the garage.
But I think you need to have the failures to have the successes.
So I tried picking up the guitar.
It wasn't working.
I wrote some stuff.
I wrote, written a couple of scripts.
I've sent them out to production companies.
No one's ever bitten on them, stuff like that.
So I think you have to have those failures to have the successes.
And I'll tell you this, man, success is weird.
Success is weird.
I know I've heard of the term fear of success.
Everyone has a fear of failure or most people have a fear of failure.
You can get over it.
Some people have a fear of success where they'll self-sabotage themselves, where they'll be
like, "Nope, this is getting too big."
And the reason why I don't have that is because I've had failures in my past and I've had
successes in my past.
Let's say I go, "You know, I'm going to spend this next couple of years being a journalist
and as a very successful journalist.
I'm going to spend these next couple of years being an actor, a fairly successful actor."
And then I had all these other failed projects behind me.
So you have to have those successes and those failures.
But anyways, let's get back to the dummies.
So the point is, is that I think it's weird that we all have this communal thing where
we don't talk about a dusty guitar in everyone else's room because we don't want people to
ask us about our dusty guitar.
And if you haven't got it yet, it's a metaphor for giving up on things you want to do.
But that experience has even pushed farther back.
In the 40s and the 50s, there were dusty marionettes and dummies and we were just dummies
sitting in corners and people finally like, they always wanted to learn how to do it,
but they just couldn't talk.
They couldn't talk without moving their mouth.
But they kept it in the room because I'm going to pick it up one of these days and eventually
they packed it in a box and stuck it in the attic.
And then eventually they probably sold it or got stolen.
Got stolen by the notorious dummy thief.
And then we can, I can almost guarantee you, we can even go farther back to like, when
did people start having fun?
I know that's actually, that might sound like a joke, but happy?
Being happy?
The old version of that was luck.
Happiness in olden times basically meant luck.
You're really, people, people did have joy, but it wasn't like, oh, I'm going to go do
my hobby now.
You basically worked until dinner time and then you rested.
And then as society became a little more comfortable, you're like, oh, now I can like read this
book.
This book that's not a religious text.
That's when people are like, oh, look at fiction.
This is awesome.
When before you were either like reading the Bible, someone reading the Bible to you or
whatever religious text of whatever region you were in and then working the rest of the
time.
But eventually we got to a point where we could start going, what is this thing I'm feeling?
It's joy.
This is awesome.
Even back then people like in that time where people were able to start to find human joy
and comfort in the little things.
And I'm not talking about the super wealthy.
I'm talking about, you know, just normal people.
They had marionette puppets, right?
They were still stuck on that.
You had little Otto in 1890 Germany who really, really wanted to, you know, he had all of
his, the story ideas in his head of his own Punch and Judy show.
He's like, oh, I'm going to have two punches and it's going to be like, they're going to
be like robbing banks.
He's like the Quentin Tarantino of hand puppets back then.
And then at a certain point he goes, no.
And his puppets got dusty in the corner.
So yeah, it's just a weird thing.
That is a new conspiracy.
I'm dubbing the, the dusty guitar conspiracy.
So yeah, that's that segment too.
That segment too.
That's technically a new conspiracy.
We can put that on conspiracy theory.
Iceberg, the dusty guitar.
Because everyone has one.
Nobody wants to talk about it.
And everyone hopes the best for themselves.
I'm not a huge believer in the crabs in the bucket theory.
Maybe because I'm not a crab in the bucket.
Grabbing the bucket theory is nobody wants to see other people do good.
If you put a bunch of crabs in the bucket, if one's about to escape, the other crabs
will pull it back down into the bucket.
And there's a humanity theory, a sociological theory called crabs in a bucket where humanity
doesn't like to see other people rise up so they'll pull them down.
People do like to see really high up people fall.
But the one thing people like more than to see people at the top fall is redemption stories.
Those are the ones.
It's a really weird cycle.
Like nobody likes to see, like say, Britney Spears.
She's the best example for this because she actually did this.
She rose to the top.
She had a mental breakdown, whatever you want to call it.
She's attacking people with umbrellas and her kids get taken away.
It's all sorts of craziness.
And everyone is like, "What did you expect?
Child celebrity.
She's nuts."
And then she came back bigger than ever.
And now that's where she's at.
Her dad's going through some health problems and stuff like that.
But people like to see people.
They do like to see people fall, but they like it even better when they come back.
Elvis Presley, perfect example of that.
So what was I talking about?
Oh yeah, yeah, dusty guitars.
I think everyone wants to see all the dusty guitars get dusted off and all the dreams
fulfilled but everyone's too afraid.
Sometimes you just got to find another guitar.
This microphone is quite dusty for a while.
Actually, I've talked about this before.
I was a musician.
I have a couple of my zombie songs online.
I had some earlier episodes and I had this microphone.
It got dusty because I stopped using it and broke it back out for this.
So you always have time to dust it off.
Let's go ahead and do one more topic.
Let me think about it.
What did I talk about already?
I talked about dusty guitars and I talked about...
What did I talk about in the beginning?
Oh yeah, actors breaking the law to get buffed for superhero movies.
Okay, so here we go.
Here's my last conspiracy.
I don't even know if this is a conspiracy.
So you're like, "Jeez, I'm not going to talk about a married hip-hop that's again."
No, no I'm not.
I don't know how to...
Let me just start.
I think it will appeal to you guys because I think it explains a conspiracy theory.
You know, I walk a lot and I have this weird thing when I see worms on the ground.
I pick them up.
I throw them in the grass.
Now I'm not a big ol' fuzzy dude.
I'm not super...
I love animals but not to the point where I don't eat them, right?
I'm always eating an animal.
I actually was a vegetarian for a couple years but then it just got too expensive so I was
like, "I'm back down my goal at poor cow or..."
But you know, I also don't go out of my way to hurt animals.
And that's kind of the same way I'm with humans.
Like I'm not super like, "Oh life should be cherished."
But I'm also not like, I'm just walking out the street randomly beating people up.
I mean, I'm a normal human is what I mean by that.
I'm a normal human.
But a lot of times I'm walking and it's a little bit of an effort to bend over and pick
up that worm.
I'm older.
I'm overweight.
Oh yeah, the keto's gone out the window.
I've been eating my body weight in soup since I got sick.
But you know, even on the keto, I'm still like 270, 43 years old.
I walk everywhere.
You know, I get a good amount of exercise.
And then over to pick up worms.
Man, that's when you know you're old.
I can't do it anymore, Judith.
I can't do it.
I don't know who Judith is.
There's some random woman walking down the street.
She's like, "What talking to me?
Sorry, Judith."
But I have a theory now.
I'm sure you're like, "I can't.
What in the world is going to come out of Jason's mouth?
Misty's already left.
She's gone.
She's left the apartment.
She goes, "I do not want to know what conspiracy...
Dusty worms?
What's going on here?"
Now, let me say this too.
This is not...
I'm not telling you to go out and start squishing worms.
Because I'm going to pick them up.
They don't deserve...
I know why worms are on the pavement.
It's because their house has got all wet and they don't know what to do.
They don't got eyeballs, right?
And the second they get on concrete, they're like, "Oh, this is not good.
I'm just going to keep going in the same direction I'm going."
They get further and further on the sidewalk.
Now, the other day was real early.
It was like four or five in the morning, walking around.
I'm a cat burglar.
That's one of my many jobs.
I was leaving a very, very successful heist.
And I'm walking on the street and I see a fat worm right on the sidewalk.
Almost stepped on it.
I didn't.
And I reached down to pick it up and I thought, "Only a..."
I had a legit head of this thought.
And I can't preface it anymore.
I just have to say it.
Only a millionaire could step on a worm.
Now that is not a knock against millionaires at all.
I've known a lot of millionaires in my life.
It's not a knock against...
So that's one of the cool things about getting older is you meet tons of people.
When you're younger, you run into the same social group.
When you get older, you meet people and you're like, "Hey, how you doing?"
"Oh yeah, I own this business."
"Oh yeah, they got like $10 million in their bank account."
"I'm totally fine."
"It's not a knock against millionaires."
I think that it's the reason why I'm not a millionaire.
So let me explain.
To have...
And you know, I've talked a lot about visualization.
So when I visualize having a successful podcast or having a healthy life, cough, cough, or
I actually don't visualize my health that often, but I'm generally very healthy.
When I talk about visualization, I visualize having a successful podcast.
I visualize all these things.
I also visualize being financially successful, having advertisers and things like that.
But part of visualization is believing you're already there.
I already believe this podcast is incredibly successful.
So it's no surprise to me when it is.
Very, very happy that we're huge in Argentina and other parts of the world.
Today was a great day for downloads, 2000 downloads in a single day.
Huge in the world of podcasts.
But I visualize those things already.
I know they're going to happen.
But those are all just numbers and things.
The reason why you need to be able to step on worms to be a millionaire is because part
of being a millionaire...
This is like I said, I've met a lot of millionaires in my life.
Part of being a millionaire is saying no to people.
Now I'm actually really good at saying no to people.
I don't think you can be successful unless you say no to people.
But at the same time, I don't have a lot of respect for money.
I see that as kind of a number as a kind of a thing.
So if I was given a million dollars and people started coming out of the woodwork asking me
for money, how would I deal with that?
Interesting question.
I don't necessarily consider myself a nice person.
I'm definitely not someone who can be manipulated.
But if you want to know who can be manipulated, it's generally people who say that they can't
be.
If I had a million dollars given to me, I feel like I would have to isolate myself for a
period of time to prevent myself from being taken advantage of.
Now I've actually done a really good job in my life surrounding myself with people that
I can trust and people who don't really care about money either.
They either have enough of it themselves or it's just not something that concerns them.
So if all of a sudden, let's say a network came to me and said, "Hey, we'll give you
a million dollars for your show.
We want you to be exclusive on our network."
It would trouble me because I know that that worm, so much as I love it, it's biological,
it's alive.
It's kind of gross, right?
And it's in my way.
But I'll take the time out to pick it up because I don't want to hurt it.
It's not just me stepping over the worm.
It's the fact that I picked the worm up and put it to where it'll be safe.
I've done this for years.
Obviously, when I was a kid, I was burning them with magnifying glasses and stuff like
that.
We used to take bees and ants and make them fight.
But as I've gotten older, it's not only that I'll step over the worm, I'll pick it up and
put it to where it will be safe.
So other people won't step on it.
So when people come to me and say, "If someone comes to me and says I want you to invest
in a business, I'm not dealing with that," or make your podcast grow if you get mad,
I'm not dealing with that.
I'm talking about people coming to me and saying, "My daughter's sick."
Or "My son needs to go to a private school.
He's getting bullied."
Stuff like that.
I'm not going to give you money just because what I'm talking about, like people coming
to me and I have a million dollars and they're like, "Can I have 80,000 of it?
My daughter's life is on the line."
That's not really me being manipulated unless it's some sort of big scam.
But I'd be hard pressed to say no to that, obviously.
Because to me, money doesn't really mean anything.
I think it'd be different if I earned the money if I went from having $30,000 a year,
which is roughly what I'd make, 20,000, somewhere around there, 20,000 to next year, 50,000
to next year, 100,000 to next year.
That would, I think, be different because I would learn along the way how to say no.
Because they say making money is not super hard.
Keeping it is the hard part.
Everyone can make money.
It's saving it and keeping it, which is the difficult part.
So if I can't step on that worm, then someone comes to me with a serious health concern or
a sociological concern, something like that.
Because I was bullied in the fifth grade particularly, or was it the sixth grade I was bullied.
I did go to a private school.
So that was a real example for me.
We had to scrounge money together.
So I was going to a really, really rough school.
And it was in the sixth grade.
I ended up going to St. Philip Nairie, which is a Catholic school, which was not as rough.
And I made a lot of good friends there.
But I think if I was slowly making the money, it would be easier for me to kind of figure
that out.
Because in my daily life, I won't step on that worm.
So in a visualized future, when I'm visualizing myself saying this podcast is successful,
I have all this money, I also visualize people coming up to me saying, "Hey, can I borrow
some of that?
I need it for this."
And me saying, "No."
And then other people saying, "I need it for this liver transplant."
And me going, "Well, I only have a million dollars and you're asking for 10% of it."
Like, "Yeah, sure.
Here you go."
So it's just a weird--and what happens is then 10 people ask you for 10% of it.
And then you have nothing.
I think that's one of the reasons why I said earlier about the fear of success.
I'm not a fear of being financially successful, but I want it to come slow enough that I can
acclimate to it.
Because otherwise, I'm just going to blow through all of it, either me doing stupid stuff
or me caring too much, just like I care about that worm on the ground.
So on that dark morning when I almost stepped on that worm, I remember I didn't step on
it.
The moral is not me stepping on it and going, "Hahaha, universe!
Give me what I ask!"
I have created the sacrifice.
But I think in that moment I thought--I picked the worm up through it in the grass and went
on my way right into the maw of a flying bird.
Went on my way and I thought, "I think this is the reason why conspiracy theories about
the ultra-wealthy being super evil and eating babies and sacrificing children and all that
stuff, I think this is one of the reasons--and this--so this is really where we're ending
this.
This is one of the reasons why that type of conspiracy theory is so prevalent.
It's never the poor people eating babies.
You very rarely hear about the homeless population injecting the blood of the young into their
bodies.
Now I'll be hobo and young forever, forever, forever.
I think it's easy for us to see a separation between us versus them because for us to look
at them and for them to have that type of wealth, it's easy for us to go--if I had that
wealth, I wouldn't be that wealthy.
If I had $200 million, if I had $200 billion, I would be giving it to my friends and my
family and be taking care of everyone.
That's who we are.
So when we see someone else who has an obscene amount of wealth, we go, "Why isn't he--they
get--why aren't they spreading the love?
That's what I do.
I think it's because it is that slow acclamation to it."
I'm learning to say no.
Doesn't necessarily mean they're stepping on the worms, but it doesn't necessarily mean
that they're not either.
If I had $200 billion, if I had that type of money, you know, my family would be taking
care of people that I believe would need it would be taken care of.
But if I slowly got richer and richer and richer, I'm not walking at four in the morning.
I'm not walking that much at all.
I'm not seeing the worms anymore.
I don't see a worm for four or five years.
I'm sure there are people who listen to this podcast who are like, "I don't even remember
the last time I saw a worm.
I've walked more in my life than I've driven at this point."
And people are like, "Where is this guy walking?
Wormville, USA?"
But you get acclimated at that type of wealth.
You stop walking.
You're driving everywhere.
You're busy.
It's not that you don't care about the worms anymore.
You don't even see them when you step on them.
You're too busy just looking ahead to your destination.
Then walking slowly and enjoying the sights.
And walking slowly may not make you rich, but it may help you help the little guys along
the way.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
Twitter is @deadrabberadio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)