A military meeting of the minds turns into a disaster.
And then we travel to the Philippines, where we meet a creature.
Sometimes it's a werewolf, sometimes it's a vampire,
sometimes it's a witch lurking in the village.
What happens when you take some of the world's worst supernatural creatures and cram them into one species?
You get the ass-wing today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You know, it's funny. It's been one week for you guys.
It's been two weeks for me since I've recorded anything, so we're gonna see how this episode goes.
Hopefully it goes pretty smoothly.
I got a lot of Patreon's over the vacation break, so I'm gonna kind of break them up over the next two episodes.
So first off, I have Trashman 1101.
Thank you. Sounds like a Star Wars character.
I don't know. It sounds like the worst Star Wars character ever.
We have Quigibo Alpo.
Quigibo being the famous Bart Simpson Scrabble word.
It means a North American balding ape. Great reference.
We have Ash Adams.
So Trashman 1101, Quigibo Alpo and Ash Adams.
Thanks so much for joining the Patreon.
And we got more Patreon's coming. I will go over you guys tomorrow.
I just didn't want to cram everyone in one episode. I wanted to give you guys space to breathe.
I wonder if Ash Adams, I want...
It almost sounds like some sort of like band name.
I wonder if that's a real name.
If it is, that's a cool name.
So thank you guys for supporting the podcast.
Now, I think that's... Oh, oh, let me say this too.
I've talked about her a couple times on the show, Lana.
She's done a couple episodes.
She's had a couple suggestions for us.
She's a good friend of mine.
She got on a car accident today.
She's fine. She's totally fine.
But, you know, I've been in a lot of car accidents.
And a lot of times you walk away and then the next day you're kind of sore and your back hurts and stuff like that.
Lana, I know you don't listen to the show, but yeah, I hope you're doing good.
She sends me story suggestions, but she can't stand the sound of my voice.
So, but no, I hope she's doing okay.
So let's go ahead and move on over to our first story here.
Now, our first story is...
Let's hop on board the Carvenercopter.
Because that is our device that has time travel capability.
So I think they all do actually. We just retcon 'em so they do.
But anyway, so now the helicopter does...
We are back in the year 1164.
Sorry.
Now we gotta go forward because they said the wrong date.
Adjusting it.
We're in the year 1184.
Man, it feels nice to be doing this podcast again.
It's July 1184.
Carvenercopter... Flying over Erfurt, Germany.
So the reason why we're here is at the time a bunch of dudes were having problems.
And not just like normal, like peasants poking each other with pitchforks.
Like these were like royal guys who were like attacking each other's castles.
Which sounds dope.
I mean, that would be...
If my problem was, "I need to send these troops out to go smash that dude's castle."
I don't have a problem.
Like that's pretty awesome.
And even if my castle was getting attacked, I'd be like, "At least I have a castle."
But anyways, these guys are getting tired of fighting.
And they're all hanging out.
Now, not hanging out.
They're all hating each other.
But they figure we need to sort this out.
Because things are just getting out of hand.
And the people...
We have these guys.
I don't know who these dudes are, but some European English nut may know.
Ludwig the Third.
Landgrave of Therngia.
I don't believe that's a real person.
I think that's a Star Wars character.
And then Archbishop Conrad of Mainz.
So anyways, these dudes are beefing with each other.
And they're like, "Please, King Henry the Sixth, fix this."
And actually, no, I think it's the other way around.
I think King Henry the Sixth was like, "Hey, you guys need to stop fighting amongst each other."
"Meet me in Erfurt."
"We're all going to meet in Erfurt in Germany."
"We're going to go to Saint...
The Church of Saint Peter."
"We'll have a little conclave."
"We will talk about what's bugging you guys."
And they're like, "He started it."
"He killed my wife first."
And they're like, "But you killed ten of my peasants."
Like, I'm sure it wasn't just...
Actually, you know what's funny?
I was about to say, I'm sure they didn't really have real problems.
They didn't.
Because what happened?
Okay, so I'm getting ahead of myself.
So these three dudes go, "Let's all meet."
"And we're going to kick it with the King and we'll get this resolved."
And then other people said, "You know what?"
"I have a problem too that I need resolved."
"So I will also go to Erfurt and get my problem resolved with the King too."
"Because I'm beefing with this dude."
Now, one of these guys who came in was this dude named Count Heinrich the First.
"Why are you the first?"
"I'm Jason Carpenter. I'm the only Jason Carpenter in my family."
"So everyone is the first."
That's kind of stupid.
But anyways, Count Heinrich the First of Schwartzberg shows up.
He was beefing with people.
And the reason why people were beefing with him, because he stole the book.
So people were getting like...
Peasants were like walking, like, you know, like doing peasant stuff.
Eating apples, cutting down rice.
Not rice, not rice.
Wheat, cutting wheat and stuff like that.
And some knight would come up and smash their brains in.
The family would be like, "What would he do wrong?"
And the knight would be like, "Uh, his master stole the book."
And they're like, "What's a book?"
The reason why it's because books took a long time to write.
Not write, but like to publish back then.
So that's how petty some of these squabbles were.
But anyways, so the King's like, "Fine."
Whoever has a problem, who's rich and powerful, come to the Church of St. Peter, St. Peter's Church.
We're gonna meet on the second floor.
We're gonna meet.
And we're gonna squash all of this stuff.
Everyone's like, "Yeah."
Count Heimerich's like, "I'll be there."
And he's like hiding the book.
He has a mysterious book-shaped bulge in his jacket.
So anyways, they all show up.
Now, they're rich and powerful and they're royal people and they're warlords,
so they don't just like walk in.
They are fully armored.
They've got all their chain mail on.
And they bring their goons.
Everyone shows up with their own little click of goons.
You have like the sharks and the jets.
And then the Thuringians, who are all like, they're like the lizard people,
'cause that's not a real place.
And then the Archbishop brought in a bunch of like fighting priests and like sexy nuns
and like tight black leather outfits.
Anyways, so they're all on the second story of St. Peter's Church.
The monks are like, "Can you leave the nuns outside please?"
We took a vow of celibacy.
They're all on the second floor of this church.
Now, you should kind of start to see-
This is a true story, by the way.
This is 100% true story.
So what happens when you put a bunch of people in full armor,
a bunch of people in full armor on the second floor of a building that was built before 1164?
Like what do you think is going to happen to this story?
So, and I forgot this point.
I have to say this point real quick too,
'cause this actually plays into where we're going.
Count Heinrich I was always like, would go off on these adventures or do these great things.
He's like, "Ooh, a library! I will steal all the books!"
It only has three books back then.
But he would always go on these quests and he would make this scene.
And I'm gonna say it in German.
It's "Wandassneichtraist"
So "sterbe ich in ihm scheiß."
And people would laugh.
People think that was funny.
I'll explain what it means in a second, but if people would laugh and think it was funny,
he'd go off on his adventure and come back.
So, they're all in this second story of this church.
And at a certain point, two of the main dudes.
Can remember we had the Archbishop, Landgrave, he's trying to get his lightsaber repaired,
that's why he's there, and then Ludwig.
And the King, those are our four main players, and Heinrich is kind of a side player.
Those four dudes, two of them actually say,
"You know what, let's go into this other room. Let's talk privately."
"Maybe we can sort this out privately."
So they go into another room.
And everyone else is still on the second floor, and they hear a...
[makes a sound of a ghost]
And it's not someone's hungry tummy.
The floor is starting to bow.
[makes a sound of a ghost]
And then, [makes a sound of a ghost]
All of the support beams in the church, holding up the second floor, give out.
There's just too much weight with all these people and all this armor.
Now, as the floor is starting to collapse, the King and one of the other dudes,
I don't remember which one, it doesn't matter,
the King and one of the other main guys grab onto these metal bars that are guarding a window.
Because apparently this church is in a bad neighborhood,
that they have to have bars on the inside of the windows too.
They grab onto the metal bars.
So the floor, the second-story floor collapses.
[makes a sound of a ghost]
And everyone else there, except for the four main people,
the reason why this whole thing got started in the first place,
and I guess I should say this, we're talking around 60 to 100 people are on this floor.
So there's some historical accounts of how many people, but 60 minimum up to 100.
The floor opens up and 60 to 100 people fall down
and they hit the first floor of the church.
Now some of them are killed when they hit the floor.
[makes a sound of a ghost]
I died the same way I lived on the floor.
Who probably- Well, those are weird final words.
You know, the first floor is nice.
It's the- Oh, it's where the church is, right?
It's like where the pews are and stuff.
So you fall- Well, it's not nice to fall on a pew, but anyways, they fall down.
Now, some people die immediately when they hit the ground,
but when they hit the floor, that floor also gives out.
So all these people, all these 60 to 100 people hitting the first floor,
weakens that as well and that collapses.
Now, underneath the first floor is the latrine.
So basically, we're talking 1184 and they're just pooping.
The monks are just pooping into holes and it all goes underneath the church.
I have no idea what they expected to happen when they just pooped for 100 years
and the poop is like soaking up through the first floor.
But the entire bottom of the first floor was just a giant latrine pit.
How did it not stink walking into the church?
You're like trying to pray and you're like, "Oh, it smells terrible."
They fall through the second floor, through the first floor,
into an ocean of monk feces.
[Burp]
That's not the monk going to the bathroom.
That's 60 to 100 people sinking into poop.
They all died.
Not a single person except for those four people survived that event.
Most of them drowned in poop.
Now, I'm assuming too that just statistically,
I'm sure there's at least one guy who survived the first fall.
[Squeaking]
Survived the second fall.
Fell into the poop, cushioned his fall, didn't drown,
but probably had a nut allergy and little peanuts,
little peanuts floating around in there.
He's like, "No, no, he's trying to swim away from it."
When a peanut touches a skin, he dies as well.
Statistically, that probably happened.
I wonder if you had a peanut allergy and someone who ate peanuts pooped
and you touched the poop, or does the peanut allergy only, like, is it the oil?
Like, can you ever take a peanut?
When I was in school, I had a teacher, when I was in third grade,
I had a teacher, Mr. Rojo's, who told me that in some countries,
they're so poor that they go through poop to find corn and they turn it into bread,
or tortillas or something like that.
And I went home and told my dad that, and he's like, "What? What?
Why are you going to that school?"
That same teacher also told me that when you see the clouds moving really fast,
that means the Earth is rotating faster.
Like, the speed of the clouds is how fast the world is rotating.
And I told my dad that, and my dad goes,
"What happens when you go outside and the clouds aren't moving?
Does that mean the world has stopped? I don't know how that guy had a job teaching.
But anyways, I don't know how long a peanut is. You're allergic to a peanut.
I wonder if, like, if you ate it, could you process out the allergen?
But anyways, one guy, two, one guy died of that, nut allergy and a thing of poop.
So anyways, a bunch of people died. A bunch of people died.
Now, the king went on to become Emperor Henry.
He ended up becoming like some world famous guy.
The other people survived the incident.
But let's go back to Count Heinrich I.
Remember that quote I read you in my impeccable German?
This is what he would tell people before he would go on adventures, in English.
"If I fail, so may I die in excretement."
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
A little, what's that word? A little scene into the future there, Heinrich?
Was there a paranormal event? Was he destined to die in monk feces?
We may never know.
All we know is 60 to 100 men lost their lives.
Because monks liked eating and pooping.
Enough to fill an entire basement of a church.
That's a lot of poop, by the way.
So that's the story of, and it's known as the Erfurtlaternstruse.
Which means the Erfurtlaternfall.
A bunch of people died in monk poop.
Which if you're going to drown in anybody's poop, it's probably best you're drowning in monk poop.
Because it will probably be pretty healthy, I'm sure.
They mostly ate berries and twigs.
They're not bears.
But it's not like they're eating Taco Bell.
It's not like they're eating super greasy food.
Your last, it wouldn't be the most pungent poop in the world.
It would be, it would be okay smelling.
As it filled your nose and lungs.
Horrible, horrible way to go.
But if you had to go that way, do it, go, drown in a monk's bathroom.
So let's go ahead and come back to the modern times.
We're coming back to the year 2019.
So we never even got off the carpet or got on that.
We didn't want to fall into the poop.
We're flying to the Philippines now.
This story is actually a request from one of my Patreons.
Actually, if I remember correctly, was my first Patreon.
It's Elkie.
Thanks Elkie.
This is the story of the ass-wang.
Now, there's a 99% possibility I'm pronouncing that wrong.
So I'll spell it and you can decide whether or not I'm correct.
It's AS-W-A-N-G.
So maybe it's Oswong or ass.
It doesn't matter.
It's an ass-wang.
So this creature is everything rolled into one.
It's basically a smorgasbord of cryptids.
And thanks for the recommendation.
Okay, this is a really fascinating creature.
Because there's a lot of origin stories.
It's fairly recent and there's a lot of origin stories of how it came about, what it means.
And we'll get into that in a second, but let's explore.
So let's get out of the carbonar copter.
Take off our gas masks.
And I hand you a bolo knife.
Big ol' knife.
I'm like, "Here you go.
Take this son.
Use it."
You're gonna need it.
And you're like, "Are we gonna murder people?"
And I look at you, glint in my eye, and I go, "They're not people."
So now you're really concerned.
You're like, "Thank you, man.
Can I take this guy and get the helicopter keys and get out of here?"
And I read your mind.
I'm like, "No, you can't.
Let's go."
We started walking through the jungle and now you're really scared.
You're like, "Ah."
So we're walking through the jungle.
We're chopping down banana bushes and vines and stuff like that.
We're chopping down a bunch of stuff.
People, farmers are like, "No, those are my crops."
We're chopping down corn.
They're like, "Get out of the way, wilderness."
And we stumble across the small town.
And we're walking through the town with our machetes, with our bolo knives.
People are like, "Eh."
They're shutting their doors.
Some guys like making caskets.
It's like a Western town.
Tumbleweed made of bananas rolled by.
And we see some unusual things in this town.
Over certain doorways, over most doorways, we see a little vile.
That has some sort of liquid in it.
We're like, "Hmm, I wonder if you could drink that."
I wonder if you would get high if you drank that.
But we're not going to try.
We might later on.
But anyways, we're not going to try right now.
And we're walking around and we start to see ladders outside of windows.
We're like, "Oh, that's kind of weird.
Why would you lock your door up?"
Put a ladder outside your window.
And so some old guy comes out and he's like, "Oh, that's not a ladder, lads."
It's no ladder.
Well, it is a ladder.
It is a ladder.
But look closer at it.
What do you see different about it?
We're looking at it.
We're like, "I don't know.
It looks like..."
Can I chop it?
Can I chop it with my knife?
And he's like, "No, you can't chop it with your knife.
That's private property.
You can get arrested for that."
But you see that ladder is reversed.
We're looking at each other.
How?
So when I was reading about the ass wing, one of the things that you can prevent an
ass wing, and I'll get into what an ass wing is, but I think this is kind of important for
where this legend, where we go with this legend or this story, is that one of the ways you
can keep an ass wing from getting into your house is to put a reversed ladder outside
of your house.
How do you reverse a ladder?
If you put it upside down or backwards, it still functions as a ladder.
If you just had a ladder, you lean up to a building.
There is no way you could turn that that would make it reversed, or at least no way you could
turn that someone could not climb up it.
So we kind of look at the old man and we're like, "Yeah, reversed.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Makes a lot of sense.
We just keep walking."
We realize that we're in for a wild ride, because we explore the myth, the legend, and the reality
of the ass wing.
So the ass wing works like this.
It's basically an umbrella term for multiple creatures that exist in the area.
One version is a vampire, but instead of sharp teeth, it shoots out like a big old tongue
with a little tube on the end of it, and it sticks you in the neck or anywhere, anywhere
that has blood in it, which is your whole body, and it sucks the blood out of you slowly.
And then you die.
Now this version likes, and all of them have shape-shifting abilities, but there's two of
them specifically that have a more sinister side.
The vampire version likes to shape-shift into a woman, marry a man in the village, and then
slowly drain the life out of him over the course of the marriage, which is like, "Any
marriage you feel me, guys?
Elbow, elbow."
You're like, "Jason, I do have a knife.
Don't elbow me when I'm holding a knife."
I'm like, "Sorry."
That's one thing to do.
They also like to marry into communities so they can blend in, and then at night, when
they're not slowly draining their husband of all hope, all like joy in his life, they
will use the village as their base of operations.
They go out the jungle and kill strangers, so no one suspects them.
They don't see their husband getting all weak and all pathetic and being like, "Oh, I shouldn't
have gotten married.
I should have started that rock band."
They go, "Oh, he must be married to an asswing."
But if they're attacking people outside of the town, then no one would suspect this particular
person.
There also is a version of the asswing that is known as the viscera sucker.
This one also shapeshifts into an attractive woman, marries a man in the community.
But this one doesn't suck blood.
It still has the long tongue with a little suction thingy on it, a long hollow tube.
But this one likes to eat guts.
It likes to eat the guts of sick people.
So this is another thing.
If you're sick, you can't groan, you can't go, "Oh, I'm so sick.
Oh, my head hurts."
Because that will attract one of these viscera suckers.
They come in, stick their tube and you suck out your guts and you die.
Now, they have a particularly brutal tactic where they join a community and then when
a woman is pregnant, they sneak up to them while they're sleeping and suck the fetus out
of the pregnant woman.
So that's gross.
I mean, that's gross.
So let's say you have a choice.
You can move into a town with a vampire or you can move into a town with a creature who
eats fetuses.
I'd pick the vampire town.
The vampire town, there's a higher chance of me getting killed.
I'm not a fetus, so I'm not worried about the second one, but that's just gross.
Imagine you're shaking hands with someone and you're like, "Hey, why are your hands so
sticky?"
They're like, "Oh, I just ate."
I mean, I guess that really, they could have just made me in a lollipop.
But if you knew there was someone in town that was eating babies, you would just be
disturbed all the time.
So they have that one.
Now, there are also three other versions I'll go over really quickly.
There's one that's like a werewolf.
And technically, this is lame.
It's a were dog because they don't have wolves in the Philippines.
Like, I guess in India, they have were tigers and in Europe, they have were wolves.
This one just has were dogs.
Blame.
I'd live in that town.
I wouldn't be scared of that thing at all.
There's just like some dog walking around eating people.
You like whatever.
And then they have one that is a witch.
You know, just basic, basic witch stuff.
She has powers at night.
She cast spells.
She's a witch.
This disease only affects Filipino men.
And people have thought that when people are twitching and jerking all about that people
go "Oh, I'm going to have to make up a legend and some myth explaining why my uncle's acting
like that."
But there is an even darker hypothesis.
If the ass-wing is real and it is interbreeding with humans, even if it's not, even if there's
none left to date, but you go back three, four hundred years and there was enough back
then interbreeding with humans.
And their genetic code is still being pushed through the population.
Half human, half cryptids, and their body is just not able, it's not compatible.
It keeps wigging out.
So what if the Spaniards didn't make it up?
What if it was a creature that existed long before them?
That hunted these people in the woods.
And then as people began to protect themselves, build villages and then cities, these cryptids
realized they needed to change their tactics.
Why hunt at night in the dark jungles when you could trace your prey during the day by
blending into society?
They may have wanted simply to feed on people the first time they entered a city, but in
the end they ended up creating a genetic disease that still affects Filipino men today.
It's more likely that the legend came out of a reason for why people suffered from this
disease, but in the darkness and the wilderness that still peppers the Philippines.
People still claim to hear the ass-wang hunting.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
(upbeat music)