What happens when you hear a ghost story so scary you never drink alcohol again?
And then we travel back to the Victorian era with world famous conspiracy theorist Hans
Warmthat to investigate his newest claim.
Steampunk was real.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend.
We got a ton of stuff to cover so let's go ahead and get started right now walking into
the show.
We're all longtime supporters of the show.
Robert Paulson was so entertained by my episode The Hey Hook where I tell a story about how
I used to carry around a hey hook.
I used to use a hey hook.
I'll put it in the show notes and you're like what's going on this is my first episode.
I'll put it in the show notes and it's a fantastic episode.
I used to use a hey hook when I lived out in Sacramento.
I didn't bail hey.
Spoiler alert.
And I ended up losing the hey hook.
I ended up not having it anymore.
But Robert Paulson made me a new one.
Look at this.
I know the photo is just of it embedded in the wood but that is a fully functional hey
hook that he actually forged himself in the fires of Mount Doom.
Apparently he made the hook, he made the handle and he made the giant piece of wood.
He says it looks like a rabbit ear and I would concur.
With the quote, the key to winning every single fight is to not get in them in the first place.
Which I said apparently I mean I believe it.
I never said believe it.
But I was like oh that's a really cool quote.
I wonder who said it.
And he's like you did.
On the episode the hey hook.
So thank you so much Robert Paulson.
What an amazing gift.
I have a policy and this is a policy I followed for years and years and years.
I never ever take photographs of any of my weapons.
Ever.
There's never any photographs of bats or knives or chains or brick a brick or whatever.
It is a rule I follow.
I never take photographs of my weapons.
But this here is more of a work of art.
However you should well know that it's right next to where I do all my work so if I do
get surprised someone may get a hey hook in their head.
It might hopefully never be used as a weapon.
But what a fantastic awesome birthday present.
Robert Paulson now let's all board the dead rabbit dirgeable we are leaving behind dead
rabbit command fly us all the way out to Alaska.
Specifically we're headed out to Sitka Alaska.
Tiny little town in Alaska.
It might be a booming metropolis for all I know.
But I looked at it on Google Earth.
They didn't look that much of a jump in place.
It looked like a rural town.
In Sitka Alaska we're looking for a place called Rookie's Corner which appears to be
a maybe a slang term for a certain road.
I couldn't find it.
Another source on this story specified the address.
It's 1615 Sawmill Creek Road.
That looks like it's in the middle of the forest.
I actually pulled that up on Google Earth as well as like I don't know if the story took
place deep in the woods.
If you do decide to try it out there you're not going to want to visit the story.
The story is absolutely terrifying.
But if you do you might want to just ask around.
Don't just show up out of the house in the middle of the woods and be like is there a
ghost there?
Because you might end up being the ghost soon enough.
We're walking around Sitka Alaska.
We are just standing on the street corner.
Rookie's Corner.
And we're just kind of hanging out.
It's cold.
We've got our mittens on.
Big jackets and stuff like that.
And drink some cocoa.
Drink some hot cocoa.
And all of a sudden we hear...
Oh man.
Oh.
That's not just me stretching.
That's not just a 46 year old man stretching.
We hear it and we're like what?
Where's that noise coming from?
Oh no.
My body.
And we're like when the world's gone.
That was me.
That was me actually stretching.
I'm like oh Agin.
We hear these moans and these cries.
Coming from somewhere around us.
We're looking around.
Where could that be?
And we're eventually able to triangulate that these voices are coming from some bushes nearby.
Like right on the street corner.
Like what?
Oh man.
Where are those voices coming from?
And you try to stick your head in the bushes.
I'm pushing you into the bushes.
You're trying to find the source of that moaning.
You're sticking your head in the bushes and as you're trying to like check things out.
A car drives by and almost screams you.
Luckily I pulled you aside.
Luckily I was the one pushing you into the bushes in the first place so I had a good grip
and I pulled you out and I was like bro dude can you believe that happened?
I almost watched you die but I saved you.
I was like oh that would have been a really cool ghost story.
A podcast host makes his own ghosts.
I was thinking about it and I was like huh.
But I saved your life.
I saved your life this time.
You may not know what happens in the next episode.
The what we're hearing is the terrifying death cries of a young woman.
This is a really interesting ghost story.
This is a really interesting one.
Let's take a look at this.
So apparently back in the day on Rookie's Corner there used to be this really well known bar.
People would go in hey Johnny give me a shot of whiskey.
Glu-glu-glu-glu.
Yeah dude that was pretty good.
Give me another shot of whiskey.
Glu-glu-glu.
And people are like playing pool.
I'm assuming right there's usually pool at bars.
People are walking around drinking beers.
They're having a good time.
And in this bar we're going to meet this young woman.
We don't have her actual name.
We don't have a time period for when this story took place.
Some people say it took place in the 1800s but considering one of the key elements is a truck.
I don't think that, well maybe Hans Wormhat would disagree in the next story.
But they didn't have pickup trucks in the 1800s.
There's this young woman.
We're going to call her Maggie.
And she's walking around the bar.
She's like oh dude I love being drunk so much.
She's shooting back whiskey and everyone else is drinking other stuff.
I don't know.
I don't go to bars at all.
I'm not a drinker myself.
Whiskey, vodka, margaritas.
They're all just drunk.
This is a very popular bar in the area.
For all I know it's the only bar in the area.
And it's a sports bar too so they would have pool and probably a bunch of television sets.
Also a reason why this didn't take place in the 1800s.
The football games going on.
People are watching boxing matches and all this stuff.
It's a party.
She's walking around.
She's having a good time.
Everyone's having a good time.
Everybody's drunk.
But now it's time for Maggie to go back home.
Well Maggie does the smart thing.
She doesn't drive.
However she then does not a very smart thing.
She decides to walk home drunk.
And she's ten sheets to the wind.
That's the term right?
Like she's done.
She isn't just having a little buzz.
She is slopping away out of the bar.
She's just walking around.
Just totally inebriated.
And at rookie's corner.
This place used to be called the old kick-soddy corner.
And then it was the rookie's corner.
Because there was an old bar called the kick.
Which is where the story took place.
And then it became rookie's corner when a new bar took over.
But she burst through the doors.
She's now walking through the cold Alaskan night.
And right on the corner there is this huge set of bushes.
That really makes it a blind corner.
When cars are driving by they can't see what's on the other side of those bushes.
And when you're walking by those bushes.
You can't see a car coming.
So Maggie walks into the road.
She's absolutely not thinking about anything.
She's just trying to get home.
And I mean even if she was sober.
This accident may have happened.
But definitely it happened when she was drunk.
She stepped out from behind the blind corner.
A truck slams right into her.
Killing her instantly.
And everyone sees this.
Everyone standing outside the bar sees this pickup truck.
Hit Maggie, slam into her.
And she falls to the ground.
She's a tangled mess of limbs laying there.
The driver of the pickup truck who was also drunk.
Jumps out of the truck and is looking at the battered body of Maggie.
Laying there in the middle of the street.
Everyone standing out on the corner are looking at her as well.
And they're like, "Dude, she is done."
Like that car hit her going so fast.
Killed her instantly.
That's what they thought.
But Maggie, who should have been dead, and really,
I mean the physicians, I guess a part of them
about to tell you, is like, "Jason, she wasn't dead."
She was dead, but she was so drunk and so in shock
and so out of reality.
She had no idea what was going on.
She stood up.
She stood up on shattered legs.
Her broken arms are kind of flailing in each direction
and she's still trying to walk home.
She's continuing to make her way across the street,
screaming out in pain.
It's a horrifying sight.
But she doesn't make it home.
She makes it a couple more feet.
She's walking around.
All of her bones are basically bone meal at this point.
And she's walking.
She walks a couple steps.
She's screaming.
She's flailing her arms about.
And then she falls dead on the street.
Apparently, at least 100 people saw this happen.
You had people already leaving the bar
because they were getting ready to go to the after party.
You had people outside the bar just drinking anyways.
You had just the traffic in the area.
And over 100 people saw this horrific event.
They say to this day, if you go to Rookie's Corner,
you can hear her screaming from the bushes.
This phenomenon usually appears before dawn,
like early pre-dawn hours.
You can hear her wailing in the bushes,
screaming for some sort of help,
help she would never receive.
And that's terrifying enough.
That's scary enough ghost story.
But then this is an interesting added element to it.
Not only can you hear her,
some people see her.
There have been reports of drivers coming down that road.
And all of a sudden, a woman jumps out from behind the bushes,
jumps out from that blind corner.
And they see her dangling limbs, her shattered knees,
her broken face, just standing there in the middle of the street,
staring at them.
They see her, they see Maggie standing there in the middle of the street,
just staring at them.
The only people who can see her,
the only people who see this phantasm jump out from behind the bushes,
are drunk drivers.
And the story goes that when you see this,
you're like, "Okay, I'm done. I don't know if that's a real ghost or not."
I've heard the legends. I'm a little too drunk.
If it's not a real ghost, I'm definitely too drunk.
I'm always too drunk to drive a car.
I'm just going to pull over and get a cab.
Or walk and be very safe about it.
So the legend goes that only the drunk drivers in the area
can see this ghastly phantom.
A reenactment of her death,
or a warning to others.
This is a super interesting ghost story.
I loved coming across this one.
A lot of these ghost stories, really,
they all have elements of urban legends to them.
Unless we can verify them, unless we can actually go in...
And I'm not saying even verify them with
seeing if we can pick up EVPs or temperature drops or stuff like that.
I'm saying even verifying that the story itself exists.
And a lot of these do.
I could not find any proof that this story was real.
Like I said, there was another source that said this happened in the late 1800s,
which I don't know when Ford F-150s were driving around back then.
But this is one of those stories like I couldn't verify that a woman
was actually killed on the street.
And there are a lot of ghost stories where we can verify
that there is a historical event or a particular crime
that could have caused that ghost.
We still don't know if the ghost itself exists unless we're there,
unless we're looking at proof, but this story has that urban legend element.
Urban legends are all about cautionary tales, right?
If you're a babysitter,
be paranoid of everything.
Don't answer your phone.
Do half-hour sweeps through the house looking for anyone that is crazy,
trying to kill you.
Maybe more than a half hour if you think there might be a maniac
and you might not want to be like, "I heard a strange noise up there."
But I was just up there five minutes ago.
You know what I mean?
A lot of these urban legends are cautionary tales.
This one is the same thing where we have a ghost,
but it teaches a good message, right?
Don't drink and drive.
It's not smart. You might kill somebody.
But then if we just look at the ghost story itself,
the idea of a phantom only appearing to a particular group of people,
drunk drivers, that's a really, really interesting piece of the puzzle.
Because then it is, you know, the ghost moaning in the bushes,
that is what we would call a recording of a ghost,
like a psychic event happened in an area,
it scarred the area so much that now it's replaying on a loop.
But the ghost appearing,
but the ghost interacting with the real world,
and the ghost only appearing to the group of people
that would fall into the class of people that killed her,
that's extremely rare.
That's extremely rare.
It's a fascinating, fascinating look at a story.
And who knows? I mean, again, it could have just been an urban legend,
it could be 100% true,
it could be a blend of the two,
but I'm sure that this legend in particular has saved lives.
Whether it's told people,
"Hey man, you want another drink?"
They're like, "Nope, I have to drive home,
and I might see a bloody ghost."
They're like, "What?"
If it's just a story, then it would hopefully scare people away
from engaging in such dangerous behavior.
They're like, "I'm just going to drive down another road,
I can be drunk as a skunk!"
As long as I don't drive down Salmille Creek Road.
But also if the Phantom is only appearing to drunk drivers
and getting them to stop and catch a cab,
that is a direct interference with a horrible decision, right?
Like, that's the ghost appearing to stop you from continuing drinking and driving.
Very interesting story that it's having that level of effect on people.
This is one of those stories though, I would say, if you are a ghost hunter,
don't reenact that part, you're like,
"I want to know if there's life after death!"
And you get drunk and you start driving around Sitka.
I think it would be better if you just caught an orb on film,
rather than try to reenact this.
You're like, "But I really want to see the ghosts."
Robert Paulson, let's go ahead and toss you the keys
to the Carbentercopter we are leaving behind Sitka, Alaska.
Fly us all the way out
to jolly old England.
First off, I want to give a shout out to
Patreon member Saint Strand.
He's the one who introduced this story to me.
So I always like to give you guys credit.
Thank you so much, Saint Strand.
And then we always got to give a little tip of the hat,
a little tip of the hat to friend of the show.
I'm sure he actually hates us, I'm sure.
If you guys don't know, because it's been a while
since I've done a Hans Worm Hat episode,
Hans Worm Hat, he's the cutting edge of conspiracy theory.
Like, as much as this guy is nuts,
at the very least, if you're going to have to deal with
nutty conspiracy theories, there at least should be
some sort of originality to it.
He's the guy who said, "I will put these episodes
in the show notes, that monkeys don't exist."
That was his biggest one.
This is all kind of in the same episode.
"Monkeys don't exist. The color orange is satanic.
Space is fake."
That was one crazy episode.
We covered another conspiracy theory of his.
I don't remember it off the top of my head.
It was in the episode "Returns of Hans Worm Hat,"
but I don't remember what it was.
I do remember him saying, and I remember, I was like,
"Hans Worm Hat, I can't even cover this one."
I'm like, "This is insane."
He said that the slave trade never existed.
The American slave trade never existed.
I go, "Do their slaves now, man!"
"There's slaves today. There's slaves all over the world."
He doesn't think that the transatlantic slave trade,
that's the term for it, he said, never existed.
Because he showed a picture of a boat,
and he goes, "They tell you that they pushed
a bunch of slaves onto the boat as many as they could store."
That's impossible. You'd have to stack them like wood.
Yeah, dude, it was a slave boat. It was terrible.
It's not like they all had their little accommodations
in foot room. It was awful.
And they were treated like property, so it wouldn't matter
how much, how comfortable they were.
But anyways, so that was another one of his theories,
was that the transatlantic slave trade never existed.
I don't even know how to extrapolate that out.
He comes up with these crazy things,
and most of them are what we call
observation-based conspiracy theories.
Flat Earth is one of those.
If you look at the world in front of you,
it appears to be flat.
So it's an observational-based conspiracy theory.
Monkeys aren't real.
It's an observation-based conspiracy theory.
He's looking at monkeys, and he goes,
"That's not real."
Basically, that's all he does is he licks at stuff,
and he just comments on it.
His idea with that is he goes,
"If you look at old art, like if you look at old biology books,
where they just have drawings,
those monkeys, those drawings,
look different than the gorillas that you see today in the zoo."
Now, it could be because the guy who was walking around
in the middle of Africa who saw the gorilla
had to come back and explain it to someone to draw it.
I mean, that's the most logical answer, and he goes, "No."
They were trying to decide what a gorilla looked like.
They didn't really work it out, and they didn't have all the animatronics.
And the reason why monkeys aren't real,
the reason why we're told monkeys are real,
and every monkey you've ever seen is a man in a suit or a puppet,
depending on the size of the gorilla,
or the chimpanzee, whatever it is,
is so we don't believe in God.
If there were no monkeys, then you wouldn't have a theory of evolution.
I know, I'm sure you guys are pulling your hair out.
If there was no monkeys for every other species on the planet,
which he doesn't believe a lot of, those are real either.
He has a video, I haven't watched it yet,
because I can only take so much of,
I can only take so much of Hans and I'm at myself.
The concepts are far more exciting than him telling them.
Like, I think I'm having a little more fun telling them,
and hopefully you're having a little more fun listening to this presentation.
If you go to his videos, he goes, "Honorom hat, monkeys aren't real."
Here's a photo, that doesn't look real.
See that?
No, that's not real.
Like, it's like 15 minutes of that.
So I haven't been able to watch this video,
I've had the time, I just haven't had the willpower.
He doesn't believe penguins are real.
He thinks penguins are fake.
Is proof?
The video, again I haven't watched it,
again I haven't watched it with the video.
Like the thumbnail is from the behind the scenes of the movie,
Batman Returns, where Danny DeVito played the penguin.
He's like, "That guy's obviously not a penguin, he's on, it's always sunny."
It's a behind the scenes video for Batman Returns,
and they're talking about the animatronic penguins they made for that movie.
Why would we fake penguins?
What does that have to do with denying the existence of gun?
Penguins aren't real, slave trade's not real,
he doesn't believe a bunch of stuff's real.
I wonder what he thinks about dogs and cats,
because then the observation falls apart, right?
If he has a dog, could you convince him it was a puppet?
Probably not, because he spins all day long with it.
But he's just looking at photos, and yes, just to...
I'm sure you guys have a bunch of questions, but yes,
he believes the gorillas you go to see at the zoo are not real,
they're people in suits.
He believes that there is a job, which I would love,
I would love that job, I would love that job,
to be a man in a suit, in a gorilla suit,
and you would just walk around eating bananas all day long.
He thinks that that's not real when you go to the zoo,
but I don't know what he thinks about cats and dogs and birds, right?
Animals that we see on a regular basis that we interact with on a regular basis.
Bats, right? When's the last time you saw a bat?
Those might be fake.
He does all this stuff.
Most of these are observation-based conspiracy theories that he talks about,
and this one's...
might be one of his laziest ones yet.
Listen, I get it.
Putting out content can be difficult over a period of time,
and when you make your bread and butter on sane stuff,
insane stuff like monkeys don't exist,
and those videos do really, really well,
you have to start looking for other stuff to not exist,
to keep your viewers happy.
His channels aren't monetized.
I don't know...
I don't even know if he has a Patreon or a PayPal or anything like that.
I don't...
I mean, for all I know, he's independently wealthy.
I'm not for sure.
Or maybe he just has a day job.
He works at a zoo. He works at a zoo.
He's like, "Ah, time to go to work!"
But it's on a girl a suit.
I'm like, "No, I was wrong all along.
He was the insider."
But yeah, so, I mean, he just kind of...
That's where he makes his bread and butter,
is saying stuff doesn't exist.
It clearly does.
This is an interesting one.
Now he's trying to convince me something that never existed.
That doesn't exist, exist.
He's switching it up.
I mean, I gotta say that.
But his videos are just...
boring.
And Hans Wormhat, if you were listening to this,
I'm sorry,
you could put a little more pizzazz in it.
His newest theory, where he's trying to convince us something that isn't real,
was actually real.
So bizarre. What a twist ending, right?
Is that steampunk?
The science fiction genre that basically says during the Victorian era,
technology both froze in the steam engine phase
and advanced rapidly at the same time.
In real life, you know, you have steam engines on your trains,
and steampunk, you'd have steam jetpacks.
Incredibly painful.
The most painful jetpack ever invented.
Steam jetpacks, steampowered guns that somehow shoot better than a regular gun,
steam-powered robots, which we actually, you know,
we were experimenting with a lot of steam-powered stuff,
but you see this mostly in Victorian era England
and then the American West, and we saw that in the television show,
and it was more exaggerated in the movie,
"The Wild Wild West," the movie with Will Smith and the other guy, Kevin Klein, yeah.
I saw it on an opening day first showing.
I was such a big fan of the old television show, "Wild Wild West."
I go, "Will Smith?"
And one of my favorite TV shows growing up, this is gonna be awesome.
There wasn't, if you know, if you've never seen that movie, it's absolutely atrocious.
It's so bad.
But anyways, Steampunk, we have it in Victorian era England
and the American West.
Every time I think about Steampunk and the American West,
I just remember that awful movie.
Anyways, this is his evidence.
This is his evidence that Steampunk was real.
There's not any, but he is looking at a list of inventions from,
legitimate inventions from the Victorian era.
He was pointing out inventions like the fax machine.
The fax machine, they had a rudimentary model back in the 1800s, late 1800s.
He goes, "That shouldn't exist, so Steampunk was real."
You're like, "What?"
And then he goes, "The Eiffel Tower."
You're like, "What? What does not even any steam in the Eiffel Tower?"
And he goes, "I don't know. I'm not for sure."
But it's possible that the Eiffel Tower wasn't built.
They found it.
You're like, "What? Wait, what? What's any of that have to do with steam?"
He also says this. This was an interesting thing.
He goes, "Steampunk today is fake."
But real Steampunk back in history was real.
The Steampunk we see today is exaggerated on purpose.
So when we look back in time and see real Steampunk,
we go, "That's not Steampunk.
Steampunk is this guy with the costume with all of the gears
and he has like the cane that has gears on it
and his coffee has little gears floating around in it."
That's Steampunk. That old-timey technology is not Steampunk.
What are you talking about?
That's the equivalent of saying Star Trek has spaceships in it
and that's science fiction.
So a space shuttle that we built is not science fiction,
which would be true. It's not fiction. It's real.
They give a fake version of space.
Well, he doesn't believe space exists.
This would just blow his mind anyway.
They give you a fake version of spaceships.
So when you see a real spaceship, like a space shuttle or a rocket,
you go, "That's not a spaceship.
A spaceship is an X-wing fighter."
I mean, this doesn't make sense.
I don't know.
See, here's the interesting thing about this conspiracy theory.
I think he came up with the title first
and realized it was a catchy title.
People love Steampunk.
Some people love Steampunk.
Not people who watch the Wild Wild West,
but some people love Steampunk
and he came up with a killer title and then he had to...
Maybe I'm giving him...
I mean, he's not monetized, so it's not like he gets any real benefit
from having a video with a ton of views other than like an ego trip,
but this one was probably his laziest one he's ever done.
And it sounded interesting,
but let's look at a couple of his other claims.
He said, "First off, real Steampunk today is fake Steampunk.
It never existed, but old, timey technology that actually did exist is Steampunk."
Whether or not it used steam, all that was Steampunk.
Okay, he also says that it's possible.
He was a little...
He wasn't for sure. It's possible that we found the Eiffel Tower,
that someone else had built it.
Then one day a bunch of French people walked into France for the first time
and said, "Oh, that looks nice."
Left it there.
He also says, you know, the photographs of people?
He says, photographs of people, right?
He has a conspiracy theory about photographs as well.
For old cameras, you would have to sit there still for a long period of time
because the way that the technology was, it wasn't so instant.
It would actually have to burn the image onto the film or soak it in however you want to put it.
Then he goes, "Look at this chair.
There's a picture of a chair that actually had like a rod
and a thing that would clasp onto the back of your neck."
So you could sit perfectly straight for, say, a half hour,
however long it takes for this photo to be taken.
So you wouldn't be all slouching.
You're all blurry the whole time.
He goes, "That is not what that chair was used for."
He said that if you went back in time,
and let's say you went back to Victorian era London,
this place of this supreme steam-powered technology,
it was a wasteland.
There was nobody there.
And if you went to Paris,
birthplace, literal birthplace because it just sprung out of the earth of the Eiffel Tower,
there's no one there.
Very, very small populations, maybe one-tenth or less than what history tells us.
And the reason why photographers used corpses to take pictures of people,
which there are death photos of people,
but he's saying that when you look at an old-timey photo,
it's actually a dead person, all of them, all of them apparently,
so they could fake that they had larger populations than they actually did.
Who is doing this?
Why? Why not just tell people?
One, that we don't have a bunch of people here,
but if everyone had less people than we thought,
if every city had this, then that would be normal,
and no one would think it was weird.
But who's doing this conspiracy theory?
Is it a modern-day conspiracy theory?
Because they're trying to lie about the past?
Is it something they were doing back then?
Like, what?
I just realized what the hell was the point, but I'm asking onto a map.
Apparently, it was a way to fake a huge population center,
because you could go, "Hey, I want to invade France.
There's only like eight people here," and you're like,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
"I did a really good episode. It's one of my favorite episodes,
as far as research goes, and just the topic in general,
if you want to know more about the mud flood and the science behind that theory,
how that worked out.
It's interesting, because Hans Wormhat goes,
he'll mention it and he'll be like,
"But I don't really know if that is true."
He's not...
...golable in that sense.
He's not someone who just devours media and goes,
"Space is fake, yeah. I mean, that is dumb,
and it's dumb to think that space is fake."
But I will give Hans credit.
I think that he...
One, I think he believes it.
I don't think he's a grifter at all.
And then two, he hears all this other stuff
and he does discard dumb things.
He doesn't discard all the dumb things,
but he does discard some of them.
In this video, he was like, "Yeah, mud flood, maybe."
He just thinks there might have been a huge reset.
Even with the Eiffel Tower thing, he goes,
"I'm not for sure on this," but it's possible they found the Eiffel Tower,
that it was built by some previous civilization.
Interesting.
He then talks, he kind of wraps it up by revealing
that one day he went underground in his university,
he went to the catacombs of his university, he was on a tour.
He found out his university was powered by steam,
and that blew his mind, that blew his mind that people use steam power today.
Okay, I mean, it's a neat fact, I guess, but we still use steam power, bro.
And we're not steam punk either, we're not steam punk either,
you can use steam power and not be steam punk.
He did have, and then we'll wrap it up like this,
it might sound like I'm kind of bouncing from topic to topic.
Welcome to Hans Worm Hat, he does...
This one, I will say, I did find interesting.
All of it I find interesting, but as far as like a conspiracy theory go,
I thought this was interesting, and sure there's a simple answer to it.
He's talking about the reset, right, the possible reset,
that humanity was moving in one direction, and then it came to a complete stop,
and then we are living on the remains of that, we're walking around.
All the world fairs with all these beautiful pieces of architecture,
that was all from the previous civilization, they go,
"Oh no, we built this in 1910 for the World's Fair, they're lying."
That's part of this mudflat thing, this mudflat theory, this great reset theory.
Do they call it the great reset?
Because I know there's a new conspiracy thing called the great reset about eating bugs,
but the great reset when I'm saying that I'm meaning this old great,
okay this is just going to get confusing, we'll just use mudflat as a descriptor,
but anyways there was this massive highly advanced civilization,
that somehow was so advanced they could build these wonders all over the world,
but wasn't advanced enough to stop mud, and it killed them all,
and wiped out most of humanity.
Again, in the 1800s, we've had cataclysms throughout our very short time on planet Earth,
but this all happened in the late 1800s according to this theory.
So all of these great monuments that we see, when you walk into a city,
and you see like this very, very old looking building,
then everything else is a state-of-the-art skyscraper,
that old building wasn't built in the 1800s,
and then was reserved as a historical monument,
and you're not allowed to tear it down, that's not what happened.
All the buildings in that area used to look like that, which was true,
and the mud destroyed all of them, but that one,
and then all of the sparkling cities are humanity rebuilding after the mud.
I mean again, it's so interesting.
I'm surprised they started this conspiracy theory out to say it happened in the 1600s.
It might be more plausible.
I'm not saying that walls of mud moved just at different time periods,
but anyways, late 18th, I feel like I'm losing the plot.
I actually don't have time to talk about the story that Saint Strand actually recommended to me.
He didn't recommend this portion of it.
This was supposed to be a very, this honestly was supposed to be like five minutes long,
five, ten minutes long before we got into this other story,
but it does dovetail into this.
We'll save that for Monday's episode, but mudflod.
Grand architecture, like Washington, DC, the obelisk.
I think those are also pre...
There's photo, here's the interesting thing, you go by Jason,
there's photos of these buildings being built.
Well, those photos are fake, by the way, you didn't know that?
All those photos were fake.
But let's get to the part that I thought was interesting.
I'm sure there's a reason behind this.
He goes, "Why is it that we can go back in time
and we can look at a king like Henry VIII or Louis XIV?"
But...
Today, there's not a Henry XVI or a Louis XIII.
Mudflod is the answer.
He didn't know mudflod, that these families were destroyed.
These families were wiped out, so people were like,
"Oh, no, Henry VIII, he died in that mud.
What am I going to name my baby?
Oh, I guess it's just Henry I, because that Henry died.
I wanted him to be Henry IX."
He says, "What happened to these lineage's?
What happened to these family names?
They got wiped out, they got killed.
And so they had to start over.
Now, I don't know, I'm broken.
Here's the thing, I did think that was interesting.
I go, "Oh, that's interesting."
And then once I said it out loud, I thought all eight Henry's
weren't alive at the same time.
They would still have named him Henry IX, right?
But I'm sure...
Like, it wasn't the problem with Henry VIII
that he kept having girls.
He couldn't have a boy.
So that would probably be why there's not a Henry IX, right?
He couldn't have a little boy, he had a bunch of little girls.
If I remember correctly, or no kids, right?
He's chopping people's heads off the whole time.
But that's my version of history.
Henry VIII was walking around with a battle axe.
But yeah, I guess that would be the answer to that.
Once I said it out loud, I thought if you had Louis XIV...
There might have been a Louis XV for all I know, but...
I'm American, royalty means nothing.
You have a Louis XIV, and then he has a son Louis XV.
Then he has a son Louis XVI, and then no kids, or only little girls.
And then there are no more Louis.
So that would explain that, I think, by saying it out loud.
I kind of figured it out.
But yeah, that's the theory.
Like, is it possible that steampunk was real?
But the steampunk of today is made exaggerated on purpose.
So if you saw steampunk from the past, you would go...
That's not steampunk.
That's just ordinary technology that's been invented.
But if there wasn't a steampunk genre today,
when you looked into the past, you would go, "Wow, they had a fax machine back then?"
Which, I mean, don't get me wrong, when I read,
because a long time ago I was doing research for that conspiracy iceberg topic,
1800s internet.
And there's... The 1800s internet is actually a book that was published.
It's not a super obscure topic.
I'll put some information in the show notes about it, but...
It's the idea that technology in the 1800s was more advanced than we give them credit for.
Not more... I mean, it's readily available in history books.
We can see articles about stuff and prototypes, drawings of prototypes and stuff like that,
and we know that they had working models of this stuff.
But he's looking at that, he discovers that, and he goes,
"Oh, this means that steampunk is real."
But this is... Again, like I said, he believes in what he talks about,
and he probably doesn't believe that steampunk was real,
and dead people were propped up in photographs to make it look like England had this massive empire,
when really it was just like 10 guys in a boat.
He probably does believe that, but this video... On the HONZO Meter?
On the HONZO Meter, this might be his laziest video yet.
Which, I mean, could mean that Hans is ready to hang up the hat.
He actually did retire last year, I think.
He said, "I'm done. I can't do this anymore."
And then he had a dream of a gorilla came to him in a dream, and he goes,
"You must... You must continue to expose the truth."
But yeah, on the HONZO Meter, I would give it five gorillas.
Five gorillas out of 15 out of 15 gorillas.
One for each Louis. I'd give it a five. Five gorillas.
It's just nonsense, and I love looking at conspiracy theory nonsense,
but I feel like he's kind of given up.
Five out of 15 gorillas is what you've earned for this video.
You can do better, my friend. I know that you can do better.
However, I say that, but in the back of my mind, I always remember he has a piece part of...
This is actually a really popular conspiracy theory that other than a very, very select group of people,
all men are women, and all women are men, and they call it transvestigation.
This is a very, very popular conspiracy theory that is blowing up.
There are whole YouTube channels and podcasts and websites dedicated to this.
It's just a photo of a man, and someone going, "That's a woman!"
And a photo of a woman and someone going, "That's a man." But again, they know they're of the select...
They're the purebloods. They are what they are.
Hans Wormhat is a man, but according to Hans Wormhat, I'm a woman because I'm overweight,
and men never get overweight. It's, again, Jason, that's a really bizarre conspiracy theory to tack on at the ending.
That conspiracy theory is what kept getting his YouTube channels yanked.
Like, he was just getting deleted off of YouTube. That's really blowing up conspiracy theory,
and I think it's just kind of... That's the most boring, right?
Obviously, I don't have time to talk about the other story, but it involves what we just talked about.
Steampunk, lost media, and possible proof that there truly was an ancient, powerful empire on the borders of Europe
that was so powerful, they not only had to be wiped off the earth,
but every mention of their name across any form of media had to be destroyed.
But we'll get to that episode on Monday. DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
TikTok is @deadrabberradio. DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great week, guys.
[Music]
[MUSIC]