Suck you by, ink you by, and everything in between.
And today we take a look at love spells
that may finally help you get the girl or guy
of your dreams today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
(upbeat music)
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode
of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day.
Today we wrap it up.
Today we wrap up.
It's our last episode of our sexual conspiracies.
There's a few more that will go on throughout the series,
but this is the last day
of the sexual conspiracy themed week.
And it's going to be a doozy.
We're talking paranormal, we're talking ghosts
and demons and all sorts of craziness today.
You know, the good thing about the internet
is you can always find recipes for stuff.
Now I don't cook a lot, so it doesn't really help me out.
But you know what, like you can go and find a recipe
on how to basically make your own Chipotle burrito at home.
Now I'll take a side note here.
Chipotle is the best chain restaurant
in the history of humanity.
I think if I had a time machine and I could go
and try out every kebab stand,
every crusader meat wagon,
every old tiny Benjamin Franklin
served lightning crusted churros.
None of them would compare to the deliciousness of Chipotle.
I used to work next to a Chipotle
and I ate Chipotle every single day for a year.
And I loved it, I love Chipotle.
I'm actually going on vacation soon.
It shouldn't affect the,
I may end up taking a couple of days off
towards the middle of the vacation.
But the good thing of it is that I will be vacationing
right next door to a Chipotle.
So I will be going there every day.
I'm thinking about going in there,
introducing myself to the staff.
So they get to know me
because I will be in there all the time.
I'll probably start dating a girl there.
We'll have a little whirlwind affair.
Get a discount of course,
because I'm dating one of the girls.
I can't wait.
Deliciousness there.
Steak burrito, chicken burrito, it doesn't matter.
It's all good.
What's the barbacoa?
Yeah, that's pretty good too.
And the carnitas, not a fan of the veggie one.
It's just a bunch of corn and a tortilla.
But it's all good.
Chipotle.
Eat fresh.
I actually don't know what their slogan is,
but if I knew what their slogan is,
I would get a shirt.
I actually wrote Chipotle
and asked them to open up a Chipotle in Hood River.
You know, I have a friend up here from Long Beach.
We're having a lot of fun.
We're having a lot of fun up here, doing our thing.
The best thing about having friends come though,
from out of town up here to the Pacific Northwest,
little hamlet of Hood River, is the comfort food.
It's always a nice treat.
A nice little diversion.
Let's get started with the episode.
So today, we are going to talk about succubi and incubi.
Now, the difference is a lot of people use the terms
interchangeably and they're actually
completely different things.
A succubi is a female demon who has sex with you
and sucks the energy out of your body.
An incubi is a male demon who has sex with you
Now, that alone should be the risk-reward calculation
for you.
Like, yes, I'm having sex with an otherworldly entity
who can be as hot as it wants to be,
but they're draining my body of energy.
That's always been the trade-off.
Now, of course, there are subcultures on the internet
who don't believe, well, first off,
they believe that succubi and incubi are real.
And those are old legends.
The idea that these creatures come and suck your soul
and are, among other things, at night,
they prey on you, those are old legends.
This is nothing new, but the new internet community
believes that you can date them.
You can go out with them and you can have relationships
with them and there's all sorts of tips
on how to summon them and have them be a part of your life.
Now, I get it, sometimes dating real people
can be a bit of a pain.
You have to actually go out and meet people
and then convince them that you're worth being,
you know, at the very least having sex with, if not,
you have to prove a little more worth
to have being a relationship with them.
So if you're feeling lonely or particularly randy that night
or you just wanna try something new,
I can see the allure of wanting to bang a demon woman.
It's probably not a smart deal.
There's quite a few websites, though, dealing with this.
One of them, the kind of the most basic thing you do
is you have to write a letter of intent to Lilith.
Now, Lilith, that's old Jewish mythology,
so basically Adam, God created Adam,
and then he created Lilith and she was a total bitch.
I mean, she just wouldn't follow any of the rules
and she was just a total pain in both God and Adam's side.
Get it, 'cause the rib, get it?
Anyways, and so she got banished
and basically erased from religious history
and then God created Eve.
Now, because of all that, she's the queen of the succubi.
I also think she's the queen of miscarriages,
like she's the cause of miscarriages
if you miscarry or maybe even abort a child.
It belongs to Lilith, whatever.
But apparently out of that horrible side quest
of her taking, you know, unborn children,
she also is the queen of the succubi.
And so what you have to do is you have to write her a letter.
Here's the ritual.
You're gonna write Lilith this demon woman
who existed 10,000 years before the rest of humanity.
You have to write her a letter, apparently.
You can't send her an email,
Lilith@gardenofedon.com.
Okay, I'll stop telling those bad jokes.
So you're gonna write a letter to Lilith
and this is what you're gonna put in here.
First off, you have to know what you want.
So if you just want like a quick flaying,
you have to go into thinking,
"I want a hot Randy succubi
"to come to my house tonight
"and we're gonna do all sorts of crazy things."
And she's a ghost, so nothing will stay inside of her
and my sheets are gonna get all sticky.
Or I wanna have a girlfriend who is from another dimension
and has wings and can set my enemies on fire.
You have to know what you're getting into.
It says the optimal time to do this ritual is at 3 a.m.
So already she's kind of set the time limits.
Don't change me, Lilith.
I'm my own man, I'll do it when I want.
You write this letter and you're gonna write,
"Watch, I'm gonna read this out loud
"and a bunch of succubi are gonna beat me up tonight."
Okay, so you write this letter out
and you're gonna write,
"I wonder if you write it out with intent."
You get a succubi, but does Lilith listen to podcasts?
If I read these instructions out loud with intent,
will I get a handy from a demon woman tonight?
Please be hot.
You know, I will say that at least the artwork
for the succubis forums and stuff,
they're pretty hot, these chicks are pretty hot,
but they don't exist in this form.
If it looked like this,
then everyone would be banging these things.
Anyways, okay, so I'm gonna write this letter out.
Let's see, what personality should my succubi lady have?
She should be randy, but not too grabby.
I hate it when she should know what she's doing.
That's the first thing.
And a one night stand.
I don't want anything long term with a demon lady.
So you're gonna write in this letter,
"Lilith, please receive this offering.
I give this truthfully and willingly."
What offering?
There's nothing listed there.
Maybe I didn't skip steps, but there's definitely,
yeah, there's nothing there.
You just write to Lilith on the top of it
and then you say, "Oh, I should specify this.
One of her daughters, one of her daughters,
not one of her sons."
Let's specify that, okay.
"Lilith, please receive this offering.
I give this truthfully and willingly."
There's no offering in here, so it doesn't matter.
You light a candle and then you set the paper on fire,
which I'm not gonna burn my laptop.
And then it says, "May the light of this candle
burn brightly and guide your daughter/son to me."
Again, I don't think that's, I think you should specify.
You see, this is a problem with spells,
is that one, you're supposed to be ultra specific,
but in the sentence itself, you write daughter/son.
So do I write or say daughter/son?
This doesn't make sense.
You're gonna cause a hot male demon
to break into my house tonight.
You let the candle burn for 30 minutes,
you relax and clear your mind for a while.
Next step, this is gonna shock you guys.
The next step, you just imagine,
you just pretend that a demon woman is in your house
and you masturbate.
Queen of the demons cannot move objects in your house.
She cannot flick your lights on and off.
She cannot turn your television on to the spice channel,
you know, for a little bit of background entertainment,
in case you can't get it up.
She can't do any of that stuff.
She only appears in your head.
So basically what you've told me to do is to write a letter
and then imagine, i.e. masturbate,
that I'm having sex with a demon.
And I know what you're thinking,
"Jason, you just picked the wrong website."
Well, I found another website.
This one, you know to trust because it has a black background
and what spooky website doesn't have a black background.
This one, you cut out the middleman.
You don't talk to Lilith.
Why?
You don't go to the middle manager.
You're gonna go to the top.
This one, you talk to Father Satan.
So apparently that's his title now.
And once again, you have to be very specific
of what type of girl you want.
This one specifies that some demons are monogamous.
Okay, I thought monogamy was a social construct,
but anyways.
So you should find a demon that is compatible with you
and it's kind of hard.
There's not really a tender for these type of things.
And this one also tells you to imagine
that they are there and to masturbate
and you'll feel it in your head
and other parts of your body.
This one's funny because it says,
"Demon friends and lovers are wonderful
"for those who are in prison,
"isolated or incarcerated in any way."
Sure, good enough, but there's a bit of a problem here.
If I'm in prison or isolated or incarcerated,
probably don't have access to the internet, dude.
So how am I gonna read this?
Anyways, this one, you also basically perform a ritual
to Father Satan stating your needs and what you want.
And then a demon may or may not show up, spoiler alert,
they won't.
And you just begin fantasizing
about having intercourse with the demon.
This one actually uses the word fantasize multiple times.
So all you're doing is praying to these creatures,
these Lord and Lady of Hell,
and then imagining that it actually happens
and somehow that's proof that it actually happens.
Suck you by and ink you by.
Now, what's funny is there's actually been a lot of reports
of people being raped by demons.
So you have the ghost sex side of it,
which is like the consensual stuff.
And then you have ghost rape,
where it is not, well, I guess you know
the definition of rape, it's not consensual.
I was looking at these articles,
one of them said that in his findings,
15% of all people on the planet report themselves
being raped by a demon.
Now, that's actually fairly common,
but there's another word for it.
It's called sleep paralysis.
It's also times a lot of connected to,
a lot of times connected to alien abductions.
You can't move your body, you feel pinned down
and you're very helpless.
And some people see that as a sign that the,
some people see it as a sign
that the grays are coming to abduct them.
Some people are seeing it as some sort of paranormal force
holding them down and ravishing you.
And then science sees it as basically
as you're falling asleep or in that,
you're in that waking state,
your body's not aware that you're not dreaming anymore.
And it does two things.
You physically can't move
'cause it thinks you're sleeping.
And you begin to hallucinate
'cause you're waking, dreaming.
To put this theory to a test,
it's something you can do yourself.
When you go to sleep tonight,
it's very interesting.
I do it all the time.
Close your eyes and you can trick your body
into thinking you're asleep.
And what you do is you close your eyes
and you lay there and you're perfectly motionless.
And what will happen is some part of your body
will begin to itch and you'll itch it.
And that's your body testing to see
whether or not you're asleep or not.
'Cause if you're asleep and your leg itches,
you won't itch it 'cause you're asleep.
Your consciousness doesn't perceive it.
And then if you don't scratch it,
that's one of the first steps to start lucid dreaming
'cause your brain goes, okay, okay, he's asleep.
Now I can start the process of unloading
all of this information and I can start dreaming.
So you, and what sleep paralysis,
it's the other side of that.
Your mind is awake, but your body,
your brain still thinks it's asleep.
And the reason why it has a self-defense mechanism,
so you're not dreaming about being chased down the street
by a bunch of bug chasers or something
and you're not running around your apartment.
You're perfectly emotional.
As you may roll side to side, but in your dream,
you're like sprinting for miles.
My body is keeping me motionless there,
but it has to test itself
and it has to stick these limits on you.
That's what sleep paralysis is.
You're coming out of the sleep,
but your body is still frozen.
Now, I don't deny that there's paranormal activity.
I don't even really deny the existence of demons.
But I think if it was so easy
that I could simply write a letter to Lilith or Satan
and get a reply that, I mean, technically,
it should, stuff should be flying around my apartment.
We're talking about two of these like insanely dark,
evil forces and the worst they can do
or the most they can do with all of their power
is put a picture in my head of a busty,
I can imagine that right now.
I am imagining that right now.
I don't need to do any sort of ritual to imagine stuff.
It's ridiculous.
People spend so much time on this though.
Now, it may happen.
People may get raped by ghosts or demons, I don't know.
But again, I don't think it's as simple
as writing a letter or anything like that.
If it happens, it happens.
Now, I know what you're thinking.
Love spells are really right, Jason.
You totally believe in this stuff.
You know, I talked a little bit about this
on the episode "Salt Mining"
where we talked about Arb corn stars
unwitting psychic sexual vampires.
I do believe that if you're putting energy out
into the universe, other people can be receptive to it,
whether they know it or not.
I definitely think it works
when two people are meeting face to face.
So the theory goes, could it work across distances
without the other person knowing?
And to that, I don't know.
I kind of think so.
I think you can affect people.
But I have nothing to back that up other than a theory.
So if anyone can prove me wrong, I'm more than welcome to it.
So I think on that issue,
can I send my energy out towards somebody
and get them to think about me?
I personally don't see why not.
And you may be thinking, Jason, you're an idiot.
That's impossible.
And like I said, fair enough.
I think that is more likely and more possible
than a love spell/love ritual.
I've never been a fan of rituals in general,
whether it's organized religion
or a bunch of wickens running around naked in the woods.
I think the fact that you can just do or say these things
and somehow you've accessed the cheat code of the universe,
I'm not a huge fan of.
Not saying it's absolutely not true,
but I think it's oversimplifying things.
But I did wanna look at some of our magic spells,
some of our love spells.
So I was looking at this one.
This one is a black magic true love spell.
So this one is going to get somebody
to fall in love with you.
They're going to, you're gonna look inside your own soul
and you'll find that block
that is keeping you away from your true love.
That's directly from the website.
These are the ingredients.
And one organic chicken wing.
Not, you gotta get like foster farms or something.
You can't get like a chicken nugget
or anything that's been pumped full of hormones.
One organic chicken wing, one pink candle,
whoa, one sterile needle.
Where's this going?
Three drops of blood, yarn or thread matches,
made out of wood, one sheet of parchment paper.
You write on the paper with the organic chicken wing.
Okay, and it says you won't see the name,
but basically use the organic chicken wing
to write the name or your name on the parchment paper.
Use the candle and drop seven drops of wax on the paper.
Get the needle to be sterile
and drop three drops of blood on it.
And then you think about your soulmate.
You blow out the candle and say,
"Sim words I can't understand."
You wrap the chicken wing in the paper
and use the yarn or thread to pack it into a little package.
That same day, bury it
and then eventually that person will fall in love with you.
Oh wait, no, you have to light the remaining candle
on the following full moon until it's burned itself out.
Okay, so easy enough.
So I had seen that one earlier and I go,
oh, I wonder if they have any other spells.
So we're on this website, Wishbonix,
is the name of the website.
So I found a black magic spell to stop cheating.
So this is going to keep someone from cheating on you,
obviously.
Ingredients, one organic chicken wing.
I think this website has own steak in a chicken farm
because a lot of their spells involve chicken wings.
It's pretty much the same thing.
You're gonna write your name with the organic chicken wing.
Seven drops of wax through drops of paper.
This one, fans of 4chan will love this.
The spell involves you saying kek three times, kek kek kek.
Plus some other stuff I can't pronounce.
That's to keep someone from cheating on you
and that will go about the same way.
Now again, I don't understand why you would have to use
any sort of chicken wing and all that nonsense.
Why can't you just use the power of the whale?
But then again, I am not a magician.
And I know what you're thinking.
You're like, Jason, you're just kind of
just reading off nonsense at this point.
You don't believe it.
You don't believe any of these rituals make any sense.
I don't believe any of the rituals make any sense.
I being the listener, you're just kind of like,
dude, you're wasting my time.
Let's talk about ageless travel again or something.
This is the problem with this.
Because again, it's praying on people.
On this website, they have comments for whatever reason
'cause it just makes them look like complete trash.
Not the people commenting, but the website itself.
On the spell on how to prevent the breakup
with the candles and the chicken wing and all that stuff.
Here's what a commenter left.
And this was just in March 12th of this year.
Please enlighten me.
It's midnight here now and I just saw this page
and I'm extremely desperate to do this specific spell.
But I only have seven pieces of pink tea light candles
while I have a good size red one.
Can I still use the pink tea light
and describe my name on its side?
Can I use one pink tea light just for tonight
as I can get a good size, same as my red one.
First thing tomorrow, then it's inscribe the new one
with my name again.
I really have to do this now.
Do I keep all the remnants of the candles?
So this woman is desperate.
She's sad.
Someone's about to break up with her life as she knows it.
She feels isn't going to be the same.
And here she is, blogging on this website
and she never gets an answer on here to her question.
She's like, I need to do this now.
Please, please help.
There's another spell on how to prevent a divorce,
which that one, surprise, surprise,
chicken wing included in that.
It's kind of the same spell as well.
And this person says, please help me.
My wife is in the process of divorcing me.
Please stop her now.
You know, at a certain point,
you're just praying on people in a moment of desperation.
It's quite sad.
You know, that's when this stuff goes
from being entertaining and being like,
ha ha, look at these rubes right in this website.
And then you just have these poor people
like really devastated and they're like, please magic website.
Please candle organic chicken wing spell.
Like help save my life.
Help save this person from leaving me.
And they're not responding.
They're just, you know, trying to sell products
and sell these issues and it's just gross.
It's just gross.
While looking for all this though,
I did find a spell and this kind of sums everything up.
It's very simple scale.
It's very, very simple spell.
It is a simple spell that will hopefully make known to you
whether or not the person you like is gay.
What do you need for this spell?
One red candle, that's all.
And it's pretty simple.
It doesn't even tell you to light the candle.
I don't know if you keep it in your pocket
as you're walking around
or if it's just sitting on your bookshelf.
This is the spell.
This, you chant these words anytime during the day.
Send me signs throughout the day
to help me know if blank is gay.
That's it.
So I'm wondering if when you say that
you'll see a rainbow up here
or your walk past the store
and they'll be selling assless chaps for 50% off.
Or you walk in a room and you see that person
giving a blow job to another man.
I don't know.
They're all signs, technically.
I don't know what you need the candle for.
Nonsense.
Nonsense, at least with the theory I have,
there could be some sort of pseudo scientific principle
behind it.
You're not walking around saying,
"Send me signs throughout the day
"to help me know if blank is gay."
I wonder what would happen if I did that to myself
if I said that throughout the day.
"Send me signs throughout the day
"to help me know if Jason's gay."
I wonder what would happen.
I don't know.
Maybe I'd end up buying some assless chaps.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com at DeadRabbitRadio
or is it /DeadRabbitRadio?
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
You can always hit us up there.
Well, we have finished our Sex Spiracy Week.
I hope you had as much fun listening to it
as I had researching it,
because I didn't have a lot of fun,
no, that's all I had, a fun researching it.
Some of the last episode was a little rough
because it got gross reading, all that stuff.
But this episode was fun.
Took the piss out of some magic users
and people who believe that they're being demons.
Dude, if I'm not mistaken,
I believe that they're being demons.
Dude, if I have sex with a demon tonight,
I'm going to be upset.
And if you end up, like, maybe this is like the ring
that everyone who listens to this episode
will end up being visited by a Suck-You-Buy or an In-Q-Buy.
Depending on your intent, of course.
Let me know.
Hit me up on email.
Send me an email.
No photos, please.
No, I don't want to see you, you know,
masturbate and being like, "I'm being a ghost.
"I'm being a ghost and it's just a 30-second video of you.
"I can do without that."
But we are going to move on.
Next week, we're going to have all new stories.
And you know, next week, I'm also,
I got a lot of requests for this.
I did not want to include it on this week
because we were talking about a lot of the Suck stuff.
But next week, we will finally cover the issue in Iowa.
Is there something going on in Iowa
with these missing children?
Missing teenagers, adults, things like that.
I just didn't want to cover it this episode.
And I was hoping for some new information to come out.
But really, it was just,
with all of the stuff we were talking about this week,
I didn't want to mix the two because one is,
you know what I mean?
Like when people go missing,
you don't want to think of that type of stuff
happening to them.
And I thought that the segues would just be too weird.
But we will be covering that.
I've been getting a lot of requests for that.
We'll be covering that too.
So after this, what I'm going to do,
I'm just going to go get some coffee.
If you're interested, you could always join me
for some coffee as well.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend and we will be back soon.
Have a great one.
(upbeat music)