our ghosts trying to beat the heat this summer.
And we wrap up Cryptid Week with a look at a local legend
with the body count today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
(upbeat music)
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode
of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm a great day, I hope you're having a great day too.
So we've been experiencing some technical difficulties
on our side here.
You'll notice that today we're wrapping up Cryptid Week.
It's a little late.
This file actually got deleted.
This is my fourth time recording this episode.
We did release the Gulf Rumors episode on Friday.
That's proved to be immensely popular.
So everyone who's downloaded that, listened to that
and even sent me emails.
Got a lot of emails about that.
Thank you for that.
Thanks for paying attention to the show.
So we're gonna go ahead and wrap up Cryptid Week though.
Now, one thing I did wanna talk about
during Cryptid Week was my own Cryptid.
So you know, I've talked to before
about how I'm an author, a writer.
That's a better way to put it.
And I love watching sci-fi channel movies.
Watched a lot of those monster movies.
Three-Headed Shark Attack.
Five-Headed Shark Attack.
Ghost Shark.
That was good.
I liked that one.
I tried watching Santa Jaws the other day,
but the other people I was with weren't that into it.
So I had to shut it off.
We ended up watching The Nest instead
about Killer Cockroaches.
That's not a sci-fi channel movie,
but it's incredibly disgusting.
Check it out.
The Nest.
It's from the late 80s.
But anyway, so I watched a lot of those monster movies.
I actually started to write my own monster movie
for a sci-fi channel.
Croco Mile.
It's about a mile long crocodile.
I think it's a great idea.
This crocodile, this alien satellite crashes into Earth
and starts to infest this crocodile.
And every time he eats, he gets bigger and bigger and bigger
till, of course, spoiler alert.
He becomes a mile long,
and the good guys have to drive a Jeep
into his mouth to drop it.
'Cause you figure of a mile long crocodile,
it's getting big.
It's not just like a snake.
It's getting big all over.
It's like Godzilla size at that point.
I don't even think Godzilla's a mile tall.
Anyways, they drive a Jeep into its mouth,
and they're like setting bombs.
And there's like a fist fight
on the edge of its stomach acid,
'cause the bad guy got swallowed earlier.
And then there was the evil general,
who the whole movie, he's talking about
how much he hated mosquitoes.
And then a mosquito gets giant
and like sucks all his blood out.
They had, I had a character named Crossbow Jones.
He was a mercenary, was with an attitude
and a specialized Crossbow that had different explosives on it.
He wasn't the star though.
He was kind of like the second in command.
But he was this team of mercs that had teamed up.
Each of their own, they were all with different military units
and they had all faced the crocodile
at different stages in its growth.
And they all are telling these stories.
They're like, yeah, man, I, me and my men,
we fought this crocodile.
He was like 50 feet tall and he just decimated us.
And then the female command was like,
when we faced the crocodile, it was 80 feet tall.
And the other guy's like, you know,
when we fought it, it was 120 feet tall.
So they kind of learn early on this thing's growing
exponentially.
So they all have to team up even though they're with
different nations to try to take this down.
And of course you have the Bikini wearing co-ed
to kind of be the every man in the story
plus to have a bikini wearing co-ed in a horror movie.
'Cause you want those.
Who doesn't want those?
I want those.
I think every movie should star a bikini girl.
I actually watched a movie called,
I think it was The Stepfather and the, right,
whoever wrote it was a genius because the main star,
the boy was a swimmer and it was summertime.
So it gave the excuse for his girlfriend to wear a bikini,
the whole movie and sit by the pool.
And I was like, this is genius.
Like whoever came up with this idea knew exactly the
audience for this movie.
That being said, Croco Mile, sci-fi channel hit me up.
Forget all those sexist comments I just made.
(laughs)
And if you wanna work with a podcaster on an amazing movie,
now that Sharknado's wrapping up, hit me up.
Dead Rabbit Radio and Gmail.com.
If you wanna see my script, it's ready to go.
It's ready to go for you.
I haven't submitted it out, but I have written
other horror movie scripts that I've submitted out
to other various production companies.
And they liked the pitch, but no one's ever actually
bought the script.
So maybe there's a, I don't know, I don't know.
I still send them out though.
Okay, so let's go ahead and get started here.
So the first thing we're gonna talk about is there is
a British paranormal, actually let me back up here
because the headline is very important.
So this was "In the Sun" one of Britain's magazines.
Again, a brilliant headline.
I gotta love these headlines.
This is about paranormal activity raising,
being more heightened during the heat wave,
the current heat wave that's going on.
The headline of the article, "Who You Gonna Cool?"
Who you gonna cool?
I mean, you know, you gotta tip your hat.
You gotta tip your hat to these reporters
and these editors who are coming out
with these catchy headlines.
I think it's becoming a lost art.
You have to give props to these old school headlines
because now all of the headlines are so clickbaity.
And the headlines tell us what opinion to feel
when you're reading the article and why it's awful
and why it's beautiful and why it's great
and why it's important.
Let me decide.
But all the headlines nowadays are becoming clickbaity.
Who you gonna cool?
That's a great headline.
So, "Hats Off to You Sun."
However, I do have to deduct points
for writing the article in the first place.
So basically, this is the premise of this article
that because of the heat wave,
there has been an unexplained spike in ghost sightings
according to this ghost hunter.
So this ghost hunter is professional
paranormal investigator Gary Parsons
said that ghostly apparitions have been summoned
by the scorching sun.
And he's like, "I don't know why."
He goes, "I have this device that we've invented
that can pick up ghost noises
and we're seeing a lot of more ghosts."
So here's one of his quotes.
"We have received a major spike in the number of calls
during June and July with people reporting scary
supernatural phenomenon."
Why, what?
What?
Why are you defining it as scary?
Like, yes, ghosts by their general nature is scary.
But you never hear a physicist being like,
"Black holes are super spooky."
Like, just be like, yeah,
you don't have to throw scary and spooky
and all sorts of stuff.
He does that a couple times in here.
I think he uses the word haunting at one point.
Oh, he later on, he goes,
he's talking about this box he made.
So of course they're selling it.
He says, "It is designed to search out
unexplained orb lights, eerie voices and deadly spirits."
Just come on, man.
You're not doing your profession any good
when you have to use adjectives like that.
It's hard to take you seriously
when you use words like spooky and eerie.
So he's saying that ghostly activity is spiking
during the summer.
He doesn't know why, but they're being,
in his words, summoned by the scorching sun.
This is one of my issues with ghost researchers,
is that it's all guesswork.
It's all guesswork why any of this stuff happens.
If you were a ghost,
why would you most likely come out during a heat wave?
As opposed, like, let's say,
actually, here's a better question.
Where do ghosts go when they're not ghosting?
Where are the paranormal?
I would assume they're not in heaven or hell
because they would stay there.
So what actually are ghosts doing
when they're not walking down your hallway?
Do they exist?
Do they go off to some ghost resort?
Is it super cold there right now?
And that's why they're coming out to the sun now?
These are quite, and you know, actually,
I never thought about that.
These are kind of legitimate questions you have to ask.
Where do ghosts go when they're not walking down your hallway
or having spooky conversations with you
or standing in the mirror?
Where are they?
I don't know, because I've actually never even
thought about that before.
I've always wondered though, why ghosts wear clothes?
And why ghosts wear clothes that they didn't necessarily die in?
Most people die in their underwear or naked.
So why are Victorian ghosts wearing these, like,
beautiful ball gowns and stuff like that?
Why aren't there more naked ghosts?
Why aren't more ghosts wearing boxers with holes in them
and, like, a Walmart, you know, a Walmart journey shirt?
'Cause that's how most people die.
Most people don't die in a neatly pressed
Civil War uniform.
Yeah, of course.
Okay, maybe that's a bad example, because a lot of people
did die in Civil War uniforms.
But not everyone died in their Victorian costume
or their regal clothes.
So do you die?
Do you haunt in the clothes you're most familiar with?
Like, if I saw the ghost of, like, an old Gothic dude,
would he be wearing his trench coat and, like,
10-inch heel boots or those thick soles with all the spikes?
Or would he be wearing his, you know, white tank top
and no shorts because he died on the toilet?
We need to, these are, to me, those are more questions
that we need answers to rather than
is the sun summoning ghosts.
But anyways, if you know the answers
to any of those questions, hit me up.
'Cause I don't, I don't, why do ghosts wear,
why do ghosts wear clothes at all?
Anyways, where do ghosts go when they're not haunting?
So anyways, and I have a logical explanation
for this story, so he's saying that during June and July,
the ghost sightings are up,
he's being called out to more locations.
The author of the article says, you know,
if you see a ghost, give us a call.
And he's doing all these investigations during the summer.
Now, I think kind of the typical idea
is that ghosts come around at night
and really, like, the fall and the winter,
for me, are like the scariest time for ghosts.
I'm never like, oh no, it's 90 degrees out
and there's people windsurfing on the river,
there might be a ghost tonight.
Like, there's certain elements of time
where things get spookier, it gets darker earlier,
all the trees look dead, streets are quieter,
'cause you don't have all, like, the tourists.
I live in a tourist town,
but, you know, there's a time period
where things are quieter and creepier.
And to me, I'm a little more on edge during fall and winter
than I am during the spring and summer.
I, okay, let's put it this way.
If I'm out at the beach in my shorts
and like an inner tube around my waist
and a little like sunblock on my nose
can basically look like a character
from an '80s movie going to the beach.
And I saw a ghost on the beach, that's not scary.
That's completely not scary.
If it's sunny outside and I'm like, oh man, it's so hot
and I'm like working in my garden
and I look up and there's like a butler standing there,
a ghost butler, not a real butler,
a ghost butler standing in my garden,
I'll be like, dude, grab a rake, bro.
Like, it's hot out here and I just wanna get back inside
as quickly as possible.
There's a ghost blocking your air conditioner,
you're like, God damn it.
Get out of the way, man.
It's not scary.
It's not scary during the summer.
And here's my reasoning for why this article is coming out
and why this guy's saying that
it's been a spike in the summer.
Summertime, people don't read as much.
People don't listen to podcasts as much, honestly.
People have a completely different set of activities
during the summertime.
And there are people who read during the summer,
but generally when I was a writer,
you would see drop-offs during the summer months
because people do stop buying the amount of volume books.
They're out doing more things.
I think that's what's going on here.
He's realized, oh crap, it's the summer slump.
I'm not gonna get as much business.
People aren't gonna call me up to tell me
that their Aunt Judy is floating around their kitchen
or maybe I'll start telling people
that the summer sun is making ghosts appear.
So he's basically just drumming up business.
Now, I know you could be saying you have no proof of that
and you're kind of disparaging them.
And sure, probably.
However, and not probably, yeah, that's absolutely right.
I have no proof of what I just said.
However, just knowing the way that the economy works
and sometimes you need to pay bills
in the middle of the summer,
because here's the fact of the matter.
The sun is not summoning spooky spirits
to invade your cabana.
That's just simply not happening.
Not happening at all.
So the idea that this guy has legit proof
that the summer sun is summoning ghosts
is just ridiculous on the face.
It really, I mean, you could say
that ghosts in general is ridiculous,
but if you, okay, let's say that you were
haunting apparition who died brutally
or you were just a haunting apparition
who tripped down the stairs.
The point of being a ghost is kind of to be scary.
And there's nothing less scary than the noon day sun.
And you could say, yeah, but it gets hot at night too.
But yeah, at that point, okay, imagine it's cold
and you're huddled in your living room
and you're reading a book
and you see like a little ghost girl
like creeping around the corner.
You're gonna be freaked out.
If it's 100 degrees, it's 100 degrees
and you're just sweating your balls off
and you're super irritated
and everything pisses you off
because you can't get comfortable.
You got four fans on you.
The air conditioner is running top speed
and you're still sweating.
You see a ghost girl crawl around the corner.
You're not gonna care.
'Cause you're so, actually, you probably kick the shit out
of it because you're so irritated anyways.
Absolutely irritated.
And now you've got some creepy 12 year old
singing lullabies in your bedroom
while you're trying to sleep.
And you can't even sleep because you're covered in sweat.
So I think if there are ghosts
and they are like spooky ghosts as he's claiming,
the last time they're going to show up
is when you're already ready to like
beat the crap out of somebody.
They'll be like, "Oh, I'll come back later.
"I'll come back when he's totally comfortable
"on like falling asleep.
"And then I'm gonna like crawl under his bedsheets
"and like, let's forget that."
Forget that example, that particular example.
You know what I'm saying.
There's a time and a place for ghosts to scare you.
And it's not during the summer.
And if the ghost is just trying to communicate you,
when's the worst time to talk to somebody?
When they're sweating.
If I'm sweating and my mom calls,
I'm like, "I'll call her back."
I'm not talking to someone
when I'm losing a leader of water a minute.
So if my Aunt Judy wants to float back from the netherworld
to warn me about the coming apocalypse,
don't do it under the noon day sun.
He's drumming up business.
He's drumming up business to sell his box.
He calls it the Huff Wonder Box,
which again is a terrible name.
If you put wonder in the, okay, I've trashed this dude enough.
I've trashed this dude enough.
Great headline though.
Great headline.
Total nonsense.
Okay, we're gonna go ahead and move on to our next story.
So, the Pope Lick Monster.
Now this is gonna end off our cryptid week.
The Pope Lick Monster is a local legend in Kentucky.
He's called the Pope Lick Monster,
not 'cause he licks popes,
but because he apparently haunts an area
called the Pope Lick Creek in Kentucky.
I don't know why it's called Pope Lick.
I don't know, I have no idea why the creeks called that.
Anyways, probably 'cause the Pope did get licked there,
but it's probably bad timing for that joke.
So, Pope Lick Monster is a creature who is half man.
No, no, no, sorry.
Part man, part goat, part sheep,
which is the worst animal to be a part of.
I mean, outside of a slug,
it's probably one of the worst mammals to be part that.
What does a sheep do?
What supernatural abilities
or what advantages would you have as a sheep?
You're extra wooly?
What do sheep do?
They just get sheared and they taste okay?
Part sheep.
If I was part sheep, I would be pissed.
I would rather be a bloodthirsty werewolf
and have to deal with the constant struggle to eat humans
because at least you could fight crime at that point.
The part sheep?
Ridiculous.
So anyways, he's, well, at least he's part goat
and part goat's actually kinda lame too.
You can't really run that fast.
Your legs are all messed up.
You have horns, I guess.
I guess that's the trade-off.
Anyways, Pope Lick Monster is part man, part goat,
part sheep, and this is the legend.
So, back in the day, I think it was like the 1920s, early,
no turn of the century,
there was a very cruel ringmaster, circus dude, right?
And he had this circus, obviously.
And one day, there is a baby, a deformed baby,
dropped off at the circus.
I'm assuming like outside of the bearded lady's tent
and she's like, "Oh my God, it's so beautiful."
Whatever.
Anyways, so they get this, you can,
they get this little deformed baby
and they look at it and they're like,
"Oh dude, this is part man, part goat,
and part sheep, this is extra wooly."
And so the circus ringmaster goes,
"Oh, this will go perfect, perfect in my freak show.
This guy is like the ultimate freak."
So he, what does he do?
He immediately begins abusing the baby.
'Cause he's a dick,
'cause the ringmaster's like a total jerk.
So he's like beating up the baby and he abuses it.
He abuses it for years and years and years.
And here's my thought.
If I found a mutant baby, let's say I was a circus freak.
No, no, I'm not the circus freak.
Let's say I'm a ringmaster
and I find a mutated baby.
I too, I'm gonna say,
"This will go great in my freak show."
But I'm not gonna beat it up and here's why.
I'm gonna take that little baby
and during the day he's gonna be in the freak show.
And at night, I'm gonna send him to adult learning classes.
I'm gonna send him to University of Phoenix online
so he can help me with my finances.
So he can actually, like there's so much other stuff
this ringmaster could have done with this mutant baby.
Put him in the freak show, yes.
But why not send him to business management school
or just teach him how to like do architecture
and build better tents?
I don't understand why his default mode
was to kick the shit out of this little baby.
But he did and he did it for years and years and years
and eventually the popolic monster,
that wasn't his name back then.
His name was probably like Harold.
But anyways, this little freak is growing up.
He becomes like a surly teenager.
He's smoking cigarettes and he starts to hate his ringmaster
as you would because he got beat up.
Again, if you sent him to adult learning annex,
he wouldn't have hated you so much ringmaster,
but you beat him up every day.
Now he's this super strong,
he has the strength of a sheep
and they're coming across the pope.
So this was a traveling circus.
The circus is traveling across the popolic creek bridge.
It's stormy out.
And then a lightning strike hits the bridge.
The train goes (makes lightning strike)
If I actually had more time,
I probably would edit in professional sound effects.
But I don't, so that's what you get.
A lightning bolt, train, bridge, seagull,
bears, seeing it all through the woods.
Okay, anyways, anyway, the train crashes.
The popolic monster is now free of his cage
and he's like, "Ugh."
So what does he do?
He starts eating the dead.
And everyone's like, "Oh, I'm so glad I'm not dead
"because that goat monster is totally eating that dude."
Then he starts eating the living,
'cause you know why not?
He's been abused all his life.
And then he finds the ringmaster and eats him.
So that's the initial legend of the popolic monster.
There's other ones that it was a farmer
who made a pack with Satan and became a goat.
That's, I like the circus one
'cause it's just more, there's more to it.
And also a little more believable
than making a pack with Satan and becoming a goat
because a lot of people make packs with Satan.
They don't become goats.
It's very believable that a circus freak was misused
and turned into some sort of monster.
And we'll get into that a bit more.
But anyways, so today the legend of the popolic monster
is that this part man, part goat,
part sheep stalks that area.
There's a couple of things that will happen.
One, if you're in, if you walk by any place
that has darkness, he reaches out, grabs you,
you're never seen again.
Sometimes he carries an axe.
And if you're walking across the bridge,
the popolic creek bridge,
that's how you summon him.
He'll appear with an axe and he'll chase you
and you have two choices.
You can either get chopped up 'cause he's really fast.
He has the speed of a sheep.
He can chop you up or you jump off the bridge and die
'cause it's like a 60 foot drop.
And I don't believe that it's like a creek.
So it's not like a river.
It's not like you can jump in and then swim away
like Jumanji or something.
I don't know if they do that in Jumanji,
but I never saw that movie, either of them.
But anyways, so the other one is that,
and this one's a little more devious,
is that he can imitate voices and he can hypnotize you.
And the way he hypnotizes you is that he makes it
so you don't hear the train coming.
Now, again, you're on a bridge with a train track
and you're saying, well, Jason,
didn't the bridge blow up?
And I said, yes, yes, it did, but they repaired it.
Well, actually, no, I don't know if the bridge actually blew up.
I think that's all just legend.
But anyways, there is a working train track there.
And if you're walking across it
and the popolic monster sees you,
he can make it so you can't hear the train coming.
Train's one of the most notoriously loud land vehicles.
You don't hear the train coming.
You're on the middle of this bridge.
You look up there, so train 20 feet in front of you.
It hits you, splatters you, you're dead.
So people say, don't go to that area.
Now, obviously that's a really entertaining local legend.
Kids go across the train tracks.
Teenagers are like, hey, man,
let's go down to the popolic monster's house
and see if we can see how he's doing
on his community college courses.
It's trespassing.
The train company, the people who run it,
are like, please don't walk on that bridge.
It's super dangerous.
It's an active train bridge.
20 to 25 trains cross it, 8A,
is not a place for you to go hang out with the goonies.
Now, but people do.
And this is where the idea that the popolic monster
actually has a body count.
Because people have fallen off the bridge,
fair enough, people are gonna fall off bridges
or jump off bridges.
But something more interesting happened recently.
So there was this young couple who they were legend tripping,
which is something I've talked about before.
We talked about it during Ong's hat episode.
That's where you go to these places with these legends
and with these hauntings and you go around
and take pictures and then do your own investigation.
It's kind of like ghost hunting,
but it's with not just ghosts,
it's with all sort of local legends.
I think it's fascinating.
I used to do something like that in Sacramento.
It's, you know, just go around and,
oh, this is where that happened.
This is where that happened.
But this young couple,
they are on a trip around the East Coast, that area.
And they say, hey, the girl's like,
hey, let's go to the popolic creek
because there's this legend of the popolic monster.
And the boyfriend's like, yeah, that's okay.
It's a little out of our way,
but it's kind of what we're doing anyways.
We're looking at these local legends.
So they go out there and they say,
hey, well, we have to walk across the bridge
to summon the popolic monster.
So the boyfriend tells the cops,
so you know where this is going,
that him and his girlfriend are walking across the bridge
and he looks up and there's a train coming at him.
Didn't even hear it coming.
Which again, I live miles away from a train track.
I can hear it.
And it's kind of hard not to hear it
while you're walking on the train track.
But anyways, he says, we looked up,
the train was on the bridge.
It was near us.
There was nowhere for us to go.
So he leans off the bridge
and he wraps his arm around a girder
and just leans back as far as he can.
And the train, he's so close.
The train is so narrow.
The train actually clips his arm and scrapes his arm up.
Doesn't like rip his arm off or anything.
But cuts his arm up really badly,
but as he's hanging on,
he looks and he sees his girlfriend
flying off of the train track.
She couldn't get safe.
The train hit her and she fell to her death.
Tragic, you know, it's tragic.
He got cited for misdemeanor, trespassing.
Again, just to tell people this is not safe
and she lost her life and the legend continues.
You know, you had this young couple up there
that the train was coming and they didn't hear it
and the poplick monster may have claimed another victim.
Do I think that's likely?
No, I don't know,
thank the poplick monster hypnotized them.
But it is a weird part of that story
that how she died was the same way
that the legend has always been,
that he could hypnotize you
so you don't hear the train coming.
One thing that I've always thought was interesting
about these local legends is the train story itself
is relatively true.
The beginning of the actual legend
that you could have this deformed baby
that got loose from a circus or escaped an accident
and was running around the woods of that area.
But once you start giving him magical powers
and let's say that happened,
let's say in the 1920s,
the circus freak kid got loose in the woods of that area.
Let's say it happened when he was maybe 20
in human years, not sheep years.
And he gets loose.
He would be like 90 today.
He would be collecting social security.
He would be watching like the price is right.
Like at a certain point, the legend,
and that's what's interesting,
these legends never die,
like these characters never age.
You think they could be like,
yeah, back in the 50s,
he was like totally tearing shit up
out in the middle of the public.
But the last time I saw him,
he was sitting on Park bench,
playing chess with the Mothman.
But what happens is they have to keep the legend going.
So now he's this magical creature
who can teleport in and out of darkness
and he can hypnotize you and stuff like that.
It's possible that a mutant was running around in the woods
in the turn of the century.
And then he just fell down a hill and died
or died 'cause he was, you know,
three different species mixed together.
And that was just too much mutation
for your heart to handle.
But the initial legend could have a hint of truth.
The mind control stuff, not far, far less likely.
But like I said, it's kind of creepy
that she died the way that he hunts.
So that is a local legend that possibly,
possibly actually has a body count.
So that's it, we finally got through Cryptid Week.
I really hope this episode sounds good
because I can't record it a fifth time.
We just weren't in a new environment.
We're recording some things differently and all that.
But I'm so glad you stuck around with us.
I'm so glad you've been patient.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address.
And again, I appreciate all the emails I've gotten from you.
You've gotten a lot.
We have our Facebook is facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter.
That's another way you can follow us.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily,
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great day, guys.
(upbeat music)