A man falls in love and goes to great lengths to prove it.
And then we travel to Spain to meet a family ready to get away for the weekend.
Little do they know what they're getting away to is an alternate reality today on Dead Rabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Just a heads up, you got today's episode, tomorrow's episode, then I'm taking a week
off and taking a week off every 50 episodes and I enjoy it very, very much.
I've been listening, I've actually gone to my Patreons and asked them for what their
favorite episodes of Dead Rabbit Radio have been.
We got five great episodes for reruns next week with brand new intros.
I always like to give you guys a little behind the scenes.
What happened before the episode, what happened after the episode.
It's a really cool look.
I think it's a lot of fun for me and if I was a listener of a podcast, I would want
to know that stuff too because I'm a big old nerd.
I'm a big old nerd about stuff I love and I hope you guys enjoy all of that as well.
Let's give a shout out to one of our legacy Patreons, Gottmaster Gray.
Thank you to everyone, give a round of applause for this fellow.
You're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
Whatever vehicle we take, you're in charge of.
If you can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
Just help get the word out about the show.
That helps out a lot and I see you guys are running you guys in the wild and you guys
will be talking about the show and I just do a little smirk because I see you guys are
spreading the word and that really, really means a lot.
Gottmaster Gray, we're going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
Let's go for a little road trip.
Give us on out here.
Basically our chauffeur, we're all sitting in the back smoking big Cuban cigars.
He's like, "Oh, I want a cigar."
He doesn't get one.
We're driving out to La Palma, California and we get out of the car.
We're like tipping Gottmaster Gray.
We're like, "Here you go, sir.
Keep the meter running."
He's like, "No, Gottmaster, come out.
We're going to give him a couple cigars."
He can smoke for the rest of the story.
We're in La Palma, California.
It's November 2016.
We're going to walk into this office complex.
There's just normal people filling out paperwork, sitting little cubicles.
You guys know what these places look like, right?
Very drab, very gray, probably a catty calendar on someone's desk.
Pretty standard stuff.
There's a young woman sitting there.
She's typing on her keyboard and stuff like that.
She has a little office, a little cubicle office area.
She has her water bottle, photo of me, probably, because who wouldn't?
She has tea.
She's always drinking tea.
She's got a little bit of honey, that little honey bear thing.
You scored it out of that little pointed hat on its head.
Put a little honey in there.
Drinking some tea.
That's all she does.
She types.
She drinks tea.
She has a water bottle and a photo of me.
It's the best workplace ever.
But often the shadows.
Allegedly.
The rest of this stuff, I have to say, is alleged because it involves criminal issues.
But off-scolking in the shadows, the lightning strike.
We see a silhouette.
A silhouette in the shape of Steven's millen castro.
[imitates lightning strike]
I'm standing there.
It's like, "Oh, if only I could have her.
The woman who's not named because of the complaint.
I will call her Janet."
[imitates lightning strike]
I don't know what her real name is, but we'll call her Janet.
And Steven is sitting there.
Wherever he walks, there's a shadow following him.
He's like, "Hello, Janet.
My name is Stevens."
And they talk and stuff like that.
And you talk to the silhouette in the corner.
But she does.
She doesn't actually know where the story is going to go.
And at a certain point he asks her out.
You know, pretty young girl is going to get asked out.
And she goes, "No, no, I don't want to go out with you."
She's probably a little more subtle than that because she added in the thing.
You know, but we can be friends.
We can hang out and stuff like that.
Oh, awesome.
Let's go check a cheese tomorrow.
She's like, "Okay."
I didn't really mean the friends thing either, but at work we will be cordial towards each
other.
She thinks that's kind of the end of it, right?
But she starts to notice that Stevens is always staring at her.
She's making her tea, staring at her.
She's making photocopies.
She's in the machine.
He's staring up at her.
She's like, "Oh."
She gets the feeling that he's always watching her.
And she goes, "This is kind of the way you're supposed to handle it."
She goes up to him and she goes, "Hey, you know, it's kind of creepy.
I don't know if she actually used to wear creepy, but basically she said, 'Could you
please stop staring at me?'
It's making me feel uncomfortable.
Whenever you have these complaints, if you're not in danger, it's best to address it with
the person first because they may not be aware of what they're doing.
They may have some sort of awkward quirk."
And they go, "Oh, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I didn't know that I was actually bugging you."
And you just let it lie there because some people are doing it accidentally.
But she said, "Hey, can you stop staring at me?"
He's like, "Oh, yeah, yeah, totally."
And she's walking away.
He's like, "Oh, I'm going to stare at you so hard for that comment."
He begins staring and just kind of being a nuisance around the workplace.
She's addressed it with him and hasn't stopped.
She goes to her boss and she goes, "Hey, listen, he's still kind of harassing me.
Like he's constantly staring at me and stuff like that.
I'm pretty sure I saw him inside the photocopy machine the other day."
So the boss talks to him and says, "Hey, I got a complaint about your behavior.
First off, we need to fix the lighting around your office because you just look like a silhouette,
a Steven-shaped silhouette sitting here.
Can you leave her alone?
Leave Janet alone.
I got a complaint about it.
You need to leave her alone."
Now that is, again, the second step.
There's a process to this.
Well, some time passes and she goes back to her boss and she's like, "It's not...
If anything, it might be worse."
He seems to be...
I don't know how it's possible, but he's staring even harder now.
He's not staring daggers into my back.
They're broadswords.
So at this point, the boss has to get HR involved and says, "Hey, listen, we got this guy staring
at this woman."
And really, that's all he's doing up to this point.
That's making her feel uncomfortable.
So HR has him go to sexual harassment training.
Just sit down in a room, you watch a video, and it's like...
And then Tom walks into the room and Sally says, "Don't.
What did Tom do wrong?"
And then, you know, it's like a half hour video.
It's no big deal.
That should have been the end of it.
Really, when she said, "Hey, stop.
Knock it off.
That should have been the end of it."
99% of rational people would be like, "Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know I was staring so much."
And you got the one...
You have a bunch of weirdos around her.
I'm not fair, unfortunately.
So it had to go up the ladder.
She didn't go to HR right away.
She didn't make a big muck of it.
She did the steps.
She talked to him, then she talked to the boss, and then she talked to HR.
That should have been the end of it, though.
Sexual harassment training, all of this stuff.
Not saying that that's the cure.
I'm not saying that he's been in this 30-minute video.
You're like, "I'm no longer weird."
You're running through the streets.
You're like, "Hey, everyone.
I'm a totally normal human being now.
I don't stare anymore."
You're like, "What?"
No, that's not what happened.
So one day, what did we name this girl?
Janet.
One day, Janet goes into her little cubicle, and her water bottle is sitting there, and
she's looking at it, and she goes, "Oh, that's weird.
It looks cloudy.
You know, normally water isn't cloudy.
I don't live in Flint, Michigan, right?
Normally water should just be see-through, but it's cloudy.
She's like, "Ah, poison out."
She gets rid of it.
She didn't really think much of it.
A little pin goes into her brain, but she didn't really think much of it.
She pours it out.
She has her tea anyways.
She drinks her tea.
A couple days later, a week later, whatever amount of time passes, she goes into her little
cubicle.
Her water bottle is cloudy again.
A different water bottle.
I'm assuming, right?
She didn't just empty the water on it.
She goes, "This is safe to drink."
It's like a, you know, like a plastic bottle of water.
She notices it's cloudy again.
She's like, "Oh, great."
She starts to get suspicious.
She tells her boss about it.
Suspicions.
She's like, "You know, I'm coming into work.
I think someone's putting something into my water."
Boss is like, "Okay."
I'm sure he was probably a little more concerned than that.
It's like, "Well, it's Monday.
It's put toxins into people's water day.
Don't you know the rules here?"
He goes, "Tell you what, you know, because we need, we, let's find out if this is what's
going on.
Let's find out if this is true or if you're just being paranoid or something like that."
Again, I don't think he accused her of being paranoid, but let's put a hidden camera up
in your little office.
So she's sitting there.
At this point, she's really no longer bringing water to work.
I would assume not at least.
She's drinking her tea.
She's making her tea there.
So she knows that that is safe.
And then one day she goes in to her office and there is a milky white substance spread
across her keyboard and her mouse.
We know what this is, right?
I mean, any adult would know exactly what this is.
And it was probably what she says.
She actually, she probably didn't suspect this was what was in the water bottle, but
if you see it live in the wild, you know exactly what it is.
She's looking at it.
She's not touching it.
She has like a little CSI toolkit.
She's picking it up.
She's touching a little Q-tip to it.
She goes to her boss and she goes, "We need to review that camera because I'm pretty sure,
not a scientist, but I am an adult.
I'm pretty sure that's semen on my keyboard."
Are you expecting, you're running like a call center or something, right?
He thought it was weird enough he had to put up a secret camera in this woman's cubicle
and now he's investigating semen deposits, right?
He's like, "Oh man, it's not even semen Thursday.
What crazy workplace is this?"
So they start reviewing the video.
So they're fast forwarding it.
It's just like an empty cubicle.
It's nothing.
And then they see a movement.
They hit pause and then they hit play and they see in slow motion, they see a slow motion
blurry object.
They start moving in.
It's like paranormal activity.
They see this figure take out like a tissue and begin to smear it on the keyboard and
the mouse and then the figure turns very quickly and then they pause it, enhance it.
You guys, they knew who it was.
You know who it was.
It was Stevens.
Stevens was smearing semen on her keyboard and her mouse.
The boss is like, "Wow, okay.
We got to involve the authorities.
This is beyond...
I wasn't trained for this."
So the cops come down and this is what the story is.
So yes, well, allegedly.
This semen Stevens was masturbating in the bathroom.
Hopefully, right?
He said his chemical.
He was doing it.
He was masturbating somewhere on the work premises.
He's in the janitor's closet.
And then he would take...
First he was putting it in her water bottle.
But then when she got rid of the water bottle, he began to smear it on her keyboard and her
mouse.
And little did she know that this whole time he wasn't just masturbating into her water
bottle, not masturbating into it, that would be a feat of engineering.
He was bringing it and dripping it in there.
He was also putting it in her honey.
So all that time, and she's like, "What?
That water looks contaminated.
It's time for some delicious honey infused tea."
He was masturbating and then putting his semen in her honey.
So he is facing some serious charges.
He actually...
Actually, I don't have to say allegedly.
He was found guilty.
He was actually found guilty.
This investigation took a while.
Even these incidents took a while.
So we had 2016 when this initially happened.
He was just found guilty and he's...
He hasn't been sentenced yet.
He's going to be sentenced later this month.
His defense...the prosecutors, the police and the prosecutors were like, "This was like
a sex crime."
Like this guy was obviously getting off on this.
He's jacking off on people's stuff.
I wonder if he was doing this to anyone else in the workplace too, but he's jacking off
into people's stuff.
This was a sex crime.
Now his defense was like, "Your honor."
Yes, our client is a big old weirdo, right?
Total weirdo.
He's using his own bodily fluids to get back at somebody for rejecting him.
However, it wasn't sexual.
It was not sexual.
And the judge probably raised his eyebrow and goes, "Explain to me this avenue of defense.
What do you mean masturbating is not sexual?"
And they go, "This wasn't sexual, your honor.
This was simply petty revenge."
You see, he was afraid he wouldn't get the promotion because he had been reported to
HR for sexual harassment.
He was afraid he was up for a promotion and he would have gotten that promotion, sir.
He would have totally gotten that promotion, but just because he was staring at somebody
multiple times was still to stop.
Wouldn't stop.
That is why he got mad.
He was afraid he wouldn't get promoted or he would get fired for being a big old weirdo.
So he wasn't masturbating for sexual release.
No, your honor.
He was masturbating for revenge.
Imagine Charles Bronson in "Death Wish."
But instead of shooting gang members, the judge is like, "Okay, okay, I've heard enough.
You're not going to ruin the movie "Death Wish" for me because that's my favorite movie.
That's why I became a judge in the first place.
It was this or shoot criminals in the street."
So that didn't work.
It didn't work, obviously.
That's a terrible defense.
He's facing two and a half years in prison.
It's funny.
I've been watching a ton of true crime stuff lately, a ton of it.
And I hadn't been watching it for a long time.
I've really been watching a lot of it.
And I'm constantly amazed at how people do stupid stuff and then get thrown in prison.
I don't understand.
I mean, okay, I used to do stupid stuff too, but I didn't get caught doing it.
That's the key component.
And two, it was always a cost-benefit analysis thing, right?
Like sure, I could engage in a fistfight with this person.
How likely is it that this person is going to call the cops?
They're punching me.
They're punching me over and over again.
I'm like, "Hmm, let me think.
Should I punch this guy back?
Let me see."
If I punch this guy in the kidney, it won't kill him, right?
It'll just hurt a lot and the fight will be over.
And if I punch him multiple times in the liver, then it'll be over even sooner.
At this point, they're kicking me.
I'm like, "Hmm, but now I'm weighing the cons.
You have to do a cost-benefits analysis with this stuff."
This guy, what was his endgame?
What was he thinking?
Like, before I go and smash someone's car up with a baseball bat at 4 AM, I think, does
this person know any police officers?
Is this person a police officer?
Am I at a police station?
Is this a police car?
You think, does this person have a lot of money?
Does this person know anyone in a gang?
Is there any way that I will get any blowback from this act?
If yes, then really think a lot about it.
If no, then just start smashing.
And you have to do that.
Again, I'm not a sex criminal, so I don't get that.
I mean, maybe he was driven by some other force.
I was just driven by wanting to smash things up real good.
So I don't get it.
That type of stuff is totally alien to me, but he had to carry the song.
I mean, if he did it once, it's still awful, but he could have just done it once and never
got caught.
He kept escalating it.
And that's what makes me think it was a sex crime.
So don't be a big old sicko, but you're just like an average criminal.
If you're like picking locks, breaking into...
You can break into a shed.
You'll be fine.
I'm not taking legal advice from me, but breaking into a shed is a lot different than breaking
into an occupied house or bank, which is federal.
I don't know if I've ever told a story before, but I used to hang out with this dude who
used to knock over liquor stores.
And he told me...
He did time for that.
He did seven years for robbing liquor stores, but this is back in the 80s when he was doing
this stuff.
He said he knew these dudes who used to knock over check cashing stores.
And the way that they did that...
I'm going to give you a bit of a tip here.
I know this segment's running long, but the way that they did that was one guy would hold
the door open.
You know, cash checking stores have all that bulletproof glass.
He goes, "Bulletproof glass is used to stop small arms, like pistols."
He goes, "AK47 will tear right through most bulletproof glass.
It's just not built for it."
But he goes, "It's built to protect you from gunfire, but it's not built to protect you
from a sledgehammer."
So one guy would hold the door open.
Imagine you're working at a check cashing place.
Got master gray.
Let's hop in the Jason Jalopy and go cash our checks.
We're sitting in there and the door...
Some guy holds the door open and then someone else runs in top speed holding a sledgehammer
and they would smash the sledgehammer against the bulletproof glass.
And he said the entire structure would disintegrate.
He goes, "It was getting hit with so much force.
It wasn't designed for this.
It would just shatter."
And he goes, "Everyone..."
Now I'm thinking about it.
Maybe he did this because he was quite detailed about it.
He goes, "Everyone would think a bomb went off.
It was so loud."
Imagine you're sitting there and you have your back turned.
You're typing something in or you're reading a magazine.
All of a sudden you hear a boom and just glass shatters.
Not even real glass, but...
He goes, "They would jump over, rob the place and get out like in a minute or two.
Super, super fast efficient robbery."
He goes, "They were doing this all over the state.
It was like Northern California they were doing this stuff."
One day they go, "Hey, you know, we're making a lot of money hitting these check cashing
places, but I bet you we can hit a ton of money hitting a bank."
And they ran into a bank.
I don't know if they did the sledgehammer trick in there.
They're awaiting the line.
The music...
He's holding a sledgehammer.
I don't know if they did it there, but they robbed a bank within a half hour.
They were both caught and they ended up doing like 10, 15 years in federal prison.
This is the cost-benefit analysis.
Check cashing places are not federally insured.
It was a local police crime.
Banks are federally insured, so the FBI is on the case in minutes.
You got federal officers looking for you.
He goes, "Within a half hour they were caught."
Before it was just cops were looking for him, but they couldn't find him and they're just
like, "Oh, I guess that check cashing place just lost a bunch of money."
Cost-benefit analysis, really the best cost is don't commit crime at all.
Even young Jason knows better, so I'm not out beating people up anymore.
Do you like that pause there?
Got master great.
Let's go ahead and hop in that carbon helicopter.
We are headed out to Barcelona, Spain.
I got a fight club going on in the back of the helicopter.
Got master great.
Puts it on autopilot.
We're boxing.
The helicopter lands.
We're all bruised.
We're all beat up.
We're all jumping off the carbon helicopter.
We're in Barcelona, Spain.
It's Easter week.
We're in the month of April, 1976.
This is actually a perfect story for the carbon helicopter because we landed in airport.
This actually takes place at Pratt Airport.
And here we're going to meet a very well-to-do couple.
They're getting ready to go on a vacation to the island of Mall Orca.
So we'll call the dad, Joseph, the mother, Samantha, and then they have a nanny.
We'll call her Margarita.
Is that her name?
Is that just a drink?
We'll call her Margarita and then they have a little baby, a little toddler, and we'll
call her Jonesy.
So I forgot the dad's name.
It doesn't matter.
The dad goes, "Honey, Samantha, you stay here with the nanny and little Jonesy.
I'm going to go buy the tickets.
You stay in this waiting area."
And the wife's like, "Okay, yeah.
Go ahead, honey."
So the husband walks off and buys the tickets.
And you know, it's pretty busy weekend.
And as he's walking back to the waiting area, he sees his wife just sitting there reading
a magazine.
He doesn't see the nanny or their baby girl.
"Hey, where'd the nanny go?"
He tells his wife.
"Very brusque with his wife."
"Yes, his wife.
You know, I got the tickets.
Where's Margarita and Jonesy?"
Wife's like, "What?
They're...
She's looking around on the bench and they're gone."
She goes, "She was sitting right here just like a minute ago."
Like, literally a minute ago, like, I didn't even see her leave.
And the dad is like, "It's kind of bizarre."
But the wife's like, "She must have just gone to the restroom.
Like, it couldn't really been anything.
You don't really think anything in these first initial moments."
But a little bit of time passes and the father goes, "You know what?
We need to check the bathroom.
Can you go in and check the bathroom?"
So the mother goes in, "Jonesy, Margarita, we're going to the bathroom."
They're like, "Man, can I have some privacy?"
Just yelling out names.
They're not in the bathroom.
Now, at this point, she's starting to get panicked.
At this point, any parent would get panicked.
They walk up to airport security and they go, "Hey, listen, our daughter's missing."
The last time she was seen was with our nanny.
And we know her fairly well, but we're really, really concerned because they just disappeared.
They're not here at all.
So airport security starts looking around for them.
They start calling over the PA.
"Will Margarita and Jonesy please come up to gate A?"
More time passes.
Now this couple was very well off.
So when they start to panic and they start to push on security, they're literally pushing
them.
They're like, "Where's my kid?
Where's my kid?"
Security's like, "Hey, stop it.
Stop it."
And pushing them.
They begin to basically say, "You need to stop this airport.
You need to ground all the flights because I need to know where my daughter is and the
nanny."
It's always a secondary concern because you really want your kid.
The airport actually goes to the extraordinary measure of halting all flights.
Now I'm sure it was just all flights out.
I don't think there was a plane circling overhead.
They're like, "Listen, the missing kid's not over here.
From France."
And the air traffic control's like, "Listen, we can't take any chances planes are running
out of fuel."
I'm pretty sure planes are still allowed to land, but they weren't letting planes go
up.
Crowdgatherers.
Everyone's looking for this kid now because basically either you're concerned for the
kid or you really want to get to your destination.
So everyone's looking for this kid now.
And eventually a giant group of people kind of surround the mother, consoling her.
That's probably all they were doing.
They were like, "So, did you watch television last night?
What did you think of one day at a time?"
Oh, that Schneider.
He's so funny.
What a crack up.
No, I did not watch television last night.
Eventually this old woman walks out of the crowd and she walks right up to the grieving
mother and says, "Just pray for your daughter to return."
That's not a bizarre thing to say when someone's grieving.
Just pray.
God will help you.
Something about it strikes the grieving mother in a weird way.
She turns to talk to the old lady.
The old lady has now walked into the crowd and has vanished.
She's not there.
And then the mother, Samantha, turns back to the bench where she had previously been sitting
with the nanny and sitting there on the bench is the nanny holding little Jonesy.
The mom freaks out.
She has this mixture of joy and just being really pissed off.
She found her daughter, but she can't figure out what led to the sequence of events and
she starts kind of tearing into the nanny and the nanny is puzzled.
She goes, "What are you talking about?"
They're like, "You disappeared."
The father shows up.
"Where were you?
You disappeared."
Everyone's getting back in lines.
The planes are going to be able to take off now.
You disappeared.
We shut down the whole airport looking for Jonesy.
Nanny goes, "I was sitting here the whole time.
I never got up.
I was sitting here the whole time and I had no idea what's going on."
Now, at a certain point, you do want to question the sequence of events, but at the end of
the day you have your child back.
You can figure out the rest later.
So the mom goes to take her child into her arms.
Baby's totally calm.
Wasn't freaking out or nothing about all this.
The mom goes to pick up the little Jonesy and the nanny won't let go of the kid.
Now the mom's getting really pissed off.
"Give me my kid.
Give me my kid."
And the nanny goes, "I can't.
I can't."
And her hands are open.
This toddler is laying in her arms.
She's not gripping it or holding it in any tight fashion.
She's stuck to the nanny.
The mother continues to pull and pull and pull.
She's sobbing at this point.
I mean, "Nanny got a whole new other set of circumstances.
You have to deal with it."
The dad goes, "Enough.
This, enough of this."
And he goes to get his daughter out of the nanny's arms.
The daughter stuck.
He finally is able to get a good enough grip on little Jonesy.
And I imagine put one of his foot on the bench that they're sitting on and "errrrgh!"
Pull Jonesy.
Literally tear her from the nanny's arms because they say, because the report said, that where
her arms didn't have any clothing.
So her bare forearms were holding on to Jonesy.
There were red marks on her arms.
As if someone had peeled off, then layer of flesh.
Like a burn.
For whatever reason.
I think that should be the end of the holiday, right?
That should be the end of it.
They decide, "Listen, we have Jonesy back.
Sorry that you have that weird alien third degree burn on your arm.
We are going to go to Barcelona.
We're gonna go.
The planes are flying again."
They get on their flight and everything's totally normal.
Plane takes off, little Jonesy's doing little Jonesy stuff.
About halfway through the flight, the nanny.
"Ahhhhhhhh!"
She's making ambulance noises.
She's freaking out is what she's doing.
I couldn't really portray that as well as I wanted to.
She's freaking out.
Now, not just like she's moaning and making ambulance noises, to the point that stewardesses
have to try to calm her down and that doesn't work.
They have to physically restrain her.
She's fighting against them.
"Ahhhhhhhh!"
And they're holding her down.
They have to do that all the way to Barcelona.
They don't turn the plane around.
This is 1976.
It would be a totally different story nowadays.
Probably just shoot her.
Have some air marshal put a bullet on the back of her head.
They land the plane and she is at that point, that's like, "Okay, vacation's over."
I don't know what happened with Jonesy and the nanny, but that was the icing on the cake.
The nanny freaking out.
So they actually get on another airplane, they sedate the nanny.
They get on another airplane and they head back home to Barcelona, where they put the
nanny in a hospital and they continue to sedate her.
And at a certain point, doctors want to figure out what's going on.
You have two mysteries here.
One you have the mystery that she vanished into thin air and then reappeared and said
nothing happened.
Doctors don't really care about that.
I'm sure they were curious.
I'm sure they told their loved ones, "Now sit here on my knee, kid, and hear about the
day the nanny disappeared."
But they're there to cure whatever's going on now, which is her hysteria.
She doesn't remember what happened on the plane.
People are like, "You went crazy on the plane."
She's like, "What?
I don't remember that.
I don't remember anything, really.
I don't remember disappearing.
I think they were making that up.
I was sitting there the whole time and now they're saying, "I'm going crazy on a plane.
I don't remember that."
She undergoes hypnosis.
This is what she remembers on the plane.
She said she's sitting there next to her bosses, the father and the mother.
She's sitting there and she hears a voice in her head.
Come here.
Come over here.
Come on.
You're looking around.
Come here.
Come to me.
What she described was, "An unpleasant sounding male voice summoning her."
She said, "While this is going on," she goes, "No one else was reacting to this voice.
She's just sitting there.
She feels herself getting panicked.
She's hearing clearly this voice, this unpleasant sounding male voice."
It's Stevens from the first story.
He's sitting behind her.
Want some honey?
She's like, "Uh."
She says that she's sitting on the plane.
She's hearing this voice and then on the floorboard of the plane, she sees a little light appear,
this red light.
Glowing on the floor of the plane.
Doctor goes, "Well, okay, then what do you remember?"
And Margarita is under hypnosis and she's laying there.
She starts screaming, "Goes into hysterics!"
And they have to end the hypnosis session.
Every time they try to press her to remember something beyond the red light appearing in
the plane, she became hysterical and they had to shut the session down.
This story came from a book written by Antonio Ribeira.
He's considered the father of Spanish ufology.
This is from a book called "Sucrestidos por extraterstias" or in English, "Kidnapped
by extraterrestrials."
It's possible, I think in 1976, or I think he wrote this book in the 80s, but I think
when you didn't have a lot of different layers of the paranormal, if you only had to put
stuff under religious miracle, demonic, UFOs, or cryptids, out of those four categories,
the UFO would be the one that would fit.
But I think we have such a more broad understanding of the paranormal world that this seems like
a time-slip Mandela-effect alternate reality event.
Where she actually went somewhere where the wife was just sitting on the bench next to
her and they were waiting for the dad to come back with tickets and everything was going
fine and she slipped into that reality out of our own.
In our reality, she just disappeared.
As far as how that plays with the red light, was she being summoned back to that reality?
Who knows.
The thing I like about this story, and it's something that I talk about a lot on this
show but I can almost not talk enough about it, is that it's going to make you paranoid,
that we have this idea that there are times we are safe and there are times that we are
not.
Spooky spooky graveyard, not safe.
Sitting at home watching television with your family, safe.
But the world of the paranormal, there is no "safe".
We are taught rules that are supposed to keep us safe, but think about it.
A demon that is older than the universe.
A demon that existed before God created reality.
Can be stopped by a circle of salt on the ground.
Or that you can take sage, you can take an herb that evolved on the planet earth, that
somehow going to protect you from something that fought angels in the war against heaven.
That new God that probably was like, "Hey dude, what's up?
Remember me?
Like I used to be one of your angels and now I'm a demon."
Your herb that you can buy at the witch store is going to protect you from something that's
older than time itself.
It doesn't make sense, we're constantly taught these things about being safe.
All these stories we talk about aliens abducting people late at night, we've covered stories
where people have been abducted in the middle of the day.
This woman was sitting at an airport surrounded by hundreds of people, hundreds of witnesses,
sitting right next to somebody and she vanished.
Assuming this story is true, right, assuming this just isn't a work of fiction, assuming
all this stuff is true, she simply vanished in front of everybody.
The world of the paranormal, it's not normal, the word itself is next to normal, so normal
rules don't apply.
I know that my door will keep out bad elements, bad physical elements.
And so we go, "I'm making a door of salt to keep out these evil spirits."
It's not the same.
It is 100% not the same.
If a ghost can float through a door, why can't it float through salt?
What about all the sodium in my body, right?
Demons still possessing people.
You're not safe when we talk about the world of the paranormal, when we talk about these
extraordinary events, broad daylight, alien abductions, kids playing in their backyard
attacked by multiple aliens, we covered that story, the Kosoblanka invasion.
Kids playing soccer in a park in the Soviet Union, attacked by robots.
It was like five in the afternoon.
It doesn't matter who you're around, it doesn't matter how safe you feel.
If the paranormal world wants to muck your reality up, it will.
And it could be a fluke.
You could happen to just walk through a portal and end up somewhere that you don't want
to be.
The fact that the red light and the voice was calling to her at the end makes me think
that this was intentional.
An obscure story, almost forgotten.
I never heard of this story before.
In 30 years of research, this happened the year I was born.
Never ever heard this story before.
This story I think should be up there with the man from Toured, but it's forgotten.
It's not talked about at all.
And it being obscure doesn't make it any less frightening.
Actually, it makes it more frightening, because you wonder how many other stories are out
there like this that we don't know about, or that we never had the opportunity to hear
about.
Because the only witness was the one who simply vanished.
The world of the paranormal is not your friend.
It's as friendly as a hurricane.
Or a pack of wild chimpanzees.
We study this stuff, we have fun looking into it.
It's creepy stories to tell ourselves and tell others.
We get little willies.
But it's swimming with sharks.
It is swimming with sharks.
And the creepy thing about the world of paranormal is I can avoid hurricanes.
I can avoid wild chimpanzees.
I can avoid serial killers and grizzly bears and avalanches.
But you can't avoid this.
It gets you if it wants you.
It can get you in your bed at night.
It can crawl out of the back seat of your car.
It can chase you as you're jogging down the street.
And it can snatch you up when you're sitting in a room of a hundred witnesses.
And your story may not have the "happy ending" of simply reappearing and going hysterical.
Your story may end with you never being seen again.
And although people would always try to find a rational reason for your disappearance,
some would know the truth.
Some of us know that the world of the paranormal is vicious, it's violent, and it's always
looking for another victim.
DeadRavverRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadravveradio.
Twitter is @deadravveradio.
DeadRavverRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)