Secret service agents hot on the trail of a counterfeiter make a horrifying discovery.
And then we travel to Helltown, Ohio.
A city steeped in rumors.
But how many of them are true?
Is the town hiding horrible stories of Satan worshippers, ghosts, and serial killers today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
I'm a rock big gal.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carbenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I went to the Indotronautics dude today.
Found out that I need a root canal.
Are they going to pull the tooth?
Those are my choices.
I have $11 in my wallet.
I have $11 until next Wednesday.
And I took some cans down to get them recycled.
And I found $5 bill on the ground.
So after I did my grocery shopping and finding the $5 bill and recycling those cans, I have $11.
And the reason why I'm saying that is I always say I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
It doesn't mean things are perfect.
But need a root canal?
That's just the way it goes.
You only got $11?
Don't let that stuff get you down.
Because I don't.
And that's the best way to look at things.
It really, really is.
Positive thinking, even when you're in a situation that doesn't seem very fun.
Just go with it, man.
Just go with it.
Because being negative about the situation helps nobody.
I'm going to get the root canal done next Thursday.
And next week, I'll get paid.
I can make $11 last week.
I can actually because I've been in this situation before.
So just keep your head up, guys.
I am having a great day.
And I really do hope you guys are having a great day too.
Let's get started with the episode here.
Oh, also I saw it in-game last night.
And it was super boring.
But I'll talk about that maybe on a bonus episode or something.
But let's go ahead and get started with the story here.
Let's go ahead and hobble board the carpenter copter.
You got some money for fuel?
You're going to have to pay for the gas on this one.
Because I only got $11, guys.
So after we go to the helicopter gas station, I'm buying all these snacks.
I was like, "It's cool, right? If I buy these?"
And you're like, "Fine, Jason. Buy your keto snacks."
"These are their extra expensive keto Doritos."
"Why don't they have those, dude?"
Anyways, so I'm buying all these.
I'm buying a bunch of beef jerky.
And you're like, "Fine."
Putting it on your credit card.
We're hobble board the carpenter copter.
And you're like, "Wait, it didn't need any gas."
And I'm like, "Hehehehe, just wanted my snacks."
We're going to hobble board the carpenter copter.
We're going back in time to the fabulous year of 1979.
Three years after I was born.
So imagine three-year-old Jason boogying down to disco music,
as we're talking about this story.
Florence, Kentucky.
It's July 13th.
And there's a bank teller just doing her job counting money.
And she discovers a counterfeit bill.
Now, counterfeit bills, a quick little side note.
You guys know what counterfeit bills are.
They're fake money, but just a couple little tips here.
One, counterfeiting is one of the easiest crimes to get caught for.
90% of all counterfeiters are caught within the first year of operation.
Generally, what they do nowadays is that when you make a counterfeit bill
and when it's detected by the Secret Service,
Secret Service has two jobs, protect the president,
and investigate counterfeit money.
And when the Secret Service gets their hands on a counterfeit bill,
what I've heard is that they then scan the bill
and get every fingerprint they can off the bill.
And if your fingerprints show up on enough bills
and there's no re-- like, if you're a bank teller,
if you work with a cash register, things like that,
your chances of handling more than one counterfeit bill is higher.
But if you are like a mechanic or you work at a call center or something like that
and your fingerprints keep-- or you're unemployed
and your fingertips keep showing up on counterfeit bills,
they're gonna flag you.
Now, a lot of times they may or may not have your fingerprints in the system already,
but in the most case, they do.
But in the most case, they do.
And in the most case, they do.
The store junior was left open one day,
and he went to go lock it, and he looked inside,
and he never said anything about what was in there.
Secret service agents are like, "Okay, that's enough suspense.
Show us where it's at."
So they get to the store junior, open it up.
$52,000 in counterfeit bills are sitting in there,
which is kind of what they expected.
They found a bunch of cash papers,
so stuff to make even more counterfeit bills.
Another police badge,
but what starts to concern them
is they find a ton of sex toys in there.
Now, nowadays, people have sex toys just sitting out.
Like, you'd be walking to some girls' house,
there's like a vibrator sitting on her bed stand.
Like, people aren't ashamed of that stuff anymore.
You walk down the street, some guys just like waving a dildo in your face.
But back in the 1980s, like,
if you had sex toys, you were considered some sort of deviant.
And, I mean, you could say people,
people, if they're waving it in your face today,
would be considered deviant behavior as well.
But back then, you look, you walked into someone's house,
there's a giant dildo on the floor,
you'd be like, "What are you doing?"
So, that's where the Secret Service agents came in.
They came in, they find these giant dildos, these whips,
all these sex toys, and they're like,
"Dude, it's 1983, I didn't even know this stuff existed."
So, at this point, the Secret Service agents were sword fighting
with these giant dildos.
The boss was like, "Guys, put that stuff down,
you have a job to do." They're whipping each other.
"Hey, look at me, I'm Indiana Jones."
Guys like, "Oh, I kind of like this thing."
The boss is like, "Get it together, guys."
Secret Service agents. But anyways, after the sword fight,
after the Aero Flynn sword fight,
where they're like swinging along, they're dressed in leather chaps,
I like this suit better than my, "Take it off, Henry, take it off, do your job."
After all, I have to line the move for what's coming,
because as they're processing the evidence,
they find an audio tape, and they're like,
"Oh, I wonder if this is like the new Starship album."
Or, I think at that point, they were still Jefferson Airplane in 1982,
but, "Hey, let's put in this cool tape,
maybe we'll listen to some tunes as they're driving down the road."
They put it in, and it's a woman screaming for her life,
begging to die, just completely like flipping out.
The agents are like, "Ugh, that is, okay,
this case has gone in a totally different direction."
This woman is just screaming and begging to be killed
as she's being tortured.
Secret Service say, "There's a little bit outside of our jurisdiction."
They end up, this is so bizarre, they end up contacting the FBI,
and they said, "Hey, listen, we have this guy in custody,
he's not saying anything.
We were able to find this storage unit full of all these sex toys,
and one guy starts pulling out of his pocket,
the FBI just like, "No, I know what a sex toy is,
just put that back in your pocket."
We also found this audio tape of a woman being tortured in his possession.
So we would like you to take over the investigation
and find out, like, is this guy a serial killer,
kidnapper, rapist, and the FBI said, "No."
Because they go, "There's no victims."
Like, you have an audio tape and you have some weirdo in custody,
but there's no victims, so we're not going to help you investigate.
So this is why this case is still talked about in Secret Service circles,
is because, one, they masked, he was a master counterfeiter,
but two, this was a, like, a murderer criminal investigation
they had to take, which they normally don't,
so they still talk about this case all the time.
Secret Service is like, "Somebody needs to investigate this guy.
We're not just going to get him on the counterfeiting."
They had to look into violent crimes that took place around the times
and places where they know the molepasser was,
because he was passing the counterfeit bills,
and they identify him at this point as Mike DeBartlebin,
and he had already been arrested in the past.
Now that they know who he is, they can find out his rap sheet.
They found out that he'd been arrested for sodomy, for kidnapping,
for attempted murder, and for counterfeiting,
so they're like, "This is the right guy,
and we believe he's done something else."
The storage unit, they found photographs of women,
and some of them they could identify, some of them they couldn't.
He had five ex-wives, and they were able to track him down,
and one of them was the woman on the tape,
and she goes, "Yeah, that was like a script he gave me.
Like, I was acting," and they were like, "That allowed them to go,
'Well, that's good that a woman didn't actually suffer this,'"
and the wife was kind of like, "Well, this was a fantasy he had,
so he did tie me up and was like, it was aggressive sex,
but he had me read this script out,
so it probably was some sort of sexual thing,"
and the cops are like, "Well, that's great,
but it's good that you're alive.
Like, hearing that tape is so horrible,
we can't imagine somebody actually going through that."
But the thing is, is that through the course of the investigation,
they did match him up to several brutal rapes,
and at least one murder, possibly two.
They did find a real estate agent bound up in the attic of a house,
and she was tortured and stabbed and so on and so forth,
so they finally said, "This guy is a sadist.
This guy is aggressively raping women, he's murdering women.
We think we have enough to put him away."
He goes to trial, and they don't charge him with the murder,
because they could never prove they found the real estate agent
tied up in a sadistic manner in an attic of a house she was showing,
and he was in the area, and people thought,
"Yeah, I thought I saw him with her, like, showing the house,"
and stuff like that, could never prove it.
He goes to trial, he's convicted of six cases of kidnapping and assault,
sentenced to 375 years, he's dead now, he died in 2011.
He never, ever, ever admitted to anything.
He was stone-faced about the whole thing.
So they don't know how many people he possibly could have killed.
They do know that he was an aggressive sexual sadist,
and they do know, they believe that he killed at least that one woman,
if not many, many more.
They were just able to kind of tie him to two murders,
but he was doing this mall passing thing for so long,
plus he had this history of this, plus he had these, they don't know.
They don't know, he just never, ever, ever admitted to it.
As far as I know, he probably never even admitted that his name was Mike.
I think that story's interesting.
I came across this story years and years ago,
I read at least two true crime novels on that case.
I found it fascinating because I like police work.
I like the idea, and it's probably one of the best, like, investigative stories,
where the cops are just kind of clueless.
They're kind of, not clueless, I don't want to say clueless,
it makes them sound bumbling, but they do kind of bumble onto this case.
They're looking for a guy who's ripping off, you know,
Claire's, who's ripping off Hot Topic, and they find a possible serial killer,
but to this day, they don't know how many people he may have killed.
I just find that story fascinating, because it's basically,
it seems so mundane on its surface, a financial crime that actually hid a very dark secret.
And you gotta wonder, you really gotta wonder how many of those storage units
you're driving by those storage places all the time,
how many of those storage units hold dark secrets like that?
It could be all sorts of horrible things in there.
It's just, it's creepy.
It'd be the perfect place to hide your murder kit away from your wife or your family.
And just, you go there, there's 24 hour ones, you go there late at night under your alias,
open it up, pull out your kit, pull out your tools, and go and wreck havoc on people,
and then just put them back.
And everyone else just drives by that storage unit every single day,
having no idea what was hiding in there.
Because the secret service agents didn't.
They just kind of stumbled across a giant collection of dildos,
and a tape that caught a serial killer.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
Our next story, we are going to Helltown, Ohio.
Now I know what you're thinking, can I find Helltown on a map?
Is it the actual name of the city?
No, it's not. No, it's not.
But it's a very, very interesting story.
Let's hop into Jason Jalopy, because it's kind of in the same area, I think.
Kentucky, Ohio, it's not that long of a drive.
I don't think, hey, can we go to the gas station?
I was just joking.
So anyways, we're getting into Jason Jalopy.
It's powered by, powered by grease from McDonald's.
So it just smells like french fries as it's driving down the street.
But we do have to go to McDonald's.
You're like, "Damn Jason, so I'm eating a bunch of keto fries."
They should have those. They don't.
"Meating a bunch of meat with no buns."
You're like, "Great."
We're driving down the road.
You're like, "Jason, just set up a Patreon account.
"Could boomin' food off of me."
We're driving down the road, and we're going to Ohio.
Now, this place is, we call it Helltown,
but it's actually a collection of towns.
All in Summit County, Ohio.
So there's like Boston Township and Boston Village and a couple other towns,
but kind of absorbing all of that is this place that's been named Helltown.
It was founded back in 1806.
Again, the town leader wasn't like,
"And I do decree this town is known as Helltown."
It was just this collection of townships.
But in 1974, that hippy Ford, President Ford, environmentalist, said,
"You know what? Let's go."
And I don't know anything about Gerald Ford,
but I just love that his action to beautify the nation caused this story.
He said, "You know what? We are going to have national parks.
"We are going to create a national park service,
"and the US government's going to buy huge parcels of land to beautify America."
And everyone's like, "Yay!"
I mean, because who doesn't want to go to national parks?
It is a treasure to have these giant places where you can go and enjoy nature
and drive your ATV and hunt.
Oh, wait, you can't do that stuff there?
Just walk around with a look at trees? That's fine.
I don't have an ATV or hunt, but you have these huge, untouched, pristine parts of America.
It's a great thing, right?
So anyways, he enacts this, and everyone's like on board, "Yay!"
But what they don't realize, and this is where the story starts to get really weird for me,
and not in a weird sort of like debunk skeptic way,
but I didn't know this would happen.
When the National Park Service created Cuyahoga Park,
they actually took this entire pristine part of land,
but they also took a huge chunk of these towns and said,
"This is now National Park territory. Move."
People are like, "What? They're going to go, 'Here's some money for your house?' Get out."
So, and people were like, "Uh, no, I don't like the National Park thing anymore, but it was too late."
The government owned that land.
They gave you "fair market value" for the house, and you were gone.
And people would post signs around town saying, "Now we know what the Indians feel like,"
because they were getting driven off of their land.
The government was like, "This is just the way that it is."
I find it weird that the National Park cut into these towns.
But what happened was, people had to leave,
and you had like other houses where people were allowed to stay
because it was outside of the zone, outside of the park.
But at these houses, basically, the government would walk up to the house,
kick everyone out, put a sign on the door that said, "No trespassing,"
and then go to the next house, kick everyone out.
And the goal was to smash the houses down and let nature reclaim it,
so it could be part of this beautiful park.
But, the government being the government, they didn't do that part.
They didn't do part two.
So, these houses just would start to slowly fall into disrepair,
and you'd have burned out houses, some houses would catch on fire,
and you would have basically two streets of normalcy,
and then you'd go two more streets, and it would just be like a ghost town,
these derelict houses just rotting away.
And that's when the conspiracy theories started.
See, people said, "No, no, no, no, there's had nothing to do with the national park."
What happened was, there was a chemical spill in the area,
and to cover it up, the government said, "Oh, no, that area is also part of the park.
Everyone get out, get out. The government agents are in gas masks and stuff like that."
They're like, "Go, go, go."
And people are like, "What are you talking about?"
People are slowly turning into mutants.
So, to cover it up, they added those parts of the town to the national forest.
So, that's where the conspiracies began.
For a while, it was known as mutant town,
and they believed that the no trespassing signs and all of that stuff
was to keep people from going near the chemical spill.
Now, that's one of those conspiracy theories that there's no proof of,
but it's also one of those conspiracy theories that it would require government-level knowledge
to find out if there was a chemical spill.
Do I personally think there was a chemical spill there turning people into mutants?
No, it'd be awesome, but it's unlikely.
I think they probably just did buy up that land.
But, you know, it's kind of awesome to think that maybe somewhere out there,
the Colostus is walking around a national forest.
Nowadays, though, people aren't too worried about mutant town.
People are worried about the mother of sorrows.
No, not a heavy metal band, it might be,
but mother of sorrows is what the local group of Satan worshipers are known as.
Apparently, there's two churches in the area.
And one of them is adorned with upside-down crosses.
And so people believe that church is being actively used by Satan worshipers
to try to bring the dark one back to Earth.
The upside-down cross was used in Gothic architecture.
It's actually the cross of Saint Peter, I believe,
because when they went to go kill Saint Peter, they said,
"Hey, we're going to crucify you."
And he said, "Please crucify me upside-down. I don't deserve to die like Jesus did."
So the upside-down cross in Christianity represents humility
and not being as good as God.
I don't think most people know about the Saint Peter idea of it,
but anyways, they're saying that that's why that church has upside-down crosses on it.
Great cover story if you wore the mother of sorrows,
which again, that's a pretty badass name for a cult.
But the mother of sorrow apparently operates in this area.
Now, because part of it is a national park and it does have these houses,
it would be the perfect area.
You could turn any of those houses into a trap house, sell drugs out of it.
You could turn any of those houses into a cult meeting places,
because they're basically off limits to everyone.
And if you're already doing something illegal, like child sacrifices
or animal sacrifices and stuff like that, or selling drugs,
you don't care. You're not going to be like,
"Oh, I want to kill all these kids."
No trespassing. Come on, guys. Let's go to another house.
You have those legends of these worship, these Satan worshipers,
there'd be a better term for them.
Satan worshipers just in general, not the actual Satanic church.
You'd have these Satan worshipers in the area.
You'd have these nefarious people.
There's a story which is one of those stories that I like.
It's actually really creepy.
And then we get to the school bus.
We get to the school bus. No magic school bus.
You're not going on a ride with some red-headed teacher
traveling into people's nostrils or whatever they do on that stupid show.
I never like that show. I just know that they always like fly around.
Anyways, I keep wanting to say magic school bus.
It's a regular school bus sitting out in the middle of the forest
in an abandoned house.
And apparently, this is one of the versions of the story.
The school bus was driving through the forest on a field trip
and a woman comes running down the street and says,
"My baby, my baby, my baby's so sick. You need to save him, bus driver."
Bus driver's like, "That's a weird accent, but you know, I'm going to help.
I will help you, weird lady."
So he pulls the bus up to their house.
The bus driver goes, "Hold on, kids. I'm going to go save this other kid.
You guys, you can fend for yourselves."
And at that point, a bunch of satanic worshipers creeped out of the forest.
It was a trap, you see.
And before the bus driver could do anything,
they attacked the bus and they rocked it and they killed all the kids.
Not just by rocking it. They went in and killed the kids, right?
There's another version of the story that this one's a little more outlandish.
That one's just theatrical.
But you figure, you know, 20 kids versus 10 sane worshipers,
it's, you know, they're not going to do very well.
This one has a single serial killer versus a bus of 20 kids,
and the serial killer hijacks the bus and kills the kids one by one.
And then if you go to the bus today, you can see the image of a man
sitting in the back of the bus smoking a cigarette,
and you just see all of these dead kids staring straight ahead.
That's spooky. A spooky, spooky image.
But one human, one adult versus 20 of anything will most likely lose.
One adult versus 20 chickens, one adult versus 20 squirrels,
unless he's like gassing them.
One adult versus 20 school-aged kids, one of those kids is Dennis the Menace.
One of those kids is Bart Simpson, and that, just one of them will wreck that dude.
And most likely, he can rally the other two.
I don't think one adult could kill 20--
I'm not-- wait, I'm not sure. I don't want to put this to the test, but, I mean,
if they're on a school bus, they're probably-- I'm going to get into the weeds on this one.
They're on the school bus. They're probably what?
First, second, third grade. If they're going on a field trip into the forest,
you don't take a bunch of kindergarten kids in there,
so they're probably like second or third grade, I'd say.
You'd have at least another adult on there.
One adult versus, say, 20 third graders, I don't believe could kill them all.
I just don't think that's possible.
But anyways, it doesn't matter, because neither of those stories are true.
It turns out that the guy-- the bus is real. It's actually been moved away at this point.
But the guy-- it wasn't parked by an abandoned house.
The house was being repaired, and the guy bought the school bus
so him and his family could live in it while the house was being repaired.
And then they left, and the school bus just got rotted and rotted,
and then as people will do, they made up legends about the school bus.
So, you go Jason. So what's the point of this story?
You're kind of saying, you know, this, and then you're saying, like,
this is the logical answer behind it?
This is why I think this is interesting.
I think there is something behind the legends of this town.
We've talked about this before. When I talked about it, did that episode on Stole, Kansas,
Ariana Grande and the Seven Gateways to Hell was the name of that episode.
That was a long time ago.
And this town is known for being haunted.
This town's known for having all of this, because it doesn't-- it's not really a town.
It's more like a geographical area, but people still live around there.
They do very aggressive policing to keep people out of that area.
Very, very aggressive.
They don't let people walk around late at night.
There's supposedly haunted graveyard that has, like, 24-hour surveillance.
There's constantly cops surveilling people who are out of towners coming in, looking around.
And I think it's one of those things that the people of this area could actually make money off of this.
They could have haunted ghost tours, and they could be like,
"Come, we'll walk through the National Park. It's free."
But you charge them five bucks to do a walking tour of all these creepy houses.
You could turn it into a boon for the community by embracing the ghostliness of it.
Because if people are already going there for free to check out this stuff,
you can find a way to monetize it and say, "Welcome to Hell Town," and, like, rename the place,
like, actually name your town Hell Town, and promote the hell out of it,
and get people there and make money.
But the residents there are actively pushing against that.
Even though these legends are very widespread in the area, they try to shut them down,
and they're like, "None of this is real. Mother of Sorrows doesn't exist.
Forgive me, Mother. I will pray to you tomorrow."
It doesn't exist. There's no such person.
"Please forgive me, Mother of Sorrows. I will sacrifice the cat tomorrow."
And you're like, "That's a weird press conference. Why do you keep getting on your knees and whispering?"
"I'm not. I'm not."
You're casting a magical spell on you.
But they should promote this stuff, because they could say, like, most haunted house tours,
you go on the haunted house tour and they're like, "Well, we might not see a ghost today,"
but, you know, just they don't have to be like,
"Oh, yes, you're a real killer. Killed a bunch of kids in there."
But you could still talk about it and become a tourist attraction,
because nearby is actually a ski lodge.
And it was so funny, because as I was doing research for this, research for this show kind of sprawls out.
I started researching the ski lodge and apparently it's just a bunch of hills.
There's no mountains and people were like, "Yeah, I went here to go ski,
and Ohio doesn't have any mountains in this area."
So I was just like going down a hill.
And one of the reviews was me and my daughter were at this resort, at this ski lodge,
and the bathrooms were closed. Done, done, done.
I should play some scary music right now. This is a true scary story.
Me and my daughter were at this lodge, right, and the bathrooms were closed.
Apparently Bloody Mary had broken out.
It was on the loose, so they closed the bathrooms.
And then all that was available was the porta-potties.
Yes, the spooky, spooky porta-potties.
And when I took my daughter to the porta-potties and looked out at the snow-covered hills that people were skiing down,
I opened the door up with the creek.
[Groans]
And there the toilet was so filled up you could actually see the poop higher than the toilet seat.
urine and feces had gathered to such a mighty amount that the smell overcame both of us.
But my daughter had to go to the bathroom so bad.
She couldn't even sit on the toilet seat without her butt touching the poop of previous people.
Yes, I give this resort one out of five stars.
So TripAdvisor and all people using TripAdvisor be warned the legends of Helltown are true.
It's not just a place of ghosts and myths and monsters, but a place of poop and pee and broken dreams.
So yes, yes, the area does seem to have its problems.
I'm not going to name the resort because I don't know. I mean, that was a real review.
Obviously, that's not exactly what she wrote.
I'm not going to name the resort. The resort did get a bunch of other good reviews.
But the point of the story is that the area is real and it does have economic business.
That whole thing has to just go into this next thing.
It does have economic purpose. So why aren't people promoting this?
Is it because the mother of sorrows is real?
Is it because this group of worshipers of the dark one don't want that attention?
It's really easy to make a statement like that. I have nothing to back it up.
But human greed is a really hard thing to overcome.
It's a very, very easy excuse for why people do things.
And so when someone says, "No, don't want your money," it does seem suspicious.
But who needs a little bit of tourist money when the mother of sorrows provides everything you need?
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]