What lengths would you go to to eat a hot dog? We take a look at a bizarre
phenomenon that seems to happen to people with severe dementia right before
they die and then one day a young man was walking through the forest when he saw
a deer hiding behind a tree. Or was it? Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing. Hopefully not
eating hot dogs. First off let's give a shout out to one of our legacy
Patreons coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now. Let's give it up for
Mikhail Malone. Everyone give a round of applause to Mikhail walking into Dead
Rabbit Command. Really really appreciate your continued support with Dead Rabbit
Radio. You guys can't support the Patreon that's fine too. Just help spread the word
about the show. Really really helps out a lot. Yesterday's Patreon supporter Greg,
I was looking over an email he sent me earlier back when he first joined the
Patreon. He found out about this show because of a flyer I put up in Sacramento.
I put up a flyer at a local grocery store when I was visiting a couple years ago
and he found it. So that is a great way to attract new listeners. I have flyers
you can print out in the show notes. Just tell people about the show. Talk about
it online. If you're embarrassed, if you don't want to talk about it in person,
talk about it on wherever. Just help get the word out about the show. You have no
idea how much that helps the show out. Mikhail I'm gonna go ahead and toss you a
shovel and some coal. Let's hop aboard the Carboner Caboose. We are leaving behind
Dead Rabbit Command. We are traveling all the way out to India.
Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga Chugga
We are going to be traveling to India. We are going to be traveling to India.
It will make it sound like you are pooping in a cathedral.
They poop in this hole and then the hole has a trough.
This is a real invention. They have this trough
attached to it. So they poop in this hole and then your poop
goes into it and then goes down the trough and then there is pigs there and they
eat your poop. It's a win-win really.
The pigs get a delicious meal.
You are like, "Dang it Jason." I didn't eat hot dogs
because you said not to. So I made a delicious bowl of stew.
You are like, "I can't eat stew or hot dogs."
These pigs are eating the poop. It's a win-win because the pigs get to eat all sorts of
spices and delightful tastes and the humans don't have to worry about
their feces. So it works out for both things. But remember this state
of India, mostly Hindus, they are vegetarians so they are not worried about it.
What has happened is that people
have started moving into this area who aren't vegetarians.
And so for decades these pig toilets were totally
fine. But then you'd be sitting there
and people would be like using the toilet and then they'd be like, "That's weird. It's backed up.
Why is my old natural toilet backed up?" And they go out there. There's less pigs.
They're like, "What? There used to be like five pigs in here and now there's only
like three. So the poop's not getting eaten as quickly."
And then the other person would be like, "Oh yeah, I'm
Johnson. I'm Harry Johnson. We just moved in like a couple days ago."
I saw this though. This is true. There wasn't a getting
Harry Johnson. This example isn't true. But what was happening to us
people? That's a horrible name. Harry Johnson.
People were coming in from around the country who weren't vegetarians
who saw all these pigs that no one was slaughtering and they began
killing them and eating them. And these pigs' primary diet
was human poop. And the people who lived there
were like, "Don't do that. Please don't do that. First off, that's our
toilet. You're eating our toilet. We need these. This is our sewage
system." People didn't care. It was delicious free
pork. You have all the hot dogs and pork loins
and everything that you wanted. These big plump pigs.
But they were fed off of human poop. Now people were saying this is super
unsanitary. Quit eating the poop pigs. And
it was unsanitary. It's just disgusting. It's just gross too.
It's not just unsanitary. Nowadays underground plumbing is far more common
in the state of Goa. It's not such a big issue. But there are still
pig toilets there. So if you ever find yourself in the state of Goa and you see some big old
fat pig walking down the street and it's just begging to be eaten,
don't eat it. Because that pig is probably full of human feces.
Also, it's probably not a good idea to just eat pigs
that are wandering through town. I'm sure it belongs to someone. Whether or not it's fed off of
poop, I don't think you should just walk around town
with a fork, a knife, and a bib just chasing after pigs. It will
end badly for you, no matter what part of the world you're in.
Mikhail, let's go ahead and leave behind India. Let's call in the
hair hang glider. Let's hop onto Mikhail's back. And he's going to jump off the tallest cliff
in India. I'm sure it's some giant mountain. And we are going to glide
all the way from India to a hospital in the middle
of America.
Now technically we didn't have to go all the way back to America.
This happens in hospitals all over the world, but you know home sweet home.
We go into the hospital, we're walking around, and hospitals are generally very depressing
places. Sure, babies are being born and broken
legs are being fixed, but that's not good stuff it does have in hospitals
too, but for the most part they're pretty depressing.
We're walking around the hospital and we see a guy laying in bed and he's like,
"Betty? Betty? Oh, Betty. Remember when we
used to play hopscotch together? That was such fun times. Back
in Herbert Hoover was still president and we're like, "Oh man, this poor
guy has Alzheimer's and he's like doing the jitterbug and his loved ones are like,
"Dad, Betty's been dead for three years and Herbert Hoover was
a terrible president. He was awful. I'm pretty sure the jitterbug wasn't invented
back then, but it doesn't matter. He's still doing the jitterbug." He's like,
"And Marty McFly came back and saved the day."
Before you shut it off. This segment is not me making fun of people with Alzheimer's.
Okay, before you shut it off. The point of this story, it's actually
really uplifting. It's funny because the hospital analogy, you would think
a story about Alzheimer's and dementia would be depressing, but not this one.
There is this thing called
terminal lucidity. It's not a conspiracy
theory, it's something that has been observed for over 100 years.
Terminal lucidity. What it is is you take people
who have dementia, who have Alzheimer's, who have like super advanced Parkinson's
where they can't feed themselves, they don't know where they're at.
They just, sometimes they're completely in a vegetative state, sometimes they're
just so discombobulated, they don't know where they're at or who you are or anything like that, and that's
tragic, but one day you walk into the room and they're like,
"Billy, hey, what's up, dude? Oh man, you're my bro.
Hey, oh dude, this has been so crazy, I'm sitting in this bed. And did you know
poor Betty, she died like 20 years ago and
Herbert Hoover was a terrible president." And you're like, you're back.
He's like, "I am, I am, I feel great.
I know I'm in this hospital and I know it's the year 2021, but
you look good too. Like, yeah, just everything's going so
well." What terminal lucidity is, is your
brain basically fixing itself.
This has been observed over and over and over again. You'll walk in and someone who the day before
couldn't feed themselves. They're eating, they're laughing, they're joking.
They remember everything. They're back to who they were.
The person you remember, the person that you've watched slowly fall apart
for the past couple months or a couple years is back to normal.
But, as beautiful as this moment is,
the name "terminal lucidity" says it all.
This happens shortly before they die.
But, it seems like a gift, doesn't it? You have that
person back in your life the way they were, the way they should be.
Had the illness not interfered, this is the person you would be
talking to. They'd be back to normal. And that seems like a gift. That seems
like those final memories are good ones.
It's the person you loved who's back sitting with you
in their bed having this conversation.
We don't know why it happens though. The idea, because it's linked to death,
the idea is as the brain is dying,
as the brain is basically shutting off, it goes into a fever mode.
And it actually begins to
excite dead end parts of the brain.
It's just to bring those things back to life. Some people say that
it could be caused by fever, drying up little pockets of water in the brain,
where they're a little whole. They don't know. But they've seen it so many times,
they know it is an actual thing. The problem is, we don't see it a lot
nowadays. So you could easily attribute it to
some old timing medicine thing, to medical documents written by excited
doctors and stuff like that. No. The reason why
this is going back to the sad part, the reason why we don't see it as much today,
we could start seeing it tomorrow. The reason why we don't see it as much
today is because our relationship with death has changed,
and our pharmaceutical answers to death have changed.
Nowadays when you get to that level, and I'm not judging anyone
who have had loved ones and they've authorized the doctors to do this, or doctors who have
done this, but now when people get to that state when they're so close to the end of their
life, and they're so mentally confused,
we drug them a lot. And the drugs interfere
with this process. Because if you're drugged up,
your brain's not gonna, you're not gonna wake up anyways. You're not gonna pop up the last
day you're alive and go, "Johnny!" Apparently
it's super creepy. It's not gonna happen, you're too drugged
up. So that's why they think we don't see it today. Our pharmaceutical answer is actually
preventing this. But again, it's not 100% like it's not saying that if your loved
one wasn't drugged up, they would have popped up and returned to normal.
A depressing story, but with the silver lining.
There's no silver lining, and that, they still die in the end. So yes, a depressing
event, but a beautiful story, I think. Even though it does end
with the person dying, they get to spend some final hours
back the way they were. So I think that's
really, really interesting story. Mikhail, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the
carbonar copter. We are leaving behind that hospital
in the United States. We are headed on out to Charlottesville, Virginia.
The year was 2008. We're actually walking down an old country trail
with a college student named Tyler. Now Tyler is a pseudonym that I've given this person.
We don't actually know this person's real name. They've chosen to rename
Anonymous, but we're walking along this little country area. It's mostly
Woods. We're headed to a nearby liquor store
to pick up some cigarettes, but we're taking a little shortcut through the neighborhood.
It's basically, I've never been to Charlottesville, but the way the story
makes it sound is that there's civilization dense, wooded
areas where you don't see another human for miles, and then a liquor store.
So I don't know how this place is laid out. It's by old Lynchburg Road.
If you guys are familiar with the area, old Lynchburg Road area
supposedly is pretty tree-y.
Jason, I think the word you're looking for is forest.
The sun is going down. We're still walking along this trail
with Tyler. It's a normal walk. We get to where we always get.
There's a little split in the trail. And Tyler's walked this trail before,
but this is the point where something's a little bit different today.
All of a sudden Tyler feels really uneasy.
He starts to hear sounds of movement in the area, huh? What?
What? He's looking around from side to side. He's looking
from left to right. And he sees it. He sees the source of
the noise. Standing behind a tree, almost hiding behind a tree.
He sees a deer. The deer's just
kind of staring at Tyler. He's off the trail. He's standing
underneath the tree, but still a little too close for comfort. Now, normally
you might be excited to see a deer in the woods. A little, little
nature's little gerbils. You know, they're not going to do nothing to you. They just kind of walk around.
You can pet them. You're like, Jason, I really hope you're not
wild. I really hope you're not trying to pet wild deer. You know what I mean?
Like, okay, they do have like the big antlers, but for the most
part they're not going to hurt you. Tyler's staring there and he's looking at this thing and
he goes, "Something's not right."
This deer did have antlers. It had a mighty
rack of antlers. But he said they looked
wrong. They were thick
burly antlers. He's staring there and
he's looking at this deer and he realizes, "Those are moose antlers."
And as he stood in that forest and the sun slowly
setting, it's getting darker every moment, he starts to
realize, "Not only is it impossible for a deer to have moose antlers,
those aren't even moose antlers. It's
like a close approximation of what a moose
antler would look like." And he's looking to have this
freak, this freak of nature obviously, because a deer can't have antlers like this.
Maybe it has some sort of disease. Maybe something's going on with it.
So he starts to continue his way down the trail and the deer begins to walk
as he's walking. Keeping pace with him but still in the forest.
Just watching him and following him.
He starts walking a little bit faster and this deer begins to move faster
as well. Tyler, at this point he's trying to figure out
is he being pursued? Is this thing curious? Is it just following him?
What's going on? But he begins to walk even faster and at this point
the deer is walking faster. It's keeping pace with him. So he has a
unique reaction to this. I think if I was there, or if most people were there
they would continue to run. They'd break out and run because whatever this thing
was does seem to be pursuing him and it doesn't seem
normal. You're in the middle of the woods, you're in Charlottesville, Virginia
and this thing is moving when you move.
He begins to walk even faster. The deer
keeps pace with him and then he stops.
He comes to a dead stop. The deer
reacts to him completely stopping by running at
him in a full sprint.
As this deer is running through the forest, Tyler picks up on some cues
that maybe he's not just looking at a normal deer with a weird antler
deformity.
First up, I guess this is more than just a cue. This is an
obvious thing. You're facing down something that shouldn't exist. He says
as it's running towards the forest it was making this very, very bizarre
motion. He said it was moving towards me at full
speed but all of its knees were
bent in the wrong way. And he said the way that it moved
was like a rocking horse.
It would rock back and forth on these weird
deformed knees and it would
just move closer and closer and closer to him through the forest.
He's watching this deer move in a way that you shouldn't be able to have any
locomotion whatsoever. Tyler's like, "Taylor's like, forget that."
I felt bad for it when I saw the funky horns but I don't have no idea
I don't feel bad for this now. It's doing something that is, you can't move like that.
It's breaking laws of physics. He begins running down the trail and this thing
is fully pursuing him down the trail at this point.
And he makes a turn. There's a bend in the trail. He's running.
He turns. He's now out of sight of the deer
and when he looks down the long stretch of trail in front of him, there is the deer
standing in the middle of the trail.
It has somehow cut him off.
He begins to step backwards and he actually trips over his own feet
falling to the forest floor. While he's getting himself up off the
ground, he realizes whatever this is,
this is not a deer. He said that
its eyes were facing forward.
In the sense that generally predators have their
eyes on the front of their heads and not predators
or herbivorous things like that have the eyes on the side of their head so they can see
predators without having to move their head a lot. He said this deer had its eyes
firmly in the front of its head. When he saw that
it clicked in his mind. This, whatever this is, it is a predator.
It was designed to hunt. He said its face
was more round than a deer and it had jowls
that just hung there as this creature is staring directly at him
standing in the middle of the trail. He realizes that
every single thing about this is wrong. It's not a deer. It's something
trying to be a deer, but still not being
able to hide its full lethal predatory nature.
As he's getting to his feet
he sees this creature stand up on its hind legs
and begin to walk towards him.
He said the very idea of it standing on its hind legs to him
seemed like some sort of challenge.
That was the initial reaction. This thing is trying to challenge me. It's trying to show me how powerful
it is. And he said from hoof to horn
it was 8 feet tall and towered over him.
And as he's turning to race back down the trail to get back to
safety he starts to hear this thing
chase him again this time chasing him on just
two legs. He felt that if he turned around
to look at this thing he was dead. He just
ran as fast as he could. He got to that split in the trail
and then almost immediately
he no longer heard the sounds of being pursued.
That's an interesting story. The author went on to say that maybe it was some sort of nature spirit
in the area that his friend who lived in the area believed that
there were a lot of things in the woods. Old stories he had heard that his
family had passed on. About stuff that people just couldn't
explain. That's an interesting story. It could be
a nature spirit. You would think it would pop up more often
because this didn't seem like the most remote trail. They didn't really give a lot of good
description about the area itself. But if it's a trail that's even traveled
say once a day or once every other day what's this forest spirit
doing the rest of the time? I'm just reading, just reading, not deer monthly.
So it's curious if it's a forest spirit what would
have provoked it when Tyler was in the woods. But let's go ahead and put our
conspiracy caps on and finish the episode up like this. You know, urban sprawl.
This story took place in 2008. Who knows if these woods are
still even there. We have urban sprawl. Anyone
who's lived any amount of time they can go back to the area they grew up in
and go "Well I can't believe they put all these houses up here. Look at..." And what happens
when we pave over this stuff where these
spirits or these creatures reside?
Yeah you could say maybe as we're going to start putting down
parking lots for Walmart's and build tract houses. Maybe
it'll be like a furry vengeance thing where the animals will unite under the
guidance of a warlord's spirit and they'll fight the
vibrant and frazier and push them into a bunch of cement and have a skunk
fart in his face. That could happen. But think about this.
What if we do pave over all this stuff? Build up these
McDonald's and these Arby's and these Taco Bells. We create a burger punk
society where it's fast food instead of nature.
Everything is paved over. It's glistening aluminum
and stucco. Where do these creatures go now?
If it's in the forest and assumes the form of a forest creature
if it's in an urban environment it would assume the form
of the urban environment. You're walking to catch the
bus one day. Steam is rising out of the manhole cover.
You're just enjoying your favorite music
playing through your iPod as you're standing at the bus stop.
You don't notice the man behind you. You don't
notice that he walks with an odd gate.
You don't notice him because he seems to blend in with everything.
Almost some sort of bizarre camouflage.
He stands behind you at that bus stop. It's just you too.
But anyone who drives past only sees one person.
He's the perfect predator. Five minutes later when the bus
pulls up there's no one at the bus stop. Thus driver
doesn't think anything of it. Continues along his route.
The perfect predator will blend into any
environment wherever it's at. It will find its prey.
Whether you're walking through nature, taking a shortcut
through the woods, or walking up a flight of stairs
late at night in an apartment complex.
These creatures for millennia
have hunted and consumed human flesh.
It will hide. It will hunt.
It will kill. It will
never be caught. And no one could even consider
it may be a beast from beyond explanation. A creature
from stories of old that is still hunting humans
to this very day.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio. Tiktok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]