When a young boy has memories of another place, you have to wonder is he a kidnapping victim
or a child sent from another reality.
And then we travel back in time to the days of King Solomon where we will investigate a
relic so powerful the forces of darkness can't even comprehend it.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun in this beautiful weather if you're listening to this
episode as I'm recording it.
Otherwise it might be the end of the world.
It might be the day after tomorrow and you're out running a cold storm.
But someone who could always outrun the temperature, give it up for our newest Patreon supporter
walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now.
It's Blitz Neo.
Wooo yeah!
Come on in Blitz Neo.
Come in to the door it's super cold out there.
People are like why do you keep referencing a movie that came out 10 years ago.
Blitz Neo you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That helps out so much.
Tell your friends, tell your family how much you love listening to.
Dead Rabbit Radio.
Blitz Neo I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys for the Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're driving all the way out to a pediatrician's office.
Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy's kicking up dust everywhere.
Blitz Neo's like why are we taking the Dune Buggy to this pediatrician's office.
Well you will find out very soon Blitz Neo along with the rest of the listeners here.
We're headed out to this pediatrician's office because we're gonna visit a young boy.
He's only four years old.
That's a tiny little guy.
Four years old.
We walk into this pediatrician's office and we see this young man.
He didn't post his name online.
We're gonna call him Maxwell.
We're sitting in this pediatrician's office reading these magazines playing with that weird
wire thing.
Remember he used to take the wooden blocks.
Just kinda push him up and down the wire.
You wanna talk about some weird mind control MK Ultra toy.
It was the point of that toy.
It was in every doctor's waiting room.
They may still be in doctor's waiting rooms but you know what I'm talking about?
The metal wire and they're like loopy and you move the toys around.
No one ever owns those outside of a doctor's office.
But Maxwell says that this happened quite a few times and he was four years old.
He said he'd go to the pediatrician's office with his mom.
And then he would walk down the hallways of a stereotypical doctor's office.
We've all been into them.
And this doctor's office actually opened up into a wide hanger like an aircraft hanger.
And in this aircraft hanger is a table.
And a little medical table.
It's not like a card table.
It's not like a folding card table.
He's brought to the table and he gets up on the little bench, the little leaning back
medical bench thing, seat, whatever they call it.
And he's sitting there and a doctor shows up and gives him an anesthesia.
Now I don't think it was like a topical one.
I don't think they gave him like the shot in the arm to numb the arm or shot in the
mouth to numb the mouth for dental pain.
I think they actually put him under.
He doesn't specify but he says they gave him an anesthesia.
So I think it was that general whole body anesthesia.
And he said this happened quite a few times throughout his childhood.
He remembers this happening all the time.
And then one day when he shows up at the doctor's office, he walks through the totally normal
doctor's office on the outside.
He walks down this hallway.
He enters the aircraft hanger.
He gets up on the table and the doctor tells him this time, Maxwell, this is the last time
you're going to be visiting me.
In fact, this is the last time you're ever going to see me.
It's time for you to go.
The anesthesia is administered and Maxwell blacks out.
The next thing he remembers is sitting in his house.
But it's not his house.
His mom's there.
It's somebody's house.
But not his.
Not the house that he had lived in his entire life.
He looks around and it's different.
Even at an early age, he can realize this is not the place he grew up in.
But his mom's here and his mom is acting like this is their house.
And he asks his mom, "Hey, where am I?"
And the mom goes, "You're home, honey.
It's kind of a weird question.
You're home."
Maxwell goes, "This isn't my home.
Like, I used to live somewhere else."
And the mom goes, "No, Maxwell.
Unless you own your own home, unless you have a mortgage that I don't know about, this is
the home you grew up in.
This is the only house you've ever lived in.
This is our home."
The mom just goes about her business.
Maxwell's sitting there on the couch and he can't figure it out.
This isn't my home.
Maxwell ends his post by saying, "The world has behaved differently ever since I last
was in that aircraft hangar.
Things aren't the same as I remember them."
Now, he says, "I'm sure you guys think I'm trolling.
I'm sure you guys think I'm making this up, but I have really no way to prove it to you.
I am not from here."
And obviously, people start asking questions about this.
This is a really, really interesting story.
People start asking questions about this and they go, "What do you mean how the world behaved
differently?"
And he goes, "What I remember from being a little kid."
He's not five when he's posting this.
This was years ago.
And this post is actually from the year 2012.
He goes, "What I remember of the world was that there was a lot more dirt everywhere.
Not a wasteland, not an apocalyptic landscape.
There's just more dirt.
I remember there being sand everywhere.
The other thing that I noticed that's most obvious outside of all of the sand, cars looked
different.
They just seemed to be different styles.
Like when I started looking around, I didn't recognize any of the makes and models of those
vehicles.
And those were the two biggest differences.
The sand and vehicles appear differently from his memories as a young boy to the day that
he was in this new house.
This is a fascinating story.
I really, really like this story.
It could totally be made up, right?
This is an anonymous post online.
So what I find interesting is that we have two rational answers and two paranormal answers.
One, we could easily see this.
The rational answers is kidnapping, right?
His mom could have kidnapped him from another custodial parent or from another country or
something like that.
The kid could have been put under general anesthesia.
I'm assuming the story itself is true.
Like the framework to me, he's put under.
So when his mom loads him up on the plane and flies him from Dubai to America, he's
not freaking out the whole time.
He's like, "No, no, I'm being kidnapped.
My dad's over there."
That could be a possibility.
And then his mom, I mean, that would be kind of a bold kidnapping thing where you're gas
lighting the kidnapping victim.
You kidnap someone from their house, take him to your house and you're like, "What?
No, you never lived there."
And she's like, "I clearly have the keys to a different house.
I'm trying my keys in the store.
It's not working."
Like that's a pretty bold kidnapping thing.
But you know, you're for possibility.
The other option is that this kid could have been an immigrant coming from a place that
had a lot of sand, let's say somewhere in the Middle East or somewhere in Northern Africa.
And he's coming over and it's such a culture shock to him.
That's the only way he remembers it.
Maybe the framework isn't correct.
Maybe he wasn't walking in this large aircraft carrier.
The human memory is faulty, right?
And he could have been an immigrant from another country and he just has no other way to explain
it other than this weird fantastical tale.
Now both of those, like I said, are irrational.
Obviously, you have to do some sort of bending, some sort of mental gymnastics.
The cars in Saudi Arabia are the same cars in Detroit.
But maybe they were just fancier over there in his neighborhood.
Now he's over in America or wherever he went.
I'm assuming he's in America, but that's just because I'm from America.
He's like, oh man, look at all these beaters, look at all these pieces of junk driving around.
But then we have the paranormal answers, which I just love as well.
And I think this is probably what a lot of people who were reading this thought and maybe
even you while you were listening to it.
Time traveler being sent back in time to a world before the sand took over.
He may say it wasn't an apocalyptic wasteland, but anywhere with sand everywhere, assuming
again you're not in a sandy region of the world, that doesn't sound like the best.
It's like a ton of fun.
You're like, hey mom, I'm home.
They canceled school because a sandstorm hit.
It doesn't sound super comforting.
So maybe he was sent back from the future to join us in a more comfortable time.
Also alternate realities is another one that you could really hang your hat on because
of the changes of the vehicles.
It's interesting because when we look at alternate realities, when we look at timeline changes,
it's never, I remember, well some people, some people said they've had these events,
but in general Mandela effect theory, it's not, that's weird.
I remember Mitt Romney beat Barack Obama and we had four years of Mitt Romney and then
Hillary Clinton was president.
It's never these huge timeline shifts.
It's Bernstein Bears versus Bernstein Bears.
The easiest changes in the timelines would be choices like that.
For a huge shift, like who was elected president at what time, that would be so different.
That would be a parallel reality that wouldn't even be parallel to ours.
It would veer off wildly in one direction.
If Hillary Clinton had won instead of Donald Trump, if Abraham Lincoln had not been assassinated
at the end of the Civil War, these are huge changes.
They veer off so wildly.
But whether or not when you have a bunch of eggheads at Ford and they go, "Hey, we're
coming out with a Mustang and here are designs for this new 2022 Mustang convertible."
And they have five designs and people choose one over the other.
That's not impacting the world.
That's just a different style of car.
When you're looking at who do we cast in this movie?
Do we cast Ryan Gosling or Ryan Reynolds?
That's not a massive change.
So little things changing, plots in stories.
It's not even being published in the first place, you're being published by a different
author.
Those are the little changes that would be a parallel universe.
You'd still have Bush Obama, Trump Biden, but a couple cars were designed differently.
Throughout the timeline, a couple different people got different jobs.
It's not going to impact your day to day life, what style of car you're driving.
So that tracks with the parallel universe theory.
And that also tracks with what we know of the Mandela effect.
The Mandela effect, a lot of it is people misremembering things.
But some of them, Berenstein Bears for example, I know for a fact, was called the Berenstein
Bears.
So he could have come from an alternate reality, he could have been sent over here, which would
be an interesting trick of the Mandela effect of parallel universes because from what we've
seen people slide in and out of them accidentally.
The kind of the going theory of Mandela effect is there was some sort of huge disaster around
2001.
Outside of September 11th, something bad happened.
Millions of people were sent over to this new reality where there's been slight changes
in the timeline.
That's kind of how the Mandela effect started.
That was the initial theory of what happened.
But the idea of purposely sending people over to different timelines, that's very intriguing.
That's a fairly new theory.
People being sent here from somewhere else.
Which begs the question if the technology exists to slide into a parallel universe, don't
steal my idea for television series, have five seasons mapped out.
If you have people sliding from one parallel universe to the other, if this technology
exists in other universes, would that mean it's possible, because the variations would
be very slight between universes, is it possible that that technology exists today?
Could you purposely, not accidentally, could you purposely send people to alternate realities?
Very very interesting story.
If this story is true, super fascinating.
A young boy finding himself in a different house and seeing all these differences and
he has these faint memories of this old childhood.
It could also have been a series of dreams, right?
He could have had a baby stroke.
He could have messed up his brain.
But that was a very depressing theory, but that's possible as well.
But are people not accidentally coming into our universe?
Are people being sent over here on purpose?
And for what reason?
Who knows?
Is it possible that we are the best timeline?
That is chaotic?
As things seem?
This is the best timeline out of all possible timelines.
So people are coming here, but we're not sending people to other timelines.
Fascinating story.
And we'll never know the truth until we find ourselves standing in a house that's not our
own and there's sand everywhere.
You're like, "Ding it, I just cleaned up my house and my own reality.
Now I'm in this dirty reality.
This sucks."
Blitz, Neo.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonar copter.
We're leaving behind this sandy reality.
We gotta kick all the dust out of the carbonar copter.
We are leaving behind this alternate world.
We are headed all the way out to Bible time.
So you didn't know that was a place?
You can find it on a map.
Specifically, obviously when I say Bible times, we're headed out to ancient Israel.
This is nuts.
This is one of those stories that I came across and there's so many questions that you can
ask about this.
There's two in particular we have to focus on.
Otherwise, this episode is going to be three hours long.
But recently I came across this thing called Solomon's Chomere.
Never ever heard about this thing before.
Absolutely fascinating religious object.
This thing should be as popular as the Ark of the Covenant.
This thing, I think, on a Jones should have chased this thing.
We're back in 900 BC.
We're back in this era of time, which seems incredibly recent if you think about how long
history has been.
Humans have been around, civilized humans have been around for like 10,000 years.
Empires rose and fell and were wiped out of the history books by the time we're at King
David in Israel.
This is all in the Old Testament.
You have Lil David before he's king.
He kills Goliath with his sling.
He unites the 12 tribes of Israel.
He conquers Jerusalem.
He brings the Ark of the Covenant, that holy relic, into the city.
And he said, "I want to build a temple to house the Ark of the Covenant."
The Ark of the Covenant is basically a biblical super weapon.
You would, oh, I mean, it's like right out of the movie, Raiders of the Lost Ark.
Okay, I know Raiders of the Lost Ark was based on the biblical story.
But it's insane.
It was this box that had to be carried by four people.
It had to have all this special lining on it.
If you opened it up, your face melted, you would open it up and it would devastate cities.
And this was a wonder created by God and given to the Israelites to use against their enemies.
We've covered it a lot on the show.
I'll find all the cool episodes.
I'll put them in the show notes.
The wars are done at this point.
King David has united all 12 tribes of Israel there in Jerusalem.
And he goes, "I want to build a temple for this Ark of the Covenant.
And I want to build it in Jerusalem and I want to have it available for all Jewish people.
All of these tribes that have been separated, this will be a home for us all.
This will be the Holy of Holies.
And in this temple, I want to build a windowless sanctuary where God can visit.
God can come down from heaven to earth and rest.
Just chill out for a while.
He's given us so much.
We are going to give him this windowless room.
God says, "Nope.
Not because I don't want to be in a windowless room.
I really like your idea of the temple."
But King David, you have spilled so much blood.
These wars that I commanded you to do, they're good.
You won.
But you killed too many people.
You cannot build my temple.
And that's when we meet Solomon, King David's son.
Now Solomon eventually becomes King himself and he is allowed to build the temple.
And King Solomon is a super interesting character because what happens is to build the temple,
he gets a magic ring called the Seal of Solomon.
This is actually where the Jewish star of David, that symbol that is on the Israeli flag
and that symbol that is sacred to so many Jewish people around the world, it comes from
King Solomon's ring.
This ring, this magical ring is where that symbol is from.
That's why it is given so much importance.
This was the ring that King Solomon wore.
And this ring was engraved by God and it gave King Solomon power over demons.
He goes, "You know what?
I could build this temple.
I could have all these people do this stuff, but I'm going to let my Jewish brothers and
sisters rest on this one.
I'm going to use this ring to control demons.
I'm going to call them forth from hell and put them to work.
I'm going to make them build this temple."
And that's what he did.
He used this ring to call forth these demons and they fell under his control.
Could you imagine if someone got ahold of that ring today?
What you would be capable of?
Hopefully something good.
Hopefully just building buildings.
But we're here specifically to look at Solomon's Shamir.
I've always heard about the stories about the seal of Solomon, the ring, him able to
control demons.
I was very familiar with that stuff.
I've never heard of this before.
Solomon Shamir is considered one of the ten wonders that God created on the sixth day
of creation.
He created these ten things to give to man.
One of them is a donkey that talks.
One of them in the Bible, there's a story about a donkey talking and people go, "Well,
that's impossible.
This donkey is giving people advice."
God created that donkey on the sixth day.
That's one of the ten wonders of God.
One of them, this is so fascinating to me, one of them is a pair of tongs.
A pair of metal tongs.
Now all of this stuff has come, I have never seen any of this stuff in the Bible, but a
lot of this stuff came from rabbis and theologians and philosophers as they're interpreting biblical
works and the Talmud and the Koran.
As they're looking through all of this stuff, they go, "God must have created the tongs,
the metal tongs that you use to put stuff into a furnace because you cannot create metal
tongs unless you have a pair of metal tongs.
You could not hold the metal over the heat for long enough to be able to forge metal
unless you already had forged metal to forge this new metal."
So the belief is so fascinating, the belief that the very first pair of tongs, of metal
tongs to be able to do metalworking, was created on the sixth day by God.
But again, Solomon's Shamir.
This Shamir is, in a nutshell, there's a lot of debate over what this is.
Apparently it was a worm.
There's a lot of references in the text calling it a worm, so a lot of people believe this
was some sort of living creature.
It was a worm that had the ability to cut gems and diamonds.
You could use this Shamir to basically etch into any surface imaginable.
According to Talmud, it says, "The Shamir was, without doubt, an extraordinary object
as it possessed the ability to alter stone, iron, and diamond by its mere gaze."
So again, we're talking about something that a lot of people believe was alive because
they keep calling it a worm and they keep talking about it being able to see something.
Now we call it Solomon's Shamir, but it actually originally belonged to Moses.
So we're going back to like 1300, 1400 BC.
And Moses got ahold of the Shamir and used it to create the breastplates for the high
priests of the Israelites.
He'd used the Shamir and it would basically carve in these symbols and sigils and holy
icons into this metal breastplate.
Apparently very ornate designs.
But this thing's dangerous.
While Moses was using it, it almost scalded him.
He's lucky because a couple people got killed by this thing.
Moses has it in, say, 1300, 1400 BC.
And when King Solomon is having his temple built, he's watching all these demons build
stuff, but he's like, "You know, I want stuff to be a little more elaborate.
I want that Shamir I've heard about."
King Solomon goes, "I know that Moses used to have this thing called the Shamir.
I want it."
And what he does is apparently, there's different versions of this story.
Apparently he contacted the demon, Asmodeus, and demanded that he give him the Shamir.
Because he has the seal of Solomon.
Asmodeus, who at some point must have gotten possession of the Shamir, gave it to King
Solomon.
But when King Solomon gets it, it's the size of a barley corn.
Which I'm assuming is pretty small.
I don't know if in Israel they grew these giant pieces of corn called barley corn.
It was this tiny little piece.
Because when you use the Shamir, it actually reduced in size.
He takes it.
He takes it and the little guys will just want it.
That'd be bigger.
And he wanted to use this to do very special carvings in the temple.
Because he was told, remember his dad wasn't even able to build it because he spilled too
much blood.
He was told that you couldn't have any bloodshed during the building of the temple.
So if you were hammering something or sawing something and you accidentally slit your finger,
you pretty much had to demolish the place.
You couldn't spill any blood.
So using the Shamir, they were cutting very intricate cuts into the building blocks.
Some people say that whole pieces of stone were just set in place.
And then the Shamir was used to carve it into a usable structure.
Because a lot of people have debated over what was actually going on.
But we look at the Shamir being used by King Solomon or King Solomon's people.
Because this thing was super dangerous.
Just like the Ark, it had very special precautions.
When it wasn't being used, you needed to wrap it in wool and bran.
Not bran flakes, but what bran flakes are made out of.
Some sort of barley.
And then put into a lead box.
If you did not do that, any other box would blow up.
Any other box would totally blow up.
And I don't know how they figured that out.
Maybe he commanded a demon to tell him.
He was probably putting it in wooden crates and metal boxes and stuff like that.
He's like, "You know, I'm really trying to get some sleep."
And everything keeps blowing up.
You had to wrap it in wool and bran, put it in a lead box.
And it was used to craft the temple.
And a couple people got melted by this thing.
A couple people got disintegrated by the Shamir.
It's interesting because nowadays there's been ancient alien theorists say that it may
have been some sort of laser.
It may have been some sort of laser beam that was able to etch into metal and diamonds
and into the temple stone.
But if theologians go, it probably was a space laser.
It probably was a miracle from God.
And it may have been alive.
Because in the text, it's constantly referred to as a worm.
When you look at the Talmud, when you look at the Koran, which also mentions the Shamir.
As far as we know, it doesn't exist anymore.
And again, theologians debate over this.
Some people believe that it was just used up.
That it kept getting smaller and smaller because each time you use it, it gets a little bit
smaller.
It was just used up and just disappeared.
The Talmud specifically says, "When the temple was destroyed," meaning the first temple in
Jerusalem that was destroyed, the Shamir vanished.
So it was linked to the temple that it was used on.
And that's why it's more closely connected to Solomon.
He was the guy who created this giant house for God.
And he was the last person to use it, Solomon's Shamir.
So that's just super fascinating, right?
We have, at the very least, I don't know which one's very least, but you have possible alien
technology in the hands of humans.
That's the only way you could think of this thing in any sort of rational way, that it
was some sort of alien technology, that it was a laser beam that was used to cut into
metal and stone and engrave.
King Solomon also used this to make mystical sigils on precious gems.
And he would hand these out to people.
He would have just walked through the crowd and hand them out, but he would hand them out
to people who had earned them.
These, could you, here's the thing, if the Shamir doesn't exist anymore, the gems do.
His ring does.
Where are these things?
I said, could you imagine getting your hands on that ring?
That's a high level object.
Imagine if you just had an emerald the size of the palm of your hand and in it is a magical
sigil crafted by King Solomon himself using one of the ten wonders that God created on
the sixth day of creation.
The power that would exist in that stone is mind boggling.
They're still out there.
They're either in someone's private collection, they're in some government's vault, or they're
lost somewhere in the Middle East, or maybe the Crusaders took them and they lost them.
But they're somewhere.
The Shamir wore down over time, but emerald the size of the palm of your hand is going
to last a while.
Going back to the two options, we have the sci-fi laser, but then we just have the other
option that this really was one of the ten wonders God created and that mankind had for
a moment in time had this wondrous object that let them do things that were impossible.
Things that we now need tons of technology to do, they have this little worm.
Fascinating in and of itself, but then let's look at the Quran to wrap this story up because
it gets even weirder when we take a look at this story.
This episode is going to go long, I can't help it.
This is so fascinating to me.
In the Quran, it states that it wasn't demons that built the temple in Jerusalem, it was
the jinn.
And there's a lot of, sometimes the jinn and the demons are two separate entities, sometimes
the term is used interchangeably.
But in this version of the story, the jinn, not demons, are the ones who created the temple.
Under King Solomon's command.
This is insane.
So King Solomon has the ring, he's commanding the jinn to build the temple and he watches
over them as they're building this temple.
And King Solomon has his staff and he's just kind of standing there watching them labor
bringing these rocks over.
They're like, the jinn are working and they look over and King Solomon's just watching
them.
Oh man, that guy's such a jerk.
I can't believe he enslaved us.
They keep building the temple, they look over and King Solomon's standing there watching
them, demons going about their work and they're building the temple and they look over and
King Solomon is standing there watching them, just standing there with his staff.
And this goes on for about a year or so.
And then the jinn who had been building the temple under his command didn't know that
at some point while they were building the temple, he died.
King Solomon died and he was actually leaning against his staff.
He was dead for a year just standing there and the jinn could have left the day he died,
but they thought he was still in command so they continued to build it.
And the Shamir ate through the bottom of the staff and King Solomon collapsed and that's
when they realized he was dead.
This completely boggled the jinn's minds.
They had no idea what was going on, not that they had been hoodwinked and doing a year's
worth of work.
What it turns out, this is so insane, has huge implications for the world of the paranormal.
What it turns out is when the jinn walked up and they saw that King Solomon was dead and
they saw that Shamir kind of crawling around on the ground, they didn't know what it was.
They had no idea what they were looking at and here's why.
According to the Quran, the jinn or demons extrapolated out to demons because we know
that he had power over these creatures, whether or not you're using the term jinn in this
context or demons, these are one and the same in this context.
These creatures from hell under King Solomon's magical command using his ring, they did
not know what magic was.
They looked at this little worm just walking around on the ground next to this dead body
and they go, "What in the world is that?"
Because according to the Quran, this is fascinating, only God knows the secrets of the occult.
Only God knows the secrets of magic.
So to the demons watching this, they're like, "When in the world is that?"
"I've never seen anything like that."
Because they don't know anything about magic or magical relics or anything.
Fascinating.
And you're going, "Jason, but wait, no, no, no, no, no.
He's using a magical ring.
He has these magical sigils.
People call demons up today using these magical rituals."
This could very well be true.
Demons, jinn, whatever you want to call them, may not know magic.
And you go, "Jason, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just,
just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just, just