Are you ready to spin the night in a haunted McDonald's?
A man makes a terrible decision and pays for it $1 a week.
And then we travel to England, where we meet a man who's trying to outrun a German bombing
raid and instead runs right into the long furry paws of a demon cat today on Dead Rabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I really do.
I hope you guys are having an awesome day.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're just going to get started here.
First off, I got to say thanks to my newest Patreon, McCallBongLabal.
Thank you so much McCall.
I actually asked.
Hey dude, can you tell me how to pronounce your name?
He sent me a vocal file so I really really appreciate that.
It's always helpful when I know how to pronounce your guys' names.
So thank you and it's also helpful when you guys support the Patreon.
I really really enjoy that.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine.
Just help get the word out about the show.
That helps out a lot as well.
So we're going to toss McCall the keys to the Carpenter copter.
Go ahead and grab those keys.
We are first flying off to Pueblo, Colorado.
We're flying.
We're going to fly low.
I want to enjoy the maces and the ground and stuff.
It's not...
Wait, no, I'm thinking of Arizona.
Never mind.
Go up.
I was thinking it was all magical Sedona, Arizona stuff.
Colorado is just a bunch of mountains.
I'm used to mountains.
Take us up high McCall.
Flying over and we're going to land in the parking lot of a McDonald's.
Employees uniforms because we're actually working at McDonald's right now and we're
loving it.
We walk in saying hey to our buddies.
We should all get a job together.
We should just all have...
I guess that's a cold.
Never mind.
We should all move to a commune and grow potatoes.
We're all hanging out at this McDonald's dancing around.
We have a dunk tank built over the deep fryer.
You're like Jason, this is a terrible idea.
It's only a terrible idea if I'm able to hit the target.
Throw in potatoes.
Do they actually have potatoes there?
We're doing all sorts of stuff at this McDonald's.
We're doing the twist on the tables.
The real employees there are quite disturbed, but they're not really disturbed by our antics,
even though we're super annoying at this McDonald's.
This is a McDonald's in Pueblo, Colorado, and this just happened on February 13th, 2020.
The employees, it's 3.30 a.m. and the employees are working on this McDonald's.
I'm assuming it's the 24-hour McDonald's, but it's possible they're just the cleaning
crew.
And they hear outside in the darkness surrounding this McDonald's.
You got the big expansive parking lot.
Parking lot lights shining down, just singular circles of light trying to cut swaths through
the pitch blackness.
And while they're cleaning up, they hear over the bustling noise of a bunch of young McDonald's
crew people doing McDonald's crew stuff.
[Metal clanging]
What in the world was that?
Did you hear that?
Deep fryer, turn it down, turn it down.
Other employees like, "Ahhh, I heard something."
Sounded like it was saying something, but not any language that I know.
[Metal clanging]
They hear barking now from outside the McDonald's.
But it's not the sound of a dog, it's the sound of a human barking.
Which is more terrifying.
I mean, unless it's like a little kid doing it and they're like, "Look at me, I'm Paw
Patrol.
Ruff, ruff, ruff."
You're just like, "That's not what a dog sounds like, idiot."
Then you correct them.
But if you're in the middle of a darkened area and you hear a dog bark, you probably won't
even register it.
If you're in the middle of a darkened area and you hear a human bark, you're going to
be a little concerned.
So now they've heard a strange language, human barking, and then, "Ahhh, a woman screaming,
but I'm going to assume, one, it was louder than that.
I'm trying to save your eardrums and two, it didn't sound like the mom from All in the
Family screaming.
That actually would be super creepy."
You'd be like, "What?"
And then they hear just general demonic sounds.
So any one of those, you'd be like, "Meth head," and you go back to like, "Scramming
dishes."
Here a woman screaming, you'd be like, "Uh, hopefully that someone's just playing around.
Hopefully that's not like a real terrified scream."
If you hear a weird language, you're like, "I don't know."
Could just be some people who are new to the neighborhood.
Apparently from Demonville, Demonville, USA.
They're not from around here.
But all of those pushed together, you'd think that something's wrong.
They call the police.
And you can imagine the cop.
I was a cop.
I'd love to get calls like that, dude.
I'd be like, "Aw, great."
Another meth heads beating up a telephone pole.
But when someone's like, "Hey, I think there's a ghost outside.
I'm having tunnels.
I'm like, step on it, boys."
Driving all the way over there.
Get out of the way, evil.
People are robbing banks.
So I'm driving on the road.
I'm like, "I have no time for your petty crimes.
I've got a ghost to catch."
The cops go out to the location and they check around and they don't find anything.
They don't find any meth heads.
They don't find any weirdos.
They don't find any recent immigrants from Demonville.
So they go back to the McDonald's people and they go, "There's nothing out there.
We don't know what you heard, but there's nothing out there.
So you're good to go."
And the crew said, "No.
We will not leave this McDonald's until the sun comes up."
Which think about that for a second.
Think about wherever you work.
Come on, man.
There's very few jobs where you want to keep working.
If I'm working somewhere and someone's painting too much, I'm like, "Oh, I'm getting dizzy,
man.
I gotta go home early."
And then I walk out.
I'm like, "Hehehe."
Then I go home and I'm huffing paint.
I'm like, "If I'm going to get high, I'm going to do it at home where I can start watching
movies."
People will look for any excuse to go home, right?
They could have been like, "This is too spooky.
I'm going to go home early.
My boss isn't going to be able to do anything because there's monsters outside."
No.
They could have at work longer than they had to.
They could have went home, but they were like, "No way.
I'm way safer in this McDonald's.
That's all glass walls.
This is my, this is where I'm hanging out."
So I find that, to me, that makes it more believable, honestly.
I think they heard something, definitely.
But I think the fact that they heard it and it was so terrifying that they chose to stay
at work.
They figured they were safer inside of a McDonald's than making it to their car is a sign that
they heard something that terrifying.
Because again, I will look for any excuse to go home from work.
Oh no.
That dude over there sprained his ankle.
"Oh, sympathy, ankle pain.
I better go home, man."
But maybe I'm just a bad employee.
But you know what I mean?
The fact that they decided, they not only stayed, but stayed until the sun came up.
They stayed longer than their shift.
Makes me think there really was something out there.
They heard something out there.
Now, our next one, it's kind of an interesting one.
It's kind of a short one.
I've had it ready to go for a long time, but I feel a need to talk about it today.
December 31st, 1982, we're in Fairfax County, Virginia.
There's a guy named Kevin Tunnel, 17 years old, young man, driving home from a New Year's
Eve party.
His friends go, "Dude, you're way too drunk.
You're a..."
"Good.
I'm good."
Quote, "Nothing will ever happen to me."
His friends are like, "Why did you just say quote?
Why did you quote yourself?"
And he's like, "I assume that that statement I just made will play a huge effect in my
life."
He's driving home drunk.
He's super drunk.
And at the same time, Susan Herzog is driving home as well.
She's a mile from her house.
She's sober.
He hits her, kills her.
He survives.
He's charged with drunk driving, charged with involuntary manslaughter.
Gets found guilty.
1982, though, was a different time.
This was before mothers against drunk driving.
This was before dads against drunk driving.
Drunk driving was just a thing you did.
It was a stupid decision you made, but there weren't all of the laws against it.
I mean, there were laws against it, but it was...
I mean, nowadays, you can...
It's bad.
Like, you can serve some serious prison time.
I know a guy who he was driving with his girlfriend and their friend, and he got in
a car accident.
They were visiting Arizona.
They got in a car accident, and the friend died.
Then the driver was drunk.
He was taken to jail.
And within like a couple hours, he has to process all of this stuff.
One, his best friend's dead.
Two, he's facing 10, 15 years in prison.
This guy who'd never been in trouble with the law.
And his fiance, who's actually...
I know the fiance more than I know him, but the fiance is now in Arizona, and her friend
is dead, and her fiance is in jail facing 10, 15 years in prison, and she has no way
to get home.
Anyway, so it's totally different now.
I mean, like, you're...
When you get hit with that drunk driving charge, you're like this...
And when you cause a fatality, a regular drunk driving charge...
A regular drunk driving charge, I think, can even still just be like a year of like, no
license and stuff like that.
But when you kill someone in a drunk driving accident today, it's a big issue back then.
He got three months probation in one year community service.
And there's a civil penalty.
The judge goes, "We're gonna give you a civil penalty for this as well," because that's
not right.
The judge is like, "That's ridiculous.
So we're gonna give you a civil penalty as well.
You got three months probation, you got your one year thing.
The laws hadn't caught up to the brutality of drinking and driving.
Every week, Kevin Tunnel had to write a $1 check, mail it to her family.
It only added up to $936.
Not a lot of money even back in 1982.
But he couldn't do it.
It broke him.
18 years every week writing a check.
Pay to the order of the Herzog family.
Put in an envelope.
Susan Herzog family's address.
Drop it in the mail.
Next week, pay to the order.
A constant reminder.
In 1990, he actually got thrown in jail for 30 days because he stopped sending the checks.
He did 30 days in jail when he gets out and they're like, "You have to keep sending these
checks.
You have to do it for 18 years.
You gotta send these checks."
Susan Herzog was 18, by the way.
She was 18.
And that's why there's these...
He has to write a check for every year she'd been alive.
So every week, he was reminded of that pain.
One day, he sent a box of checks that were pre-written out and says, "Here's the next
couple months of checks plus an extra year of checks.
I paid you an extra 52 bucks."
Family sent it back.
They said, "No, you gotta write a check every single week."
Sent it to us.
And he said, "You know, I'd be up at night.
I'd hear something in my house and I'd think, 'She's here.
Susan's in my house.
Her ghost is coming to haunt me.'"
He ended up completing his thing of writing the checks.
He also does...
As of writing of this article, which was a couple years ago, he was still doing community
service stuff, talking to people about drunk driving.
Susan's parents, they both joined MAD, Mothers Against Drunk Driving.
They're not gonna be like, "No, sir.
You're not allowed, obviously.
All the help is needed."
Their other daughter, after they had joined Mothers Against Drunk Driving, they had another
daughter that got hit by a drunk driver, has a permanent limp now.
But is otherwise fine.
Now I came across that story.
I thought it was an interesting story about crime and punishment and the mental toll on
people.
The simple act of writing a check broke him to the point where he just couldn't do it.
His quote was, "You get to a point where you kind of snap and say, 'It hurts too much.'"
You know, and all he's doing is writing stuff down.
I know a lot of people are like, "Oh yeah, I could do X, Y, and Z.
I could be like this total badass criminal."
Anyone can be a badass criminal.
It's a matter of living with it, not for the next week or next eight weeks.
It's a matter of living it for the next 30 years, 40 years, 50 years.
Very, very few people can do that.
Generally, it does haunt you.
And the thing with drunk driving is it's not like, "Oh, look at me.
I'm such a badass criminal."
It's like I'm trying to get home and I'm making a bad decision.
It's not only affecting my life, it's affecting everyone else's life.
And again, I've had this story probably a couple months now, just sitting in my notes
and I had a pull to do it today.
So I'm assuming, I'm thinking maybe there's some listener out there that really needs
to hear this before the weekend coming up.
Or maybe you're hearing this story six months from now before you make a bad decision.
Maybe you just discovered the podcast.
Maybe this is the first episode you listen to.
But I just had a feeling to record this segment today.
I had a friend, my cousin actually, who's paralyzed from the neck down due to drinking
and driving.
And then he was in his motorized wheelchair maybe about two or three years ago.
And he was going through a parking lot on his way to my aunt's house for Taco Tuesday
and the truck was lifted and couldn't see him and backed up and knocked him over and
he hit his head.
And then he was like, "I'm good.
I'm good.
The guy gets out of the truck and helps to write the chair up."
And he's like, "It was my cousin, Chris."
He goes, "No, no, no.
I'm fine.
I'm fine."
But the driver noticed he had blood coming out of his ears.
All the ambulance died at the hospital that night.
Yeah, so I mean, during a drive-in, it's a serious...
I mean, obviously, it might kind of sound trite, but I think hopefully this episode stops
you this one time you might go, "Oh, you know what?
I don't know.
I just felt like I wanted to tell this story today because I think somebody needs to hear
it on this episode.
Let's go ahead, though, and move on to a more uplifting story, the story of a demonic cat
and a madman with a bone to pick, or would it be a claw to pick because cats have claws?
Cats have bones, too?
So it doesn't matter.
We are traveling to...
We are traveling to London.
So, McCall, get that helicopter going.
Get it warmed up now.
We're going.
While he's warming it up, we're giving this...
He's like, "I want to hear the introduction, too."
We're like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just work on the helicopter, bro."
I'm giving the...
I go, "Hey, guys, come over here.
We're going to talk about this McCall can here this part."
So we're going to go to London, and it's October 1943, and one of you guys goes, "What's
the exact date?"
And I go, "Hmm.
Kind of look down at my feet."
And I go, "It's one of those stories."
And everyone's like, "Ah."
Now, what I mean by that is there are a lot of stories that I come across that are super
vague and they shouldn't be, because the people involved in the stories, this would be the
most important night of their life.
So generally, when a story doesn't have a specific date, it tends to lean towards it
being fake.
And I originally heard about this story on Backpackerverse, and at this point it's almost
a full revolt.
So guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, hold on, hold on.
Now for you guys who don't know, who are new to the show, Backpackerverse, I haven't talked
about them in a while.
I've very been very, very restrained.
However, the episode I did recently about the Popobawa, I found that on Backpackerverse,
and that was a great episode, so don't get mad.
Backpackerverse, for the new listeners, is a website that is basically like a California
hippie psychic website, but they also tell ghost stories, but they make them up.
Now this one's not made up.
Neither was the Popobawa.
Well, I mean, they might be made up in the fact that they don't exist, but I'm so sorry,
no, you exist, Popobawa.
The thing is, is that they tend to exaggerate certain details.
So we're going to go into that in mind.
So we're going to turn back, and I made McCall wear big headphones, big of those big old
aviator headphones.
I'm like, you can take this off now.
We are hopping back in the Carbenter Coffin.
Take us at McCall.
We're going to London.
Again, not a very specific place.
And there we're going to meet a man.
Well, I guess that is a city.
Public Colorado.
I didn't give you the address of the McDonald's.
That was real though.
Anyways, we're traveling to London, and there we're going to meet Howard Leland.
So hello, Howard.
Pip pip cheerio.
He's shaking hands with this guy.
He works for something called air raid precautions, because it's 1943.
Did I say that?
So we're in the middle of World War II.
So we're not just going to London and like drinking milkshakes over there and stuff.
We might be, but there's also bombs dropping, the threat of Nazi Germany overtaking the
planet really.
We're meeting this guy.
He's works with the air raid precautions, which in my notes I put, what the hell is
that?
Like what is, you have your air raid precaution is the air raid siren.
I can just imagine these sirens are going, bombs, and a guy's like, look out everyone,
bombs, bombs.
Run, run.
It's like the one thing you can't hear is the man running through the city going, bombs,
everyone, bombs, bombs.
What is your job?
That's a made up job.
That's the job that they give the idiots who can't have any other job in the military
or really in civilian life.
Yes, Howard, you're warning people of the bombs.
You're doing a good job, a real good job.
Here's your medal.
It's a gold star.
He's like, thank you.
Dude, you either hear the air raid siren or you don't.
The guy running through the street.
Now I'm sure someone might email me and be like, this is actually like a super integral
job.
They repaired the air raid sirens, whatever.
Air raid precautions.
Look out guys, bombs are coming.
Huge explosions everywhere.
See?
Anyways, there's a bombing run.
He's out in the middle of nowhere and there's a bombing run.
Basically, it's the sound effects of a game of battle ship, electronic battleship.
But in real life.
So he's running, he's out running these bombs.
He's like, oh no, I got to warn people of these bombs that have already fallen.
Look out guys, a bomb blew up.
He jumps into an abandoned house and he's sitting there in the dark.
I better get my torch because that's what we call it in Britain.
We don't call it a flashlight.
Also, I should get one of my cigarettes but I'm gonna use the American word for that.
Puffing on a cigarette with my torch.
Anyways, Howard is sitting there at the bottom of the stairs and he gets a feeling that something's
watching him.
He's like, there must be something else in this house.
Something not too pleasant as I smoke my cigarette.
And then he notices that he's getting the feeling of being watched from the top of
the stairs.
I will crane my head ever so slightly to...
He gasps.
He sees at the top of the stairs a giant cat.
Now that's not scary, right?
I mean, unless it's like a bobcat.
Actually Britain has a huge thing.
Like you know we have Bigfoot in America supposedly and every other cryptid, Mothman
and Melonheads and...
I don't know, you can listen to best episodes, I've covered them all.
In Britain, they have giant cats.
That's their big thing.
They have people who hunt giant cat hunters.
They can pronounce it correctly.
And they are like getting footage of the giant cat.
It's so lame.
Because when I grew up reading the 40 in Times magazine, which covers like all just weird
stuff around the world, there was always a section just on giant cats in Britain and
I'd always skip it.
I'm like, who cares?
Who cares if there's giant cats in Britain?
There are or there aren't, I don't care either way.
If it turns out Bigfoot's real, that has implications for a lot of different things.
Like how could something that big be existing?
Do we then give credence to other supernatural phenomenon if it turns out that Bigfoot was
real?
This is just a giant cat.
Who cares?
It's such a big thing over there.
There's actually a term for them.
They're called like ABCs or something like that.
Like all black cats or something like that.
I don't remember but there was like an acronym for them.
But anyways, this isn't one of those.
This isn't one of those.
This is a cooler cat.
I want to waste your time with just a story about a giant cat, Garfield.
Hey, this actually is a tabby.
Garfield's a tabby, right?
But anyways, it's a big tabby cat.
You're like chasing that's not, that's even less scary than an all black cat.
Like I said, I imagine it's some sort of panther.
Now I'm just imagining it's basically Garfield up there.
Heathcliff is up there getting ready to go into a garbage can.
I wonder if Heathcliff and Garfield got in a fight who would win.
I actually, I know that Garfield has like that weight behind him.
He has that mass.
But Heathcliff, you know, he's out and about.
You guys are like, dude, I'm not 43 years old.
I have no idea who Heathcliff is.
Anyways, back to the story.
Howard smoking a cigarette, bottom of the stairs.
Looks up, he sees this giant cat.
But again, it's not just any cat.
It has glowing red eyes.
What?
See guys, this whole dude is going to be spooky.
And long horns.
Whoa, dude.
Have you ever seen a cat with horns?
I know you haven't.
This is a demon cat.
Cat from hell.
Howard's looking at this thing.
It's at the top of the stairs looking at him.
Making that super annoying cat noise and Howard snuffs out his cigarette.
Fogus is his torch on the creature.
And it jumps through the air towards him.
Giant claws sling out of those big old cat paws.
It's coming down the stairs.
And at that moment, two of his buddies who also work for the air raid precautions people
bust through the door.
Did you know bombs just fell?
We're doing our job.
And Howard looks over at his buddies who came through the door and he looks back at the
cat and it's so close and it's going meow.
And fades from existence.
But the echo.
Continued on for a little bit longer.
Cat never got to him.
But what would have happened if it did?
Well that's the part Backpacker verse made up.
That's the part Backpacker.
This is the way I first came across this story.
So this is a real cryptid story that has been going around in the paranormal world.
It's not super popular but you can find a lot of sources on this.
But it's not one of the big cats of Britain.
According to Backpacker verse, the cat comes down and slashes his arm open with big old
grody cat claws and then super realistic blood shot out of the wound and he goes no.
And then the cat disappeared and he's holding his bloodied arm and is chewed up to pieces
and to this day the scar still remains of the demon cat that none of that happened.
None of that happened.
There's a question of whether or not the story happened at all.
And I think it did.
I think it's vague which makes me a little suspicious about it but there's just some
follow up to this.
But then Backpacker verse just adds that he actually gets maimed by this thing.
What?
Well okay Backpacker verse, you gotta make it a little sexier I guess but let's go back
to the real story.
So apparently what happened was Howard Leland was traumatized by this event.
Traumatized by this event right?
So Howard Leland ends up meeting or going to a clairvoyant named John Pendragon and
goes oh you know I heard that you're really good at making stuff up and people believing
you and John's like that's how I get paid.
That is 100% my profession.
I simply make vague guesses and rubes like you believe me.
And Howard Leland goes perfect that's what I want.
He goes I ran into this demon cat at this house and he pulls a map out.
He goes this house right here and John Pendragon goes this house and puts his finger on the
map and he's like yeah that's the house I just pointed at and he goes oh yes that house
my powers my quote unquote powers are activating.
I can tell you what happened at that house.
I can tell you that something's in my head now.
I'm seeing images.
I see a man surrounded by a dozen.
No.
A hundred angry hate filled cats.
And now he's holding he's looking directly at the camera.
He's looking directly at the camera.
He's holding the news.
Oh the connection's been broken.
Howard Leland's like that sounds insane but you're saying it and you're a renowned clairvoyant
so I'm going to believe you.
Now Howard Leland apparently goes and does more research on this house and finds out
that the former occupant was actually a practitioner of the dark arts black magic.
This guy was trying to do some really heavy metal stuff before heavy metal was even invented.
And he did it with cats.
He had apparently according to neighbors hundreds of cats in his house.
They're just hanging out.
You can't walk anywhere without stepping on two or three cats.
And of course they're hate filled because one there's a hundred cats crammed in one
house so you can just imagine the smell.
Two he's sacrificing them.
This former occupant is taking these cats he has an altar built for him and he's sacrificing
these cats.
Now eventually I love this.
This is a quote from cryptids.fandom.com.
This is probably the greatest sentence researching this quote.
He eventually went insane and hung himself at the top of the staircase.
I don't think hanging yourself is the symptom of being insane.
I don't think he eventually went insane.
I think he was insane the first time he started sacrificing cats.
And I would definitely say he was insane when the time when he said he had 50 cats in his
house and he goes you know what I need?
Double this amount.
I think that's when he went insane.
I don't think he eventually I don't think the hanging himself was the sign he was insane.
He was insane long before that.
So you're go Jason this is interesting because you just said to this guy this clairvoyant
John Pendragon was a hack was a fraud.
You're saying all that stuff allegedly.
I didn't say allegedly back then but I'm saying it now so it still works.
But Howard Leland went and he did this research on his own and the thing matched up.
Well here's my thing.
What I believe happened with this story again assuming any of it's a truth assuming it's
not some viral marketing stunt for some horned cat 8-bit rogue like video game that's going
to come out in 8 months.
Assuming it's not that.
Here's the thing.
Generally what happens and it's really easy to control the narrative on this.
Let's see how my clairvoyant.
I've told you I used to work for a psychic phone hotline and all that stuff.
It's a really easy trick to pull.
You come to you call me up and you'll say hey can I make an appointment.
I need to check out something I have this experience with a horned cat and then I kind
of put the phone on hold and I laugh and then I go oh yes yes the horned cat.
Yes tell me some information about yourself so I can prepare something and you coach you
maybe not that blunt about it but you say it in such a way that the person gives you
information.
They don't know you're giving information and in this case all John Pendragon would have
to know is do you roughly know the location of where you were at.
He'd be like yes I was during that bombing run I worked for the air raid precautions
board John puts the phone back on hold.
Oh my god I'm going to make so much money off this room.
Oh yes you do a lot of great service for our country sir.
Once he knows a general location you can just do research because if this story is true
and again we're going to assume it's true Howard Leland was able to find this information
which means that John Pendragon could have found the information first and had the quote
unquote vision.
This is very very typical scam.
So it's possible I will believe that I will believe that there wasn't a cultist sacrificing
cats because we know people do that.
I will believe a man ran into a demon cat during a bombing run because I mean why not.
It's funny because I would believe both of those stories before I would believe John
Pendragon had any sort of clairvoyant power.
That's one thing you know and now I'm saying that.
That's one thing that I'm extremely skeptical on because I know the tricks behind it because
I've done tarot cards and I've done fortune telling and stuff like that.
I know how it works and not only do I know how it works I'm really good at it and I do
it all the time.
It's just a subtle manipulation and it's looking for reactions in you and that's when I'm trying
to figure out something about you when I'm reading your future or your past because when
I do the tarot cards first off I tell you what your past is then I tell you your current
situation and then I tell you your future.
By the time I get to your future you're so convinced.
Now this has become a debunking psychic thing.
Goodbye horned cat.
Now that you've become so convinced because I got the first two kind of right then I tool
the message so I'll be looking at you looking for subtle shifts in your eyes and you'll do
it either way.
It won't be like I'll be like oh you used to rob banks and your eyes shift from side
to side.
If you're wrong you'll have a reaction too.
Some people try to really hide their body language because they know the trick.
I've done it over the phone when I was a telephone psychic I've done it over the phone that's
just guesswork.
But yeah so I'm super skeptical of it because I've never seen anyone fake a haunting other
than go what's over there?
Oh your mom.
Like fine you made me turn around when we were in a haunted field you tricked me but
I've never seen anyone in real life fake a haunting or fake a UFO sighting or things
like that.
I have faked psychic powers so I'm super suspicious of that stuff.
So anyways haunted demon cat we'll bring him back so it's possible that there is a demon
cat and that even offers up a more interesting question.
Was the demon cat a conglomeration of a thousand cat souls that have been sacrificed in this
house that had become a monster cat or how I like to think of it?
A man who spends his life sacrificing cats which I don't normally like to think about
guys who do that but a man who spends his life sacrificing cats must really really hate
cats right?
He could have picked anything to sacrifice frogs or mushrooms or something but he sacrificed
cats for unlimited power and in the end it's his soul trapped in that house in the form
of the thing he hates the most.
A cat.
And not only is he trapped as a demon cat he's impotent.
He's a useless demon cat.
He couldn't even attack this one dude.
He just jumped down the stairs and then disappeared when his buddy showed up.
So you could have a man looking for power from beyond the veil calling on the dark ones
to turn his fury and rage into something useful to him.
But instead he just became a big ol' house cat with long horns, red eyes.
And if there's any justice in the universe when this house cat isn't jumping down the
stairs and disappearing, it doesn't even get to eat lasagna.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
[Music]
(upbeat music)