A man uncovers a fiendish conspiracy that happens every Halloween.
And then we travel to the household of a single mother and her 17-year-old son.
On the outside, this seems like a normal family.
But little does anyone know that this mother harbors a dark and terrifying desire.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvin, or I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I'm so tired.
I don't know how it's daylight savings time.
I gained an hour of sleep.
I'm barely awake.
I'm literally sitting in front of this microphone.
Hopefully I'm able to make it through this episode.
Otherwise you'll just hear a man snoring.
But someone who never hears me snore because they're so exciting to be around.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is a huge supporter of Dead Rabbit Radio.
Everyone give it up for Doomy Kins.
Woohoo!
Yeah!
Walk on in to Dead Rabbit Command Doomy Kins.
Giving you a big round of applause.
Really, really appreciate it.
All of your support.
Doomy Kins listens to the podcast so much out loud in her house that her mother now
recognizes the sound of my voice.
And when she's listening to the podcast, the mom goes, "Is that Jason?"
And that's one way to get the word out about the podcast.
Listen to it constantly at top volume.
So Doomy Kins, that's why you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
I do.
But like Doomy Kins, just spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That really, really, really helps out so, so much.
Doomy Kins.
I'm going to go ahead and talk to you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy, but don't
take off just yet.
We got a couple of announcements.
First off, this is the end of season 19.
This week is the last week of new episodes until December 1st.
And Thanksgiving livestream on November 24th at 12 p.m.
Pacific Standard Time.
Join me on the YouTube channel for another Dead Rabbit Radio Thanksgiving livestream.
This is the reason why I stopped posting on YouTube, because they were getting ready
to shut down my account.
They've been harassing me for months behind the scenes.
I said no more episodes on YouTube because I want to keep it up for our livestream.
So 12 p.m. Pacific Standard Time, November 24th.
Please turn out for our Thanksgiving livestream.
I think it's going to be a lot of fun.
They always are.
If you're not there for the livestream, it will be available on YouTube.
And I will also upload the audio to the podcast channel.
A lot of stuff going on.
A lot of announcements.
I can tell Doomy Kins is ready to hop in that Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy.
So let's get in it with her.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Take us all the way out to a street, any street, on Halloween night.
Bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing,
bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing,
bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing,
Ferrero, they're the makers of those really disgusting ball chocolates covered in nuts. It's like the kind of candy you give someone.
It's like all fancy and wrapped in gold, but it's like, "Ha ha, look at it, it looks pretty, but it really tastes like dirt."
He worked for them, and apparently they bought up other candy brands, actually edible candies like Babe Ruth Crunch bars and Butterfingers.
And he says, "Listen, you're half right." It was really interesting. They go, "Yes, the quality of the chocolates have gone down over time."
That's true, because they're trying to save a buck. He goes, "The reason why the miniature candies taste different than the large-sized candy."
And this is what I love about conspiracy theories, right, when we get these inside guys. Forget the big candy guy from Hershey's trying to tell us lies.
This guy works for another production company, let's trust him.
He says, "What happens is, as the bars get smaller, the cheap chocolate is easier to taste."
Because all the other ingredients get smaller, too. The Nougat or the wafers, like in a Kit Kat, you know, the wafers and stuff like that.
He goes, "So as it gets smaller, the cheapness, you're tasting more of the cheap chocolate than you would on a regular Kit Kat."
That is a rational explanation for why Kit Kats were discussing this Halloween.
But who knows? Who knows whether or not these anonymous people online have stumbled upon something that has no effect in any way, shape, or form on how we live our lives.
But I love it. It's an interesting conspiracy theory. I tasted this one first hand. Hopefully it's not true.
I would hate to live in a world where generations that come after us go, "Hey, Mom, can I get some candy?"
And the mom's like, "Yeah, what do you want?" And the kid goes, "Anything but Kit Kats." Because those taste like berries.
That's a world that I don't want to live in. I don't care what else happens. I don't care what type of dystopian hellscape is coming.
As long as the Kit Kats don't taste like disgusting berries.
Doomy Kins, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonar copter. We are leaving behind this Halloween street.
The carbonar copter is overburdened with all this chocolate. But we don't get lighter because we're eating at the rest of the trip.
We're leaving behind this Halloween street. Take us all the way out to a suburban neighborhood.
[imitates car noises]
Doomy Kins, who also goes by probably one of the best Twitter handles I've seen in a long time. Section 8 Sasquatch. How's that not a movie?
How is your Twitter name not a movie? Doomy Kins, go ahead and land this carbonar copter outside of this suburban house.
And we're standing outside the house, looking in, peering through their window like a bunch of freaks.
Now, that actually, if that was true, if somehow we were teleported outside this house, and we were staring in the window like some peeping toms,
that would be the least disturbing part of this story.
And in this house, we see a woman. She didn't post her name, but we're going to go ahead and call her Veronica.
We're looking at her. She's a 34-year-old single mother. Totally normal looking. Totally normal looking.
Jason, why'd you say that twice? Is there something I should be concerned about with this woman?
Normally, people only get described as totally normal looking if they harbor some sort of dark secret.
And then bounding into the house is her 17-year-old son. We don't have his name either. We're going to call him Bobby.
Bobby walks into the house and was like, "Hey, Ma, I just had a great day at school. So much fun."
And Veronica, all of a sudden, she seems to snap out of a deep thought she's having. She turns around and she's like, "Bobby, so good to see you."
She walks over and she gives Bobby a big hug. And then it happens very quickly. I don't even know if Bobby noticed it.
I don't know how you wouldn't notice it, but just for a sake of argument, Bobby doesn't notice it.
We're staring right at this loving interaction between a mother and a son.
And we see Veronica. She's hugging her son. She leans in really close.
And she goes... takes a big whiff of Tommy's neck.
And then she turns to the camera and goes, "All I've ever wanted to do was eat my son."
Now, this is the story of an anonymous woman who posted back in 2013 how every single day...
Sorry, let me correct myself. Almost every single day, all she can think about is eating her son.
She said, "Cooked or raw, doesn't matter." Almost every day, I fantasize about eating my own child.
Now, she wants to clear up some misconceptions we might have about this... incredibly disgusting desire, right?
Imagine if one of your friends told you that. They said, "Hey, man, glad we could get some coffee together.
It's been a long time since we've hung out. I want to eat my kids. I want to look straight in your eyes
and tell you that I'm joking. I want to eat my kids." You'd obviously have some questions.
So she wants to get these questions out of the way. First off, she says, "Listen, I'm not a pervert.
I would wait until he was 18 years old. If I was going to eat my son, it has to be consensual."
People under 18 can't consent. So after he turns 18, I want to eat him.
She wants to eat him. This is so weird. She wants to eat him now.
But I imagine to kind of, in her own world, not be a... what? Like a cannibal offender?
Like a cannibal sex offender? I don't even know if there's a watch list for these people.
There should be. All the people who should be on a watch list. It should be moms who want to eat their children.
Now actually, I should back up because it's so funny. I used to have a friend named Annie that I hung out with all the time.
And she constantly talked about eating babies. She wasn't a politician. She wasn't a politician.
I wasn't friends with Hillary Clinton. She would constantly talk about eating babies all the time.
Whenever a baby... this is when I worked for Gateway Computers. Whenever a baby came into the store, she would go, "Oh, bro."
She would like make these noises. And I laughed because I'm a super villain at heart. I thought it was hilarious.
And she goes, "Babies look like dinner rolls to me." The way that they're little chubby legs and they're little chubby arms.
She goes, "It looks like those dinner rolls, like those Hawaiian rolls you buy at Thanksgiving time."
I just want to eat them up. I just want to eat babies all the time. Now she never ate a baby.
She never ate a baby as far as I know. As far as I know, she never ate a baby.
But she would talk about eating babies all the time. And what I found out, Sabine was telling me this not too long ago.
She said, "There is a desire to eat babies. Mothers want to eat their own baby."
And I said, "Oh, okay. Look back up." She didn't specifically use the word "eat."
She says, "Mothers actually put their baby's feet in their mouth."
Not right when they're born. They're all covered in ambiotic fluid. And they're like, "I'm sucking it off like jelly."
"Mothers want to suck on their baby's feet in hands."
And the reason why is you want to get their... I was fairly paid attention to what she was saying as she explained it.
You suck on a baby's foot and then you get the baby's bacteria into you.
And then it comes out of your breast or something.
Probably should have paid more attention since I want to talk about it now.
People are like, "Oh, great. Not only does Jason know nothing about science, none of his friends do either."
She could explain it more thoroughly, but you suck on a baby's foot and then it goes into your breast milk.
And then when the baby's drinking the breast milk, it has more immunities built into it.
And again, it's not like you let your baby walk through a cat litter box.
You're like, "Now you'll be immune to cats."
It's clean babies. I think you wash them off, right? I don't think you're just letting them play on the mud.
And you're like, "Mmm, nuh-uh-uh, eating them."
Anyways, she could explain it better, but she doesn't have a podcast.
So this is all you got.
Moms want to suck on their baby's feet.
And a friend who loved, who thought, didn't love, she never ate a baby, but she wanted to eat babies.
And I don't think she even wanted to devour them.
She just wanted to like suck on their little baby legs because they look like Hawaiian rolls.
Well, that isn't what we're talking about here with Veronica.
It's the one, the kid's 17 turning 18.
The story, she posted this on November 19th, 2013.
His birthday's in February, so it's not like this is a newborn baby and she's posting how much she wants to eat her baby.
Which again, would be quite alarming as well if it's out of context.
And even in context, it's pretty crazy, but she wants to eat her son, but for her it's important that he can consent to being devoured.
She's not a pervert, right? She hasn't been grooming her son this whole time.
She hasn't been like, "It's back time!" and she pulls out a gravy ladle.
You know, you could easily groom a kid into wanting to be eaten constantly before every Halloween.
He's a roasted pig with an apple in his mouth.
He's like, "Mom, I'm the same costume every year."
She's like, "I know, but she looks so delicious. I mean, so spooky."
But that's not what she did.
Her son has no idea that his mom wants to eat him.
Which is creepier, right?
Like, if your mom was constantly making jokes about eating you and was always dressing you up as edible things,
dressing you up as a carrot, and you would kind of get it.
You'd kind of be like, "This is super weird. Like, every night when I go to bed, I sleep in a giant pot full of warm broth."
It's kind of weird. I think my mom wants to eat me.
And this revelation kind of dawns on you over this course of years, right?
She kept going every night, she kept going in a pot.
You're like, "I think my mom wants to eat me." That would be disturbing enough.
But not knowing would be creepy as well.
If your mom was fantasizing about eating you, and that's the word she uses.
Because when she says she fantasizes about eating her son,
she says it is the single most intense and arousing fantasy she's ever had.
She thinks about eating her son while having sex with other men.
I don't know how the mechanics of that work. I guess she would have to completely leave her body.
But while she's having sex with men, she will fantasize about eating her adult son.
And that's what gets her off.
She says she even does it when she's masturbating.
When she's masturbating, she imagines herself eating her son.
And she gets into some specifics here.
And you're like, "Jason, please don't. Please don't! This came out of left field!"
The first one you were talking about, berry flavored kid cats, and then all of a sudden, it went to 0 to 60 real quick.
She wrote this online. She wrote, quote,
"The thought of my teeth piercing his flesh, or the smell of him roasting over an open flame,
or imagining the look in his eyes as I bite into one of his thighs."
Isn't that the doctor suits rhyme you never thought you'd hear?
These things absolutely drive me wild.
And what's interesting about that, other than the fact that it's Mom wrote this about her son,
you can tell these are reoccurring fantasies over a long period of time, because they're all different.
If you just thought occasionally, "You know what? I'm really sick and tired of my son.
I just want to beat his head with a baseball bat."
That's alarming, obviously, if someone said that to you.
But you'd probably be like, "Oh, you don't really think that."
And he's like, "Yeah, I really don't think about that."
And he's looking over at his baseball bat. He's like, "Or do I?"
When someone can give you multiple examples right off the bat,
that's because they've been thinking about it for so long.
Eating him was...if they just said, "I fantasize about eating him all the time," that's so vague.
But they're able to say, Veronica's able to say, or just like the smell of him roasting.
You got him on a spit? What do they call that? A spit?
They're cooking him over a fire.
And then, so that one, he'd be dead or being cooked alive, right?
That is a fantasy that we see pop up in some really hardcore, BD, SM culture.
It's cooking somebody alive. You have them on the spit, and you can put the rod through a human
without killing them, and you can slowly cook them.
So that is a fantasy we see in that community. It's a subset, a subset.
If you're getting whipped by a woman, that's one thing.
If she ever brings out a seven-foot-long metal rod, you might want to run.
You might want to run, or you're going to get cooked alive.
And then the idea, the other one is while he's still alive and her biting into him.
These are all separate fantasies. She's thought about this so much, it plays out different ways in her head.
And she tells it, she keeps going back and forth. She goes, "Listen, I know you think I'm sick,
but I would wait till he was 18. I'm not a pervert, and that's not the reason why we think you're sick.
It doesn't matter what age he is." And then when she talks about, "I just want to eat him,"
I also want you to be very, very aware of the fact that don't worry about him.
It's not like he's going to be sleeping one night, and I'm going to run into his bedroom with a knife
and start stabbing him and eating him. That doesn't work. I'm not going to do that.
That's actually not her fantasy. She doesn't want to jump out of the darkness and stab him to death.
She wants him to want her to eat him.
She said, "Listen, what I want to happen is my son to come up to me and say, quote,
she actually has a quote of how she would like this dialogue to happen, quote,
'Mom, I know this sounds weird, but I want to be your next meal. Would you please cook and eat me?'
She said, "If my son ever says that, I absolutely would."
No, I wouldn't even give him his own sleepwalk and he's having a nightmare.
She's like, "Oh, that counts." No, take-backs.
And what's so weird is that no boy would ever say that to a mom.
But actually, I shouldn't say that. I shouldn't say that there's enough weirdos out there.
But a boy might say that to his mom, but what are the chances of the boy who has a desire to be eaten
and also has a mom who wants to eat her son? Somewhere out there.
There is probably a boy who would love to get eaten by his mom, but it's not her son.
They're soulmates on opposite sides of the planet, thankfully.
I don't believe these two people never meet.
But she wants her son to come up and say, "Will you eat me?"
That's never going to happen with this guy. I'm assuming, right?
Now, this happened back in 2013. We'll get to how this all plays out in the end,
out of all the things I could think of to possibly say to another human.
That would be so far down on the list. It's statistically not even on there.
I would. Would you please eat me? But that's what she's hoping, see?
But of course that's not going to happen, and she knows that's not going to happen.
She hopes for it.
So what do you do when you have a fetish? I always feel bad for people who have, like, these super disturbing fetishes,
because there's no way they're ever really going to get fulfilled.
I mean, you can eat somebody, but she doesn't want to just eat somebody. She wants to eat her son.
There was that big thing on the internet. This was probably like 12 years ago.
It was a blind man who liked hearing teenage boys poop.
You're like, "How do you even develop a fetish like that? Like, how does that--where was that chain of events--
chain of events that people were trolling him by throwing--
[laughs]
--in the audio clips of stuff falling into a toilet, and because he was blind, you figure out he couldn't tell.
But he could. He had heard teenage boys poop because he would, I think, pay for these videos.
He had heard teenage boys poop in a toilet for so long.
There was this daredevil power. He could totally sense it that he could tell that, "Oh, no, you just threw--
like, there's a hot wheel in the toilet. I want poop. Send me the poop."
Well, not me. Just send me the audio clip of the poop.
And I was like, "Man, that would suck to have such a specific fetish and not be able to, like, do anything about it."
To have such a disturbing fetish that places you so far outside the mainstream.
There's not even a support group for that.
She wants to eat her son. Now, she wants him to come up to her and say--she wants it to be consensual,
but of course it's not going to happen. So what do you do?
You can A) not fantasize it about anymore. Stop feeding that wolf. Get over that.
Think about something else. Or...
Now, she says--listen, my son obviously doesn't know that I fantasize about eating him.
How could you? How could you possibly think that this was even a real thing?
You're living in this household, you would never ever think that.
She says, quote, "My son doesn't know that I fantasize about eating him.
He doesn't know that my mouth literally waters when I look at photos of him at the beach."
He's all putting on suntan lotion. It's barbecue sauce.
He's like, "Mom, I don't know. I see--whenever you put the sauce on me, I actually feel like I'm getting cooked.
I don't think this is a really good sunscreen." She's basting him.
She says--he doesn't know that my mouth literally waters when I look at photos of him at the beach
or see him by the pool. You know, just even that alone, right?
Could you--looking at a photo book with your mom? And every so often she turns the page, she's like,
"Uhhh, she's drooling?" And you're like, "Ugh, you having a seizure?" "No, no, no, I'm fine. I'm fine."
Now, let's look at the time you went to Waterworld.
Why did you take 500 pictures of me at that water park, Mom?
Quote, "He doesn't know how turned on he makes me." This is a mother talking about her teenage son.
She can say, "Well, I'm going to wait until he's 18, but--"
Quote, "He doesn't know how turned on he makes me."
When we--this is the part where I go, this almost sounds like a troll. This almost like a joke at this point.
But who knows? It's very specific to be a joke.
This person has never posted again. It was an anonymous post, deleted account.
Quote, "He doesn't know how turned on he makes me."
When we watch the walking dead together, and he rests his head on my belly.
Now, this is the line that people were calling it out, being like, "This is a troll. This is a troll. This is made up."
Not because they were watching the walking dead. Nobody watches the walking dead anymore.
Well, this was back in 2013, so this was like season three. This was like peak walking dead, but--
It wasn't that they were watching the walking dead together, which for a cannibal must be like soft-core, cinematic spawn.
It was the fact that there like no self-respecting boy or man would rest his head on his mother's belly.
That's just not--that's made up. That's fake.
And that's not true. I'm not saying that I've done it as a teenager or an adult, but this is where any sort of grooming action would take place, right?
This type of stuff would be normalized in the house, that when he was a little boy, he'd be like, "Put your head on my belly. This is where you're gonna be someday.
This is where you're gonna be someday. Would you say, 'Mom? Oh, nothing.'"
This is where grooming takes place. This is the reason why you have families where kids are being given baths until they're 12.
And I'm not saying it's necessarily like sexual grooming at that point. It could be a power play.
I knew a girl in middle school who her mom made her brush her hair. Not the girl's hair.
The girl--the mother made her daughter brush her hair. This still sounds grammatically wrong.
The mother would make the daughter brush the mother's hair every single night.
And the mother had this long hair. And I was always more mature than everyone else in my class.
And I remember I was like in seventh or eighth grade. I was at St. Philanary Middle School.
They're gonna love to be associated with this. Actually, it was like, I think it was K through eighth.
I think it was all stuff. It was a private Catholic school.
And I remember I was there, and I was with the teacher, and I was with this girl, and she said, "Yeah, my mom makes me brush her hair every single night."
And she gets mad when I don't, and she'll yell at me. And then once I start brushing her hair, it calms her down.
And I remember I was also in like seventh or eighth grade, and I looked at the teacher, and the teacher looked at me, and we both--
it was unspoken. We didn't say it out loud. But we both know that was super unusual.
That was--that may have been something sexual for the mother, or that may have been a power play.
And we didn't say anything. We didn't tell the daughter that her mom was a big weirdo.
But I remember when the girl said that so matter-of-factually.
Me and the teacher both kind of looked at each other, and we gave a look. Like, we knew that that was--there's something wasn't right there.
It was very, very interesting. Like, I was--that--yeah.
You listen to this podcast as you're combing your mom's hair.
You're like, "Uh, mom, why am I still combing your hair? I'm in my twenties right now. Why am I still combing your hair?"
That's where the grooming would take place, where it would be totally normal for this guy to lay his head on her belly.
They would have normalized that in the household. So that's kind of my pushback.
Like, obviously this could totally be fake. Which, again, would be disturbing because if it was fake, it's also someone's fake fantasy.
But that would be less disturbing than the mother actually typing this out, being her fantasy.
So, you know, getting to this, what do you do when you're locked in this fantasy world?
You really want to do it, but you want it to be consensual. We already see now here that she has been grooming him in a way.
I mean, there's nothing wrong with laying your head on your mom's belly, right? Again.
It's up to you. It's up to you. If your mom's demanding it, then that's a little creepy, but...
There probably is some grooming that's been going on because this fantasy is so intense.
I'm sure she has--even though she seems to think that she hasn't encouraged this at all, that her son doesn't know.
He may have picked up these little signs, but she says, "Listen, I want to tell him about my fantasy."
"I want to tell him about my fantasy, but if I do, I'm afraid it will be weird."
I'm afraid that it'll totally freak him out.
I'm afraid he'll be afraid of me. Which is totally rational, right?
You would be afraid of anyone who said, "I've been thinking about eating you for the past 17 years."
"Think about it all the time. I think about it when I'm having sex with other men."
See, here's the thing. Not just because it's the cannibal thing, but it's also the sexual fetish of hers.
She does not want to ruin the relationship she has with her son.
Now, again, there are people who have all sorts of bizarre fantasies and all sorts of crazy fetishes and things like that.
They may be married and have kids and have this life, but they also have this really dark desire they want to take part in.
I'm going to leave that in the world of fantasy because I don't want to lose everything I've had.
That's quite common. The hell dark fantasy can vary.
I want to just go out and sleep with whoever I want, but I'm not going to do that because I've made a commitment to this marriage and to these kids.
So I'm going to not do that. I'll fantasize about it, but I'll not do that.
Two, I want to go out and murder young girls. I have this dark desire. I want to be a serial killer.
But if young girls are my own, I'll just keep that in the closet and not do that.
You have all sorts of horrible fantasies. You run the gamut.
And most people, I think, go, "That's just a fantasy. I'm not going to do that."
She's been successful in doing that so far, but she says...
First, I want to tell him. Second, he'll be afraid if I tell him.
And then she says, "I absolutely will not tell him about this fantasy until he's at least 18 years old."
Which is just a couple months away.
Once he turns 18 or he asks about it, I'm not going to mention this.
So that clock is ticking. When she posted this in November of 2013, it's just a couple months away.
He'll turn 18 and then she won't feel for whatever reason. That's the weirdest...
It's all weird. I can't say it's the weirdest component, but it's so bizarre.
Where that's her big hang-up. She's like, "I want it to be consensual and you can't consent until you're over the age of 18."
"I want him to consent to being eaten, but I want him to be..." It's so weird.
I mean, what he's consenting to is so bizarre. When you're that lost in the fantasy, it's just a weird hang-up, I guess.
She goes, "Here's the thing. I want him to go away to college and I want him to have his own life experiences."
Which is good. She's thinking about that. She's thinking about him not being eaten.
But to finish what she was saying, she goes, "I want him to go to college. I want him to have his own life experiences."
Quote, "Before I introduce any sexual elements into our relationship."
So that is where she really plays her hand.
She is going, this is so disturbing. She will let him go off to college. She will groom him. She will manipulate him.
Because once he turns 18, the floodgates are open.
She is going to, once he turns 18, begin to sexually manipulate him, have a sexual relationship with her son.
And then slowly introduce the fantasy of eating him. That's her goal.
It's a very interesting post because she kind of goes on and on and she uses all these wiggle words like, "Oh, you know, I want to put him to consent. Don't worry about that."
But at the very end, she mentions introducing sexual elements.
And that's how it would work. That's 100% how it would work. If she walks up and says, "I want to eat you."
She'll never see him again. She'll never see him again. He'll run.
But she will seduce her son. That's step one.
And who knows what groundwork she's laid for that?
A groomer won't admit to grooming, right? "No, no, no, I never set this up. We were just friends that whole time."
It changed later on would be the argument.
But who knows what she's done over the years? Just like, "Let's watch Back to the Future again."
Again, mom, "Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, let's watch it."
We're always going to watch those scenes with Marty McFly and his hot mom.
She's laid the groundwork for that. She's going to sexually seduce her son.
And then as they engage in this relationship, she's going to start introducing stuff like,
"Hey, do you want to use some toys?" And she brings out like a spatula.
She's like spanging him with a spatula that she's flipping him over.
She turns her bedroom into a giant kitchen.
He's like, "You know, mom, it's been fun having sex with you and all, but do we have to do it in a giant cast iron skillet?"
She's slowly going to introduce the fantasy of the sex, or the fantasy of the cannibalism.
So her in goal, that is what she wants to do. She does want to eat her son, which we knew in the beginning,
but even though she tried telling us it was just the fantasy, it was just the fantasy,
after he turns 18, she will seduce him. She will physically, sexually seduce him.
And a mother's bond is hard to break.
Like, if some dudes get so into the mama's boy routine that no matter what girl they date,
the mom's like, "She's not good enough. She's not good enough." Stuff like that.
And you're just digging the hooks in the mama's...
No, I'm not saying that every mama's boy is getting seduced by their mother.
I'm not saying every mother that disagrees with her son's relationship choices.
It's trying to bang them.
But this woman is, this Veronica woman is, she wants to eat her son,
and she knows that she can't jump right to that, so she's going to sexually seduce her son.
And then over time introduce these elements.
Now, she may never fully devour her son. It may be some sex game they play.
Which I mean, it's also equally disturbing. You're like, "Jason, that's not any better."
Whether or not this guy got eaten, he's been groomed by his mother.
He's paying his mom. He's paying his mom. I feel bad for this guy.
He's stuck in this horrible situation.
Whether or not he's actually devoured in the end is irrelevant.
He's been trapped into his mother's fantasy. He's trapped.
Now, there's a chance that, again, we don't know how this story ends.
We know what her goal is to sexually seduce her son, and at the very least, role-play eating him.
But her main goal is to eat him.
Which is terrifying.
To be raised by a mom who wants to eat you and all of the little things you could do throughout someone's life,
and them not noticing it, laying the groundwork for you wanting to eat them,
and then waiting until they're 18 to sexually seduce them.
And then, over time, like, I mean, that'd be weird enough, right?
You're in a sexual relationship with your mom. You're already, that's already kind of messing with your head.
[laughs]
Just when you thought things gonna get worse.
She's trying to fowl you. She wants to eat you. She wants to cook you alive or eat you raw.
Just when you thought your life gonna get anywhere disturbing.
One day your mom walks in wearing a big chef's hat, and all of a sudden you're reenacting that scene from The Little Mermaid, and you're the crab!
It's a terrifying story. It's a horrifying look at how a dark desire can drive a person mad.
Like, this woman's insane.
This woman has been laying the groundwork for years over some twisted fantasy she has.
And she has all the power in the world to make it come true.
[laughs]
So after getting ready for Thanksgiving this year, when your mom invites you over, you make the long drive out there.
Okay, I was gonna go on this really long. You're like, "I Jason, listen, I shut the podcast off. I shut the podcast off."
When you mentioned my mom calling me, 'cause I knew exactly where you were going.
You're gonna spend the next five minutes telling me that my mom wanted to bang me and then eat me.
Okay, I won't go there. I won't go there. Just here's the story.
So this Thanksgiving when you do meet with your family or get together with your friends, however you celebrate Thanksgiving.
When people ask, "Hey, what have you been up to?"
You tell them you've been listening to a podcast called Dead Rabbit Radio, and they go, "Oh, what's it about?"
Tell them this story. I just told you.
Go, "You know that there's a woman."
Trust me, you will be the life of the party.
And then your mom's in the kitchen.
Your mom's in the kitchen looking at photos of you and her mouth is watering.
She looks at the camera and her eyes turn yellow.
[laughs]
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is gonna be our email address.
You can also do this up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[music]