Can you get so high you can predict your own destruction?
Then we travel back to the 1500s to take a look at a satanic serial killer who cut a
bloody swath across Europe.
Is it possible that this madman actually had access to black magic that turned him into
an unstoppable killing machine today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so you're ready to get started right away.
First off walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our newest Patreon supporters.
Everyone get on your feet and give a round of applause for Flix is cool.
Woohoo!
Come on in Flix!
You sure are cool.
I guess you can't say he's not.
It's in his name.
Flix you're going to be our captain, our pilot of this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon I totally get it.
Just helps spread the word about this show that really, really helps out a lot.
Now Flix let's go ahead and we're going to start off by tossing you the keys to the Dead
Rabbit Durgible.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're headed all the way out to Calabasas, California.
Brrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
So this man, he's 53 years old, begins to experiment with ayahuasca, which is a very,
very powerful hallucinogenic.
They've used it in shamanic journeys for centuries and now it's the brand new craze.
If you can get a hold of some, you can do it yourself.
You're supposed to have like a shaman there to help guide you, but you can just take it
yourself if you're famous enough, if you have enough money, you can just have the ayahuasca
delivery service show up and be like, "Mmm, I'm going to drink this all by myself.
What could possibly go wrong?"
Now this man said, "Listen, I've done ayahuasca up to 15 times.
I'm experienced with it, but there was one time that I had such a hellish experience.
It changed me."
This man, he says that it takes about 45 minutes for the ayahuasca to kick in.
So he's famous, right?
He's wealthy, he has stuff to do.
He goes, "You drink the ayahuasca and it's 44 minutes.
It hasn't kicked in yet.
Maybe I need more."
So this guy basically doubled toast and might have tripled toast because he kept waiting
for it to kick in.
He's like, "Oh, 44 minutes and 30 seconds.
I'm still not high.
Time for another sip of this ayahuasca."
After the ayahuasca kicked in, because eventually it will, right?
He's sitting in his mansion that he bought with the money that he earned coming up from
the bottom, coming up from nothing.
Everything this man has, he earned it.
He spent his entire life working towards this goal.
Working to be rich enough to take ayahuasca in a Calabasas, California mansion.
He's sitting in his mansion and what happens is he starts to see his money floating through
the house.
He goes, "Wait a second.
Money's not supposed to do that.
He's watching hundreds of dollars and thousands of dollars and then millions of dollars just
fly through the house like a tornado and it's just disappearing."
He's trying to grab as many bills as he can, but each time he grabs one, it just completely
fades away and he's watching all of his wealth vanish.
And then the mansion around him begins to fade from view.
Now he is standing in a vacant lot and his career disappears as well.
I don't know how he visualized that.
I don't know if he saw a newspaper and it's like, "This guy sucks!"
But he starts to realize that his entire career, his wealth and his fame has just evaporated.
He's standing there with nothing and he built it.
This wasn't a guy who was given anything.
He built an empire and he watched it disappear in front of him.
He said that while he's sitting there in this state of utter loss, utter devastation, he's
hallucinating that he's lost everything, his daughter walks into the room in real life.
Not in the vision because there is no room in the vision.
The mansion's gone.
She walks into the room in real life.
I don't know what this guy was doing.
I was in the living room or something like that.
He's watching sports and he's like, "You know what?
It's half time.
It's time to take a psychedelic trip to the world beyond."
His daughter walks in and snaps him out of it.
"Dad, dad!"
And he said, "I could hear her calling for me and I stopped caring about everything
that I had lost.
I stopped caring about my career.
All I wanted to do was to get back to my family."
And then he had a really interesting quote to wrap this up.
"When I came out of it, I realized that anything that happens in my life, I can handle it.
I can handle any person I lose.
I can handle anything that goes wrong in my life.
I can handle anything in my marriage.
I can handle anything that this life has to offer me."
That man was Will Smith like a year or two before his career disintegrated on Oscar night.
"Will Smith about four months ago did an interview."
I don't know when he actually did the drugs, but about four months ago, Will Smith was
on David Letterman's Netflix show, "My Next Guest Needs No Introduction."
It was just recently released, but it was recorded months before the Oscar night.
So the Iowa Oscar journey, I don't think it happened right before the taping.
He woke up and he's like, "Oh wait, I gotta get down to the show."
So it had happened previous to this.
So him watching his entire career disappear and losing all of his money and his home and
everything like that.
Was it a prediction?
Like it's really, really interesting.
When he took the Iowa Oscar, did it basically show him the future?
Because Will Smith is on the skids.
He's had like two or three movies canceled because of this.
He's banned from the Academy Awards for 10 years and I know what all of us are thinking.
Who cares, right?
We don't go to the Academy Awards, but his name is Mudd at this point.
What happens is he really pissed off a lot of, not just Chris Rock, right?
Chris Rock just rolled with it and got 10 more years of material from it.
The powerful people in Hollywood who take the Academy Awards super, super seriously,
it was spinning on them.
And I guarantee that for a long time when Will Smith goes out for a role, someone's gonna
get a phone call from some dude that we've never known, right?
Some producer who has a lot of power and he's gonna be like, "Don't hire him."
That's gonna go on for a long time.
It's possible that Will Smith never makes another movie.
That hidden network within Hollywood, they've shut him out.
And all because he slapped a guy on camera.
That was really it.
He slapped a guy on camera at their most prestigious ceremony.
So did the Iowa Oscar trip actually predict that his career was going to disappear?
Because that's really what's happening.
It's interesting as we can always go, "Well, he's a millionaire."
But we don't know people's standard of living.
Like if you are a millionaire and you live in a mansion and you have all these fancy
cars, you're assuming you're gonna keep making millions of dollars each year.
If someone just says that they earn $20 million a year, they may spend $40 million a year.
Right?
On credit and all this other stuff.
Because they assume I'm gonna be in the business for another 10, 15, 20 years.
Will Smith has been in the business since he was like 16.
So why would he assume at 53?
He was going to not make any money anymore.
And he said before, that was his worst fear, was going back to poverty.
That's where he came from.
And he built this empire and then he slapped a dude and he spit in the face of the powerful
establishment of Hollywood.
It humiliated them.
And he has shut out.
And the Iowa Oscar thing, like did the Iowa Oscar predict that this was gonna happen?
Or did the Iowa Oscar, this journey, prepare him for it?
Like was there no way to prevent what was going to happen?
Like the stars were going to align in just the way that Will Smith was gonna walk up
and slap Chris Rock.
And the Iowa Oscar journey was to say you are going to lose your career very soon and
this is what it's gonna feel like and you better be prepared for it.
Or, so it could have predicted something that couldn't be changed.
You could have predicted something and tried to help him psychologically deal with it because
it couldn't be changed.
Or was the Iowa Oscar there to prevent it?
Not just predict, but prevent.
Was it showing him that you are at risk of losing everything?
And when he comes out and says I can handle any person I lose, I can handle anything that
goes wrong in my life, I can handle anything in my marriage, I can handle anything that
this life has to offer me.
Will Smith, I love you, I love your work, but I don't know if that's true.
Like you can say that, but Chris Rock made a joke about your wife and you couldn't handle
it.
Like the Iowa Oscar journey was incomplete.
Because I do believe, I don't do psychedelics at all.
Because my grasp of reality is so tenuous already that I don't do anything that messes
with my bill.
I don't drink either.
Like I drink maybe two or three times a year.
I don't do drugs because they affect my sense of reality way too much.
I don't do psychedelics, but I do believe that they can open up pathways for you to
see things.
I'm not encouraging the use of psychedelics either.
I don't want someone to go chase and set it.
I'm gonna eat all these mushrooms and drink all this Iowa Oscar.
Maybe the journey wasn't complete.
Maybe there was another lesson he had to learn and when his daughter came in she interrupted
that spiritual journey.
I feel bad for the guy.
I think he was pushed to the limit and he went up and slapped his dude, but his career
is over.
Although I will say this, America always loves a good comeback story.
So I'm hoping in the next five to ten years he has some great role.
He comes back.
He steals America's heart again.
Will Smith is on top.
I think that's what will happen.
But he has to go the next five to ten years without making the money he used to.
Did the Iowa Oscar try to prevent that from happening or did it try to prepare him for
the inevitable?
And was there another lesson he needed to learn?
But his spiritual journey was interrupted.
I can handle anything this life has to offer me, but if it's someone insulting someone
you love, you know, I'm not saying that if someone's trash talking to someone you love,
you should let him get away with it, but it's a fascinating story.
It's a fascinating story and I hope it ends well for Will and his family.
Flix is cool.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys of the Carbenter Copter.
We're leaving behind Calabasas, California.
We are headed all the way out to the Palatinate.
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-du
Flix is cool.
He was a monstrous fiend.
Other people just, he was a sick serial killer.
Some people say the story's mostly true.
Some people say there's a lot of folk tales in it, a lot of fables.
But really the difference between the true version and the fables is how many hundreds
of people did he murder?
Did he murder 200?
Did he murder 300?
Whatever the number historians want to agree on, it's a lot.
And I gotta give a thanks to Fabio.
He's the person who sent the story over, always sending over fantastic stuff.
Fabio, a long time listener of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I appreciate it very, very much.
Back in the 1500s, this is so fascinating.
You talk about like a subculture, right?
You had robbers.
Robbers have been around since the beginning of time.
But when villages started to become towns.
When you started to have people really, really protect the things that they love, their family
and their gold.
It wasn't enough for a single robber to jump out with a dagger.
I mean that might work in a big city, 'cause there's a lot of other places you can hide.
You can assassinate and creed up a wall, then jump in a pile of hay and no one will see
you.
But for the most part, you would do some of that, but for the most part you got better
odds if you attacked people in a group.
And that makes sense.
I mean today we have the gang, right?
You can get mugged by a person, but it's far more easy to have three people go into a
liquor store than just one.
But because the penalty for theft, for robbery was death, if you got caught, you knew you
were going to die.
They killed indiscriminately.
If they stole your stuff, it's not like nowadays when someone comes up to you and is like, "Give
me your chains."
You give them your chains, give them your wallet, they didn't ask for the wallet, you
just made a complaint.
And then they'll hopefully leave you alone, right?
Most of the time they're just going to take your stuff and leave, 'cause they're a robber,
they're a stick-up man, they're not a murderer.
And the penalty for robbery is what, a couple years, if you get caught, might even be a
misdemeanor if you plead down to something.
But if the death penalty is on the table, if you're going to die, you're going to kill
any witnesses.
And all these groups of marauding robbers would wailay stagecoaches, any travelers in
between cities.
These were the most dangerous places.
And what's interesting is in this time period, shepherds were basically considered a step
above a robber.
I wouldn't even say barely a step, they were right next to them.
People hated shepherds because they believed, and rightfully so, this happened a lot, the
shepherds would migrate from area to area, and they were out by themselves, and they
would know the lay of the land.
So in between the villages, in between the cities, the shepherds would know all of the
secret passages, all of the back roads, all of the little goalies you could run down.
And so basically, if you were a shepherd, you were basically considered a criminal.
Like people knew that there had to be shepherds out there, but it didn't help, there's a lot
of these robbers who disguise themselves as shepherds, or they would be shepherds on
the times they're not robbing.
Like in between big jobs, they'd just be, they'd go back to their sheep, the sheep were
like, oh, we were wondering when we were coming back.
It's like, yeah, yeah, I'm here, I love you guys.
And then he sees like a stagecoach going down the road, and he's like, oh, sorry guys, I
gotta go to the store to get some cigarettes.
They're like, not again.
There's this quote from a novel in 1554 talking about shepherds.
This is how they thought of them, quote, "Far from civilized society and alone with the
animals, he has time to think over his misdeeds.
Members of such a group were unsurprising suspects."
Unquote.
So the story of Peter Nearest takes place during this reign of criminals, just these mobs
that would waylay travelers, and do these huge heists, and then they would break up into
smaller groups and then travel around, they'd get their sheep together, they'd ride them
around like little ponies, and then they would go to the next job.
And then if they heard, hey, the king's moving all this gold through this area, they would
start to group up again.
So you might be facing down 30 of these guys taking, and we see parallels to this, like
the train robbers in the American West and the pirates, right?
You have these huge, you needed a group of pirates.
You're gonna have one guy on a pirate ship, it wouldn't work.
But you have these gangs, but the story of Peter Nearest, the reason why it stands out,
is that he is also associated with the darkest of dark magics.
Peter Nearest was more than just a standard robber/serial killer.
He was a cannibal, and he was a master of magic.
And this is where people go, "Okay, the fables, the historians are like, we don't know how
much of this is true."
Like as a historian, I'm not officially saying he's a magician, but a lot of people claimed
that he did have powers.
And it's interesting when we look at his career.
He was active for quite a long time, quite a few years, but in 1577 he was caught along
with other members of this gang.
And he was caught, he was tortured, and he confessed to killing 75 people.
But he escaped.
He got out of jail.
The rest of his gang was caught, they were all executed, but he got out.
And that is really, like obviously people already thought this guy had access to some
ritual magic, because they took him long enough to catch him this first time.
But escaping from a jail when he was definitely under heavy guard, they knew who this guy
was, made people really think the stories of his powers might not be exaggerated.
One of the stories that does seem pretty folkloric is that he and his gang had a meeting with
the devil himself.
They called upon the devil and said, "Hey, we're those shepherds that have been killing
all those people.
You love our work?"
And the devil was like, "Ah, the shepherd thing's a little boring, but I love the murders."
And the devil gave his blessing to Peter Neers.
And this is dope.
I didn't know devils did this stuff.
I didn't know Satan did this stuff.
Apparently not only did he give his blessing to Peter Neers, he gave him a monthly paycheck.
Which my question immediately is, how much?
Like it's the devil, right?
Any amount would be way too low.
He has access to all the riches.
If he was giving him $10,000 a month, I'd still be like, "Come on, devil.
Come on.
You're like a little bit more, a little bit more, buddy."
So he always had money on him.
And that was actually, there was a few things that you could always know that you had Peter
Neers in your company.
Because people were looking for this guy.
Right?
He's killing a bunch of people.
He'd been arrested.
They had descriptions of him from survivors and they had descriptions of him when he was
arrested.
And he was described as being a very old man who had a long scar down his chin.
He had two crooked fingers.
And he always had money on him.
Which is where I think part of the devil's allowance is coming from, right?
A thief, you would imagine.
The reason why you're a thief is because you need money.
It would be odd that a thief would always have money on him.
But that was one of the call signs of Peter Neers.
He always had money on him.
He also, they say, he also, he always had the money on him.
He also had two loaded pistols hidden in his pants.
And he carried around a huge two-handed sword.
So you would think, "This guy, you should be really easy to pick this guy out of him."
Right?
He's the guy who can't walk right because he's afraid he's going to blow his kneecaps
off.
He's constantly carrying around this giant sword like it's out of a video game.
But apparently, despite this stuff, he has pockets full of gold like Scrooge McDuck,
two loaded pistols, and this giant sword, he was a master of disguise.
Now, some people say it was the magic that did it.
Some people say that he could turn into a rock.
He could turn into a log.
If you were pursuing him, you'd go into a forest and he'd be gone.
And if they had only looked down, they would have seen a hollowed out log with a human
face on it going, "Hehehehehe."
And then it's full of gold and there's two pistols lying next to it, and a giant sword
sticking through it.
He could turn into a rock.
He could turn into a log.
He could turn into a cat or a dog or other popular things of his shapeshifting abilities.
What historians believe is they actually believe that he wasn't a shapeshifter because normal
historians don't believe in that stuff.
They believe he was a master of disguise.
They believe that the-- because he had mentors, right?
He wasn't the first guy to do any of this stuff.
There were people doing this long before him and he was joining these gangs and he was
learning from other people.
They believe that his mentors taught him how to disguise himself.
And they believe-- and this would actually work.
This would totally work.
He would disguise himself as either a foot soldier, just a dude walking around in armor.
I don't know if it was like a suit of armor, but you know what I mean?
He would dress like just a common soldier who would totally just fit in.
He wouldn't fit in today, right?
If you saw a guy walking on the street in chain mail, you're like, "Uh, I think I'm
gonna call the cops."
But back then, it wouldn't be odd.
You'd just think it was a foot soldier or a mercenary passing through, especially if
you were in a big city.
You wouldn't think anything of it.
The other disguise that he would often use, and this one's genius, he would be a leprosy
victim, which people would just stay away from him.
People would just stay away from him.
So that would explain why people thought he was a master of disguise.
He actually could just disappear.
They don't explain how leprosy victims walk around with a giant two-handed sword and not
getting any attention, but apparently it worked, because he was unstoppable.
And because they were these whispered rumors of cannibalism and his connection to dark magic,
they started to believe that his powers must be coming from somewhere.
Not just the devil.
He must be doing something really despicable, because they're coming across these crime
scenes and people are just destroyed.
People aren't just killed, they're ravaged, they're mutilated.
So the stories start to pop up that Peter Neers must have access to some unholy objects.
We did an episode a long time ago about the Hand of Glorial, but that episode on the show
notes was an early one.
It was one of these old, thief techniques where you would take a human hand and you'd
have to prepare it in some way, and you would light the fingers one by one, and everyone
in the house would fall asleep and then you could just burgle the house and be in and
out and no one would ever know.
That was a really cool episode, although that one on the show notes.
So people knew about relics like that, but they didn't know if that's what Peter Neers
was using.
Some people believed that that was it, but it turns out his artifact was far more terrifying.
In 1581, in Newmark, which is modern day Bavaria, Germany, our protagonist, Peter Neers, is
staying at an inn called the Bells.
He's there for a couple days and no one knows it's him, right?
There's posters of him all over town, but no one knows it's him, his master disguise.
He's at the inn for a couple days and he goes, "You know what?
I've been here a couple days in this town.
It's time for a bath."
There's not a bath in his room because it's old timey stuff, so he had to go to the public
bath and he's walking out there and he's like, "I'm gonna be completely naked, so I don't
know what type of disguise I'm wearing, but I think I'll be fine.
I don't think anyone's gonna catch me."
Well, he gets in there and yeah, you can't wear disguise.
You can't be a soldier or a leprosy victim in a public bath.
I guess you could have a leprosy, but I don't think they'd let you in.
So he's in there and people start to talk.
It's crazy.
Before photographs or anything, you just went off of a drawing.
People started saying, "I think that's Peter Neers.
I think that's Peter Neers."
At this point, he had been active for 15 years.
People have been looking for this guy.
So two people snuck out of the bath house undetected and they found out what inn he was
staying in.
You know, it's a small town.
A stranger shows up with a two-handed sword.
Everyone's gonna know what inn he's at.
They asked what inn he's at and they go see the innkeeper and they said, "Hey, you know
anything about that weirdo who just came in and you're in a couple days ago?"
He was smelly for one.
He had an added bath in a couple days and innkeeper goes, "Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That guy, he actually gave me this bag for safekeeping."
And the two people are like, "Dude, we gotta look in this bag.
It's either full of cotton or tulips or it'll be proof that Peter Neers is at the public
bath house."
So they take the bag and they open it up and what they find is a bag of fetus hearts and
hands.
I don't know why adding the hands on makes it even worse.
It would be bad enough if it was just a bag full of fetuses, right?
Sorry, Flix is cool.
It's like throwing up in the corner.
Sorry, you're on this episode.
Someone had a bag of fetuses.
That would be pretty bad.
I wouldn't be like, "Well, at least it's not the hearts.
It's just babies.
It's just little fetuses in there."
You open up the bag and there was a bunch of fetuses in there.
You'd still call them the cops.
But fetus hearts is awful and then the hands is just kind of gross because you'd recognize
those.
I don't know if I'd recognize a little fetus heart, right?
They look in the bag and they're like, "Uh, we expect to find two guns and a bunch of
gold.
We didn't expect to find a bag of baby hearts."
So they go to the constable and they're like, "Just believe us.
We're going to tell you a story.
Just believe what we're saying.
Don't look in the bag."
And the constable's like, "I kind of got to look in the bag."
And they're like, "Uh, you're not going to want to look in the bag."
But anyway, so the constable rounds up a bunch of people.
They go into the bath house and they arrest them.
And he is then tortured for quite a while and he ends up confess...
People don't know if this number is accurate.
This is what he confessed to under torture.
People say a lot of stuff under torture.
He confessed to 544 murders.
Those are the ones he admitted, which either means he exaggerated it or he did way more
than that and he was too embarrassed to talk about those ones.
544 murders.
I mean, nowadays obviously that's still an astounding number, but back then there were
villages that didn't have 544 people living in them.
Insane.
So like all good medieval stories, this one ends with a good old fashioned torture.
Day one.
I'm just going to shut the podcast off.
I'm just going to shut it off after the fetus hearts.
Is he really going to read out the tortures?
Day one.
It was September 13th, 1581.
They...
Here, and I'm going to say this too, people always get so pissed off.
I get like angry emails and YouTube comments when I say this.
I think this is exaggerated.
This is what news reports said at the time in like wood carvings, but I think it was
propaganda.
I did an episode about a guy who was strapped down to a hot burning throne and his skin
was pulled off inch by inch and I was like, "That's impossible.
That's fake.
Here's why it's fake."
But people were like, "No, you're fake.
You're fake.
Don't say the torture's not real."
I don't know who's defending the torture.
I don't know who wants it to be real.
I'm pretty sure it's fake.
So let's take a look at this.
Day one.
His flesh is torn from his body.
Not all of it.
Just some of it, right?
They got another two days to do.
There's three days of tortures.
Day one.
They tore some flesh from his body and they poured heated oil on his wounds.
Okay.
I'm not saying okay, but that's okay.
He's like, "Boring.
When's the real torture start?"
I'm saying you could survive that.
That's torture.
So that was the first day, right?
And I don't think they did it for all day.
They probably took him an hour to do that.
They pulled off some skin, poured some oil on him, and then the executioner's like, "When's
lunch?"
Then it's day two.
So like, what did they just send him back to the cell?
He's like, "Ow, ow, ow, ow.
I have this hot oil on my skin."
Day two.
Total de-escalation, right?
Day one.
They tear his skin off and pour hot oil on his skin.
Day two.
They take his feet, which are still attached to him, and they put heated oil on him.
They're like, rubbing it on.
I imagine it's like that red spicy oil from like a Thai restaurant.
He's all, "Yummy, yummy, yummy.
I am a cannibal after all.
Mm-mm-mm.
I'm gonna eat them feet."
They held his feet over hot coals, not even a fire.
They couldn't even afford like, logs and stuff for this.
They held his feet over hot coals and his feet roasted, 'cause he had like, on the hot
oil and then they held it over hot coals.
Here's my question against all your torture aficionados.
One, who was holding his feet over the hot coals?
They're getting burned up too.
They accidentally spilled some heated oil on their hand.
They're like, "Oh, I hope I don't get cooked."
They're like, "Hey, can you hold his other foot?"
You're like, "No."
Like someone has to be holding him over the hot coals.
Two, why didn't they use a fire?
Why is it just hot coals?
Three, he's a cannibal.
This is super delicious to him.
He's loving it.
Even though it's painful, like all those little cartoon wavy lines are coming up, the
scents coming up from his feet.
Mm-mm-mm.
Day three.
I was so disappointed in day three, 'cause I had to look up something that I always
thought was real and it's not, well, it's real, but day three, they drag him to the
place of execution, which at that point, I mean, he can't feel anything really.
He's been all burned up and stuff like that, but they're like, "Oh, it's gonna be all dirty."
They drag him to the place of execution and he is broken on the wheel.
So I always thought, I see pictures of this, right?
It's a giant wheel and I always thought that they tied you to the wheel and then I thought
this, I mean, if you said broken on the wheel, you tie someone on a wheel and then you roll
it down a hill.
They're like, "Wee!
Ouch!
Wee!
Wee!"
Ouch!
And they're getting crushed.
Kids are like, "Oh, Ma, can I murder someone so I can be broken on the wheel?"
Not today, Johnny.
But I imagined, shocker of shocks, that the wheel did a wheel-like motion to kill you.
You know what it means to be broken on a wheel?
This is so stupid.
When you are broken on the wheel, this is what they did to Peter Neers.
They dragged him across the dirty city to his place of execution, tied him to the ground,
and then dropped the wheel on him.
That's what they do.
They pick a wheel up, a giant wheel, and they drop it on him.
And then they pick it back up and then they drop it on him.
And then they pick it back up and they drop it on him.
What?
You can do that with anyone who doesn't have to use a wheel.
You can use a bat or a sledgehammer or something or a boot.
Why build a giant wheel if it's not going to do a wheel-like thing?
I guess eventually, sometimes, if your bones are all busted up and you're still alive,
they'll pick up your body.
And then they'll like thread your arms into the wheel.
So like your arms all busted up.
People are like, "Dude, you're doing this podcast for no one at this point."
Your arms are all busted up and they'll thread it through the wheel so you'll be hanging there
from the wheel and then guess what?
They beat you up.
They beat you up, they beat you up as you're there and then you die.
At no point could I find hilarious death.
At no point could I find someone being tied to a wheel and then it rolling down a hill.
Maybe at some point people are getting tied to water wheels and they were drowning and
then getting a little bit of air and drowning and get a little bit of air.
I'm not saying I want advancement in torture technology, but if you're going to call something
broken on the wheel, it should do a wheel thing.
So very disappointed.
He's not disappointed.
He's dying very slowly.
They dropped this wheel on him 42 times and he still lived.
Shows how inefficient dropping a wheel on someone is.
He was eventually quartered by horses and he died.
That's the story of Peter Nears, probably one of the most prolific serial killers in history.
The reason why we don't really classify him as a serial killer because it was a side job.
His main thing was robbing people.
The killing was just to cover up the robbery.
That normally doesn't get classified as a serial killer.
Back then that term didn't exist, but on a paranormal aspect, let's wrap the episode
up like this.
I find it so fascinating that we spend so much time pressuring the Air Force and the Pentagon
for information about UFOs.
But we never stop to ask police officers and FBI agents about their encounters with the
paranormal in the field.
Never.
I'm sure there are beat police officers working the streets and FBI agents investigating crimes
and they come to something that they cannot believe.
It's so unbelievable they can't even put it in their report because they would get laughed
out of a job.
Same reason why pilots weren't talking about UFOs for 50, 60, 70 years.
It's still a lot.
Don't do it today.
So if you had a police officer chasing down a thief, the thief runs around the corner,
the officer runs around the corner and the thief is gone.
He's going to assume the thief just got away, right?
He's going to call in backup, maybe call in a helicopter depending on the severity of
it and how much of a risk this guy is to the community.
But what if an officer actually saw a suspect vanish from him right in front of him?
Disappear.
Turn invisible.
Because this thief had access to a bag of black magic.
A bag of fetus hearts.
I'm not sure what you're doing with that part.
This magic, if it's real, it's not like it would have worked up until the 1500s and then
someone goes, "Ah, it doesn't work anymore."
If it worked up to the 1500s, it would work today.
And these secrets would still be taught in thieves' guilds.
These would be passed down in prisons from an old criminal to a younger one who has time
to get out.
These dark secrets could be still used today.
Invisibility spells, shape-shifting spells.
Deals with the devil not for fame and fortune, but to be their ally on earth.
To spread chaos for material gain.
We don't know how to call these beans forth or we don't know specifically what ingredients
need to go in this bag or we don't know the incantation to turn into a rock or a log or
a cat.
But someone does.
And secrets like that would be passed down over the generations.
If these spells worked in the 1500, as disgusting as they are a bag of fetus hearts, if that
worked back in the 1500s, it would work today.
And if a police officer was chasing a suspect and that suspect notices that the cop is about
to get him and he reaches into a little pouch and then suddenly he's gone.
A white in front of the officer completely disappears.
That would 100% go unreported.
The officer would never put that in a police statement, he would just say, "I lost him."
And so there could be these tools still out there.
There could be a crime wave, and we've covered a lot of stuff like this, a crime wave using
black magic to get away from law enforcement.
Just because it's an old timey tale doesn't mean every element of it is false.
In fact, the opposite's true.
If it worked back then, it would work today.
And we would never know it.
It would never be revealed to us.
There may someday be disclosure about the UFO phenomenon, but there will never be disclosure
about the way that dark forces interact with our daily life.
It's not a light in the sky.
It's a broken car window or a gun in your face.
A crime wave fueled by black magic.
A crime wave that continues from generation to generation to generation.
The criminals may change, but the crimes don't.
Murder is what the devil demands.
And murder is what the devil gets.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)