A massive volcano eruption can't make that sound funny.
But anyways, the volcano is erupting in Guatemala.
Scientists discovered that animals are talking to themselves and we have yet another greatest
horror movie ever coming out.
I'm Jason Carpenter and this is The 14th Family.
[Music]
Okay, so unfortunately we have another volcano erupting right now on the planet Earth.
I think everyone's heard about the Hawaiian volcano erupting.
I don't know why I'm laughing.
This is such a tragic story.
But we're having this volcano also erupting down in South America in Guatemala, Central
America.
Central America.
69 people dead as of the recording of this.
I'm looking at the DailyMail.com website about it and really the news article is mostly
about the pyroclastic flow that erupted down the mountain.
And apparently I didn't know this.
You see in movies it's the hot lava that's chasing people and movies like Volcano and
Dante's Peak.
But the pyroclastic flow is realistically what's the most damaging.
It can move up to 60 miles an hour and it's just hot ash.
There's, go to DailyMail.com, I don't know, search pyroclastic flow, search Guatemala
volcano.
I'm not worried about putting links up on the website or anything like that right now.
But anyways, they have these just amazing heartbreaking photos of this horrible event.
People running away from, you can see the pyroclastic flow pouring off of volcano and
just these people running from it, video of people who got trapped in it unfortunately.
Lots of bodies, lots of funerals.
It's tragic.
You know volcanoes are one of those things.
I would say it's probably at least the most suddenly violent thing we see on this planet.
We have earthquakes and tornadoes and hurricanes.
And those are bad.
Like I've never been, I've been through a couple earthquakes because I'm from California.
I was in the 88 earthquake in Alameda.
So it's not like I was far away.
I was right in the middle of that one.
But you know, watching the hurricanes come and they just destroy houses and tornadoes
come and they destroy houses, that's bad.
I'm not minimizing that at all.
But the, just the act of the volcano of like the earth, burping up, new rock of just liquid
earth pouring out.
And again, a lot of that's from the visuals from the movies and you see the hot bubbling
stuff, but it just like reshapes the planet.
A tornado or hurricane will level, you know, structures, but a volcano will actually reshape
the earth.
I just think it's fascinating.
But I think it's definitely, it's heartbreaking that these people, I mean, I'm in this nice
little apartment here in Hood River and these people are going through some horrible tragedies
right now.
So despite my laughing in the beginning, a little bit of a nervous laughter, it's just
absolutely terrible.
I hope every, you know, hope everybody gets through this.
If you're listening to this and you want to help, I'm sure you can find, you know, Red
Cross, any place, donate your money, donate your time to help people out over there.
Because you know, obviously there's going to be a lot of reconstruction.
There's just, the photos look like they're grayscale because it's just ash everywhere.
It's very odd.
It is very eerie, makes it look moon-like.
So we're going to jump to a topic that's just a little more, just what's actually much
more cheery.
I kind of planned it out that way.
This is an article from BT, whatever website that is.
It looks like it's some sort of, I don't know, television website.
BT.com.
Article is entitled.
I guess it'd be easy if I put links in here, but I'm just going to assume you know how
to Google.
Articles entitled, "Animals are busy having conversations all around us," say scientists.
Which I think it's one of those things that, on one hand, I think we kind of knew that,
but you know that animals are talking to themselves.
What this article really goes into is that they can, scientists, or you know, the scientists
involved in the study, are basically said that animals take turns talking, which you
know, tweeting and birds tweeting and animals like chirping, of course they're communicating,
but what they've found is that some species will actually say something and then wait
for the other animal to respond.
So it says, I'll read a little bit of the article, "Two-way conversations, once thought
of as a uniquely human, are common across the animal kingdom," say scientists, not all
scientists, just some scientists.
"The whistles of dolphins, low rumblings of elephants, soft chirps of naked mole rats
are, and wrapping of clawed frogs might be somewhat lost in translation, but according
to a new review of scientific evidence, they all follow the turn-taking rules of human conversation."
And then it goes into it, it's saying that researchers from the UK and Germany have been
looking into this for a while.
It's a subject that they say really hasn't been moved forward in the past 50 years and
so on and so forth.
So that is interesting.
So the way that separates it is that some animals will just sing a song and then other
birds will be like, "Oh, I want to mate with that dude because he has a good song."
Some species will actually have conversations.
So that implies a level of foresight.
Like when you're having a conversation with someone, you have to listen and then respond
and then at the same time expect them to what their response may be to that.
It's not, we don't just say, "Food there," and then someone goes, "Food where?"
I mean, I guess we do.
But when we're talking to people, we have to, it's far more complex than if I was standing
out on the street corner going, "Food, food's over here, food, food's over here."
If, okay, so yeah, let's go with that analogy.
Imagine that I'm like a porcupine and I'm standing, what do porcupines eat, berries?
Imagine I'm a porcupine and I'm standing outside of a river and I find a bunch of berries and
I want my friends to come over and eat with me.
I think this analogy is totally on sideways already, but I want to come over with me, but
I can't really communicate.
I don't have this turn taking that they're talking to scientists talking about.
I can stand there and go, "Berrys, berries, berries," like I'm chirping and the other porcupines
hear that I'm saying.
I'm making the noise that when berries are nearby and they walk over, we eat some berries.
That was, okay, so that's the first part.
But this is basically saying, which is super, that's super easy.
Ice cream truck, I hear ice cream truck.
I know instinctually that there's ice cream nearby.
What they're saying with the turn talking thing is that a porcupine not only is going
berries, berries, but it'll say there's...
There's berries over here, guys, and then the other people walk over and go, "Where are
the berries at?"
And then he goes, "Well, they're right over here.
They're super tasty."
And then the other guy goes, "Okay, maybe I'm reading a little too into this article."
The point is, is that if animals are actually taking turns talking, that...
I'm gonna go back to my original point, that I think that leads to a level of awareness
of consciousness, maybe not consciousness, but at least awareness of, you know, having
to be a little bit smarter than we've given them credit for.
Let's see if I'm getting anything that I said, anything that I just went off of.
Let me see if it's backed up.
And it doesn't really...
But it does say that this...
The fact that animals do this does make more sense to why humans have developed language.
So I think it means that animals are probably more aware and have more idea of what's coming
down the pipe.
They're not necessarily instinctual animals, if they can communicate back and forth like
that.
Maybe I'm reading too much anyway, but that's what I get from that article.
And sometimes it's better what you get from the article than what the actual article is.
Here's a interesting...
This will be the last article we talk about right now, and then we'll go into the movie
thing.
So on PJ Media, I'm so lazy, I'm not even linking to stuff, but PJ Media has this article
that there is this massive...
Man, that is huge.
The headline is "Massive cloud of flying midges descends on Cleveland, visible on weather
radars."
And it's huge.
It crosses at least...
Well, okay, no, it doesn't cross more than one county, but it's huge enough to show up
on the radar.
So I guess this is an annual thing.
These bugs, these mosquito things come flying through, and there were so many this year that
they actually showed up on the weather scanner.
That's pretty crazy.
I've never heard of a midge.
It must be an east coast thing.
Cleveland?
Which is Cleveland at?
East coast?
Whoa, there's a picture of it.
Yeah, it just looks like a giant cloud.
That's disgusting.
I would live in a mosquito net.
And nature is just amazing.
And I think that's just so weird that we live in a world that can still surprise us.
Maybe it doesn't surprise them over there.
Maybe they're used to it.
It does seem like it's an annual thing, kind of looking at that article.
Okay, so we have a new horror movie out.
Once again, it's the scariest horror movie ever.
It's the greatest horror movie of all time.
That's what they said about the Babadook, which sucked.
Babadook was okay.
It follows.
Oh, that's supposed to be the scariest movie.
It's supposed to be the scariest movie.
No, it's lame.
I don't like it follows.
What was the other one that they really...
After it follows in the Babadook, the next time they said, "Oh, this is a great horror
movie," which I think might have been.
It comes at night.
There might have been one in between that.
They're like, "This is it.
This is like the most artistic horror movie.
I'm a big horror movie fan, big sci-fi fan, big genre fan."
So I was totally suckered into the Babadook's trailer and got it.
Renna did it the first day it came out.
It was very disappointed.
It was good, but the ending just completely fell apart.
It follows.
I fell asleep.
I thought it was boring.
I thought nothing that the characters did that made sense.
I think the fact that the characters just all of a sudden decided that the weakness
of the "It follows" monster was electricity.
So they have this big set piece where they're trying to fight it with electricity, even
though nothing in the movie showed that it was weak to electricity.
It did take a gunshot to the head.
It was just really poorly put together.
I can understand why people liked it because it was very moody, but it just wasn't well
put together.
I didn't like the script.
I wasn't a huge fan of the mood, like the 1970s vibe.
I'll go into that in another podcast.
So anyways, Hereditary is the movie now that they're saying is great.
It's amazing.
Hereditary, Rolling Stone calls it, "The Family Horde Tale is the scariest movie of 2018."
Oh great.
"Story of a family suffering from grief and something vaguely supernatural is an instant
scary movie classic."
Babadook was.
That was the problem with the Babadook.
There wasn't a spoiler alert, but the movie's like a thousand years old now.
There was no monster.
She was just severely depressed.
There was no Babadook.
She was just super depressed.
But then nothing made sense because her little boy's getting magically dragged drug upstairs
and things she destroys or rebuilt.
It just didn't make sense.
But that was much better than it follows.
So why can't I just have a horror movie with a monster?
Oh you know what?
Here's another.
I'm looking at the sidebar here.
It talks about that movie raw.
You know, that was another movie that the critics really liked.
That movie actually wasn't that bad.
I wasn't a huge fan of it.
I thought that the quote unquote "twist" at the ending was really stupid.
But that movie I did enjoy the script and the acting and the plot and the tone.
I thought that was very well put together.
The last five minutes stunk.
And you know, I would say that's the same thing with the Babadook.
If the Babadook had a different ending, if it turned out that the creature was real or
that it was completely in her head and none of it ever ever happened and she was like
locked up in an asylum, I would buy either that second ending.
It's pretty stupid.
But I would buy that rather than trying to have it both ways.
It followed.
I'll say this about it.
It follows.
I like the concept.
I like the whole concept of it being sexually transmitted.
I like the whole concept of it being this unstoppable force.
It's one of those movies that when you hear the concept you're like, "Oh man, what would
I do?"
And you kind of come up with your own scenarios.
The execution just wasn't good.
I didn't like the characters.
I didn't like the dialogue.
I didn't like the clam.
The futuristic clam.
I thought that was incredibly distracting.
They kept pulling me out of the movie.
Instantly pulled me out of the movie.
I'm not knocking the director.
I'm not knocking the actors when I say the acting.
I think the acting was fine.
I just don't think the script was there.
I think the big problem was that script.
So the actors acted kind of like robots and that could have been a directing thing.
It could have been a scripting.
I don't know.
But anyways, the idea was golden.
It follows.
It's a sequel and if it wasn't trying so hard up its own butt, I think it would be successful.
I think I'd watch it.
But anyway, so we have this movie Hereditary coming out and I am...
I don't know.
I've never seen a trailer for it.
I have no idea what it's about other than what I just read.
I'm not going to read the whole review because I don't really like spoilers.
So the review... you know what, I'm going to watch the trailer right now and we will find
out if it's scary.
Maybe you'll hear a little bit of it.
I don't know.
Okay, well that was weird.
That was pretty creepy.
I'll give them credit for cutting a good trailer.
Very interesting.
Let me split it this way.
Unfortunately, I'll probably watch it.
I don't want to get fooled again.
How many times do I have to get fooled by these movies?
But so I'm going to watch Hereditary.
I will get back to you.
I think it's out now if it's not coming back.
But let's go ahead and I'll go ahead and watch that.
That was probably super boring for you to have to listen to a trailer and me comment
only like every three or four minutes.
But that's the way it works.
That's the way it works on these semi-live podcasts.
Well that's it for this episode.
I am going to drink a soda and start editing this.
I hate to say that my life isn't more exciting than that.
But I'm going to go ahead and edit this and get it out there.
My name is Jason Carpenter and this is the 14th Family Podcast.
If you are hearing a theme song or a song playing right now, that may be the theme song.
I don't know.
Maybe.
I might have random songs.
I don't know.
I'm like slowly raising as my voice is fading out.
If I'm doing it right.
If not, it's just way louder than it needs to be.
And I don't have a catchphrase to say goodbye.
So maybe that'll be my catchphrase to say goodbye.
I don't know.
We'll figure it out.
We'll be on this journey together.
I guess I just need bye now.
So bye.
Bye.
(upbeat music)