Today we go to the Monroe Institute to get a first-hand look at what the effects of lush
may really have on the human psyche. And then I am going to give myself a challenge. I am going to,
by the end of this episode, prove to you, using science, that prehistoric creatures may have
helped build the pyramids today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter,
or I'm having a great day. You guys are having a great day too. It was a awfully radio DJ sounding.
First off, let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, Hoots Cheech. Hoots Cheech,
thank you so much for supporting the show. You're going to be our pilot of this episode.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. Just help get the word out about the show.
That really helps out a lot. We also have a merch store and the Minecraft server is set up for the
new update. So if you want to play the Minecraft server, that'd be awesome. So Hoots, let's go
ahead and give you the keys. We're going to start off in the Jason Jalopy. We're going to take a
little drive from Oregon. We are headed out to the Monroe Institute in favor of Virginia. I'm
recording my episode. I'm doing a lot of advanced recording right now because I plan on taking a
real vacation soon. I haven't had more than a week off in two years since I'm doing the show.
I'm trying to record episodes in batches. So when I take an upcoming vacation, I can actually just
sit and watch sci-fi channel movies for three weeks in a row and not have to be recording stuff.
I'm taking all my recording gear with me in case there's a late-breaking story, but it'll be nice
to just kind of relax. So the reason why I give you that little interlude, and I've been telling
the Patreon people that for a while, I've been posting actually previews of upcoming stories
because I'm recording so far in advance. The reason why I'm going through all that is I actually
am recording this story before the Loosh episode comes out. Now you guys will have already heard
it by now, but I'm going to give you a little behind-the-scenes thing. I don't think that episode
is going to be received very well. I think that's an episode I want to get a lot of feedback, a
negative feedback on, Loosh feedback on, because it's one of those stories where I kind of, it's
a very popular belief system and I was ragging on it for like 20 minutes straight. I imagine that
it's an episode that people are going to be upset about. But one of the reasons why I'm
upset about it, and if you don't know what the Loosh is, you don't really have to go back and
listen to Friday's episode. This is just kind of a side thing, but I still believe, even though I
just recorded that episode a couple days ago, I still believe in that time period, and my mind
hasn't been changed in 48 hours, that I think any religion, any belief system that's structured around
fear is a bad one. I mean, is that something we should all agree on? I think anything that invokes
fear in the participants, and you can say, sure, you know, Christianity, Hell and Brimstone and all
that stuff, but the point of most religions is there's hope in the end. If you're a good person,
you get rewarded. And good conquers evil. The ideas that are put forth in the stories of Loosh
that I've read online, now I haven't read Robert Monroe's books or anything like that,
maybe he has a happy ending at some point, but every time I come across Loosh online,
the idea of Loosh, which is that there are archons, I can't pronounce that word a couple days
ago, and I can't pronounce it now, there are these interdimensional beings that make us suffer,
and we're basically just a farm. The entire planet, all realities of farms, so these creatures
are farmed in our delicious, delicious misery. And the only reason we exist is to live horrible
lives and then eventually we get eaten, and it was for nothing. That's really Loosh in a nutshell.
Apparently there's some way to transcend it, but you know, again, most of the people who come
across, most of the stuff I've come across with Loosh, it's pretty, it's pretty heart, it's pretty,
it's pretty negative. So all that being said, it's just like turning the car around. I don't want
to finish this story. No, no, no, come on, it'll be dope for all fighting over the steering wheel,
or there's a bunch of Loosh eating aliens floating above the car being like, "Ha ha ha,
the chaos in the car is extra delicious." Eventually we get to the Monroe Institute. I
read this interesting article and it was too cool to just kind of summarize during my Loosh episode.
It was written by Stephen Barling called Cosmic Degrees, Out of Body at the Monroe Institute.
And what happens is this dude, this journalist, works for a like alternative magazine it looked
like called The Hook, a local alternative magazine. So he decides to check into the
Monroe Institute and see what it's all about. The Monroe Institute was really about like astral
travel, balancing the mind. So you go there, you pay 1500 bucks. Hoots, you got enough money to cover
me and all of the listeners. Hoots is not an okay, perfect. 1500 dollars per person. I have that
and after Hoots is already paying. And you go in, you basically, it's like you spend mornings,
eating breakfast and then you like, like do stuff with people who are like guided astral travel
people, they're ghosts. They're all trying to take your credit card at the coins, they're just like
dropping through the hands. And then at night you are in a pod. So and that's not a, that's an,
you're in an actual pod apparently. There's like these deprivation type chambers or something like
that. And so this journalist, Stephen Barling, goes to do this to see what it's all about. It's
just kind of a puff piece. And he joins us up and the way just the, I don't know why they did this.
I mean, if I'm paying 1500, 1500 dollars for this program, I want my own room. Apparently,
you have to have roommates with this. And you're not bringing your own astral travel buddy because
you just astral travel at home, right? You just, one person falls asleep in dreams and then you
wake that person up and go, my turn. And then you fall asleep and dream. It's funny because on the
loose episode, I kept making fun of the idea of visions while you sleep. I actually believe, and
I don't know if this came across in Friday's episode, I do believe that you can astrally travel.
I do believe that you can project your soul from your body. Now 100% believe that. I don't base
my belief systems on it because I think one, it's not super easy to do. And two, a lot of it is you
probably dreaming or having a seizure. Astral travel is actually one of the hippie-dippy things that
I believe in. But I think it's also something that can easily be a mistake and for a dream or
a grand-mall seizure. And then you have to go to the hospital. So anyways, if I wouldn't pay 1500
dollars to have someone teach me how to float around, but I mean, if they could guarantee it,
right? I'd be like, what? Yeah, here's all my money. And then I'm floating to the bank,
canceling my check, but you have to share a room with someone. So anyway, Steven goes in and he
signs up for a $15 program and he meets a guy like they're in this big meet and greet in the
beginning. He meets a guy named Jack. Now Jack is not his real name for obvious reasons coming up.
They had just had dinner as a group. Someone says they're going to bring out Cherry Pie and
Steven starts going, "Pie? A pie? Oh, a pie?" Like just joking around. Actin' like he's really excited
for Cherry Pie. And Jack turns and stares to Steven and goes, "Pie?" Everyone's like, "What?
What was that? Well, yes, we're having pie. No, that's not what this means."
Jack goes on to tell this story, okay? He used to have a problem with pie. Now, not in the delicious,
yummy food, but in the number. In that magical, mystical number known as pie, which I never got
the big deal about, but I'm not a math dude. I guess maybe it is something awesome. But anyways,
four years earlier, we go back into Jack's past and he's sitting there and he's like in his house
and everything's pie. Everything's pie. Like that's all he's talking about. He's writing it down
everywhere. He's like waking his wife up in the morning. "Hey, guess what? Guess what? Pie."
Like that's a bit of an exaggeration, but not much because he becomes obsessed with pie. Actually,
that might be an understatement. He becomes so obsessed with pie, the implications of what pie
means that he will not stop talking about it. Eventually, his wife gets so concerned, she calls
the police and the police finds out that he's a licensed federal gun dealer. So they call in SWAT.
Call in the SWAT unit for this pie guy and then we get to this great quote in this article. "So,
I don't actually, before I start the quote, I don't know if SWAT showed up before, during, or
after this. I think that it was during because all this stuff seemed to be going on, but if it was
during, I can't imagine the SWAT team walking past this dude or maybe they were even confused by what
was going on." Here's this quote from this article. "Jack found himself naked in the street,
demanding to speak to a mathematician as flak-jacketed teams ransacked his house.
So the reason why I don't know, so I'm imagining like, did he walk past him? He's like,
'Good morning, gentlemen.' And he's taking his clothes off and the SWAT team's like,
'We better just secure the house and make sure there's no, we know he doesn't have a gun. He's
taking his clothes off. He's naked.' So while SWAT is kicking in his door, looking for his guns,
he's outside going, 'Does anyone have the number of a mathematician? I must know pie.' So he obviously
went off the deep end. He tells everyone at the table the story and then they tell Stephen,
the author of the piece. And everyone knew he was a journalist, but they go, 'Oh, guess who's
going to be your roommate? It's Jack. It's the pie guy.' But Stephen goes, 'He seemed to be pretty
fine by now. He had all his clothes on, right? That's a plus. That's a starter.' He did actually
end up going to a mental hospital for a while after that, but and he's no longer allowed to possess
a gun, so he had to get a new job. But now it's his roommate. So the next morning they wake up
and they're like sitting around in a classroom and they're asking about their dreams because they
have to listen to like binaural beats. Can't pronounce that word still either. While they're
sleeping and they try to invoke visions and stuff like that. And spoiler alert, Stephen said he went
through all this stuff. He didn't really have any visions. He didn't really feel like it was doing
what it was supposed to be doing. He also started off by saying, 'I'm not a skeptic, but I'm not really
a believer either.' He's open to this type of experience, but he didn't really think it worked
out. But anyway, so Jack is, they're doing their meeting the next day. Jack goes, 'I had a dream
that this was Survivor. This was a television show, 'Show Survivor,' because this story takes place
like in 2008. It's the show 'Survivor,' and you got voted off and he points at Stephen. Stephen's like,
'Oh, this is going to get weird, right?' Then a couple days pass and Jack, they're doing this whole
meeting thing again and Jack goes, 'I had another dream.' 'I had a dream that you.' He points at
Stephen again, his roommate. The man who has to sleep next to him while he's trapped in a pod,
which I don't know if being in a pod would make you feel safer. Or I think it would be more scary
if you slept in an egg, right? Like you're more commending. That's an old reference. Like, okay,
just imagine a chicken in an egg. That makes more sense. You're in an egg, right? You're in a pod,
and there's a crazy person outside the pod. Technically, you're safe in the pod. Not an egg,
they just crack the egg, but you're safe in the pod. But the thing is, pods are generally built to
be open from the inside and the outside. So now, if a crazy person opens up your pod, where are you
going to run? Like on a bed, you can usually roll off on one side and like crawl underneath it,
or just stand up and walk away. Rather than being trapped in a pod, I imagine being like
getting in a tanning bed and seeing like a silhouette walking up next to you and just
standing there would be far scarier than if you were laying in your bed right now and you saw
a silhouette standing at the edge of your bed. I mean, I guess they're both scary, right? But one
of them you can maneuver. One of them you can duck and weave, duck and weave. Anyways, Jack now
tells us another dream about Steven, where Steven was driving a male car like a box van down the
road and plows into a group of people. And you can just imagine what Steven is thinking at this
point. Like dude, first off, this cost me $1500. Secondly, it's not working. And third, can I get
a new, can I please get a new roommate? Jack says he has this dream where Steven's driving a car and
he plows into a group of people, killing them. And one of the people in the group was a young boy
and then the boy begins to morph into like a fetus, like 2001, like a big old baby.
And then Jack realizes that he was the boy and Steven killed him.
Come on man, give me another room dude. Like seriously, first he's having dreams where I
get voted off the island, which whatever, but now he's having dreams where I murder, murder him.
He turns into a space baby. Like please, I will pay you an extra $1500 for another room.
And so then really to make a long story short, the other people in the group, all Jack wants to
do is talk about Jack. Every time they, you know the guy, you know that type of person, right?
Every time a story comes up, Jack goes, oh, oh, you had a dream about murdering someone, so did I.
Wait, it wasn't me, it was Steven, but I was the victim. And then someone's like,
hey, does anyone have any orange crush? Orange crush? I used to crush oranges back on the vineyard.
People are like, orange is still growing on the vineyard. What? Vineyard? I used to drink wine,
like, you know, no matter what, right? They always have a story. And so eventually someone said,
listen, I've experienced stuff too. Can someone else tell their story?
And at that point, Jack fell totally silent and then went completely off the rocker. Here's the,
here's this quote from this article. That was it. He never fully came back. After sitting quietly
through the rest of the group session, Jack began his descent. And by the next day, he was in full-time
channeling mode and had to be separated from the group. They took him off the tapes. He could no
longer listen to the Byron Earl tapes. He's like, oh, man, that was my favorite song. Put it on a
Spotify playlist. It's all, he's flipping them out. He had to start seeing an on-site psychologist.
Eventually he had such a deep, like mental breakdown, they had to call his mom to pick him up.
And then Steven basically ends the article being like, it's a wacky place. It's a wacky place.
He said the most normal people there were the people who worked there, which was odd considering
they were talking about astral projection all day long. So that's the story of Jack and Steve.
And I thought it was an interesting little microcosm of just the conspiracy world, the world of
fringe beliefs just kind of melt. You have someone who comes in, who's an outsider. He's just like,
oh, that's kind of an interesting topic. And I think that's how most of us view this stuff.
I mean, obviously I've spent decades of my life researching it, but I'm always like, oh, you know,
I'm always looking for something cool, new, something, and I never give too much credit for it.
I'm just like, oh, that's interesting. And then you have people who just dive in headfirst and
whether it's a belief that the number Pi can unlock the universe. Oh my God, I hope he never
saw that movie. I hope that Jack knows. He's tearing off Ragnosky, I've been around his name.
It's the actual director of Pi. After this incident, he's like, ah, well, I got kicked out.
I got attacked by SWAT and I got kicked out of the Monroe Institute. Maybe I'll make a movie.
And then I'll follow it up with a really long boring movie called The Fountain.
That could be Darren. Don't sue me if it's not or if it is. But I think it's an intro microcosm.
We have the tourist who's the journalist just trying to get an interesting story. And I think
this was an interesting story. Then you have the person who jumps in, pays the $1,500,
goes full bore with it and loses it. And whether it was being isolated from his support group,
maybe it was the binaural beats, maybe it was being the center of attention. Every time he
told a story, people were paying attention to him. And it just, when they stopped paying attention,
he lost it. But it's an interesting look at that those two aspects of the paranormal community.
I think most of us are curious about this stuff. We're tourists. We may take a couple of the
subjects more seriously than other subjects. And then there are other people and you guys have
seen them online or maybe know them in real life. No matter what the conspiracy theory is,
no matter what the belief is, they believe it 100%. And the people who believe all conspiracy
theories, you know, they may be right on 10% of them. But the other 90% they're wrong. They're
wrong. And you know what? When you're wrong, you end up eating a slice of humble pie. Hoots,
cheech, let's hop in that carbonar copter. We are leaving behind the Monroe Institute. We're headed
out to Egypt. Now, this was a challenge I gave myself. This is a topic on the conspiracy theory
iceberg. This is a topic I got off the conspiracy theory iceberg. And again, hats off to some
weirdo on Twitter, aka Jack, different Jack, different Jack for putting together this all in
Excel document, because it's really made it easy for me to go through. Hoots, let's bring it down.
We're flying over Egypt. And we see those great pyramids. That's the first thing you think of
when you think of Egypt, right? You think of the pyramids, you think of the Sphinx, and then the
desert. And then if you live there, you think, "Mom, Dad, I love you guys." But for, you know,
the other 98% of the planet, the pyramids and the Sphinx. On the conspiracy theory iceberg,
we have the conspiracy theory. Dinosaurs helped build the pyramids. And I looked at that and I
did some research on it. And I thought, I'm gonna make this work. I'm gonna make this work. Using
science. Using science. Let's see how close I can get you guys on this. Neocreationists is the term
I like to use. There's a lot of people who are creationists, and I would consider myself in this.
I believe that God created the universe, but I believe that, and there goes 50 subscribers, but
hold on. I believe that he created it in the realm of science, if that makes sense. I don't believe
he created it in seven days. I think that when you look at the Hebrew word for day, it means epoch
or era in that translation. So he built it over time and evolution's real. I believe all that
stuff and God is a guiding hand through all of that stuff. Neocreationists is the term I use for
these guys. Are the guys who believe that the world is only 6,000 years old. Now in that theory,
there is stuff saying that dinosaurs helped build the pyramids. That's foolish, right? They'll have
like drawings of a brontosaurus pulling a brick. It's super funny looking, but that's not real,
right? Right? It's not right now. Dinosaurs, the best estimate we have is they died out 65 million
years ago, even if that number is wrong by double half whatever, 30 million years ago, even if it's
wrong and fourths 15 million years ago, it's still nowhere even close to the rise of humans, or even
close to the stone age or anything like that. So when you look at the term did dinosaurs help
build the pyramids, I think right there we can say no, but stick with me. Stick with me. I might
surprise you on this. The pyramids were built around 2500 BC, according to our best radiocarbon
evidence. Now some people say that that is taken from the wood inside the pyramid and the wood
may actually be newer than the construction of the pyramid itself. Let's table that for a second.
When we look at Egyptian artwork, Mesopotamian artwork, there's a creature known as the
Serpapard, the Serpapard, the Serpapard. It's a cross between a leopard and a serpent. It's a
leopard with the long neck of a snake. Now people have said that's a really weird design, because
here, let me read you this quote. The Egyptians are well known for their accurate depictions of
animals, leading some archaeologists to believe that the Serpapapard is not a mythical creature,
but an extinct animal that existed during that time. Where did I get that quote? I got that quote
from Cryptid Wiki. Now sure, they're not an Egypt specific website, but again, let's think about
that for a second. In other places other than Cryptid Wiki, they do talk about this Serpapard.
And some people have said, well maybe that is their version of a dinosaur that helped them build
bricks, carrying these big bricks up the pyramids and things like that. But it's interesting because
people don't know what to make of that. People say everything else in the Egyptian
bestiary is real. I mean, when I read that I go, yeah maybe, what about the dude with the dog head,
right? Like that guy's not real. Anubis? That dude's not real, as he kicks in my door, he's like,
I am real. Sorry Anubis, but I mean, probably not real. Probably not real, right? Get ready to eat my
loosh. So even if these things were real, even if this was a contemporary creature of the Egyptians
that died off, according to the measurements that we can pull off, they're only three feet tall at
the shoulder and 30 feet long from the neck to the tail. So from the head to the tail. So
those things may or may not have existed. Again, it is weird that everything else appears to
match up according to Cryptid Wiki. And again, other sites said that, but it is weird that everything
matched up. But even if that's the case, they weren't big enough to be carrying rocks, you could
throw your kids on the back of them and go for a ride, it'd be totally awesome. But I don't think
they're going to help you build the pyramids. Hear me out. Hear me out on this. Robert Beval is an
author and he's a guy who came up with a fringe theory that the pyramids match up to Orion's
belt. And what's funny is I heard that theory for the longest time. Orion's belt, if you don't know,
it's a constellation in the sky. It's not an actual guy was walking by with a belt and they're like,
well golly, stand there for a thousand years. We're going to match this up. Orion's belt,
the constellation in the sky, the pyramids match up to it perfectly. And I've heard that stated
over and over and over again. And it's one of those things like the ancient astronaut theory and all
of that. And the Sphinx was built from what they can tell us that the Sphinx was not built at the
same time of the pyramids. It was built about 500 years earlier than the pyramids. So it's older
than the pyramids and some people think it could be far older. There's a new theory appearing and
again people say it's a fringe theory but based on water erosion it could be way older than we
think it is. But we'll go with the general science. I'm going to go right now with the numbers that
the pyramids were constructed in the year 2500 BC. The pyramids as we know were constructed in the
year 2500 BC and the Sphinx was constructed about 500 years earlier than that. But Jason
Priestork animals weren't around in 2500 BC. Unless these serpipods were running around
there weren't a Priestork animals in 2500 BC. Hold up. Robert Bevall has a theory, it's a
fringe theory, that the pyramids match up to Orion's belt and the Sphinx matches up to a star as well.
But the only time, which is true, they do match up to that. But the only time it would have matched
up because you know constellations move around, everything's constantly moving. The only time
that Orion's belt would have been perfectly aligned with Egypt. So like the distances and the degrees
you could figure out, it looks like Orion's belt. But the only time that Orion's belt would be over
Egypt was in 10,000 BC. And the pyramids, so his argument was that the pyramids are far older.
The pyramids were built in 10,000 BC and all the radiocarbon dating is wrong.
But I want to go with science on this one. I'm trying to use as much real science as possible.
Now I could throw out the radiocarbon dating. I could go, "Eh, it doesn't work." And apparently it
doesn't work any, going forward, after 1950 it will never work. It doesn't work because there's so
much radiation in the air. Before 1950 we can match stuff up. And there's, it's been contested and
stuff like that. But I don't want to get into that. Let's say that yes, the pyramids were built in
2500 BC and the Sphinx was built before that. How do they match up to Orion's belt? Now again,
Egyptologists say it doesn't or it's just a coincidence or it does, but they just kind of
looked at it and it was at a distance and that and that. Robert Bavall says if at 10,000 BC
those stars are perfectly lined up to the pyramids. Hear me out. This is where I'm going to make my
case. You know that the Christian church has a bad habit of doing this. I don't know if they do it
anymore. I think they've kind of done it as much as they can. But when you would have a holy site
that was created by another religion, say like a druid or a pagan religion or something like that,
they would knock it down. You'd get a ring in the forest where pagans used to go there,
dance naked, talk about pie all the time, a swat is kicking in some elf door. They're right in this,
they're right in the dwarf fortress. The Christian church would build a chapel on top of it.
They'd go to these places that were being used for hundreds of years by paganistic religions.
They knock it over, they build a church on it. Now I have a theory about that. A lot of people go,
it's so the people like, let's say you're in Ireland and you worship some ogre or whatever,
whatever pagans worship, a big tree. And there goes another 50 subscribers, my pagan listeners.
The church would come down, chop down the tree, put it up basically to one,
subvert the local power. They say, nope, we're the most powerful people in town.
Two, so that way all the Irish people know where to go, right? Because they're like, hey,
where's church at? And they're like, where did you, Seamus, where did you pray last week?
I prayed at the giant tree. Well then just pretend it's a tree, but you're going to walk
inside, you're going to sit down instead. I can walk inside a tree, just go there.
So they would know where it was basically, they wouldn't need directions. I have an idea,
I have a theory that this is throwing out the science thing for a second, but I have a theory
that there are certain, the reason why that tree or that glen was picked by the pagans in the first
place, because it held power. I know I said I was going to talk about science, but it held an
intrinsic power in and of itself. And the Christian church, when they came in, they weren't, they
picked up on the power as well. Holy ground is holy ground. Holy ground is holy ground. So
whether it's holy because it was to Artemis or it's holy because it's to Saint Michael,
it's holy ground. And it's been holy for tens of thousands of years before people even stumbled
across it. That's my theory. I think that the reason when you had the churches being built,
that was one of the reasons they go, well, we can already feel this place is powerful,
there's a presence here. It has nothing to do with science. And they're probably muddying the
issue. But anyways, that's what I think. But regardless of my theory or the general theory that
they were just knocking, the Christians just like knocking down trees, building churches there,
I think it's a useful tactic either way, right? But who's to say that the modern Christian church
pioneered that effort? I always know, I always hear about it of the Christian church. But who's
to say that other groups haven't done that? Who's to say that the Druids who found that glen,
there wasn't a Stone Age monument there before the pagans got there. The Bramble had been cleared
out by hand. A tribe that had long been decimated considered that spot holy. Again, because holy
land is holy land. What if the pyramids were built in 2500 BC, but the specific locations,
the layout of the pyramids, was laid out in 10,000 BC when a Stone Age tribe of Egypt looked up at
the sky and saw Orion's belt aligned perfectly with this patch of land. Now they didn't have the
ability to make pyramids. They weren't able to pour concrete or work these giant mechanisms. I do
believe the pyramids were built by humans too. I guess there's no aliens aren't going to show up
anywhere in the story. I'm sorry to disappoint you, but they didn't have the ability to do that level
of engineering, but they knew that this was a special place, a special point in time where they
could look up and see these stars. So they did what they could do. They do what we've seen so many
other cultures do around the world. They built mounds. They built mounds marking the spots
of the Orion's belt and then that star where the Sphinx would later lay. You could mark that territory
and it wouldn't have to be anything that would stand the test of time and most likely wouldn't,
right? The Stone Age culture that built these mounds or depressions or whatever they were to mark
this point where this beautiful star arrangement aligned perfectly over Egypt. This Stone Age
tribe does it and then when they're wiped out and another tribe comes in and they're wiped out and
another tribe comes in and eventually we move to the Bronze Age. We move on through the ages. When
the pyramids are being built there's no historical record as to why they're there, but they put
them there perfectly, matches up to Orion's belt to mark these places as holy forever rather than
just earthworks, mounds. If that area of land was marked to match Orion's belt, which matched up to
the year 10,000 BC, mammoths did not die out until 8,500 BC. So we would have a 1500 year period,
so we would have, we know humans do not run alongside dinosaurs as dope as that would be.
Almost makes me want to be a neocreationist, right? But that just didn't happen. But humans did live
alongside mammoths. They didn't wake up and pet them in the morning, but they hunted them.
Why couldn't they have taken them as beasts of burden, train them to be beasts of burden,
maybe little baby ones, and use these massive creatures who actually weigh as much as a tyrannosaurus
wrecks. I didn't know that until I was researching this, and use them to make these earthworks,
these massive markers that match up perfectly with Orion's belt. These wouldn't
show up in any sort of historical reference today, other than the fact that it marked a place in time
that would only exist in 10,000 BC. The pyramids don't have to be built in 10,000 BC.
They only have to be, the locations only have to be marked in 10,000 BC.
Like we have the major earthworks of the Native Americans, still here in America,
where they took their time and they made these giant mounds marking these areas.
My using, I should have said this earlier, with a conspiracy cap fully on,
using science and the phrase, "Did dinosaurs help build the pyramids?" I think we can state a
reasonable hypothesis that a Stone Age tribe used mammoths to mark this area. And why mammoths?
Because they didn't need mammoths, right? But it just makes the conspiracy theory work.
And why not mammoths, right? But the mammoths aside, the mammoths make it one fitness theme,
prehistoric creatures help build the pyramids. But two, I think that you don't need to have the
pyramids built in 10,000 BC for this to make, to work, because the pyramids could be built in
2,500 BC. The pyramids could have been built in 2,500 AD. The point is, is that they were,
that area was marked in some fashion in 10,000 BC to celebrate that star alignment over Egypt.
You can take this episode as a cautionary tale of what happens when you spend
too much time looking at Excel spreadsheet full of nonsense sayings, or you can take a look at it
and go, "That's what happens when you take a conspiracy theory and work backwards."
You can make almost anything sound plausible, even did prehistoric animals help build the pyramids.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true
crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great day, guys.
Bye.