The world is full of stories involving cursed objects.
Well recently, I came to possess what could possibly be a blessed object.
And then we meet a young woman who lives every day of her life in fear.
Her stepmother embodies all of the worst stereotypes of the fairy tale evil stepmother.
She's brutal, she's insane, and she wields dark magic.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carbiner, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun.
Just so, just so, just for full disclosure, I'm recording this episode just minutes after
I recorded yesterday's episode.
And so if you didn't listen to yesterday's episode, there was a ghost in the recording
studio.
There was a ghost in the haunted closet.
And the only reason I'm telling you that is because I'm still a little jumpy.
I went for a little walk, but I'm still a little jumpy.
So if this episode just abruptly ends, that's why.
Because I wet my pants and I ran away.
But someone who never runs away from a fight, walking in right now as a self-proclaimed dead
rabbit grandmother monster, give it up for Bonnie.
Yeah, Bonnie, come on in.
Woo, yeah, come on in, give her high fives.
Bonnie, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, I totally understand just help spread the
word about the rabbit radio.
That really, really helps out a lot.
And speaking of that, Bonnie's coming in with two of her buddies, Mark and Echo.
They actually were recommending the show to her.
So thank you so much, getting the word out really, really does help.
So Bonnie is the captain this episode, but Mark and Echo, you can both be second in command.
You can fight over who's wearing the cute little second in command outfit.
It's a Donald Duck outfit.
Bonnie, we're gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the dead rabbit dirgeable.
We're leaving behind dead rabbit command.
We are headed all the way out to my place.
I guess we're just circling the dirgeable around dead rabbit radio.
I know it's not the most spectacular journey, but I wanted to talk about this.
So I want to be honest with you guys, there's a lot of stuff that I do and I've done that
I don't talk about on this podcast and it's actually related to the podcast.
I still am pretty active in paranormal investigations on the ground, paranormal investigations, not
as much as I would like to be.
And then there are other stories that have happened to me in the past.
They're either just too bizarre to talk about or I don't really know how to classify them.
So there's a lot of stuff that I've done and continue to do that I don't talk about on
the show because I just don't really even know how to broach it.
And so this is something that I've had in my possession for a couple of weeks and I've
wanted to talk to you guys about it, but there's not a lot of information I can reveal about
it.
It puts me in a tight spot, but it's fascinating.
Absolutely fascinating.
I have come into possession of what I can only describe as a blessed object.
It's a wood carving.
It's a single block of wood.
I'll take a photo of it.
We'll use it for the image for this episode.
It's a single block of wood that someone carved in the image of the pioneer church.
That's a very famous, very old church in Portland, Oregon.
Let me go grab it.
I didn't want to bring it into the closet because this thing's crazy.
Let me go get it real quick because I got to get you some more information on it.
It is, let me sit down.
I need to leave the door open for a little light.
It is a wood carving of the pioneer church that was established in 1851 in Portland.
It's really called the St. John's Episcopal Church.
And this piece of art was made by Kent R. Smith in October of 1987.
And due to ongoing investigations and due to people not wanting me to reveal a lot about
this piece, I can't tell you where I got it.
I can't tell you how I got it.
And I can't even tell you about the miracle I witnessed with my own eyes in the vicinity
of this.
But this truly does seem like I'm going to have to take my word for it.
And hopefully I've earned that trust from you.
This is a blessed object.
I watched this perform a miracle.
And I don't know specifically what I am going to do with it.
I am bringing it to the McMinemans UFO Festival May 14th.
I will be there at a vendor booth.
DeadRabber Radio will have a vendor booth.
And we're going to have this object as well as some of the haunted objects I've collected
over the years.
The Veronica the Haunted doll will be there.
And then I have some paintings that whether or not those are haunted or those claims are
dubious.
I've never been able to investigate those myself.
But I'm bringing them.
And you'll be able to touch these items.
You just don't want to touch your haunted doll.
Maybe I'll touch your painting though.
But you'll be able to touch this.
And I don't really know how to classify this.
I watched this work a miracle.
That's one of the things when you do on the ground paranormal investigations and even
not on the ground in paranormal investigations.
Again being as honest as I can be with you guys.
I've covered stories and have been contacted by high ranking people.
This story was a UFO story.
And I was contacted by a highly established expert in the UFO community.
To reveal more information about that story.
And I actually turned that down.
I actually turned that down.
And again I'm not going to reveal who it was.
But the reason why I turned it down.
It was because they wanted to give me more information.
And they said but this information is just for you.
You can't share it with anybody.
And I responded back to them.
I said I appreciate the offer.
But the research I do now is to share with other people.
So I won't tell anyone who you are.
Like I won't say your specific name that you contacted me.
But that's the type of researcher I am now.
Now I used to be a researcher where I would just find the information to find the information.
And I've met some very, very diverse group of people.
I have contacted over the years.
Remember I'm doing this podcast.
This podcast has been around for four years.
I really love it.
I've been doing paranormal conspiracy research for 30 years.
I'm 45.
It's been more than that.
I mean when I was 12 I was just reading books.
That's all you had back then.
But in my 20s I was doing interviews.
I'm a journalist.
That was where I get that was my that was my area of study in college was my journalism.
So I would I would do interviews with people.
That knowledge they were giving me again not to tell anyone but I was on a journey for
knowledge.
But I've been contacted by people in the UFO field.
This one in particular and he wanted to give me some additional information but I couldn't
tell anyone.
And it's interesting as that was right is that offer was I said that's not the research
I do right now I do research to share with people but you do run into that when you are
a paranormal researcher and I know a lot of you guys just listen to the show for entertainment.
And some of you want to be UFO paranormal researchers and I'll tell you this.
Keep your mouth shut.
When you talk to people and they say this is off the record no matter how juicy it is
you do not share it.
That is just a rule that you should have going into it.
So when I was giving this piece and I saw its effects and all of that stuff I cannot
and will not reveal that information.
I also got to say this too one morning I woke up and I got an Eve this is awesome.
I'll tell you this guy's name.
I got an email I woke up one morning to an email from Lucas Haney Lucas Haney hopefully
I'm pronouncing your name right hopefully I pronounce everyone's name right.
Lucas Haney was the director of the movie Mope.
I did a whole segment on that I did a dead rabbit recommends on that movie and then I
did a whole segment on it and he emailed me and that was really dope a friend of his
listens to the podcast and passed it on to him.
So I get cool emails as well.
That was awesome.
When I looked at that email and I woke up I got I know this name from somewhere I'm
familiar with his name and I still recommend Mope it's such a fantastic film.
So I can reveal stuff like that but there are stories that I can't talk about and this
is one of them.
This object is blessed.
I don't know how it works.
I don't know when it works.
I haven't I haven't been able to replicate anything.
I will say this.
I don't blame it for the ghost whatever I saw yesterday in my closet but things do seem
to be weirder now that this is in my possession.
I'm holding it right now.
So yeah very very odd piece.
It will be this isn't an advertisement.
This isn't just an advertisement for the UFO Fest but it will be there.
It's a fascinating piece of work of just artistry.
You'll see it in the in the photo and then yes it it I've seen more evidence that this
is a blessed object than I have seen my other objects being haunted including Veronica the
doll I bought it on eBay as a haunted doll.
No knock against you Veronica at all but I haven't none of the paranormal phenomenon
that was supposed to be associated associated with Veronica's popped up but this is blessed
in some way.
I don't know how to access it.
I don't know how it works or why it works and I think these objects are far more rare.
I think these I mean you have people making fake haunted dolls and you have people making
fake blessed stuff you know by the stone will give you good luck but in the natural world
where this stuff actually may exist I think blessed objects are quite rare.
But yeah I wanted to share that with you if I'm able to document anything now that it's
in my possession now anything that I see or anything that is experienced with I can pass
on to you.
Fascinating relic could just be a block of wood but again I saw what could only only
be described as a miracle that was performed when somebody held this but again I don't
know how to access it I mean wouldn't it be amazing if this could you know heal people
or but how do you get it to work.
Anyways so that is here now I'm gonna take it out I'm taking it back out of the closet
this closet is some sort of vortex it really is.
I hope that story wasn't too anticlimactic for you I don't even know if you classified
as a story it was I can't tell you this but I have it but we'll see what happens again
a blessed object I really do believe they're quite rare.
Bonnie go ahead and we're gonna jump out of the dead rabbit dirgeable it was just tethered
it was tethered to dead rabbit command we weren't taking it anywhere Mark and Echo are
still fighting over the Donald Duck outfit and I'm gonna toss you the keys to the carbonar
cocktail we're leaving behind dead rabbit command and we're headed all the way out to
an old house.
I found this fascinating story posted online the other day and to do a little bit of setup
the person who's telling the story is a grandchild this grandchild who has a mom and has a grandma
and he says my grandma is one of the nicest women you could ever meet like she's this
tiny little like four foot nine little old grandma that kind of dotes on you she's just
type of woman anyone would want for their grandma you're looking at your grandma right
now you're like oh you're five six loser I want a four foot nine grandma get out of here
but you know just personality talking about physically right you're like oh I always had
a tiny grandma I put her in my backpack like baby Yoda and he goes my grandma was always
super nice and just very caring and my mom said the reason why grandma is so nice is
she was raised by a literal evil stepmother and so this guy is writing this story he posted
it online but he's telling it from the point of view of his grandmother and so we don't
have a location this is all anonymous right but we're gonna call the grandmother Sarah
and we're gonna call the stepmother Margaret we're going back in time here we don't have
a time period don't have a location but Sarah is a young girl and she's being raised pretty
much at this point by her stepmother Sarah's mom passed away and Sarah's dad his work required
him to travel for weeks at a time so in this household it was often just the stepmother
and Sarah this house seems to be in a relatively secluded location it's surrounded by a forest
and there's a river about five miles away that's the second closest water source is five miles
away this river the nearest water source is a well well in the backyard of the house but
Sarah wasn't allowed to get water out of the well the stepmom was so just cruel she wouldn't
let Sarah use the well she would tell Sarah that she'd have to walk down to the river
and she would tell Sarah you can't drink any water that's a delicious delicious water
you can't drink any of it and you can't spill a drop and I'll know if you spill a drop even
just a drop I will know Sarah because the head will tell me the stepmother often used
this as a ploy to get Sarah to cower in fear and to do whatever she wanted stepmother said
that she had a severed head that she spoke to and the severed head knew everything and
saw everything and with the knowledge the severed head gave the stepmother she would
dish out cruel punishments to Sarah now if Sarah disobeyed she got beat by the stepmother
if Sarah was bringing the water back and she took a drink or she spilled some she got beat
by the stepmother because the head told her that she had spilled some water but Sarah quickly
learned it didn't matter what she did even if she didn't spill a drop of water even if
she did everything this cruel woman said she'd still get beat because she's a cruel stepmom
right she's just a sadistic freak so it didn't matter what she did right but Sarah was also
constantly on edge because for a child and to never lie for a child to never disobey for
a child to do everything right but make a mistake right aligning and disobeying you do on purpose
but just making a mistake and the head told me you did that Sarah would have to wonder
how did my stepmother know so Sarah starts to buy into this idea that there's a severed
head somewhere the stepmom is talking to but as Sarah gets older she starts to not believe
the story right it sounds like poppycock sounds like something out of a fairy tale as Sarah
gets older not only does she stop believing in the head so much but she also starts to
become more assertive again that's something that kids do they're going to rebel against
authority figures but the beatings never stopped it wasn't that she got more assertive and
the stepmother got scared the beatings still continued but Sarah began sticking up for
herself a little more and the stepmother was taking notice of this one day the stepmother
says do you want to know how I got the severed head I was married before your father and
one day these bandits came to our house my husband was sleeping they took him out first
had a razor and a slittest throat while he was laying next to me I wake up and there
they are these bandits trying to get our riches and take care of any problem that could present
itself so they killed him and now they're going to kill me and they came at me with
razors and the stepmother showed Sarah her arms the stepmother's arms had long scars
in her flesh she says the bandits came to me and they sliced my arms open and they sliced
at my legs but I got away I ran out into the night and got away the authorities never
caught the bandits because in truth there were no bandits one night I took a razor to
my own husband's neck and slit it open while he slept spilling warm blood all over our
shared bed and then I took that same razor and sliced the cuts into my arms into my
legs and you can see those cuts can't you Sarah you can see what I'm willing to do to
get what I want I slit his throat I told people that the bandits had attacked us and they
believed me and then when I was in the clear I dug up my husband's body and took off his
head and that is the severed head I talked to that is the severed head that knows everything
because it's watching you and if you're not careful I'll do the same thing to your father
I'll slit his throat while he sleeps and cut off his head and use it as another dark instrument
in fact maybe I'll take your head off too Sarah ran out of the house tears streaming
down her face as her stepmother's laughter echoed throughout the house and Sarah took
off and ran across the field and ran into the forest and she ran and she ran until she
collapsed and later there crying herself in panic in fear in hopelessness she had no escape
from this woman and now she knew how truly evil her stepmother was Sarah laid against
the tree in that forest and cried and cried and cried until she cried herself asleep
Sarah woke up hours later forest was dark she had no idea what time it was but she knew
she was going to get beat up for staying out too late and she comes up with this plan she
goes maybe I can sneak into the house maybe I can get up into my room stepmother will
never even know that I was missing for a couple hours unless she talks to the head Sarah began
to creep back through the forest and she's kind of making a big circle around so now
she's coming up to the back of a house and she's moving through the the moonlit branches
walking towards her house and if her plan does not go off well she's walking towards
a beating and as she approaches the back of the house she sees someone standing next to
the well the silhouette is obviously her stepmother she's standing back of the well but Sarah can't
figure out why she would be there was she looking for her did the head tell her that
she was going to be coming through the back of the forest trying to sneak in but as Sarah
began to move slower and quieter through the tree line she hears her stepmother talking
and then she hears another voice answer she ducks down she's in the bushes now and she's
watching the silhouette of her stepmother at the well talking and then a very deep very
slow speaking male voice is answering and Sarah goes I don't really understand what
my stepmom was asking she the questions didn't make any sense she was asking these questions
that seemed just so bizarre and then she would hear this deep male voice respond she has to
be talking to the head and that head knows I'm here I'm so close I can hear them and
while my stepmom couldn't see me I'm hidden the head knows everything Sarah's terrified
she's waiting at any moment for the stepmom to turn around for her eyes to search through
the darkness of the forest looking for Sarah but nothing happens Sarah just continues to
hide and listens in on this conversation but curiosity starts to get the best of Sarah
she's hearing this other voice I need to see the head I need to see it I need to know I
need to know this thing is held my life in torment for so long I have to see what's going
on so Sarah gets down on her belly begins crawling across the dirt trying to remain
unseen but trying to get closer trying to catch a glimpse someone is watching Sarah freezes
the stepmother ducks down behind the well a few moments pass Sarah is perfectly still
she sees her stepmother's head kind of pop up from behind the well and kind of scan the
area looking for someone the stepmother doesn't see anybody and she hurries off into the house
Sarah is laying perfectly still her fear now is that the stepmother in the house has a
better vantage point of the field she can be hidden in any of those windows on this
estate looking out watching for a movement Sarah is petrified but then Sarah has another
thought I think she left the head behind Sarah waits there in the darkness too scared to
move but she has to know she begins crawling out of the forest she's crawling across the
field and she's inching ever so closer to this well afraid that her stepmother will
spy her at any moment he come running out but no one leaves that house and Sarah is
able to crawl all the way to the well and she sees a pile there pile of dead grass pile
of dead leaves she reaches her hand into this pile and she finds a handle slowly opens it
there's a secret compartment right next to this well it's about two feet deep and inside
of it is a wooden box has to be the head Sarah thinks has to be the head and even though
she wanted to get a glimpse of it when she was in the trees now that she's next to it
now that it's in her possession she does not want to open the box but she does look at
the box lifted up it's heavy heavier than she would have thought it was she lifts the
box up and she goes hello there's no response Sarah knows that she needs to get rid of this
whatever's in this box probably but she's still in a quandary she's in an exposed field
and she's carrying a black magic relic she's still just a kid if that stepmom comes running
out of that house Sarah's gonna get beat down and if the mom comes out with a weapon Sarah
will become a head in a box buried next to a well a soulless form trapped by sorcery
a slave to an evil woman's demented wishes Sarah grabs this box and she starts crawling
again she's dragging it across the soil dragging it back into the forest and once she is hidden
by the dark shadows of the trees she begins to run through the forest carrying this box
with her and she stuffs it into a hollow of a tree and there it'll have to wait she has
to get back home Sarah goes home and her stepmom is awake just sitting there the stepmom goes
where have you been Sarah goes I was crying I was crying I ran out in the forest and I
cried to myself to sleep and the stepmother just told her go to your room and as Sarah
is walking to her room she realizes that this is uncharacteristic for her stepmother generally
she'd get beat up she's not missing it but generally she would get beat up or at the
very least the stepmother would have said I'm going to talk to that head and if he tells
me you're lying you're gonna get beat up it was either always physical violence or threats
of physical violence but this night the stepmother just told her to go to bed the next day passes
uneventfully but when the sun sets and the moon rises when night has fallen on this estate
Sarah sneaks back out of the house this time she's prepared she's standing in front of
that hollowed out tree and that wooden box is still sitting there but still she can't
bring herself to open the box instead she destroys it she sets the tree on fire and watches the
flames devour its branches watches the fire destroy the box and she stood there and watched
until the flames died out until the box was destroyed the next morning she woke up her
stepmother was still in bed it's unusual so Sarah went into the stepmother's bedroom
and there the stepmother laid she was sick she was frail she seemed broken and as Sarah
was walking towards the stepmother's bed she gets a good look at her face she said it looked
like her face had been warped she said it seemed like her mouth was on one side of her
face not the front side that's where everyone's mouth is it's like she's laying down and her
face is like just warped and her lips look like they've been moved across her face now
obviously nowadays that looks like a stroke right that's what I'm thinking when I'm reading
this is the stepmother had a stroke and maybe she did maybe she didn't have a stroke we don't
know the medical reasons for this but after that morning the stepmother never recovered
to her full health she was always frail after that she was always weak and Sarah said at
that point the brute cutting and Sarah said at that point the beatings pretty much stopped
Sarah said she never opened the box and she never knew for sure that there was a head
there she said when she went back to the location at a later time she saw no bones there there's
no sign of a human debris so even she in her own mind knows what a skeptic would say you
never looked in there there might have never been a head in there could have just been
some boogeyman that she made up that's a logical answer right I know that story sounds like
a fairy tale that'd be the logical answer and she said you're right I never did look
in the box I had two opportunities to and I couldn't bring myself to opening it I didn't
with my own eyes see there was a head in that box but I know what I heard at the well she
wasn't alone out there a terrifying story of gothic horror right I mean obviously this
could be fiction someone could have written this and it's all made up it's presented as
a true story but the world of the paranormal this stuff tracks I'm have this blessed object
in my house and this would be the opposite this would be a cursed object an object created
for murder to spread mayhem like you literally can't get more of a cursed object than that
this man's soul cut this man's essence trapped in this dried up severed head forced to tell
this evil woman the sins of a young girl just a terrifying story really does harken
back to the days of old pagan magic but the thing about old pagan magic is that you sure
you can kill everyone who practiced it back then and you can destroy all of their sacred
sites you can wipe them from the history books but if you killed every mathematician on the
planet and burned every math book the math still exists and eventually someone will
rediscover it just like it was discovered in the first place someone will rediscover
it and just how the old magic and the old ways were wiped out as advancing religions
moved into areas and just completely annihilated anyone who practiced these old ways the magic
is still there the old ways still exist we just don't know about them you can wipe out
the worshiper but you can't wipe out the mechanics of the spell casting now it's possible that
this was just a ploy it's possible that the stepmother weaved this story all these years
to just keep Sarah under her thumb it's possible even that the stepmother was more crazy than
we think she was and she was doing both voices that's not completely unheard of either but
then how would she know all of the ways that Sarah had done bad things had lied had made
mistakes how would she have known that this story is just another reminder that in the
world of the paranormal there are fates worse than death in the real world there's some
pretty grizzly ways to die but you die and that's it but in the world of the paranormal
you could live your life a good man and then one night wake up choking on your own blood
because your wife slit through your throat with your own razor and as the world fades
the black and then that white tunnel appears in the distance of this void you find yourself
moving on to the afterlife but your journey towards the next step in reality is interrupted
by the sounds of your wife's voice chanting unknown words the next thing you know that
white light disappears and now you're just lost in the void a robust man turned into
a head in a box an earthly prison of wood and dirt and dead leaves is what separates
this man from entering paradise black magic kept him alive and a brave young girl freed
him the severed head never directly talked to Sarah but if it could say anything to her
I think it would say thank you.
Thank you.
(upbeat music)