Tonight a game show reveals a terrible secret
What would you do if you found tiny people taking a bath in your bathroom sink?
What and then we travel to West Virginia or a small creek
bubbling
through the dark forest
Actually has a powerful secret. Is there a ghost in West Virginia?
That can warn us whenever a president will be assassinated today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too feeling a lot better
I think you guys can hear that on my voice
Still have the cough that coughs been around for a couple weeks now, but we got a lot of stuff to cover
So let's go ahead and jump right into this now. This show is a daily show
So this is happening tonight, but this also takes place in Germany. So by the time I'm recording this at 7 p.m. On
March 24th by the time by the time I'm recording it. It's probably already happened in Germany, but still
That's our timely music news so Big Brother is the show where you get the contestants
They sit in the house and then like people get voted. I think I've I
Can't ever say that I've ever watched more than a few episodes of it, but they get voted out
I believe and
If they win money or something or they win the house
I don't know maybe the end the last person in the house actually owns the house
But it was a British show and then it was spread all over the world
Big Brother Germany is going on right now. There's a couple other big brothers going on right now and the the idea is this
10 people or whatever you're chasing any basic research
You get a group of people in a house
They're totally cut off from the outside world and they bicker and squabble and us
Normals us homo sapiens get to watch these guys 24 hour on camera feed
Technically, we're the big brother. We're the observing audience
But there's actually a big brother in the house that can give news alerts or it doesn't really give news alerts can
Prompt drama basically there's an overriding force in the house
So people get voted out of the house and then there's like this huge crowd
Because you go in and you're a nobody and then you come out and your celebrity people have been watching your antics for a week
Or two or three or four however long you last on the show
Yeah, you come out and you find out you have a fan base and or a bunch of stalkers, but
You know, I'm so we have two different things going on. We have a bunch of people isolated in a house
And they have no access to the outside world. They have no television. No news nothing the big brother show in Germany
It started on February 6th this season started on February 6th into that time
coronavirus you had like maybe
Couple dozen cases in Germany a couple dozen cases in America and stuff like that
They've had no news about what's going on in the outside world. This is there's a lot of stuff this messed up about this one
They're not telling them about it. They're not this is the gimmick. Okay, this is what they're doing tonight on IT on live TV
They're going to announce to these people who have been sequestered in their house since February 6th
They're like ladies and gentlemen for the first time in big brother Germany history
We're gonna let you guys know what's going on in the outside world. Whoa. What's it gonna be?
Everyone's sick. There's a there's a disease rampaging across the planet. Be like what?
I want to know that they're getting ready to announce that on live television tonight
There have been so when someone gets voted out of the house and other person takes their place
The people who have taken their place one person just entered the house a couple days ago. I hope they tested them
I hope they made sure the guy wasn't sick and they said you cannot mention what's going on outside at all
Even the pandemic especially the pandemic you can't say anything where they've been teasing
They've been advertising this tune into night where we let ten people know what's going on and that's horrible
That's horrible and that definitely raises the stakes for the show because now you definitely don't want to get voted out
Because you know where you're at you're isolated you're in the lap of luxury you have unlimited food and water now
You're like oh my god
I live in an apartment with like ten other roommates and they're super disgusting
Please don't vote me out like the stakes for the show are so high now
So and I guess I should say this when we had a similar thing here in the States
9/11 happened and they were doing a season a big brother and the rule was don't tell anyone what's going on in the outside world
But one of the girls in the house lost somebody in 9/11
So they did say hey guys
We got attacked by terrorists and they kind of broke the rules for that and they a couple other seasons are doing big brother right now
They've broken the rules for that but to let them know what's going on in the Canadian big brother. This was Crete. This is creepy
Canadian big brother right the way I described you remember the people get voted out and they leave and there's like a massive crowd outside the house
Charing you were nobody two weeks ago, but now we love you
Recently they had the vote out thing right and
They voted the person saying goodbye to him and they walk out the door and everyone's like getting ready to hear the abhorious applause
It's dead silent outside because there's no audience
Social distancing the Canadian television network or whatever didn't have anyone come they you can't be that close to anyone
So you know the gimmick of the show you've been watching it growing up and now you're on it
You know what to expect someone walks out the door. It's dead silent outside
The people are like
Because they have the hour-long special that you can watch on television and then you can watch them on webcams
When people were watching the webcam footage after the person leaves
People in the house are waiting to hear the roar and they don't hear anything
And then they're talking among each other later that night and the people are like why didn't why didn't we hear anything?
Another person's like, I know that was really weird right and they're yeah
Yeah, like did they like soundproof the house somehow which would be impossible, but
That's what they're thinking. That's the only thing you can think of like they must have somehow created some sort of did the Canadian television
use all that money they got from Degrassi High and build like a
soundproof
sci-fi dome around the building like what and they start discussing why weren't there anyone outside and
Then the big brother who like I said can speak in this intercom system over the house to talk to them as these people are trying to figure out
What could possibly be going on outside that there was no one there to greet the person exiting the house
The big brother voice speaks from above and says please stop talking
Everyone in the house just gets quiet
They did eventually a couple days a couple days later
Tell the big tell the people in that house what was going on and that's why there was no crowd
But again definitely raises the stakes for the show. You don't want to get voted off now
I wanted to cover that story for two reasons one
I think it's absolutely inhumane to make people fight to stay in a house when this is going on - I want to talk about a
Show called
Dead set this is and when I was reading this article
They talked about the show dead set dead rabbit recommends dead set it is a show
About the big brother house in Britain, which is where big brother originally started the big brother house and all these people
They're totally isolated
They're a bunch of like you get all these strangers put in this house together and they have 24-hour cameras on them and a zombie apocalypse starts outside
It's it's one of the best zombie movies I've ever seen it was actually a mini series
But I have it in the show notes. You can watch it on YouTube. I also got that movie dig. I said it was super rare to find
I found that on YouTube. That's also in the show notes for this episode as well, but I definitely watched dig
I watched the other night. It's still an amazing documentary, but dead set
It's and then they're in the big brother house and zombies are laying siege and this one girl's boyfriend is like
Trying to get to the big brother house to save her. It's really dark
So you may want to save it till after all this is done, but
Definitely it's on their dead set dead rabbit recommends dead set and dig. It's such a great documentary
I also want to say this
I've reached my level with
Coronavirus like news
I don't even read it anymore and I would suggest to most of you guys if you haven't reached it to stop reading it
I know the basic stuff. Don't take ibuprofen. They say don't take ibuprofen
Keep your hands washed it can stay now. They're saying it can stay on services for 17 days
But then you look into that and it's like it doesn't it's not contagious at that point
You know, I just know if I get cardboard from outside. I don't touch it for 24 hours anything
You know what the basic stuff I stopped reading all of the horror stories about it
I don't even look at the headlines. That's not true. I look at the headlines
But I got tired of clicking on these clickbaity links
And finding either fake information
That makes it far more horrible than it actually is
And there's a lot of that going on. It's really weird
I found stories that were 100% that were absolutely horrifying
I was like, oh my god
And then other people goes that twitter from that doctor who's telling you that story from italy that he's misspelling words
He misspelled his job
That's not a real tweet. This is fake stuff
But they're getting clipped in hammock. It's scary. Don't get me wrong. It is scary and you should
Social distance and if you can self-isolate and do all these containment things
I'm not saying that it's fake or anything like that
But what I'm saying is that we can overdo on the scary news about it. We need to know the basics
That's the same thing. There's one thing between knowing about ices and then watching ices be heading videos, right?
You get the point. There's a there's a brutal terrorist regime
Taking over swaps of the middle east. You should be aware of basic facts
But that doesn't mean you have to go start reading articles where it's telling you what they did
Stuff like that. So that's that's the approach I've taken towards this
I got the basic information and I think it was really overwhelming for me, honestly that first week and a half
We're still in it, but just reading so every hour looking for new articles to read about stuff
And it was really really affecting me. It was really getting to me. Doesn't mean I'm ignoring the danger
But it doesn't mean that I'm overwhelming my sense of self and my
My like you don't want to get too anxious about it. You just want to be careful. That's the main thing
This is something that we and now this is turn kind of preachy
But I just I want to be preachy right now because I don't I don't I know that we already feel isolated just in a normal life
And now that we actually have to stay away from people
We can feel it even more isolated
So don't ignore the news, but know your limit. I've reached my limit
Now I'll go to websites a look at the headlines
That's it. I've reached my limit. I'm doing what I can do
And I'm I'm no longer clicking on these horror stories of this person suffering from this or this
I got really too deep into it
And it was just too much people may say, ah, you're putting your head in the sand, but I say no
I think it's the same thing as
Knowing about a global terrorist group versus having to delve into what they do when they enter a village
You don't need to know that information. You just know that they exist
and stuff like that so
Know what the problem is know how you can prevent it yourself
Know what you can do to not get yourself sick or other people sick
And then go on you don't have to be clicking on every single creepy twitter or article that has a sad headline
Just keep going forward. Let's go ahead and move on to our next story though
Our next story takes us to Malaysia. So let's hop on board the carpenter copter. We're flying out to
Salingh Bahru Salingh Bahru
You guys know where that's at, right? I hope so because I don't I'm flying the carpenter copter. We're flying out there
It's march 1989. We're gonna meet a little kid, right? So nine-year-old boy his name's faizul. Affindi
And he's walking to school
He's a little backpack. He has it over one shoulder because he's one of the cool kids
He's not one of those lamos that has it over. I used to be that kid
I didn't want to put my backpack on both
Both shoulders because it looks super lame and then like your back starts to hurt
But the time you get to high school and the books are super heavy
You're like, oh you look like quasi moto every time you walk everywhere
But anyways, I still did it nowadays. I put it on both shoulders because I don't care
Faizul is walking on the street to school and he sees this guy walk by now
That's normal, right? A lot of times when you're walking on the street other people are walking on the street too
But this guy was only six inches tall and this little dude
Is just kind of walking by now here's the thing you're walking on the street you see a six inch person
Which is unreasonably small
Obviously there are people there are little people and they'll be like three feet two feet tall
But six inches is is not normal for anything outside of a uterus, right?
But you see a little six inch person walking on the street. What do you do quick?
Quick reaction time. What do you do now? I would
Probably like jump back
And then I would um regain my composure because I'm cool and I'd put my
Easily take my backpack off because it's only on one shoulder and then I'd get down on one knee and go
Who are you?
And I'd try to communicate with this six inch person
Faisal does what I think I think you'd basically have three reactions
You'd run away
Because it's super spooky you try to talk to the six inch dude
Or you'd grab it because anything that's small enough to grab now again. He's a kid
But I can understand why he grabbed it because actually no I can't because I think kids don't normally walk around grabbing squirrels and stuff like
I mean babies, maybe but I mean now that I think about it. What if this was just a six foot guy?
Faisal was walking on street. Would he be grabbing on it? Get off of me kid. What are you doing?
But he grabs the six inch dude the little guy little guy
bears his teeth and then begins super scratching him up
And scratches him up so much that fazal drops the dude
Guy runs into the bushes
And they're thinking okay, that's bizarre right a little feral, you know, it's not that he just scratched him up
Bared his teeth and then scratch him up
It wouldn't make sense for a six inch person to have some really good self-defense techniques
Not that it has to know like chokeholds and stuff like that, but that it would have claws
I wonder
No, that's not wait a second think about it
Small animals have claws and big animals don't right so like cats have claws
And then tigers have claws like tigers aren't small. Well think about okay
You have like birds they're tiny they have claws right, but then humans don't
And then cats have claws because you know, they're like claw on it
Mice and stuff like that
Why don't dogs have claws? Why don't dogs?
What would that be like good when they're like attacking bears and stuff like that bears have claws
They're pretty big that doesn't work in my hypothesis. But this is what I'm getting at hippopotamuses rhinos
Elephants they don't have claws
So I think the bigger you get the less likely it is you're going to have claws
If you have claws you need every advantage possible to have what if
Everyone says that cats are small tigers, right?
So like there's a bunch of tigers running around and they kept having
Having babies and the babies got smaller and smaller and that's where house cats came from
I'm going to give a different idea
You're like Jason that's nobody said that that's no scientific theory
You have what if all cats started off as little and then they got big and that's why they still have their claws
But then a thousand years from now lions and tigers will no longer have claws because they'll not need them
What do they use claws for anyways? They don't they don't really climb trees like
Why do bears have claws actually like isn't just because gorillas don't have claws, right?
So I I'm going to stand by my theory. I'm going to stand by my theory that the bigger the animal
The bear doesn't count the bigger the animal the less likely it is to have claws
Because if an elephant had claws is an elephant eat meat that might be the thing maybe it's meat eater
Wait, no, but rhinos. Oh wait. No, that's it. That's it
Meat eaters have claws and omnivores and herbivores
You have elephants being like ah rip and open but in every minute. Okay, so where was I at?
Oh, so so this guy must be a carnivore because he has claws. That's what I was trying to get at
I wonder if there's a carnivore. Never mind. I'm not gonna. Okay, so
That's that april 1989 one month later. Selang Bahru Malaysia. We're still here. We never left town
We've been eating their delicious noodles. I'm assuming that they eat noodles over there
We're eating noodles and rice and it's so super tasty
It's tasting so good in my little quarantined belly
tasting so yummy
We're gonna meet a dude named nor osmy mod jamal nor osmy mod jamal
He's walking home from school. It's coming the opposite direction, but the same area
I don't actually know if it's the same geographical area, but same town. He's walking home from school
He is sees walking across the street
Two six inch dudes one of them is actually a girl
So two six inch dudes one of them is wearing a brown shirt and shorts
Which is actually kind of comfortable because malaysian is pretty tropical
They're not dressed like the leprechaun. They're not dressing like big old hats and stuff like the jackets
That's actually a good point. The leprechauns dressed up like
Okay, wait a second. I'm thinking of the leprechaun from the leprechaun movies. That's not his actual
But leprechaun wears a jacket and you wear like big old socks and pants like pants like shorts
They're shorts, but he has like long so because irland is cold irland's cool
but if you had
Cryptids in more tropical areas, they'd be wearing like little sun hat and like
Bermuda shirt little short-sleeve shirt
You wouldn't want to see like if you are a cryptid if you were a mythological creature in a warm climate
You would dress accordingly. That's actually really interesting because it shows
Well, it shows one of two things
It shows that cryptids would have to maintain some sort of internal body temperature that they're also
Effected by the climate or that the people making up the stories make them up in a way
That's relatable to the people in their culture. i.e. if you were in irland and you were talking about a leprechaun
You wouldn't say he was he had a boogie board and it wears shorts and no shirt people be like
But it's run any freeze to death and why does he have a boogie board? What's a boogie board?
So it's one of those two things most likely the second one. Anyways, he's walking on the street
He sees two six inch people one of them is wearing a brown shirt brown shorts
the other one is wearing a brown shirt and a little skirt and
He sees these little guys and he does this is what I think would be more likely than reaching out and grabbing one
He starts chasing them
Now I said I would sit down and go. What's your name? But if it was like walk
I would also probably be likely to pursue them as well. I'd still want to talk to them
But that's a pretty natural thing. He starts chasing them and they take off into the bushes
But a few days later nor this kid nor is at home
So he walks into his bathroom and there's like you have like the bathroom sink
And he sees one of the little dudes just kind of hanging out sitting on like the porcelain
Just hanging out just chilling on his sink. What the world's going on?
And then he looks and he sees that the basin of the sink is filled with water and the other one's totally naked
Washing itself now. I don't know if it took like a sliver of soap
Aye, laddie. Gotta get clean irish spring. Maybe this is a really commercial for irish spring
The little dude is washing himself which
that
Would be awesome, right? I would do multiple things right there one. I'd get a camera now to be fair
That's not I'm not pervert. I'm not a pervert. I'm not gonna post these photos on found cryptids new dot com or like
Cryptids on camera stuff like that. I'm not trying to be a pervert because there's a there's a naked cryptid in my sink
I'd grab a camera for proof because no one's gonna believe you obviously
And then I would still try to talk to the guys, but then I would sell the water online a bunch of weirdos and be like
Hey guys, how would you like to buy water that a six inch person took a bath in?
And they would respond man or woman and I'd go
Doesn't matter a six inch person took a bath in this
Okay, it was the woman. No. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'll buy it to buy it. So anyways
He doesn't specify if it was the dude or the girl who was taking the bath
But we'll just assume just to make the story a little more sexy
It was a six inch woman in there
And so anyways, he's watching her take a bath and then he reaches in a court. This is the instinct
He goes to grab the girl in the sink
and surprise surprise
He gets attacked he gets bit really really hard and dropped sir and the two little people took off now
He goes to tell his parents obviously asked to explain why his hand is bleeding profusely. What happened to you?
I tried grabbing a naked woman. No mom. Don't give me that. She was only six inches tall
Okay, I'm not pervert. Well kind of a pervert. But what would you do?
He tells his parents this and this story I got both of these off of that website think about it docs.com
Historians with this sentence quote. He told his parents about the incident
But they did not believe him
Unquote isn't that the the tragedy that lives on forever
Haven't we all been there that moment where we got bit by a naked six inch woman and we went to our parents the people who love us so much
Mom dad. I got bit by a tiny person taking a bath in our sea
And then you being not believed that is the true tragedy of this world
Let's go ahead and move on to our I find that story funny. I like that story
I like little people running around I think it's cute. I mean the the constant assaults by the giants
Maybe not so cute, but I do find it fascinating and it makes you think what would you do if you saw a tiny person
I think I would try to talk to them
And probably take pictures of them and sell their bath water
But I don't think I'd be grabbing them all the time just because they're tiny because again
I don't grab mice that are running around. Let's go ahead and move on to our last story
We're headed out to west virginia all of this information I got from an article
I want to give credit where credit's due from a website called west virginia explorer
The article is horse creek ghost set to foretell the demise of presidents and it was written by david sibray
So let's hop back on board the car. Let's take the jason jelopy. We haven't been driving for a long time. We're in melasia
Fine. Let's hop back on the carboner copter. We're gonna fly out to west virginia. We're gonna learn about the horse creek ghost
april 8th
Major walter hansen and his buddy elisha miller. Those are some old-timey names for you are hunting
They're out hunting by horse creek in west virginia and they hear something the bushes turn around quickly
They spin around to face the noise think it's a deer an elk possibly an elk with claws
They've evolved they eat meat now and is the majors ready to face this evolution abomination
A woman steps out of the bushes
Dressed in all black clothes
soaking wet
She points her finger at the man and says
Lincoln will be gone
For the full moon rises
And they're like what because lincoln's still president and then she I don't know if she flashes away
Or she just kind of like points at him for a while then kind of puts her arm back down
This just stands there silently and then is kind of like i'm gonna i'm gonna go back into the bushes
She turns her walks away. She simply disappears now. It's 1865. It's not like you can just pick up a newspaper
Major Walter Hanson said it took him two months to find out that abraham lincoln had been shot
By the coward what was his name and i remember jimmy olson. What was that guy's name?
Lee Harvey olswald. No, that was the other guy
Who was the guy who shot lincoln not erin burr and then he jumped and he like
Fell day jumped and he like slid down a curtain all dramatically. What was his name? Dude. He was that actor
um
Who shot lincoln?
And then he ran and then he hid in a barn and then the authorities surrounded you're like jason
You know all this stuff. You you don't know his name. They said the barn on fire and he died
There's always been that big conspiracy theory that he didn't die in the barn
That he got away. What was his name?
Patton hallswald it started with an o. I think it had an o in it, right? I'm gonna google it here real quick
Had an o in it that that's specific. Let's see. Um, who killed lincoln?
What
What was his name perkins john wilkes booth see there's three o's in it. That's what was throwing me off
There's too many o's is throwing me off john wilkes booth shoots a ram lincoln
Uh, then does all that other stuff I said and may or may not have gotten away with it
But anyways now we're going to go to the year 1881
And this guy named clide purdew and his wife doesn't matter what her name is are driving are
Writing their horses or whatever down this same street by horse creek in west virginia
And this one's interesting. So the first time you had the woman i'm gonna assume she was hot coming out of the bushes
Dressed in all black dripping wet this one you still have the black clothing. So this thing comes out in a black shawl
That's still dripping wet, but this time it's a flaming skull and crossbones. It's kind of weird
They're driving down the road and they see this flaming skull and crossbones with a wearing a black dripping wet shawl
up here in front of them and the skeleton guy goes
James carfields going to be assassinated
Again, I don't know if it faded away or just kind of floated there for a while
And then they drove past it and they're like waving to it in the rearview mirror or they're on horses
So they were just I don't actually know whether what were cars
I was thinking that I was like cars who are around in 1881, right?
But like there was only like two of them and you're like Jason this might be your least informed episode ever
That that may be true, but I think cars were around in 1881, but nobody had him
So I think these guys are on horses. It doesn't really matter as no bearing on the plot
The point is is that a flaming skull and crossbones said that james garfields are going to be assassinated and he was
in 1881
There's this dude named max alberts. Tell me if this is the most depressing job possible
He's a traveling
I mean how much money could you possibly this is the albundi of the 1960s
He was a traveling magazine subscription salesman
So you would just walk around the country or drive around the country because I know cars were invented in 1963 or they were around
And you go knock on people's doors and says would you like to buy 12 issues of this life magazine?
Like how much money could you possibly make doing that?
It's ridiculous. I mean and then you basically or you can buy a magazine and all those little cards fall out of it
That you can do subscriptions and stuff like that for complete. That's so sad
That's so sad, right? But anyways, this guy maybe it was his favorite job in the world max albert's
traveling magazine subscription salesman
I remember once this this salesman came to my mom's house. Why was my house too when I was a kid?
She this traveling salesman came to our house to sell us like a vacuum cleaner or set of knives or whatever he was selling
Right and we had a little bowl of milk laid out
For like a local cat. It wasn't our cat was like a stray cat, but we fed him fit of milk every day
I mean if we were you know, we didn't know that milk causes cats to have diarrhea everywhere
But it wasn't our cats and we didn't care and so we'd set this milk out
And I remember one day my mom like I see her talking at the door and she's like no no
That's okay. We don't want anything and then she goes. Oh, oh, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry and um
Then she shuts the door and I was like what what happened and mom goes
Oh my oh my goodness. I feel so bad. I feel so bad. I go what what okay now
What's going on? She goes well this man came to the house and he all he looked down on his luck
He looked like things were not going well in his life and he's a door-to-door salesman
so that's a really difficult job and he already looked like things weren't going well and
Knocked on the door tried selling my mom something. She said no and then as he went to leave he stepped
he stepped
He stepped in the bowl of cat milk spilling cat milk all over his pant leg, right
It wasn't cat milk. It wasn't milk from a cat
But it was it was a sizable amount of milk. He got her all over his leg
And I remember my mom was she felt really bad about it because here you have this guy
Who's already things aren't going good for him now he has milk all over his clothes the worst material because you got to wash it
Right away. Otherwise you're going to start smelling like sour milk. It's all over his sock. It's all over his shoe
And my mom's telling the story and she can't finish it without kind of smiling, right? Because it's also kind of it's like
You're so down on your luck and then you get milk
And then you get milk all over you and we always we always felt super bad for the guy
But me and my brother and my mom always used that as
An end of a phrase whenever we were talking about bad news
We're like, yeah in johnny not only did he fall down and break his ankle
But then his girlfriend left him and then he stepped in some milk
Like that was always the way for us to end a phrase of a streak of bad luck was stepped in some milk
So maybe that maybe that salesman is listening to us right now
Anyways cat milk aside or just milk for cats aside
Max albert's is driving down the street. He sees the woman. It's a woman again this time
Dressed in all black soaking wet clothes now. This is interesting
Because all of these stories were a local legend in the area and then they became campfire stories that people told all over west virginia
And then they were collected
In a book of writings by a guy named jim comstock. He wrote wrote about this story in the 1970s. It's been
nationwide sense
This one's interesting because this one he's driving down the road and this phantom this woman walks out of the bushes
Dripping wet black clothes a phantom an oracle of death and the guy doesn't hear what she says
He's driving down the road and he sees her step out into the road
And she points at him and he's she's saying something but he doesn't hear what she's saying what what i'm sorry
Lay what she's like kennedy will die. He's like, well, I can't hear you. I'm like what car's super loud
She's like i'm trying to warn you kennedy's gone. He doesn't stop
He just keeps on driving and this story is included in this collection because in 1963 is when kennedy died
Now he apparently told people when he got to the next town of super weirders or haven't on the road
This woman popped out of the bush just started yelling at me
And I just kept driving and people are like, uh, and then kennedy dies that year
What's interesting about that part of the story is that
If the story is made up
That wouldn't be in there, right? If the story is 100% made up
You wouldn't add in a part where the guy doesn't hear the warning
Does that make sense like if you're I've always you I've used this for a couple different times a couple different episodes
If the story is made up, it should be more
A little more sensational doesn't have to be over the top
It doesn't have to be that she actually like hopped out of his glove box and said lee harvey all's well
It's going to shoot you don't have to have it that dramatic, but he should at least have heard the warning
Because if you're making it up you can change the facts here if you want
The fact that he didn't hear the warning at all and simply told someone later that this happened and everyone was like, oh
Makes me think that the story might be true
So that's kind of creepy that for whatever reason this location now there are five different places in west virginia called horse creek
Nobody knows which one
It actually is which again makes me if it was made up
You would say it was this horse creek and this location and these these are what happened each time
This is what the person said you can make it super specific because you're making it up out a whole cloth
This is the interesting part. Let's say that this is true. Let's accept that these stories are true
There's a location for whatever reason horse creek in west virginia
That a phantom will appear whenever a president is assassinated
If that story is true, you know as well as I do that there is a secret service agent
in that area now
The first time there was no secret service back when Lincoln was killed. You didn't know what to think about
And the second time when garfield died, you'd be like, oh, that's kind of weird, right?
But by the third time that it happens, you know if the cia is testing like psychic abilities
Walking through walls all this stuff. You know that someone in the government has heard these stories and said
Let's find this horse creek. There's only five of them
And if they don't know which one's which you could have someone in each location
You could easily pay someone to just fish all day long at horse creek
It doesn't have to be the same guy. They can work shifts, but you'd have someone there all the time
What would it really cost you have five locations?
Rotating shifts you have two to three people working a camp at a time. So for 15 employees
You could predict whether or not a president was going to be assassinated
And what's interesting is that the last sighting was in 1963
And all of these sightings the person warns of the death ahead of time
Let's them know it's coming
So is it possible that after 1963 word gets out about this urban legend of west virginia
Which is right in that hub of you have the pentagon you have Langley all that stuff. They say let's take some agents
Have them camp out
Big big ol they can sit there and make s'mores all day long big ol jamboree. We can come and visit on the weekends
And if this happens again
Will be warned in the 1980s the Reagan was almost assassinated he was shot
You got a secret as the guy was pulling the trigger putting bullets into Reagan
one of the secret service agents jumped in and stuck his finger in between the trigger
And the other part of the gun where the trigger goes he stuck his finger in behind the trigger
So another shot couldn't get out. That's one in a million
That's what training's for sticking your finger as it's going pop as that trigger's pulling back pop
Pop his finger goes in and jams the gun. He can't get another shot off
Is it possible that on that day people were prepared for an attack?
On the president. Is it possible that there are creeks in west virginia staffed by secret service agents?
Just in case
It may seem like a tall tale. It may seem like a campfire story
But when you have the life of the leader of the free world on the line
Is it really that much trouble to have a couple secret service agents fishing?
hunting and waiting
For a spirit to warn them of an assassination
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but i'm glad you listened to it today. Stay safe. Be kind. I love you guys
And I will see you tomorrow
You
(upbeat music)