Minnesota, a hellish winter wasteland in the middle of an otherwise beautiful country.
You would think that all sorts of ghosts, demons, monsters and UFOs would be drawn to
this bleak, war-torn state.
But surprisingly no.
Actually it seems to be one of the least haunted states in America and almost no cryptids.
Why?
Who knows.
But I was able to dig up a few ghost stories, one of the most obscure cryptids I've ever
covered and yes, this is an interactive road trip today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenterner, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
So this episode has kind of an interesting origin story.
So what happened was I did my birthday special episode and it started off with a story about
this little kid who tries to run a 5k and ends up winning a 10k.
Again, adorable story, don't really know if it fit the format, but it was my birthday
and I wanted to share that story with my friends.
Anyways, because I have a particular format for this show, KakiCube on YouTube goes "Oh
man, I thought the story was going to be paranormal because you normally cover stuff that is paranormal,
you don't normally just tell heart lifting stories.
Heart warming stories?
What's heart lifting?
That's terrible.
Oh, I feel like my heart was just lifted.
It was an uplifting heart warming story is what I went to say.
KakiCube said "I was a little disappointed because I thought the story was going to have
a paranormal angle to it, like he was going to get sucked into another dimension or he
was really running like instead of a 5k, he was running like a 5D, he's in the fifth dimension,
he's running through.
Like I'm everywhere at once, I'm both a winner and a loser."
And he goes "I thought it was going to be paranormal, I was a little disappointed because
nothing paranormal happens in Minnesota."
And I read that comment.
I was thinking that can't be true, like there has to be something in Minnesota.
I'm gonna prove you wrong KakiCube, I'm gonna prove you wrong.
And so I set out to prove him wrong and I actually, yeah, he's kind of right.
The first thing I went, I was going, they have to have monsters over there, right?
The place is like a hellish winter landscape.
There's not, there has to be some sort of goblin or ghoul hanging out Minnesota.
Mysterious Universe lists the Minnesota Iceman, a known hoax, it was basically a fake corpse
and a block of ice.
It listed the Mystery Monster, which was a rotted badger that washed up on the beach.
These are their cryptids.
There is a sea monster named Peppy, which is pretty stupid.
And then they have the Windigo, which isn't even Minnesota, that's like an immigrant cryptid.
It's from another part, it's from Canada, it's from another part of the country, he
just happens to travel through Minnesota.
So I was like, when I first saw that, I was like, whoa, KakiCube's right.
And it leads to a bigger question of why.
Why doesn't Minnesota have a lot of creatures?
And we'll get into that if I remember, because, well, let's get into it right now.
I think it could be one of two things.
I could think it could be that.
Minnesota is as old as the rest of America.
We have states that are newer and obviously the geography, it's not like there's a
giant hole there and then one day they're like, oh, it's filled up with sand.
We will call this Minnesota.
It's a very old established state, there are Native Americans there for a long, long time.
There's a lot of Native Americans still there, I think, maybe hopefully.
I hope there's at least some.
Anyways, what I'm saying is that it has a long history.
Why doesn't it have a lot of ghosts?
It could be that the people who live there don't really care about it, which will cover
that in one of these stories coming up, or they just don't really think it's that important
to talk about.
It could be that the places is really such an inhospitable place to humanity with its
cold, cold winters that not even a ghost, not even the undead want to live there.
The window goes like, oh, I'm going north for the winter.
I'm going to sunny, sunny Canada.
Lack and leaves.
Who knows?
But let's go ahead.
I took up his challenge and I go, there has to be something out there.
Let's take a look at some of these guys.
I dug up, get it?
Because they're ghosts.
Okay.
Pick a number between one and five.
Now let's hop on board the Jason Jalopy.
You're like, haven't picked my number yet, bro?
Well, hurry up.
Hurry up.
Pick it.
Okay, you got it?
Okay.
Let's hop inside the Jason Jalopy.
We're going to drive around Minnesota.
So I hope you have like eight layers of clothes on.
Do they even have a summer?
I don't want to spend the whole time ragging on Minnesota.
But whenever I hear about Minnesota, it's in conjunction with the Twins, the famous
Siamese Twins that ran for governor, or it's like bleak cold winters.
Are there any sitcoms that take place in Minnesota?
Are there any movies that take place in Minnesota?
Okay.
So we were driving through Minnesota and we come across the soap factory.
Which sounds, I mean, come on.
And then the teenagers got lost in the abandoned soap factory.
What?
I'd be like, yay, I'd just be spraying water everywhere.
The teenagers chasing me. I'd get in a giant bubble and float away. Not scary.
But anyways, soap factory, one of their most famous, we're in for a while to ride on this
one guys.
Because I really had to dig for these.
These are the most intriguing.
A lot of them were just a ghost walked by a house in 1874 and it's haunted.
That's how lame the ghosts are in Minnesota.
These ones are kind of cool though.
Anyways, as the story continues, I'm floating away in a bubble going, haha, and there's
like this haunted doll shaking its fist at me.
I'm floating away.
You're not floating away.
You didn't come up this plan.
You got attacked by the doll.
But anyways, back to the real story.
We're in the soap factory.
This is on, I'm sure, I think I can give out this address.
I'll give out the street.
It's on 2nd Street, Southeast, in Minnesota.
Oh, I guess I'd probably need this city.
I'm assuming it's me.
Whatever.
Just look up soap factory.
The links are there.
There we meet a man known as Adrian Lee.
He's a paranormal investigator.
My favorite job occupation.
And I'm reading this article and they're like, yes, the soap factory is one of the most haunted
places in Minneapolis.
Adrian Lee, paranormal investigator says, here's one of his quotes, "One of the most
paranormal thick environments I have ever had the displeasure to investigate."
No one's making you do this.
You don't have to sound like a snobby art critic.
I imagine walking around a haunted house rubbing his finger over the bookshelves and like testing
the dust.
I hate this place.
He calls it bordering on the demonic.
And I love this line in the article.
It says, Lee doesn't go in without a couple of pastors.
So apparently this psychic investigator, paranormal investigator, whatever, has on-call multiple
pastors.
Like he picks up the phone.
He has like the Bible phone.
He picks it up.
He's like, it's time to go boys.
And they're like going down a fireman pole.
They live in a giant chapel.
They're going down the fireman pole, driving away in their chaplain mobile.
That's a stupid name.
Bible mobile.
Whatever.
They're driving away in a Bible themed vehicle.
The Bible mobile.
I already said that one.
Anyways, anyways, the joke's over.
I love the fact.
He's like, it's demonic, one of the most paranormal-y, blah, blah, blah, blah.
So he says all this stuff, but this is actually like, well it's not anymore, but at the time
when Adrian Lee was kicking down the door with his team of pastors posing in the doorway,
ready to confront the demons, it was an active artist space/workshop/residency.
You could stay there and you got to stipend and you could paint or do your Ovent Guard
dancing or shoot paint out of your butt hole or whatever form of art you chose to do.
And the most demonically possessed place in Minneapolis.
That's a problem with this narrative.
He's trying to build it up as being like this horrible place that smells of sulfur and you're
like, no, that's just the guys over there, they don't shower.
It's part of their art.
And they roll in sulfur and you're like, ah, they eat a lot of eggs.
So you go, that's not scary.
And that's what I was thinking too.
I was like, that's not scary.
And at the same time, the article I was reading this from must have thought, yeah, it's not
scary, isn't it?
That's not really that scary.
So they added this part.
While factually true, let me read this to you.
So actually, let me start off.
It was originally a soap factory.
It wasn't some nutty art commune that became the soap factory because it's a funny name.
It used to be a soap factory.
Then it shut down and then a bunch of Bohemians took it over and now Adrian Lee is showing
up and now the place is closed at this point.
But anyways, it's like office building.
But anyways, it was used to be a soap factory and to make soap, you needed animal carcasses.
The article is like, isn't that spooky?
Listen to this quote.
The flow of bloody skins through the factory rivaled the current of the Great River next
door.
That's a bit of hyperbole.
You've got a raging river and all these skins go, pfft.
People are rafting on the skins.
And at the turn of the century, the building's appetite for flesh made it a repository for
stray dogs that the city paid to be rounded up and strangled.
That's a rumor, very, very popular rumor in the area that a lot of their sk- think about
it, you're an industrial soap factory.
So you have orders that have to go out every single day.
There's not enough stray dogs in the city to last more than a week or two.
If that, they're obviously ordering animal hides from slaughterhouses.
They're not sitting around and they'll be like, "Oh, Jared doesn't get back with those
thousand dog skins.
We're closed!"
And everyone's like freaking out.
It was an industrial scale soap factory.
But anyways, I'm sure a couple of dogs ended up in there, but I don't think that was their
bread and butter.
Or bread and blood-er.
So anyways, then it goes, 'cause even that, the article knows that that's not a really
good selling point.
The article literally says after that sentence, "Not gruesome enough for you?"
Consider then that before the warehouse was built, the site was home to a small business
that produced artificial limbs for soldiers wounded in the Civil War.
That's some creepy stuff.
I'm like, "What?"
That's quite noble.
That's odd.
I'm not...
When I walk by a guy with a prosthetic leg, I'm not like, "Where's his real leg?
Is it a ghost somewhere?"
And if I worked for a factory that made metal hands and legs, I wouldn't be like, "Oh, I
wouldn't be scared."
I'd be like, "I'm doing a good thing.
I'm doing something for people who lost their limbs fighting for the nation."
It was the Civil War.
It wasn't like some lame war that happened.
It wasn't like some French Indian war or whatever.
It was the Civil War, the defining war in American history.
Anyways, history lesson's over.
So you're walking through the soap factory.
I'm floating in my bubble.
I'm still in my bubble.
You're like, "Damn it, Jason.
Dahl's chasing you everywhere."
I'm floating up in the bubble.
You're looking for a pin and a straw to shoot it down.
I'm like, "He he he."
I hit all the pins.
I have them all with me.
I'm holding all of these pins in my hands.
And I go, "If you picked number four," you're like, "Oh, I forgot we're doing this
gimmick."
I'm like, "Yes, we are doing this gimmick."
If you picked number four, this is your resting place forever.
A place, and you have to live through all stages of it.
So first off, you start off as a noble handyman and you get to build the first cybernetic
arm for George Washington's great uncle who was still alive during the Civil War.
Wait, no, it'd be his great ancestor.
Anyways, you're able to build him a robot arm.
You're like, "This is a cool fate."
But then you flash forward to the soap factory days, but you're the dog and you're running
through a sea of skin and flesh and you're trying to hide under all the flesh as meaty
Minnesota hands reach through the flesh trying to grab your fur and you're all scared.
That's dark.
Okay, let's get out of that one.
Let's get out of that one.
You're disappointed in me.
Even the dolls looking up at me in the bubble and being like, "Dude, that's too dark."
Okay.
So the worst fate of all, you're a struggling artist sitting in an abandoned soap factory
trying to paint something and you're trying to hit the brush against the easel.
Not the easel, you're trying to hit the brush.
That's why you fail at your art because you don't have a canvas.
Anyways, you get a canvas.
You realize you're mistake.
You go get a canvas, but as you're painting on the canvas, you see a little bloody paw
print appear on the painting.
You're like, "That's not scary."
A little bloody paw print goes away and you're like, "Oh."
And then from behind you, you smell sulfur and you turn around and you think it's just
your buddy Jake, but it's a dark cloud and you suck it up.
And then you become a famous artist.
The most famous artist to ever come out of the soap factory.
You've never thought you could be this famous, but it's really the demon in control of your
body and you're just a witness to all of the fame and all of the luxuries and all of the
horrible things he does with your body late at night.
How long is this episode to run so far?
Oh geez.
Okay, so let's go ahead and move on to the next one.
We got to blow through this here.
What's the next one?
Geez, that took forever.
Hop back in the car.
We're going to First Avenue.
So I think it's nearby.
There's a place called the Dancerteria.
We're going to the Dancerteria.
The Dancerteria is not a cafeteria full of dancing.
It's actually a dance club, the Dancerteria.
Now I don't know if that's what it's called now.
I think actually it's called something a little more hip.
I think it's called First Avenue.
But anyways, it used to be Dancerteria.
Maybe it's still, I don't know.
Anyways, back a long time ago.
Super specific.
It was World War II.
Everything was swinging and jazzy and a young beautiful woman was in love with a dude.
That dude loved her back.
They kissed and they held hands and then he goes, "I have to go fight World War II."
And she's like, "What?"
And she's not really a part of it.
She had no idea.
So he sat down and he explained the rise of Nazi Germany and imperialism.
And when they got to the Pearl Harbor part, she was totally like shocked.
But anyways, eventually, after about an hour long discussion on this thing, he's like,
"Oh, by the way, I'm leaving right now.
We could have been making whoopie, but I had to tell you about World War II."
So anyways, he leaves and she's like, "I hope he comes back to me."
Now obviously this is a ghost story, so you know that he's not.
Because he doesn't.
Now he's not the ghost.
This young woman, he dies during World War II.
And she's like, "I don't know why he died."
And they're like, "He died fighting for the country."
She's like, "What?
What do you mean fighting for the country?"
They hadn't explained it to her.
But anyways, she's so heartbroken over the fact that her lover died due to unknown circumstances
that she's at the dance ataria where she loved to hang out and she goes, "I gotta kill myself."
And what's weird is, we've covered this on another story before, not this particular
incident, but this same type of death.
This young woman goes into the women's restroom, goes to the fifth stall, and hangs herself.
How, and this is what I said in my original episode, how do you hang yourself in a bathroom?
I understand how it's possible.
You have to use your underwear to do it, and you just kind of lean over and choke.
It's very, very painful, and it takes a long, long time.
But it's possible.
That's generally how people kill themselves in jail.
When you hear someone hung in jail, they're not thrown an old-timey noose.
Sometimes they'll use bedsheets and they'll wrap it around a bar.
But it's the same thing.
You basically put something around your neck and lean over.
Don't do it.
It's quite awful.
But it's possible to kill yourself in a bathroom.
I don't understand why you would do it in a bathroom.
If someone said you have to kill yourself, I would go, I would kill myself in the most
beautiful location ever.
A movie theater showing Transformers 3.
But I want to kill myself in a gross, disgusting place.
Like at least let me see the sunset.
I don't want to game myself, not only in a restroom, but a public restroom.
Their last moments are thinking someone really needs to clean that toilet.
Ugh.
Horrible.
So, she does this.
Now, if you go to this nightclub and you go into the fifth stall, this is terrifying to
me.
This is honestly the scariest ghost.
I think it's one of the scariest ghosts possible, other than a ghost under your bedsheets with
you.
That can be kind of sexy.
But going to the bathroom and looking up and seeing a full-bodied apparition standing
in front of you.
Because, for a couple reasons.
One, you're going to the bathroom and it's always creepy when someone's in there with
you.
Two, there's not a lot of room in a stall, so it's not like I'm in a graveyard and
I'm looking at a ghost far away and I see the little light.
Like, we're knee to knee.
And I can't run without doing several actions.
I can't, I gotta finish going poop.
And then I'll probably have to poop more after seeing the ghost.
But you have to finish wiping is optional in this situation, to be honest.
Like if there is a ghost in front of you, I'm not worried about whether or not my butt
is going to itch.
10 minutes from now.
But you still gotta pull your pants up, open the door and get out.
And there is a ghost with a bent neck in front of you.
You don't have a lot of, like you're basically jumping out of there.
Now luckily, I don't go to the women's restroom, so ladies, this is your deal.
But now, she is known to be seen also on the dance floor.
Along with what the article called, and this isn't backpacker verse by the way.
This isn't backpacker verse.
This is like Minnesota Monthly.
So you can see where this is headed.
This is the actual line.
She dances on the dance floor, quote, along with other legless ghosts.
Where did her legs disappear at any point in the story?
And more importantly, how does a legless ghost dance?
Is it just a torso swaying back and forth?
So you're a ghost, you're trapped in a public bathroom forever, one of the worst places
for a ghost to live.
And then eventually you go out to the night club and you're thinking, oh that's cool.
You can listen to music.
Yeah, remember she's a World War II ghost.
So she's like swinging and jazzing to like Benny Youngman and Bobby Darron and whoever
else.
Now she's in the dance club and her and her legless ghost are showing up and they're
like, oh I wonder who's playing tonight.
And it's 2019 and they'll be like, hey everyone, welcome, anal snot.
And what are the ghosts, your musical tastes are pretty set, honestly.
Like people don't radically change musical tastes, especially after they're dead.
So if you chose number three, you walk into the women's restroom, the lights flickering
on and off.
If you're a guy, this might be a little awkward, but you still gotta do it.
You count the stalls, you go and you sit on the fifth one, it keeps going dark.
Nothing happens.
You're like, oh that was interesting.
You pull your pants up or assuming you're a girl, put your, what do girls do?
Do they take their dresses off when they go to the bathroom?
I guess they just lift them up.
I guess not all women wear dresses.
Anyways, yeah, like if you have like a skirt that unzips, do you unzip your skirt and put
it around your waist?
What?
I never even thought of that.
Anyways, so the women do, they do, men and some women put their pants back on and you
walk out of the bathroom.
And then you encounter Slippy.
Because there's also another ghost there.
There's a staircase that descends down into the basement of the dance atyria.
There's a ghost down there named Slippy.
And Slippy has a unique power among ghosts.
Very very rare power.
Seen it a couple times.
Slippy can manifest items into our world.
So as you're walking down the stairs, you see a balloon just appear in front of you, slowly
starts floating towards you.
But as you go to leave the basement, the door slams and the balloon just floats closer
and closer and closer to you.
And then pop!
Everything is pitch black.
And that is when you learn why so many ghosts have lost their legs.
I'm making up this last part.
This part's not true, but the balloon pops with such velocity.
Both of your legs explode off of your body.
And for the rest of time, you have to just wiggle your torso in midair to the sweet,
sweet sounds of terrible independent music.
You're like, "Oh no, oh no, another Maroon 5 cover band.
This is so horrible."
I guess actually they wouldn't play there.
They'd be at the state fair.
But anyways, you're trapped in the dance atyria.
Okay, let's move on to...
Let's move on.
Let us move on with this now extra long episode of Dead Rapper Radio.
I really gotta stop doing these.
I shoot for a half hour because I know how valuable your time is.
I try to keep them short.
But we've had a bad luck recently.
Anyways, I'm having fun.
So I hope you guys are having fun too.
But we'll get back to our normal schedule, because this episode, there's no way this
episode's 30 minutes.
So let's go ahead and hop back into Jason's Lappie.
If you pick number three, number four, you guys are toast.
One of you guys, what happened to the first one?
I don't even remember.
Second one got his legs exploded by a balloon.
The first...
Oh, soap factory, soap factory.
So anyways, you're trapped in.
The rest of us hop in the Jason's Lappie.
We're driving to a place known as Grey Cloud Island.
This is in eastern Minnesota.
What's interesting about Grey Cloud Island, first off, not an island.
It's not an island at all.
I had to look it up on a map because I had a sneaking suspicion.
Because I read in these articles about Grey Cloud Island and other than calling it Grey
Cloud Island, they never specifically said, "Well, the island is situated."
They never referred to it as an island.
There is a strip of land.
It's not super wide, but there is a strip of land connecting it to the mainland.
Not an island.
It may have been at one point, but it's not anymore.
So change it to Grey Cloud Peninsula.
Has a ton of Native American burial mounds.
This was a kind of a sacred spot for them.
There's a bunch of burial mounds there.
Now there's a giant gravel factory, which people assume have just destroyed tons of
archaeological stuff there.
A bunch of bodies getting chewed up with the gravel.
That's why when you're riding your bike super fast down the road and you just like flip
off of it and you can't figure out why that piece of gravel came from a haunted burial
ground.
It does have some interesting things, though.
That's why I'm covering it.
One, this would be an interesting game to play.
I don't know how true it is.
A couple of people have stayed to this, but it seems like it could be some sort of optical
thing.
There's a row of 12 graves.
When you walk down the row and you count them, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, and
then you turn and you walk back the other way, there's 13 gravestones.
Now obviously there's not.
And I guess like the 13th gravestone is supposed to be your gravestone or something like that,
but obviously there's nothing paranormal going on there because again if it was and
it was that easily replicated then it would be completely steadied by science.
They're like there's a dimensional shift.
Something appears when we turn around.
It would be complete.
It would be all over the news.
But it's interesting because it's either completely made up or it could be some sort
of visual trick where you don't see the 13th gravestone when you're walking by originally
or it could just be a perspective thing.
I think that's kind of interesting.
But it has two things that I find really, really interesting and that's why we're going
to Grey Cloud Peninsula on this one.
One, it has a population of about 300 people and they hate ghost hunters and this is considered
like a sacred area/full of ghost stories.
But they don't want any ghost hunters.
They run them right off their territory.
The graveyard is locked down.
You can't even go in the graveyard unless you are related to a dead person in the graveyard.
No visitors allowed.
That always makes me suspicious because it would be an easy way to get that sweet, sweet
tourist money.
By saying, "Yeah, yeah, we're haunted.
You pay five bucks, you go to the haunted graveyard."
That always makes me suspicious when people don't want to do that.
But really the most consistent rumor about Grey Cloud Peninsula is the idea that it's
run by the Ku Klux Klan or a satanic cult.
It goes back and forth.
But the real reason why these people are super secretive and they want to keep people off
of their land isn't because they don't want a bunch of teenagers throwing beer cans at
green lights floating by.
They're actively engaged in cult activity or that's where the Ku Klux Klan in Minnesota
hangs out to do whatever they do nowadays.
I don't even know the Ku Klux Klan.
It seems like such an archaic group.
But anyways, that's the rumor going on right now.
So people tell stories about being chased off by residents and having drones fly over
their head, hiding in the bushes.
And a lot of these people say, "I went there to go see this green light."
And then this white pickup truck started chasing me.
Now, the white pickup truck could, apparently that's like a common thing.
If you go there for any amount of time, a white pickup truck starts following you around.
Some people say it's security for the gravel company.
Other people say it's the Klan or the cult.
But a lot of these stories are out there of people like hiding in the bushes as like
neighbors are looking for them.
And they're like on raid.
The one guy was saying he could hear a woman talking on a radio to somebody else being
like, he was saying it sound like she was looking for him and she was communicating her location
to somebody else and all this stuff.
So anyways, that's a myth that's going on.
So if you picked number one, you're outside of the Jason Jalopy.
You're standing in the middle of a giant gravel pit.
You're like, oh, there's no way I'm getting out of this.
And you start trying to climb up and gravel just keeps getting kicked out from underneath
you.
And you're like rolling down.
After about three days, you finally crawl out.
Actually, the next morning, the workers show up and they're like, what are you doing at
our workplace?
And they help you out.
But anyways, you still don't have a car.
So you're walking around Great Cloud Island and you see 12 gravestones.
And you're like, oh, this part's interesting.
You start walking and you count them.
And when you count up to 12, you turn around and now it's nighttime.
Big moon in the sky.
You see the 13th gravestone and you're like, that's the second most unusual thing that
just happened to me.
The first one is the massive time jump.
And around that time, you see a bunch of people come out of the woods and black robes.
They're not white robes because I'm not going to make jokes about the clan chasing you.
But it's a little more sensitive than that.
These guys have black robes.
They're like, we are not affiliated with any racist organizations.
Yes, we are sane worshipers and we are going to kill you, but we're not going to kill you
because of your ethnicity.
We're going to kill you because we're evil, evil, demonically worshiping people.
And you're like, oh no, at least I'm not being killed because of something I can't control.
And then as you feel the knives going to your body, you feel a little bit better because
you know that they're equal opportunity murderers.
I really had no way.
I have no other way to end that one.
Sorry if you picked the number one and you expected a racist cult to kill you.
I don't think you guys realize how on the, you guys might actually how on the seat of
the pants this show is.
I just write notes and then just talk.
So sometimes I realize as I'm talking, I'm like, oh wait, am I going to have to have
the clan show up at the end of the story again to do something funny?
Yeah, that was, yeah.
Anyways, let's go ahead and move on.
How long is this?
Okay.
So let's go ahead and move on to our next haunted spot.
We got two more guys.
We're almost done.
We got two more.
Okay.
So let's move on to our next haunted spot.
Sorry commuters who only have a 20 minute drive to work.
This is a two-parter for you.
We're going to St. Anthony, Minnesota.
And I think that might be where the, the 5K took place if I remember correctly.
Probably don't, but I think that's where the 5K took place.
And after all of our adventures, soap factory guys showing back up covered in animal carcasses
like Conan the Barbarian, then the Danzatiria guy shows up, no legs, so he's just kind of
floating.
He's a disembodied spirit floating around.
Great cloud dude who just got taken out by the cult shows up, suspiciously wearing black
robes.
Well, what?
Why are you wearing those?
Oh, nothing.
What happened to the guy at the soap, the soap factory?
I forgot.
He wasn't wearing animal skins.
He became possessed by the demon and was like killing people at night or something.
Anyways, anyways, he's here too.
Whatever.
We're all at Dairy Queen.
We're all at Dairy Queen in St. Anthony.
And now we, now when a Little League team wins a game to go to a pizza parlor, when
we are all murdered by ghosts and/or non-racist cults, we go to Dairy Queen.
Now at Dairy Queen, this is Haunted Dairy Queen.
This is just product placement for Dairy Queen.
I used to work at Froster Freeze, which was bought out by, I don't have enough time to
tell those stories.
Sorry.
So anyways, we're at Dairy Queen.
So here are the signs that this Dairy Queen is haunted, according to multiple articles.
Okay, I'm not making these up.
These aren't jokes.
We're in this Dairy Queen.
The first thing we do is we hear children laughing.
"Oh, we look around.
There's a bunch of kids behind us."
We're like, "Oh, okay.
That makes sense."
We order some blizzards and the receipt comes out and they go, "Okay, you guys ordered five
blizzards.
Sorry, the receipt here said you ordered six.
There's a free blizzard."
We're like, "What?
We've never been in a fast food restaurant where an order was wrong."
We're looking at each other.
Oh no.
Mysterious cold spots in a Dairy Queen.
A restaurant that specializes in ice cream.
Sometimes it gets cold in there.
A sign of a haunting, according to multiple articles.
Now the last one is a little more haunted-rific and that's where the employees hear names,
their names being called when no one else is around.
So it could just be that you're 16 and you have your listening to XXXxtentacion in one
ear and your boss is going, "Jeremy!
Jeremy!
Turn around!"
And you're like, "What?
I think I heard something, dude."
He threw his headphones out.
"What?
Someone was just calling my name."
"Yeah, it was me.
What?"
"Your orders are always wrong, dude.
We keep giving out free blizzards.
What, dude?"
I mean, okay, it's most likely not haunted, but it was reported multiple times this Dairy
Queen was haunted.
So if you picked, you're like, "Dammit, Jason!"
If you picked number five, you're trapped in a haunted Dairy Queen.
Okay, here, we'll make it even better than that.
Your soul.
Because I could be trapped in a haunted Dairy Queen.
I could do that.
But anyways, because you'd be going down, some of them have the playgrounds and stuff,
you're all, "Wee!"
You're popping out of the balls.
Kids are like in the ball pit and you're like, "Bleh!"
All the time.
It would be hilarious, but we're gonna make it scarier for you because otherwise that
one was kind of weak.
If you picked number five, your soul is turned into a waffle cone, right?
So it's like all twisted around and you're all like, "Never mind.
Never mind."
If you picked number five, you're just in a haunted Dairy Queen and every Sunday night
you turn into a haunted waffle cone and somebody eats you and then you turn back into a regular
ghost.
And then you come back and now you're the ghost of a waffle cone.
So now you can't even hop out of the ball pit.
Dun dun dun.
Sorry, dude.
That one.
I thought I was gonna be able to come up with something, but to be fair, I didn't even
think about it.
So let's go ahead.
There's four of us who aren't waffle cones.
If you picked number five, you are a waffle cone.
And we're gonna walk to the Minnesota State Fair.
But we're all getting our waffle cones unless you are one.
No, then you'll have a little tiny waffle cone as well.
You got a little arm.
We're walking to Minnesota State Fairgrounds.
Now obviously if you picked number two, this is you.
This one's kind of long, but anyways, this one's weird.
It's a little story I like to call Curse of the Pigman.
Now apparently, I didn't know this.
Pigman is a very popular last name.
And it seems to be especially popular in Minnesota for people who have bad luck.
October 4th, 1777.
Come on, get 'em boys.
It's the Battle of Germantown.
It's the American Revolution.
Stab a dude in the neck.
Come on, keep going.
Let's fight them British.
Ah, guys are getting gutted, right?
And in this fight is John Pigman.
He's actually leading the fight.
Come on boys, follow the old Pigman.
Let's do this, you skewering British dudes.
We used to be related.
Not anymore, you British dudes.
Kill 'em.
Anyways, after the bloody battle is all over with, John Pigman goes, "Oh, that's pretty
dope, dude.
Kill 'em bunch of dudes.
Fight 'em from a country."
Now, while he was off fighting and becoming a war hero, which he was remembered as, his
wife and his idiotic son were left back at the farm, and his son was a dummy, so the
farm went into debt.
And eventually when John came back, he lost all of his land and was thrown in debtor's
prison, which was a thing.
If you had debt and you couldn't pay it, they threw you in prison, which it's luckily isn't
a thing, because otherwise I'd be doing 25 to life.
But now we're jumping into the year 19-- that's bad luck, right?
You become a war hero, come back thrown in debtor's prison, because your stupid son doesn't
know how to plant corn.
1911, there's a dude born-- oh, that guy was from Minnesota.
That all happened in Minnesota, I forgot to say that.
This is the curse of the Pigman.
1911, there was a guy born in Minnesota.
His name was Melvin Lewis Pigman.
His nickname was Fat.
So his nickname was Fat Pigman.
Real guy, real guy.
1924, you like Jason?
That really-- all the only unlucky thing.
If your nickname was Fat Pigman, that is about as unlucky as you can get.
1924, the curse of the Pigman strikes again.
And trust me, I'm going somewhere with this.
I'm just not going to talk about it.
Anyways, just trust me.
1924, HF Pigman.
Which I'm pretty sure HF stands for High Flying, because HF Pigman, he was a human Daredevil.
Sorry, I read that wrong.
He was a daredevil human fly.
So that's a guy who climbs up buildings and stuff like that.
Nowadays we call him human spiders.
I guess he also probably flew.
He might have some sort of glider.
But anyways, HF Pigman, I'll read the sentence.
HF Pigman, a daredevil human fly.
This is from an article.
Loses his grip in 1924.
Loses his grip and falls 70 feet from the courthouse tower in Albert Lee.
He survives the fall but sustains serious injuries.
No duh.
70 feet is quite a long way to fall.
But anyways, so I found that when I was looking at Pigman in Minnesota history.
That's unlucky, right?
This one-- okay, so this is where I told you to hold on.
I'm going to tell you one more cursed Pigman story.
And then I'm going to tell you a Pigman story.
And then we're done, okay?
Just a little bit longer, guys.
Hold on.
Even the ghost with no legs is somehow tapping his foot impatiently.
This one's weird, dude.
2015, there's a dude named Christopher Cruz.
He's sleeping.
And he hears a boom, like this loud noise.
And he wakes up and his wife is laying next to him in bed.
Dead, shotgun blast to the chest.
There were kids in the house.
He wakes up, calls the cops, tells them, "I woke up.
I heard a loud noise.
My wife's dead.
Her chest is blown up."
The cops show up.
Kids are there, all this stuff, right?
Cops show up.
They don't find the shotgun.
But they find a spent shotgun shell in her room.
Four years later, Christopher Cruz is arrested.
He's currently on trial for the murder of his wife.
His wife's name, Jan Pigman Cruz.
Pigman Cruz.
So it's hyphenated.
But it was originally Pigman.
So the Pigman curse can strike you even if you just know a Pigman.
And you go, "Jason, it's obvious he probably shot..."
This is what's weird.
How do you, you know the police tore that house apart looking for that shotgun.
How do you shoot a woman with one of the loudest personal weapons you can carry commercially,
right?
He's not shooting a howitzer cannon, but he shoots her with a shotgun that ejects the
shotgun shell, then runs, hides the shotgun in a place where nobody finds it for four
years, calls the cops.
And the whole time the kids don't see him running, none of the neighbors see him running
outside, burying the shotgun.
The cops, I can guarantee you, tore that place apart looking for that shotgun that night.
I don't think that they would have been like, "Oh, you know, it's been four years.
Let's go look for that shotgun."
And they're like, "Oh, we should have looked for it earlier."
They obviously probably suspected him right away.
They were looking for that shotgun.
How did he get the shotgun out of the house and hidden from the police all this time?
I can understand if they're on a camping trip and this happened, but in your house she
gets shot and somehow even with the kids you're able to get that shotgun to a place, you couldn't
bury it because they had seen freshly buried soil.
They were immediately suspicious of this guy.
To this day the shotgun's never been found.
He may have killed her, or he could be a victim of the curse of the pig man.
Like a ghost shot or something like that.
So you ask, "What's the curse of the pig man?"
Now obviously I've selected these four people named Pigman who have bad luck, other than
just having the last name of Pigman.
The guy's other name was Fat Pigman.
You're thinking, "Jason, you're wasting my time at this point."
I wouldn't even say I selected these guys.
I typed in Minnesota Pigman.
You're like, "Why?
Get to that part.
Hold on.
I typed in Minnesota Pigman and I found these just like right off the bat.
People with the last name of Pigman seem to suffer terrible luck."
So that is in and of itself a bizarre thing.
Pigman people from Minnesota suffer terrible luck.
There might be great pigmen out there somewhere, but whatever.
The reason why I typed in Minnesota Pigman, the reason why you picked the number you
picked, which was number two, was because when I was looking for ghosts and hauntings
and cryptids, the reason why we went on this whole adventure that Kaki Cube sent us on,
was I found on this website, this is where it gets weird guys, there's a website called
hauntedplaces.org.
And I'm just looking for just, this is when I'm first doing my research.
I find this entry on Minnesota State Fairgrounds on hauntedplaces.org.
This is what it says, "The Minnesota State Fairgrounds, according to some, is haunted
by a ghost pig, or half human half pig, called the Pigman."
Other reports say a brown bird that nests here is believed to be a reincarnation of Wayne
Murray, the maintenance man who died here in 1986.
And I read that and I go, "I could care less about the brown bird."
What?
You see a brown bird you're like, "That's good ol' Wayne.
Wayne used to fly around and chew up worms.
That son of a gun.
Still flabbin' his wings.
Why is that?
What the hell is this Minnesota Pigman?
The Minnesota State Fairgrounds, according to some, is haunted by a ghost pig, or half
human half pig, called the Pigman."
Guys we all know how the internet works.
We know how urban legends work.
I've covered dozens of these things over the course of this show.
You can have the most obscure urban legend.
When I was 12 there was some homeless guy named Joe Trombone, who's a schizophrenic
dude who rapped on buses.
There's YouTube videos of him now.
So 20 years later people are still posting stuff about Joe Trombone.
There is nothing on this Pigman.
At all.
Nothing.
But what's weird are there are traces of Pigman in Minneapolis culture.
Now it's hard to determine whether or not these things were founded, but here's my
best example of this.
There is a Pigman triathlon.
So there's like, what is that, swimming, boating, and running or something like that, right?
Three things I don't like doing.
It's called Pigman Triathlon.
You go, well maybe John Pigman founded it.
Maybe when he was killing British soldiers he had to run, swim, and then boat.
Maybe.
But very, very interesting.
I was like, oh that's interesting.
I kept finding traces of it.
There is a photo.
It's a fake photo.
And the guy admits it was fake.
He sold it on eBay.
He said he found it at some shop.
It's basically a Photoshop picture of a baby and a pig mixed together.
And the headline of the article is "extremely rare photo of Minnesota Pigman for sale on
Craigslist."
And the article goes on and says, "That's fake.
I just think it's a funny photo.
I'm gonna put it up there as a joke."
So people in the media, that article specifically talked about the Pigman as if it was a real
cryptid in Minnesota that people would know if I used to turn Minnesota Pigman.
People would be like, oh yeah I remember hearing about that as a kid.
The Minnesota Pigman.
There are no resources on this guy.
Nothing.
And what happened was when I was typing in Minnesota Pigman, it kept bringing me up
stuff about human flies and dudes blowing their wives away.
Except for those little pieces and those little traces.
Really really bizarre.
And I have two conclusions to come from that.
One, here's my conspiracy theory.
What if, I have two of them, but what if, we talked about Great Cloud Island, right?
And we talked about the fact that the community there doesn't want anyone to know about any
of the ghosts.
They're always running people out.
What if the entire population of Minnesota is keeping a cryptid from us?
What if this is a Great Cloud peninsula on a giant scale?
There's a Pigman.
There's a half human, half pig that everyone in Minnesota knows exists.
He's like, hey guys, what's up?
He's skateboarding, has his sunglasses on, and they're like, Pigman!
He's skateboarding off into the sunset.
But no one outside Minnesota gets to know about this dude.
Because that sentence on the hauntedplaces.org is the only record that I could find of the
Minnesota Pigman.
And to make the story even more weird, when I went to go verify a detail from the Minnesota
State Fairgrounds entry to the hauntedplaces.org, I can't access it.
Because of recording this, and I just checked a couple minutes ago, the link that I provided
takes you to the front page of hauntedplaces.org.
The whole website, if you click on any link from that website, none of the links work
now.
They all take you to the front page of hauntedplaces.org.
Is it possible that this website found out that I was getting too close to the truth and
shut itself down for maintenance?
No.
It is not possible at all.
That is completely paranoid delusion.
I do think it is weird timing though.
I think it's 100% a coincidence, but it is odd.
I am curious that if when the website gets fixed, you can go to the website, you just
can't visit any of their entries.
I would be curious that when the website gets fixed, if Minnesota Pigman is still there.
But that is not it.
I have something more to go on.
Because I'm looking up Pigman, an article came up about these dudes in China or Ireland
or something like that trying to make a half human, half pig.
Now not to release to the Minnesota State Fair, but so a pig can grow human organs,
you can take the organs out and put it in a human.
Groundbreaking if it's possible.
But remember, I'm looking for the term Minnesota Pigman.
I find this in...
Oh wait, never mind.
It wasn't in China or Ireland.
It was in Lajala or is it La Jolla, California?
I think it's La Jolla.
Anyways, this was in the article.
Professor Daniel Gary, a cardiologist and head of a different chimera, it's basically
it's the term where you take two animals and stick them together.
You basically take like a dove and a rat and just sew them together, but genetically.
Professor Daniel Gary, a cardiologist and head of a different chimera project at the
University of Minnesota said this is a significant advance that raises opportunities and ethical
questions as well.
Gary said that the rapid progress in chimera research had prompted a range of troubling
questions including whether the progeny would look more human or more pig.
What would happen if a chimera had a human thought and whether it was possible for the
human cells to cannibalize the pig embryo, resulting in a mostly human, slightly pig
offspring?
So what, this guy's talking about pigs.
He's talking about pig people.
Jason, why are you giving this guy...
University of Minnesota, I go, oh, he's also working on doing this chimera project.
I wonder what he's working on.
Is he also working on a pig, half human, half pig thing?
There is no mention.
This guy really does exist, because I had to look him up too, but there is absolutely
no mention what he's working on at all.
Even though this article states he's working on a different chimera project, but I couldn't
and I looked all over for this guy.
He did not say I'm working on like a half draft, half lizard or nothing like that.
We just know that this guy in Minnesota is working on a different chimera project, but
has enough information about how it works that he can adequately explain the possible
outcomes for a human pig.
Is he also working on a human pig hybrid?
Has he crafted and created a human pig hybrid?
Is the pig man... there's two questions here.
One, is the pig man a real urban legend?
And then two, is the pig man real?
Normally with cryptids it's always the first question.
We know the urban legend is real because we've heard the story.
We know about Bigfoot, Mothman, uh, Mellonheads.
We heard about all these guys before.
So the fact there's so many resources on it, we know it's not just one guy telling the
story.
It's not your uncle being like, "Hey, did you hear about pig man walking down the street?
Like, you know it's an urban legend."
That's normally not in question.
I don't think I've ever questioned whether or not the story itself was actually even
being told.
Factually, whether or not it's real is different.
We're actually questioning whether or not the legend exists.
Whether or not anyone else has ever heard the story of the pig man, other than there's
two sentences on this website that's down right now.
But then we find all this other pig, the pig man triathlon and the Minnesota Pig Man news
article and stuff like that.
So in the Minnesota Pig Man news article, I should say, doesn't say, you, everyone knows
who the pig man is.
He's that cryptid running around Minnesota.
It just is like, "Oh, here's a photo of a weird looking pig, Minnesota Pig Man."
It almost assumes that you have a working knowledge of this cryptid.
So if you picked number two, you wake up in a laboratory one day and you're in a cage.
You're all hunched over in a big old human cage.
You see other people in their own cages and they have little hooves for hands and you're
like, "Oh, this isn't going to be good."
And you get unhooked from the cage.
They open the door.
They need to oil the cage.
It's not a really well-funded laboratory.
And they make you get out and they're like, "Come on, come on."
And they take you to a laboratory and they have a giant needle and you see in the liquid
and you see little pig fetuses, right?
Flowing around in the vial, in the ambionic fluid and they inject it into your veins.
You're like, "Ah."
And then you look down at your hands and you have hoof hands.
You're like, "No."
And then this is so cute.
I'm just listing stuff at this point.
Anyways, if you pick number two, you're a half human, half pig.
And you're like, "See all these other pigs?
They're getting like tags put on them and they're like getting punched in the stomach.
I don't know.
They're bad stuff.
Stuff you don't want to see happen to an Ascension creature."
And you're being led through the facility and you're led to a...
It's getting darker and darker and darker and you're like, "Ah."
All you can do is go, "You've lost the ability to speak, but you still have a human brain.
It's your little pig feet are like kicking down the linoleum hallway and it's really
scary."
And then you feel a little curlicue tail stick out of your butt and you're like, "Uh-oh."
Transformation is almost complete and you can't wait for the point where your human
mind becomes as dumb as an animal.
So you don't have to contemplate the horrors that awaits you in this giant pig body.
And that is when the door opens up.
And you're let out and you see a giant slaughterhouse.
Not the soap factory.
That's on the other side of town.
You see a giant slaughterhouse and you see a bunch of pigs going in it.
And you're thinking, "This is a really inefficient way to give pigs my turning people into pigs."
But it's not about the meat.
That's just a byproduct.
The science is what they want.
He explains that to you.
He's like, "Bad pig."
And then as they're leading you to the slaughterhouse and you're starting to poop out pig blood,
poop, because you're super, super scared.
This old rickety truck pulls up.
Some guy goes, "No, I don't take him to the slaughterhouse.
I got special plans for that pig."
And you're like, "Uh-oh.
I'd rather go to the slaughterhouse."
But the dude picks you up.
He throws you in the back of this pickup truck and this dirty old farmer starts driving away
with you.
You've still got a human mind, but you've got the gross, gross pig body.
And then he pulls up to his farm and you hop out and you're like, "Oh man, what's going
to happen to me now?"
And then you see the corner of the farmhouse.
You see a little spider web.
And you're like, "What?
That looks familiar."
And the little spider comes down and goes, "Hi.
I'm Charlotte."
And then you live the life of Wilbur.
Your name was Wilbur.
That was the twist ending.
You didn't know that, right?
Your name was Wilbur.
You looked down, you had a name tag.
And you are Charlotte's web, dude.
You're Wilbur the pig.
Now you may say, "Jason, that's a happy ending, but if you remember the ending of Charlotte's
web, it's not because you lose your best friend in the end.
You say goodbye to Charlotte and then all of her children abandon you too."
So whichever number you chose, you either got an ending with a violent death or an ending
with an emotional death.
The death of your best spider friend.
And then you got that gay rat Templeton annoying you for the rest of your life too.
You got to worry about that.
So there we go.
Our journey.
And now I'm floating around in that bubble again.
I'm looking down at all of the victims of this story.
I'm floating in the bubble.
I go, "So there we go, travelers.
I hope you enjoyed these stories of Minnesota hauntings.
Did you enjoy them?"
And you guys are like, "I guess.
Yes.
Can we get a ride home in the Jason Jalopy?
Can we get the keys?"
And I'm like, "No."
You guys all have to stay in Minnesota.
That is your true fate.
I was like, "No!"
You are trapped in Minnesota forever.
Even after the heat death of the universe, you are trapped here in this hellscape known
as Minnesota.
So then I'm just floating away in my bubble.
So I don't think I'm doing another multiple choice one for a while.
Those take a long time.
But DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[Music]