Have you ever seen something on the ground and wanted to pick it up?
Sure, we all have.
But what happens if that item is cursed?
First, we travel to Africa to find a man who sees a ring just laying there.
But when he puts it on, he gets far more than he bargained for.
And then we travel to Russia to meet an old woman who does the same thing, but she doesn't
see it just a ring laying in a ditch.
She sees an alien baby today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Do you want to see that?
Actually, I'm a walkthrough gal.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
First off, let's introduce our newest Patreon supporter.
She is the sun itself.
Everyone give a round of applause to Eve Jones as her high temperature melts us all.
Our hands stopped clapping.
A giant effervescent sun ball comes flowing in.
It's Eve.
It is Eve.
These intros are getting more and more abstract.
Eve, turn into a human please and I'll toss you the keys to whatever vehicle I don't want
you to melt them.
Eve, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or if you're not a celestial body, that's fine
too.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
Eve Jones, I'm going to toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed out to Ghana.
Specifically, we're headed out to Casso, Ghana.
Dead Rabbit Durgible is flying on out there.
Thank you so much Eve Jones for piloting this vehicle.
It's March 12th, 2021.
Incredibly recent story.
And in Casawa, it's pronounced differently every time you say it.
It's a weird city.
Every time you say it, it has to be pronounced differently.
It's the law.
In Casawa, in Ghana, there is a place called Casawa Iron City.
It's not a school.
But if you're going to have a school name, might as well have it named like it's a Transformers
headquarters.
In Casawa, Iron City, there's a young man named Emmanuel O'Tibble.
He's 17 years old.
He's playing video games with his friend.
And his friend for whatever reason has taken off his ring and set it on the table.
Now that's not unusual.
Maybe they're playing like some Super Smash Bros. thing and you need to get like extra
button presses before Star Fox goes to the box level or whatever it is.
For whatever reason he took the ring off.
That's not important.
I can't get lost in the details.
Emmanuel is looking at this ring on the table and he's obsessed with it.
He's just staring at it.
His guy's got kicked off the ledge 100 times.
He can't beat his buddy because he's staring at this ring.
He takes the ring and he puts it on.
And his buddy goes, "Bro, that's my ring.
Why are you wearing that ring?"
And Emmanuel actually has a really interesting point of view, really interesting way of looking
at life.
He says, "If you own something and you're my friend, then I can use it too."
Which is a super bizarre way of looking at the world.
But if you agree with me, if you agree with me and you don't want a friend like that,
he's walking around in your clothes all the time, driving your car at best.
He could also be sleeping with your significant other and doing a bunch of other stuff.
He's wearing your skin.
If you guys think that's a terrible mindset, don't worry.
He gets his just desserts.
But maybe a little too much for this sin.
He takes the guy's ring and he actually means to give it back, but he kind of forgets.
You put a ring on, you go, "Ooh, this is cool looking."
And then you completely forget it exists until you either have to wash your hands or someone
goes, "Hey, nice ring."
A ring, I'm sure it's the same thing with earrings.
I used to have pierced ears in college, but I don't remember them.
I don't remember waking up and being like, "Oh, dude, I remember that Tuesday back in
July 1994 when I had my earrings and my ears."
You don't remember jewelry.
But anyways, so he takes it home, he goes to sleep.
When he wakes up the next morning, birds, "Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo."
You know, like the little music, there's sun coming in.
If Jones is risen for the day, little bluebirds floating around, Emmanuel is waking up.
But before he can get through his first yawn, he realizes searing pain, horrible, horrible
pain is shooting through his hands, specifically his ring finger.
And he looks down and his finger is starting to swell up.
He tries to take the ring off.
Kind of hard when your finger's swelling up.
He tries to wash it off with soap.
He's trying to do all this stuff to get it off.
His mom is trying to figure out, "Hey, Emmanuel, why are you screaming in pain in the bathroom
and where did all of my soap go?"
And he finally admits to his mom, "Mom, okay, so you know my friend Jeremy, the friend's
name isn't in the article, but you know my friend Jeremy, I stole, I mean, I borrowed
his ring because he's my buddy."
And the mom's like, "Of course, you can have all your friends stuff."
He's like, "Yeah, I know.
I put this ring on and now I can't get it off and my fingers swole."
The mom's like, "Hmm, okay, well, it's one of two things.
Either the ring was too small for you and it's cutting off circulation in your finger.
Oh, you have fallen victim to black magic."
Now, Emmanuel doesn't want to think of the idea of why no one wants that as an alternative
while you either have arthritis or witches cursed you.
So he goes and he calls up his buddy.
His buddy comes over with a hacksaw and a pair of pliers.
And I'm sure the buddy's laughing about this whole thing.
Actually, to be, I'm sure the buddy's laughing about the whole thing as he's driving over
there, but once he gets there, because there's photographs of this kid's finger.
It's huge.
It's so gross and bloated.
Several photographs of this.
Once he came over, he probably stopped laughing when he saw his friend's finger is about to
fall off.
He hacksaws it.
He's pulling with the pliers.
It's already tight on the finger.
It's already so swollen.
He is able to break the ring and they still can't get it off.
It's actually worse now because now there's two jagged pieces of metal digging into his
flesh.
So most of these photos you'll see online is of the ring already cut and it's bleeding.
His finger's bleeding.
The next step, so here now you have a half a ring on your finger, possibly a cursed.
You've already tried the hacksaw.
You've already tried the pliers.
You've tried soap.
What ever.
They bring in a welder.
I don't know what they expected this kind of to, right?
He's usually putting steel together or cutting steel in half.
I don't know what they expected him to do with this piece of jewelry wrapped around his kid's
finger.
But at this point in the thing, we might have to eventually chop the kid's finger off.
It's definitely like losing circulation.
It's swelling up.
But eventually the mom says, "Okay, before we let the welder, as he's getting his blow
torch ready, okay, okay, okay.
Hold on.
Let's try the whole black magic thing.
Maybe you just have some sort of ghost on you."
So they called up a spiritualist.
She came over.
She performed a ritual and the ring came off.
Happy ending, right?
Well, kind of.
Because while the news articles state that the boy is no longer in danger of losing his
finger, one news article said, "The boy wanted his friend."
This whole thing.
So basically, let's recap this.
Emmanuel finds a ring, puts it on.
Magic curse happens.
Can't take it off.
They have to chop it up.
They have to destroy it.
The best friend, or maybe just friend, maybe just acquaintance at this point.
He wants a new ring.
That's all he can think about after knowing that in this world, in this real world, this
is not fiction.
This was reported in several newspapers.
In this reality, magical rings exist and you just watched your friend almost get his-
You just watched a welder show up to your friend's house with a blowtorch.
You want a new ring.
I would never wear a ring ever again if I knew that was a reality.
Apparently it is.
This was in several newspapers.
And not only that, not only does he want a ring, he wants his friend.
He wants his friend, who he magically cursed, to give him a ring.
How do you know your friend's not gonna curse you?
And make your finger almost fall off.
Anyways, one of the articles said the friend wanted a new ring and I had a good chuckle
at that.
But that gets an idiot.
Right?
I never wear jewelry again.
Another article, and these aren't- these are like from- let me- these aren't fringe
news sites.
These are from- well, Coast to Coast AM is where I first saw the article.
And then I went into moderngonna.com, which is a mainstream news site in the country,
and then announcernewsonline.com, which is a mainstream African newspaper.
These aren't the Daily Mail or Daily Star.
Another article said the friend not only wanted a new ring, he wa- I was like, "What is going
on?
What is going on with these friends?
These guys are nuts."
The other friend of the other article- I was- I can't believe this.
The other friend- I can't believe the journalist wrote it down and was just like, "Mhm, yep.
I'm gonna go cover a city council meeting after this.
This is totally normal."
The friend, in the according to this other article, wanted not only a new ring, but also
wanted- how would you even get this?
How would you even get this?
The other article, just Plain of Day, states that the friend wanted newborn baby blood.
"Hey man, you borrowed my ring and that wasn't cool and I had to break it.
You have to buy me a new ring and you have to give me a vial of baby blood."
And the guy goes to turn and he goes, "No, no, no, no, no.
Newborn baby blood."
He's like, "Aw man, that's the hardest to get.
What is he going to do with it?
Why are you gonna be friends with a guy who that's a demand at all in any situation?"
So that you might think is a one-off story, right?
You would hope it was a one-off story, someone demanding newborn baby blood.
And again, the article doesn't say to bless the ring, it just states it.
That's what he wants.
No questions, no questions at all.
But you go, "Jason, maybe it's just a guy with like a swollen finger and they like photoshopped
his bloody ring on it.
This isn't the first time this has happened in Ghana.
In November 2014, Eric Bu-Bang in Ghana was walking home from church, sees a shining gold
ring in the dirt, compelled to pick it up.
I pick up stuff all the time.
I'll pick up little rocks, I'll pick up sticks if I find like little stuffed animals or little
creepy toys.
Take them home."
So I would do this.
He picks up the ring.
He's compelled to pick up this ring.
And once it's in his hand, his hand, you can't hear that.
You can't hear that sound effect when my hand is shaking next to the mic.
And he wants to throw it away immediately, but he can't.
His hand's shaking so much.
He actually thinks it'd make it easier to throw.
It's like you're throwing dice.
But he can't.
He's compelled, he puts it on.
The next morning he wakes up, his finger's swelling up.
There's photos of all of that as well.
They're all being in the show notes.
There are pictures of people with really, really swollen fingers and rings wrapped around
them.
And he has the added thing.
He says at night he can't sleep because once the sun goes down, he hears voices in his
head.
"Ugh, you shouldn't have put that ring on!
You should have thrown it away when you had the chance!"
All of that stuff.
They might just also be telling him about events of the world.
He's like, "The City Council meeting was held today in Ghana.
They demanded 10 bites of baby blood before they fixed all those potholes."
Who knows?
But his article, it doesn't have an ending.
His article says they couldn't figure out a way to get the ring off and they're hoping
to get it off soon before his finger comes off.
That happened in 2014.
I could find no follow-up.
So there may be a dude named Eric walking around Ghana right now with nine fingers.
To be specific, to be fair, I'm sure there is at least one person named Eric in the entire
country of Ghana who doesn't have all their fingers.
But if it's their ring finger, you might want to ask Ashley, "Don't walk up to someone
who's missing a ring finger and say, 'You didn't have to put on a cursed ring, did you?'
The reason why I wanted to highlight this is because once we covered this before about
the guy who picked up the pile of corn and got stuck to his back and they had to bring
wizards out to help him, magic must exist."
I'm totally perplexed by these stories that are coming out of Africa.
Because you could say the corn one, people are like, "Maybe he faked it.
Maybe it was a public service announcement."
Who?
You know, a public service announcement like the cops are trying to say, "Don't steal.
You might get cursed."
What is the public service announcement here?
Who do they talk to to say, "Hey, man, we got a deal.
How about we let your finger swell up?
Super disgusting and super painful.
Take photos of it, send them out online, and then in return, you can all the baby blood
you can drink."
Like what is, what would be the point of having this hoax?
Does magic exist?
Have all of the naysayers, myself included?
I have a limited belief in magic.
I believe magic exists in a certain point.
I don't think we've ever really talked about my beliefs on magic on this show.
I don't think we've ever gone in depth.
I don't have time to do it now.
I've got a whole other segment to do.
But I think at a limited scope, what I call scientific magic, or I think the technical
term for it is high magic, works where it's very ritualistic, I think can work to a limited
degree, to a very, very limited degree, and everything needs to be in place.
You just can't pick up a couple books and learn it.
It's a whole thing, and I could honestly do an entire segment on it.
I probably will at some point, but that's always been my thing.
I didn't think you could just throw cursed rings.
I didn't think you could just curse a bag of rings and just drive through town, throwing
them on the ground.
Magic might exist, and it would be so...
What if we...
Let's put on our conspiracy caps here for a second.
What if it turns out that magic exists, these type of things exist in Africa?
Like the continent itself.
The continent itself is magically charged.
What would that...
A conspiracy cap falling on, what would that do to the world's economy?
It would basically be like Wakanda, but with magic.
Like if people are like, "Yeah, we don't know what it is.
We don't know what it is," but in Ghana, magical curse rings exist.
They're a real thing.
And scientists would go out there and they're like, "No, it's not here.
Give me your ring."
And they put it on.
They're like, "Ahh!"
They're screaming.
Bill Gates has no fingers.
I was like, "Oh, I kept trying to prove them wrong, but I was the one who was wrong."
What if it turns out that for some reason, like all the lay lines intersect underneath
the continent of Africa, and it's magically charged?
Would that change society?
Would people just want to move there?
Or would you be like, "No, I don't want to go there."
There's a bunch of cursed dolls and there's a bunch of cursed rings and I can't steal
corn anymore.
Either all of this stuff is fake, which is very, very in the realm of possibility.
Or some of it's fake and some of it's misconstrued events.
Like the same time they put on the ring, a bumblebee landed on their finger and they're
allergic to bumblebees, but they're only allergic on their fingers.
Or that magic exists worldwide, but for some reason we don't see stories about people putting
on cursed rings in the Balkans.
We don't see it in Arizona.
We don't see it in Paraguay.
But we just run into these weird stories that come out of Africa and you look at them and
you go, "Magic, if this story is true, then witches and magic and spells and curses 100%
exist."
Witches do exist all over the world and magic is just like a volcano just kind of got sucked
up under Africa or I don't know, I don't know.
Now even more hypothesizing that there's a magical volcano ready to erupt.
But I just think on a conspiracy level, what would that do to society if you could, even
if it wasn't Africa, you could say it was Australia, you could say it was the middle
of Peru, what if you found out that one country or one continent magic actually existed?
What would that do to world society?
There you go.
That's your writing prompt for you guys, for you guys, for you writers out there, for
your 90 day challenge.
There's your writing prompt.
What if one country, only one country, became magical?
But we won't be able to explore that right now.
I think I already explored it much longer than I thought it was going to.
Eve Jones.
Let's call in that carbonar copter.
We're waving goodbye to a man who won Eric.
Hopefully they have all their fingers for the rest of their lives.
Let's leave behind Ghana.
We are headed out to Russia.
Eve, I want you to go ahead and land us at Kalinovy.
Kalinovy, you all know this, you guys are all well up on your Russian geography.
It's a little village near Kaisnam.
That's in the Chelyabinsk Oblast region in Russia.
The story was actually recommended to me by Yuri.
Yuri, thanks for sending this one over.
It's May 1996.
And there's an old woman named Tamara Vasylina of Prosferina.
I can pronounce that last word.
Walking down the street.
Now it doesn't say how old she is.
She does appear to have an adult son who's in prison.
So 50, 60 years old, but she's definitely considered an odd duck in the village of Kaloinynov.
Tamara is out for her walk and everyone's down the windows.
They're like, oh no, here comes that crazy lady.
She's not necessarily known as a crazy lady.
She's just known as a little bit odd.
But that's going to change very quickly.
She's walking down the road and she sees something laying off to the side.
She looks down.
She sees a tiny little body moving in the grass.
It's around 10 inches long.
It's a super tiny guy, right?
She's laying there.
No hair on its head, which I mean it's to be expected, right?
Really 10 inches tall.
I don't think you're going to have Samson locks.
Totally bald.
Totally bald little baby.
He has a big eye.
But all of that stuff, I mean, coming across the tenet humanoid in the woods is bizarre.
Coming across the tenet humanoid in an office building is weird.
Doesn't matter where it's at.
But the most notable feature about this thing is it had ridges along its head.
It was described and there's lots of quote unquote photographs of this thing.
We're going to get into some weird stuff with this story.
It had ridges on its head that seem to form a central, like all lead to a central ridge.
It's described as being like a leaf where you have like the main vein and all the little
offshoots of them.
And Tamara picks it up.
She's like, wow, my name's pronounced differently all of a sudden.
Now that I found this creature, Tamara picks up this little dude and she goes, I will name
you Alishiozenka, which means tiny Alex.
I will call you Alexiokshnia.
And the rest of the story, she just calls him Alex.
That bit of information is all that we know for sure.
Now you may go, Jason, I know about this story.
No, no, no, we know all this other stuff.
I've done a bunch of research on this.
I'm not saying that you haven't, but every article I've read about it has added and subtracted
certain details.
The only thing every narrative had in common, Tamara, she's at the village of Kalowniav.
She finds something, it's this tall, it looks like this, that's what she names it.
Those are the only details that are all the same.
Literally, every detail changes from story to story.
So I had to create this narrative out of different versions of this.
She takes the creature home and she begins to take care of it.
Now she would feed it a diet of cottage cheese, which is gross anyways.
That's the gross of all cheeses.
The cheese I covered with the maggots on it, I'd rather eat that.
She gives him cottage cheese, he's forced it, he's like, "Oh, I wish I was dead.
I wish you'd left me in the wilderness."
She's feeding him cottage cheese and condensed milk.
And she's like, "Isn't this the best little baby man?
This is where it'll help you grow to be 11 inches."
He's like, "Ah, kill me."
Her daughter-in-law came over once and tomorrow was like, "Hey, watch this, watch this trick.
I'm going to shove this cream down this little creature's mouth.
Eat it."
She's watching her feed this creature and the daughter-in-law said, "He looked sad.
I felt pain while looking at him."
Couple people in town did stop by to see this take place.
Did stop by to see her feed this little dude.
And probably do have a shove.
She has strings tied to him.
She's like, "Hey, look at my marionette show."
He's like, "Kill me, please, kill me."
It's like that dude and Johnny got his gun.
He can't communicate, but he really wants to die.
She's doing, I don't know, she's doing tricks.
I don't know, she's putting him on a little bicycle and making him run right little daredevil
loops or something like that.
She's probably caring for it as if it was a baby.
To be fair, to be fair, I don't want to turn her into some sort of circus ringmaster.
That's what I would have done.
So a couple of people had seen this thing move around.
They said it made a squeaky noise.
But other people in town just saw old nutbag Tamara walking through the streets with a blanket
going, "You want to see my baby?
You want to see my mutant baby?"
I found in the bushes.
She would unwrap the blanket and it would just be like a doll.
They said it didn't look alive.
It looked fake.
It looked like if it wasn't alive at some point, it wasn't alive now and it probably
wasn't alive, it's probably a doll.
So you had different, again, this is what we're talking about.
There's tons of evidence of this story.
Air quotes around that.
It's really fascinating to look at because you'll see a ton of photos of this online
and video, but nobody can really pin down who took the photos.
Japan went crazy over this story.
It's a shocker, right?
They made a replica of it.
There was a news station that made a replica of it.
So a lot of photographs you see are of the replica.
But how do they get a replica if they haven't seen the original?
So there must have been some photos going around.
There is video footage from 1996, which could be faked.
There is video footage that has the date on it, 1996, and it is a couple months after
May, which is when the story takes place, of supposedly Russian scientists messing around
with it.
But they put it on Marynep of it.
At that point, it is clearly dead.
Whatever it is, it's not alive.
So first off, we have a question of, what is it?
Was it ever alive?
If it was alive, how long was it alive?
And what happened to it?
We can answer some of those questions, but you're not going to like the answers.
She already had an oddball personality.
She's walking around with this thing.
She's saying it's her baby.
She's showing it to people.
Eventually, the authorities get involved.
Tamara is arrested.
What's the crime, right?
What's the crime?
Picking up litter.
She's arrested and she's put in a psychiatric hospital.
And then the neighbor supposedly goes over to take care of Alex.
And then after a couple hours, he'll be like, "Oh, this is boring.
That's going to be way more funny."
He had a little evil, conneval outfit built for him.
He's like, "Oh, it doesn't do any tricks.
This is lame."
He then gives Alex to the authorities, where supposedly that's where the video comes from,
was when the government got hold of Alex, who at that time had passed away.
But again, was he ever alive?
Was he alive for a couple weeks, for a couple days, when she first found him?
These are all interesting questions.
But Tamara is actually locked up in the insane asylum and they don't let her out.
She wants Alex back.
It's her baby.
She saved this guy.
So one night, she breaks out of the insane asylum and while she's escaping, a ambulance
runs her over.
In the dead of night as she's running down the street to find her child, she's killed.
Even that's an interesting detail because apparently she was sent to a hospital.
Whether or not it was psychiatric or regular hospital, we don't know.
But she did die in 1999.
She died in a car accident, was one version.
Another version was she died in a car accident escaping.
Because she might have just been like, "You're free, Tamara.
You're no longer crazy."
She's like, "I have the keys in my car."
And they're like, "Sure, you haven't driven in three years.
Here you go."
And she just got in a car accident.
Some people say she got in a car accident escaping.
And the third one was she ran over by an ambulance while she was escaping.
Which in that way, you could add malice to the fact.
If you're escaping from a hospital, you get ran over by an ambulance.
You can kind of build a conspiracy that they didn't want her to get out.
So what was this thing?
Like again, we can talk all day long about the details of what happened after the fact.
But everyone can agree that this woman found something in the woods.
That's something that all the stories agree on.
Some people believe it was a hoax.
So even they believe that the story happened, but they believe that the doll was handmade.
It was made to be a hoax.
Which would be totally unfortunate if you come up, if you craft a hoax and you're like,
"Oh man, everyone in the village is going to love this hoax."
And it ends with you being arrested and thrown in a psychiatric hospital.
You're like, "It's just a prank, bro.
It's just a prank."
As the ambulance is running you over.
That would be the most tragic.
Well, that would be one of the most tragic because it gets pretty dark.
Some believe it was an alien.
It was a little alien ship.
Nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem, nyeeem,
nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem,
nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem, nyeem,