Just when you thought eggs couldn't get any more disgusting
They did like Jason. I love eggs. I don't know why you ate eggs so much. Anyways, they're disgusting
And that's not the whole story. I'm gonna talk about other stuff and then a man has a close encounter of the tea time
You know Jason these are making less and less sense. Hold on and
then and
Then we cover a true crime story
That should strike fear into the heart of any
Well-meaning citizen when a young woman is stumbling home from a bar many good Samaritans reach out to help her home
But she ends up falling into the arms of a killer today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Garvin
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys are having a lot of fun
I'm still doing my breakneck recording to try to get as many episodes out before this heatwave hits
But let's go ahead and introduce one of our legacy patreon's coming into that
I'm hurry up hurry up coming to Dead Rabbit Command, bro
I gotta get this episode recorded coming into Dead Rabbit Command is user profile name everyone give a round of applause
Give a round of applause to this Tron character who has a default name. What happened? I actually reached out to you
I try to figure out what was going on user profile name
I remember they set up an account the name had a profanity in it
I saw it pop up in a notification, but by the time I went to look at it
It came to user profile name. So you are now one of the users you are now one of the gods of the Tron world
User you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon
That's fine too. Just help spread the word about the show really really helps out a lot user
I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command
We are headed out to Dong Yang China
Dead Rabbit Durgible is taking us high above the heat up in the stratosphere where it's super cold
We don't have oxygen. We're slowly nine, but it's nice and cool user take us on out to China
Specifically we're going to Dong Yang that's in the Zee's Yang province
I was recommended the story by Mason one of my longtime patreon supporters longtime supporter of the show
He sent this over to me on the patreon discord. So he sent me this over. This is a delicacy in Dong Yang
You get an egg you get one egg fresh from the chicken has to be steaming right out of the chicken's vagina
You look at you're holding it. You're like yes
Perfect chicken body temperature and then you've got to soak the egg and water you cook it right?
That's how you would normally boil an egg
Fresh out of the chickens vagina, but are they vaginas or is that what they're called on a chicken? Jamie?
Look that up. Look me look that up and then don't tell me because it's super disgusting
That's how you normally boil an egg you take the chicken egg or duck egg or goose egg or whatever
Put it in water and boil it but dong yang man. They're like that's lame
We got to do stuff differently step one you want to boil an egg
You want to boil an egg in dong yang dude step one?
Go to a local elementary school and you're like is that where the chicken coops are it is like dong yang have this farm
Built into the school. No you're driving by you see all the chicken farms you pass those you see fresh egg stores
It's just the shape of a giant chicken vagina. That's what you walk into to get your eggs
It's not many people shop there. No you go to the local elementary school
And you're walking in with the dude and you're like dude. I'm so hungry all I do
I need to cure my hunger is one hard boiled egg
I don't know why my body's built like that, but that's what I need you're walking into this elementary school with this dude
And he's like oh don't worry man
You're gonna get your one hard boiled egg, but first we got to go to the elementary school
Then you go into the boys restroom. You're like wait what what is there chicken in here? There's a basin
There's a giant trough and you see the your friend from dong yang going
And he picks the basin up and then he's like help me carry this basin of children's urine
To my car and they're like what man you have this basin of boys urine has to be urine from ten-year-olds your friend tells you
You're wondering why this guy is your friend
He's like what we do is we get urine from boys who are under ten years old and he begins to scoop out this urine
I'm sure he has some sort of funnel or something like that
I'm sure it doesn't spin all day doing this
But he takes the urine from the trough in the boys restroom and puts it in buckets and takes it to his car
And you're like okay. This must just be a side quest or something like that
Right this must be collect five barrels of boy urine and then you'll get some experience points and then we'll just cook an egg
So he drives you back to his kitchen your little word because he's bringing the urine into his kitchen with you and he explains to you
Okay, so this is what we're gonna do. I'm gonna take this egg this egg. You need so much. We're gonna boil it and you're like finally
Let me finish we're gonna boil it and boys urine
Like what so many questions have popped up in your head none of them are answerable
Some of the questions are is this healthy? Probably not right is this clean? Probably not
So in schools in these elementary schools in dong yang, this is a this is so real
There's like infrastructure built into this when a boy needs to go to the bathroom
The teacher reminds them remember to use the basin. I don't know where else they're going, right?
I don't know if they're just going on the floor and they're also told if you're sick
Don't pee in the basin
Because we want to soak our eggs in boy urine, but we don't want to soak our eggs in boy urine if they have the flu
You know, you got to think safe. So I don't know if they just go behind a tree or something like that
I guess there's like a normal toilet to poop in too. There's not the poop basin next to it. There's some chef there
He's like, mm-hmm. This is all for me girls just use normal toilets. They don't want to use girl urine
They're like that's cooties in it. We tried that everyone got cooties
You bring this boy urine out of this basin
Some people are lucky enough like if you have a boy if you have a son in your house, you just have them
P you're like, oh, yes, my own eggs. I don't need to buy those store bought eggs anymore. Honey, we're off the grid
We're gonna live in the middle of nowhere and I'm gonna eat all the virgin boy eggs myself. That's what they're called
I should have I should have announced that earlier. These are called virgin boy eggs and what they do is they take a an egg
All over the place. They take an egg. They boil it not in water. They boil it in boy urine
You're like, okay, you know, that's fine
You would never say that I'm totally putting words in your mouth
But let's say for let's say for a second. You think that's fine
You take the egg you boil it in boys urine and you pull it out
Then you're like, I'm just gonna wash it off. Right? Like maybe the boys urine
You can't even think of any rational reason of why you would do this
But let's say you do let's say you do and you go maybe the boys urine whatever
I'm gonna take it out. I'm gonna wash it off. Anyways, a boiled egg is a boiled egg
It doesn't matter if I'm boiling it in water or in hydrogen peroxide
Probably does don't try that. Don't even try boiling hydrogen peroxide that might explode or kill you
But this is what they do. They boil it. They get it nice and a hard boiled egg, right? Which are disgusting
I hate hard boiled eggs. I don't even want to look at them. I deviled eggs. They're all disgusting
I can only eat scrambled eggs
kind of but
You you take a regular egg you turn in a hard boiled egg
You pull it out of the urine
Then you crack the shell and now you have a hard boiled egg and that would be bad enough
But then they take this
Unshelled egg and you go you know what this recipe is missing?
More boy urine
So then they put the unshell the only thing that was protecting it from this disgustingness
They put this unshell egg back in the urine and you boil it until it soaks up all the boy urine
Which is not which is not anything you want to see in any recipe ever
It's like you know, it's done when there's no more boy urine available
It actually turns golden. You're like, oh, that's a nice color and the yolk turns green
Like moldy green and then you eat it and then you then you do your best to try to enjoy a virgin boy egg
These are very popular in dong yang
It's a cultural dish like i'm sure you know, what's funny because when you read articles about this
It's it goes back centuries
People say it redo it's one of those things like it does everything which should tell you that it does nothing
Like a like I take Tylenol and it helps pain. It also doesn't improve my eyesight and make me faster
Like any food or drug that claims too many different things does none of them
So if you eat virgin boy eggs you reduce inflammation it promotes blood circulation
It gets rid of fungal infections of the mouth
Which i'm sure also costs by eating boy urine. It has all these
Homeopathic traits, but most likely none of them exist. The residents of dong yang are actually
There's a 50/50 split people are really divided over this because some people say it's delicious
And it's totally cured my inflammation and I can run fast mom look at how fast I can run after I ate an egg
And then the other people go I think they're disgusting and that would be fine
Not everyone in town is going to eat mcdonald's right, but the problem is
Is that
Whether or not you eat a mcdonald's
You don't smell boiling boy urine all day long the people in town who hate the eggs
Hate the town because they constantly smell like at certain times of the day when everyone's making these eggs
You just smell boiling boy urine
Wafed through the town so the people who hate the eggs they go I don't eat them
But I can't avoid them. They're everywhere and walking on the street. There's like a stink cloud following me around
So that's the story of virgin boy eggs. It's bizarre. It's disgusting
It's like my best combination of things that I love mason. Thanks for bringing this to my attention
User i'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the jason jelapi. We're gonna leave behind dong yang china trying to
Outrun this stink cloud. We are headed out to a small town in america
Old timey jason jelapi is being driven by user. We're headed out to an unnamed city
Somewhere in the heartland. There's a young man
He's at his house
He's sleeping. Let's call him
Jeremy let's call him a name. Let's call him a name. I can pronounce. Let's call him
michael
michael is sleeping in his bed one night and he wakes up
Can't really figure out why you know just one of those things he kind of wakes up and he's sitting there in the darkness of his room and
He sees that there's a light on downstairs
It's like what it's weird. I'm sure that I shut that off. So he gets up out of his bed
He's still kind of unsteady, you know, right when you wake up. He walks out of his bedroom
He walks downstairs to go shut off
the light
And he sees something in his kitchen
He sees what he calls a little green man
Which is an interesting description of an alien that is an old term usually that was like almost a mocking term
Nowadays they're usually classified as greys or reptilians or humanoids if you don't really know how to place it
But he actually uses the words a little green man in the kitchen
He says it was about the size of an eight-year-old
just standing there
And he goes he didn't get any sort of sense of terror from this thing
He wasn't scared of it and it wasn't scared of him. It just turned to him and smiled
He doesn't get any he doesn't give any other descriptors of how this alien being looks
Just that it has green skin
And it's quite small
Andy
He doesn't know what to do he this normally when you would find an intruder in your house
You would have a fight or flight response will fight response. There's nowhere to go. You're in your house, but
He looks at this bean and says
Uh, hello, would you like a drink?
And he got a telepathic message in his head. Yes
I would like a drink
Michael asks
What do you want? Do you want some coffee? Do you want some water and he gets another telepathic message?
I would prefer tea, please
So Michael Michael looks in his cupboards and finds some tea that he has
Which is interesting because
This alien probably knew that he did have tea if he can read his mind
He may have seen that he bought tea
So many months ago, but he does make this tea and the humanoid is just standing in the kitchen just observing him
When he's done making the tea he puts it on the table and the alien just stands there and looks at the tea
Michael goes aren't you going to drink the tea?
And the alien smiles and says
Oh, I don't drink tea
Well, why did you want me to make it then?
Michael asks
The alien goes
I appreciate the form of the tea
And the effort that went into making it
Michael asks why are you here? What's the cause of this visit?
He doesn't get a vocal answer. He doesn't get a telepathic answer
Instead
He sees in an instant
A million images blast through his head
He sees people enjoying themselves
At home
On the beach
Walking through the woods
He sees world peace
He sees a world of no pollution
He sees a world of
World of pure abundance
All of these images in his head
And he's overwhelmed
By this
He says they're coming so fast
And they don't stop
He's seen all of this joy
But it's too much for him to comprehend
And he passes out
He wakes up in his bed
And he thinks this must be a dream right?
It must have been dreaming. There's such a bizarre encounter
And he's like
I'm not sure if he's gonna make it
And there's such a bizarre encounter
He goes downstairs and he notices
There's no tea left out
So was I dreaming?
Did my wife
Who Jason didn't mention was in the story earlier
Next to him in bed?
Did my wife wake up earlier and clean all the tea stuff that I leave?
I don't know what happened
I might have just been a dream
So he tells his wife because
I had the weirdest experience last night
And he tells her this story
And she sits there and she goes
"Last night, I woke up in the middle of the night
And there was a little man
At the foot of our bed
He was just standing there
But I figured I was dreaming
I figured that couldn't be
So I just went back to sleep
Michael said shortly after this
Event they ended up leaving the house
They ended up selling the house
And moving to the countryside shortly after
I found the story on the X-board
Probably earlier this year
I didn't archive the link
I feel bad about that
But lately I've been doing that more
With Reddit and X-board posts
But I just thought it was such an interesting story
It's very
The thing that I love the most about it
Let's assume that it's true
It could be fake like everything we cover on the show
It's just one person's same thing
We don't know, but the thing I love about this
Story is the tea moment
I love that little piece of information
Where you have this alien
Who can travel the cosmos
Who has these telepathic powers
Who did he come from a world
Of pure abundance and joy
Or was he showing what humanity could do
We have all of this high level stuff
We have a man meeting an alien
We have telepathic communication
A vision of a possible future
A vision of an alien world we don't know
But to me the reason why I saved this story
For so long was the tea part
I just love that moment
Because yeah, you can forget
To take the little things into account
And you have this alien
Who has all of these powers
And the ability to transcend space and time
But there's just something very special
About boiling water
Boiling non-urinated water
Boiling water and taking a little bag
And putting it and
Steeping it and then
Having this refreshing drink
That's made of water
And plant
It's a very, very basic drink
It goes back thousands of years
And there is kind of a
Calmness
To the creation of tea
Unless you have one of those whistling teapots
And then it's not, but I just love that story
I kind of love that small moment between this alien
And this human, and I keep saying alien
We don't know what this thing was
The term little green man could have been
A slang term
Forgery, it could have been that this person was actually green
You know, because it's just this
Thing on export
It's just these few words that you didn't really
Follow anything up, but I love the story
Whether or not you picture it as a little green human being
Or a gray alien, I just think it's a very, very
Fascinating insight
To that human alien relation
User, let's go ahead and talk to the keys of the
Carbonary Cofter. We've had our fill of tea
We're waving goodbye to the alien
The families paralyze now
And more of the aliens are showing up
They're like, it's probe time. We're like, oh, they're just
Going to have so much fun making tea together
Let's leave behind this town
And we are headed out
To whole
England
I want to tell you guys something before we get started
On this next story. This next story is real dark
This next story is real dark
It's a true crime story. It's something that I've wanted
To talk about for a while
It bugs me. This story really, really bugs me
And I'm including at the end of the episode
So if you want to bounce out now
And I'll see you tomorrow, that's so
Go enjoy your urine boy eggs
And I'll see you tomorrow
But if you want to stick around for a darker true crime
Story, we're going to go with this one
It's not incredibly dark. It just really bugs me
It really makes me mad
It really, really makes me mad
So it's not like it doesn't involve kids or anything like that
But it's true crime story and it...
Okay, so, we're in whole
H-U-L-L
That's in East Yorkshire in England
It's January 31st, 2019
If you live over there, I'm sure you already know
Where this is going. It's fairly big
True crime case that just
Ended. The trial just ended
There was a young woman named Libby
Squire. She's 21 years old
And her and her friends are out clubbing
They're enjoying life. They're getting drunk
They're partying. You know, I used to do all that stuff
As well. You can't judge them for that
They're out just doing their thing
What happened though is that
They're going from club to club
They're getting drunker and drunker
And they go to this club and Libby is
Visibly drunk
There's a difference between being
Buzzed, being drunk and being so drunk
That you legally can't be allowed
To buy more liquor
Which that happens
That happens with a lot of alcohol
I'm not saying Libby Squire was an alcoholic
But that's the point where
Bouncers at clubs, they have to look at liability
They're like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa, no, no, she's too drunk
She can't come in here. Sure
She's probably going to spend money, but
We have an obligation. We can't do that
A lot of times it's a legal obligation
In the United States, I know for sure
You cannot serve someone alcohol if they're legally drunk
So the friends want to continue
There are poor friends
The poor friends in this story
There's a lot of people who suffer in this story
But can you imagine if you were one of these
Young woman's friends
They say
"Listen, we still want to continue to party
Like, you need to hold your liquor"
I'm putting words in their mouth. I don't know if they said any of this stuff
These are real people
But they do say, "Libby, we want to continue our party
We will pay for a taxi to take you home
You're too drunk to get in, you can't wait outside
So they call a taxi, they pay the taxi
They put her in and they give taxi driver the address
And they go into the club
Taxi cab driver
Upstanding citizen
Drives this horribly drunk young woman home
Safe and sound
And there's a lot of people like that in this story
Libby gets out of the taxi cab
She's right in front of her house
I think it's like a dorm type of thing
I think it was like an apartment complex
But she's right outside of her building
And the taxi cab drives away
This is England, there's cameras everywhere
We have a lot of video footage of this woman
Apparently the taxi cab drives away
And Libby is just kind of standing out there
And she falls face first on the ground
She's so drunk she just gets up
Brushes herself off and walks away from her house
It's January 31st in England
It's freezing cold
And she's dressed to go to the club
She's dressed in club clothes
Which don't include parkas, they don't include ski pants
She's walking around the town of Hull
Some of her fellow students
Yeah, I think they dropped her outside of a dorm
I know she was going to college
Some other students are walking down the street
And they see this young, obviously drunk woman
Walking down the street
And they come up to her and they...
Do you need any help? What's going on?
Do you need to find a way home?
Should we call you a taxi cab? What's going on?
And she refuses their help
And you can't force somebody to be helped
So these students go, "Well, I hope she makes it home okay"
They don't know that she's walking away from her house
Hope she makes it home okay
Upstanding citizens, these young people
See one of their fellow students in trouble
They want to help her out
And we have CCTV video of Libby walking down the street
And this... I love this part of the story
It's probably the only part of the story that I do love
Stranger after stranger after stranger
Stopping and asking, "Do you need help, young lady?"
"Can I get you home?"
And she refuses
Over and over and over again
People see her stumbling on the street
They're leaning out of their car
"Hey you! Hey you mate! What's going on lady?"
"You look like you're not feeling good"
She walks away
Couples are walking on the street
They see her, "Hey honey, do you need help?"
She walks away
She's refusing all this help
And we have this footage of her walking down the street
When her friends get home, she's not there
The next day, they can't find Libby
That feeling
As a kid, you know, you're babysitting
You're sibling and they go missing
That's happened to me a couple times
You're like Jason, you're a terrible babysitter
You know what I mean?
Like they go running off or do something stupid
And you're like, "Dude, where are you man?
I'm trying to find you"
And you're mad
Because you know that they're just kind of messing around
But at the same time you get that pit in your stomach
But I've only had that happen for maybe like 20-30 minutes
You're like 20-30 minutes Jason, you are a bad babysitter
Can you imagine that happening for 24 hours?
48 hours
We put Libby in the cab
The cab took her back home
We don't know what happened
Authorities are called to police
Start reviewing this video
And they see this young woman walking down the street
And they see person after person
Reaching out to her
Trying to help her
She's freezing cold and clubbing clothes
She's horribly, horribly drunk
One thing the police notice in these videos
Is cars pulling up
And people leaning out or getting out of the car
And asking if she needs help
And her refusing to help
And then the car continue on
But a couple times
They see the same car
Following her down the street
Seems to be stalking her
They start to try to identify this vehicle
The police continue to view video
To try to find all the different angles
Of what could have happened to Libby
And they do find that at one point
This car stops
A man gets out of the car
Begins talking to Libby
They'd seen this happen before
But then he puts his arm around Libby
And leads her to the passenger seat
She gets in the car
And the car drives away
March 20th, 2019
Seven weeks after Libby's squire has vanished
They find her body
Floating in the Humber Estuary
She'd been in the water for so long
They don't know how she died
But they do notice some bruises on her
That could be signs of strangulation
And there also appears to be
It's hard to tell because
The body had been in the water for seven weeks
They're assuming
Signs of rape
So they think it wasn't an accident
They don't think she just stumbled off into the darkness
So an estuary
I had to look this up
An estuary is where a large river
Meets a stream basically
So they believe at some point
She had fell into the water
Or had been pushed into the water
Or disposed of if she was already dead
And she'd been floating around this entire time
Until her body was finally recovered
But they believe they have a murder investigation
On their hands
It does happen
We covered that a long time ago
When we talked about all those people
I think we were talking about the happy face killers
That whole theory about all the people who are found
Drowned in the rivers and the waterways in America
I'll post links in the show notes
But we see the same thing happened in
Holland, I believe it is
Where they have a thing where young men
Just a weird thing that young men do
They leave bars, they have to urinate
They're super drunk
And in Holland
They do it a lot, they pee into the canals
That's where the Holland is
One of the canals in the water, right?
And they fall in
And in America, the happy face killer
Conspiracy theory is that there's a gang of people
Who are pushing young college aged men
Into the rivers and the streams of America
And it's counting for all these deaths
There's two homicide detectives that have been investigating it
For decades
I did an episode on it a long time ago
And in Holland, they have the same thing
They don't think it's a serial killer
They know that this is a common occurrence
It's tragic every single time
It's called death by misadventure
I believe is what it's classified as
But they think someone who's drunk
They're walking around in the dark, it's easy to fall in a river
And they're drunk, they can barely walk
They're not going to be able to swim
So they're looking at that, but they're also looking at this car
And they do identify the driver of it
His name is Paul Well-Reloids
26-year-old husband of two children
Now he denies it
Right
They're talking to him and he goes, "I don't know what you're talking about"
Like, I didn't kill anybody
Everyone knows the story of Libby Squire
It's a big missing persons case in England
But I didn't do anything
I'm married, I have two kids
I don't need to be out on the street murdering people
And they go, "But here's the thing, Paul Well
We have you on video, we have you on video
Following her in the car
We have you on video getting out
And leading her to the passenger seat
And Paul Well goes, "Okay, well here's the thing
I did that
But I didn't murder her
And I didn't murder anybody"
And they go, "Well, then what happened?"
This might be the worst alibi
Ever
And we just recently called, covered story
But a guy says he was possessed by a ghost
He's using that as his defense
He says, "Okay, here's the thing, you're right
You do have me on video doing this stuff"
Let me tell you the whole story
I was at McDonald's, I was eating some McDonald's
Late at night
And I said, "Oh, I'm done with this
Normally people don't live in McDonald's
I'm done eating my McDonald's, it's time to leave
And he goes, "I'm driving around the city
And I'll be honest with you guys
I was looking for
Some strange
I was looking to bang a girl
Because I do like having sex with women
Even though I have a wife
I wanted a little something on the side
He's totally up front about that
And he goes, "So I'm driving on the road
And I see this fairly attractive young woman
And she's dressed like she's at the club
And she must have been so cold outside
So I actually got out
And invited her into the car
And I'm like, "Okay"
He says, "We had come to the conclusion
That we were gonna have sex
She wanted to have sex with me, I'm a very attractive man"
He says, "This is the two cops looking at each other
I'm a very attractive man
And we needed a place to go
Obviously we can't take her back to my place
Because of my wife and two children
So we drove out to this field
We drove out to this field
And the police are like, "You mean the field?"
The field by the stream
Yeah, yeah, the field that has easy access
To the waterways, yeah, we went out to that field
And we had sex
We had 100% consensual sex
Now you see these scratches on my face
You see these scratches on my face here
And the police are like, "We didn't see those scratches
Until you pointed them out"
And he's like, "Oh great"
Well these scratches on here are on my face
Because after we had sex
I realized that I'm a married man
And I had to go home
And she was so mad I wouldn't have more sex with her
Because I'm such a sex machine
That she scratched me
Because I said, "No more sex"
The cops are like, the cops are taking notes
They're like, "This guy is moron"
And he goes, "I'll tell you what, I'll tell you what
She scratched me
And I got off of her because
I didn't want to have sex with her anymore
Because she scratched me"
It's like this Schrodinger scratch
Which happened first
And the cops go, "Why didn't you just take her home
At that point?" And he goes, "Well the problem is
Is she was so drunk"
And really at this point he's admitted to raping her
Because she's so drunk
And he said that she was so drunk
But he goes, "She was so drunk
So I may sexually assault a drunk woman
But there is no way I would let her
Vomit in my car
What type of monster do you think I am, officers?"
So I left her
In the park
And she was totally alive when I left, officers
She was totally alive when I left
And they're like, "Well, she was freezing cold"
"Yeah, I was kind of cold down, I probably"
"You know you're right, I probably should have done something"
"She might have stumbled into the waterway"
Apparently she did, officers
But I don't know what happened
Or after she left, I actually
Left her in that field, totally alive
And I went to go eat some McDonald's
The police are like, "That's suspicious"
"No one eats McDonald's twice in one day"
And he's like, "Dang it, my alibi has been blown"
They do have him on video at McDonald's
Twice in one day, that actually did not
That actually did not have anything to do
That is true, but it is not what caused the
Break in the case
So all of this stuff comes out in trial, right?
His alibi that he does, they're showing this
In real footage, and
A bunch of other stuff came out as well
Because you could argue that
Like, that is a, you've just admitted to rape
You're gonna do some time for that
But a good defense lawyer could probably argue that
Yes, he did all that stuff
Why a client is a total disgusting human being
But he didn't murder her
Someone else may have come along and murdered her
After the fact
Or, that's where the bruises came from
That it was rough sex and she walked into the river afterwards
So like, a good defense lawyer could argue that stuff
But
Here's some other factors that happened
They go and get into his car
They find a bag of sex toys
He's like, "Eh, everyone has sex toys"
He used underwear
Not his
And not his wife's
It was stolen underwear
From other women's houses
And he says, "No, no, no, I don't know why you're getting this whole
Stealing from women's houses thing"
"I don't know where those came from"
"When I bought the car, it had a complimentary bag of sex toys
And used women's underwear"
They also found in the trunk of his car
A scream mask
You know, ghost face
And a clown mask as well
The police begin to investigate him
And they realize that Paul Well
Has been convicted several times
Of sex crimes
Now they're really on to the sky
They're reviewing footage, they're looking at all this stuff
It turns out that not
This information is not
That not, this information did not come out during the trial
He was found guilty
Of the murder of Libby Squire
Because they have the video footage
He basically placed himself at the scene
His defense lawyer really had no argument
He definitely raped the woman
She was too drunk
Too drunk, she was so drunk she was about to throw up
He was found guilty
So now we're in the sentencing phase
And that's when even more information came out
Because you can't always reveal this information when you're trying
It's such a weird thing, like you're being tried for that crime
So that you usually can't bring other crimes in
Oh, it turns out he's a sex pest
He's been committing sex crimes for years
Earlier that night
Before he killed Libby Squire
He was masturbating outside of a woman's house
While watching her
He had done that earlier that night
And there were other instances of him
Masturbating, breaking into women's houses
Stealing their underwear, masturbating into the underwear
And creepy of all
I find this deep in the dark
And I find this deep in the dark
And creepy of all
I mean, we're talking about a young murdered woman
And all of the lie
I mean, can you imagine being one of her friends?
It's hard to place ourselves in the position of the murder victim
Right?
But can you imagine being one of those friends
Like we've all been in those situations
Where we've been like, "Hey dude, you're not good to drive"
"Oh no, I can totally drive bro"
We've all been in situations like that
And most of the time they work out
But it only takes one time for it not to work out
And the friends who just go, "Well, we're gonna go club"
"And we'll send you home the cab driver"
Every single person who stopped
Those are us, those people are us
We can't, it's hard for us to sympathize with Libby
I mean, we can definitely
And we don't want to empathize
Or sympathize or care anything about Paul Well
But we can all
We've all been that person on the road
And seen something weird
Seen it and been like, "Hey, are you okay?"
So yeah, I mean imagine being those people
We can imagine that
And trying to help
I almost feel like so many guardian angels
Were sent down that night
I know that sounds really highfalutin
Maybe to, you know, New Agey
But I think everyone had
A message in their heart that night
"Hey, try to help this woman"
"Try to help this woman"
It's several times they have on CCTV
But it didn't help, she was killed
And so that's all creepy in and of itself
But after he murdered her
He went home and he watched porn
He was watching porn after he had just raped
And murdered this woman and earlier in the night
He was masturbating, staring in women's windows
Watching them
It's still not enough
He goes home and he watches porn
And he's masturbating again
And then
They have video of him in the middle of the night
Walking out into the field
Where he says this was the last
What they imagine is he took her out to the field
He had sex with her, she fought back
He murdered her, and that's probably
How it was
Probably wasn't consensual at all
He murdered her, he got off on it
But he goes back to the
And then disposed of her body in the river
Because they didn't find her out in the field
She was just floating in the water for so long
He goes back to the field where he had
Murdered her
And there's video of him
This is so creepy because I can just imagine it
They showed this video during the sentencing
Apparently I don't think they showed it during the trial
Oddly enough
But I could be wrong in that detail
Because information came out in different phases
And different articles and stuff like that
But this would have been the end of the trial
It would have been a one day trial
Had this video been released
There's video footage of Pawe
Walking into the field
And he's masturbating in the darkness
That's terrifying
That
That image to me
Is so terrifying
That is a man whose blood lust
Cannot be satiated
He just raped and murdered a woman
Went home, watched porn
Went back to the spot where he
Raped and murdered the woman
After the body had been disposed of
He didn't go back to clean up evidence
He didn't go back to tie any loose ends
He went back
And just jacked off
And he just took off his clothes
And he was like
"What the hell is this?"
"What I wanted to cover it was that final image
that really creepy
image of that man just masturbating in the darkness
He's celebrating
his crime
He's celebrating and who knows if he's done this before
right?
But the other reason I wanted to cover it was because of all the people
helping out. I think that's a
interesting part of the story
in an alternate universe, damn it
in an alternate universe
I don't mean to be make light of it
but one of those people were able to get her home
but she kept on walking into the darkness
until the darkness
finally took her away
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com
is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio
Twitter is @DeadRabberRadio
DeadRabberRadio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day
listen to it today. Have a great one. Thanks
[Music]