What would you do if you drove out to a bridge in the middle of the night?
And there was a baby there.
A baby who wanted you as his new mom.
And then we travel back to the year 1982 to meet a legendary rocker on tour in America.
Everything was going according to plan until the aliens froze his genitals.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
It's a countdown to Halloween.
Unless you're not listening to what the day came out, for all I know it's March 2032.
But either way, either way, I hope you're getting ready for Halloween.
But someone who's always ready for Halloween, no matter what month it is, walking into Dead
Rabbit Command is our newest Patreon supporter.
Dressed up as a giant bumblebee, everyone give it up for Gertie Gwynnorn.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in, she's shaking her little behead.
It was that close.
Gertie Gwynnorn.
Is her name?
I believe, I believe she sent me the correct pronunciation and hopefully I said it right.
Gertie, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't swear to Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about this show.
That really, really, really helps out a lot.
Gertie, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Fly us on out with your little bee body to Delaware.
For all I know she's allergic to bees, she's like, that's the last thing I would dress
up as.
But flying out there, flying out there, apparently if you dress up in the costume, you are the
costume, you got six arms and you're super tiny, you're flying us out to Delaware.
Now we're going to take a look at some very interesting ghost stories in Delaware.
I hope you guys like this ghost story a day for the month of October because I'm never
doing it again.
We've covered a lot of really good ghost stories, but man, we fly all the way out to Delaware
and it's late at night.
It's about 2, 3 in the morning and we're out in the outskirts of Smyrna, Delaware.
There's this little stone bridge there, not like cobblestone, not like old timey.
It's concrete, I guess probably a better way to describe it, a more accurate way.
There's this concrete bridge out there.
It's not spooky looking.
I imagine when I read this story, I imagine it was going to be like wooden with a couple
beams missing a couple ruined cars in the lake below.
I actually don't even know if there's running water under here.
I might just cross a canyon.
Like Jason should be the one doing all this research so you can accurately tell the story.
Well yeah, probably, probably, but anyways, there's this concrete bridge here and it's
known as Cry Baby Bridge.
Now Cry Baby Bridge, these stories are everywhere, almost every city.
I won't say every city in the world, but in a lot of especially rural locations, there
are Cry Baby Bridges and the phenomenon is this.
You go out to this bridge late at night, you hear a baby crying underneath the bridge.
Which would be alarming.
I would say this, as a ghost hunter, if you find yourself going to a place called Cry
Baby Bridge late at night and you do hear a baby crying anywhere around you, under the
bridge and the bushes or whatever, don't assume it's a ghost.
Don't just assume it's a ghost.
It might be a live baby.
I wonder how many people want to get rid of their kids and they go, "Oh man, I really
don't like this kid anymore, but I can't go to prison for murdering it."
This episode got dark real quick.
What if I took my baby and dropped him off at that Cry Baby Bridge everybody's talking
about?
Then the baby would cry in the darkness all night long and no one would discover him.
Anyone died due to the elements, man.
This got really dark.
I don't think that's ever happened.
I don't think anyone has wanted to get rid of their baby and then also driven to a remote
location of an urban legend to do it.
But who knows?
Who knows?
It's possible, right?
In an infinite timeline in multiple universes, I'm sure on one of them that scenario has
happened, but Cry Baby Bridges are super common.
So when we look at Dellawares or Smyrna Dellawares version of the Cry Baby Bridge, you think,
"Oh, we're standing out on this concrete bridge it's late at night and you hear this
baby crying."
And after a good two, three hour long search party as you're like, "Jason, trust me, that's
not a real baby.
It's a ghost baby."
And it's like, "But we have to be sure.
Infinite timelines."
After we're all done searching for this baby.
There's no baby.
It's actually a ghost baby.
We go, "Well, you know, this is typical of the Cry Baby Bridge phenomenon.
We have these babies crying in the middle of nowhere."
What's interesting is this one also has some of the hallmarks that we see of Cry Baby
Bridges where if you park your car in the middle of the bridge and put it in neutral,
it'll roll backwards.
It's supposed to be ghosts.
It's not because the bridge is angled or anything like that.
It's supposed to be ghosts pushing it.
We see that a lot.
That happens a lot in these Cry Baby Bridges things.
Sometimes they'll put a baby powder on the back of the car to taunt the baby.
You'll never have this.
You'll never have baby powder.
You put baby powder on the back of your car.
Sometimes these bridges aren't necessarily baby related.
There are a bunch of kids have died.
This show is so dark.
This show is, I never meant for it to be so disturbing.
But all of these stories involve dead children.
All of these ghost stories involve dead children.
You put baby powder on the back of a car and they say that your car will roll in a certain
direction and you'll see a little hand prints of all the kids who had died on the bridge
because a train hit them or something like that.
And now they're trying to push your car out.
They're pushing your car into the train.
You're like, "No, no, stop it.
Two more payments and it's mine."
These are very common phenomenon in these areas.
The reason why we're at Smyrna Delaware though is that this one has some unique characteristics.
This story goes like this.
At Smyrna Delaware, a long time ago, a teenage mother gave birth to a little baby boy.
"Ugh, uh, get out of there.
Uh."
And it comes out and she's like, apparently she did this in like a wood shack or something
like that.
There was no doctors around.
She gives birth to her own baby and she goes, "Oh, baby, my favorite baby, my only baby.
I'm gonna call you my wood shack baby."
And she goes to hug it and then she realizes that her baby is super deformed.
So she takes her baby out to...
It wasn't called the crybaby bridge before this.
It was just called like bridge 81 or whatever.
Country road bridge.
She takes her baby out to this remote bridge and she's like, "See you later."
And she chucks the baby off the bridge.
That would be the birth of...
Or if there's bad choice of words, that would be the start of any crybaby bridge legend.
Usually a baby has to die for the crying to be heard.
But the reason why she chucked this baby off a bridge was its deformity.
And its deformity was he had huge legs.
So regular baby head, regular baby body, but these massive legs, these big meaty thighs
and calves that any bodybuilder would die for, she chucks it off the bridge, she goes home.
And so at the crybaby bridge in Smyrna, this deformed baby's ghost still roams this area.
And sure it'll cry.
It'll cry in the darkness for you.
And sure your car will roll, put your car in neutral, which I've never...
Every car will roll in neutral, but anyways, roll uphill.
This baby wants a new mom.
This baby grew up in a canyon.
But didn't grow up.
He died.
He died pretty quickly.
He was checked into a canyon, but this baby wants a mom.
And this baby has some powers to ensure that you may be its next mother.
Now I've never seen this before in a crybaby bridge story.
What happens is if you go to the crybaby bridge late at night, you'll find...
This actually sounds quite terrifying.
I can't imagine a scenario where this would be any good.
Your doors all lock.
All the car doors lock.
Click, click, click, click.
What?
We can't get out.
Well, why would we want to get out?
There's a ghost baby running around and it locked their doors magically.
Good.
We'll just stay in the car.
Then this ghost baby will roll your windows down.
That's such a bad combination, right?
Being locked in a car with your windows rolled down.
Now you're just vulnerable.
You can't get out, but something can get in.
Right?
Something baby-sized.
If it was a full-sized man outside my car.
Not being able to roll my windows sucked.
I remember once I picked a fight with a guy and I was driving a convertible Mustang and
I kept cutting this guy off.
I think he cut me off once, so then I kept cutting him off on purpose.
I was being a jerk to put it lightly, right?
And I was like laughing and I kept cutting him off and I'm like, "This is like on a city
street too."
Which wouldn't have been any better if it was in the middle of the country.
Suddenly he cut me off, the light turned red, and he jumped out of his car with a crowbar.
And I don't have a roof on my car.
I don't have any way to protect myself and I'm like, "Uh-oh."
I figured something like this might happen, but I guess I should have known what's going
to happen.
My brains are going to get bashed in.
I'm in a car stuck in traffic with no roof.
A guy just jumps out with his crowbar.
I almost became a ghost that day.
His girlfriend jumps out and is trying to drag him back to his car.
I'm sorry, bro.
I'm so sorry, dude.
I didn't even see you there.
I'm sorry.
Then he got back in his car and I cut him off.
The light turned green.
I slid right in front of him.
Almost caused a big car accident because I just slid right in front of him.
I sped off and laughed and I made sure he knew I was laughing.
I was waving at him and stuff like that.
So I know what it's like.
I know what it's like to be a Dennis the Menace type character in an automobile.
I know what it's like to be trapped in an automobile even though I had no roof.
My options are really limited.
So when those roll down, you're locked in the car.
There's a baby.
There's a baby out there.
A ghost baby.
And then, because this guy has such massive legs, what he does is he kicks over trees
and he makes trees fall down on the bridge and then you definitely can't get away.
And then he goes, "Mama?
Mama feet, baby.
Mama."
And he starts walking towards the car all slow and creepy.
I guess he could totally walk with a strut like he owns the place.
It's terrifying.
It doesn't matter how he's walking.
It's a ghost baby with massive legs who just kicked down a bunch of trees and blocked your
escape.
What's interesting is, so here we have this story on the one hand.
We have so many tales of the Crybaby bridges that it's just a no one phenomenon.
All over the world you can find a Crybaby bridge.
What makes this one interesting is the deformed baby kicking over trees.
At this point you have to go, "How much of it is true?"
Like, "Jesus, probably none of it.
Probably none of it.
It involves a super strong baby kicking over trees."
But it says that this baby is always looking for his mom and people are always going out
here.
Like, I just randomly found a group of ghost hunters.
These two ghost hunters who were driving out there trying to hear the baby.
They didn't hear anything.
And then they said, "As we were out there another car pulled up so we left but we figured
they were also just some kids out there trying to find a ghost baby."
Like, a lot of people are going out here.
You have to wonder, "How many people have gone missing?
How many trees have been kicked over?"
Probably none.
Right?
But it's an interesting story because it's such a bizarre, it's such a specifically
bizarre ghost story.
A mutant baby kicking over trees.
I wonder if they have had, like, one time back in the 1950s, a tree just happened to
fall over and they connect.
They then back, then they made up the story about how did that tree fall over?
"Oh, the baby wants to kick it over."
They're like, "You're an idiot."
Do you think that's a reasonable explanation?
It might have been that hurricane that was going on.
I don't know where the mutated baby came in.
Obviously, I couldn't find any proof of this.
There were no news reports of a teenage mother throwing her baby off the bridge and then
getting arrested and stuff like that.
And as she's being dragged off to the jail, she's like, "You should have seen his legs.
You should have seen his legs.
You would have done it too.
You would have thrown him off the bridge."
None of that.
So I don't know how we went from a cry baby, a very standard cry baby bridge story, to
a mutant baby with big old calves.
But an interesting story nonetheless.
And the next story we're going to see also in Delaware kind of makes you think that
Delaware hates children.
That's kind of what I'm thinking here.
Because on the other side of Smyrna, we're still in Smyrna, "Gertie, let's go ahead
and have you drive the Jayson Jalopy around town.
We're headed out to the Vila House."
The Vila House is another ghost story that I really tried to find some proof that had
happened.
And it's one of those stories that I'm glad I didn't find anything.
Because this one's absolutely horrifying.
We walk into the Vila House and people are like, "What are you guys doing here?
We're like, "Albert Ghost Hunters, don't worry about it."
We're sitting in the living room and we see a little boy standing in the corner of the
room.
That kid actually is dead.
That's a ghost you're looking at.
And at that point you notice that the boy is holding a funnel.
He's just holding a funnel.
And you'll see him kind of walk around the living room holding this funnel.
We're trying to throw ping pong balls in it.
That's a whole ghost story.
There's a little boy who walks around with a funnel in this house.
But you go with, "Why?
Why is this kid walking around with this funnel?"
Apparently, again I wasn't able to find any proof of this and I'm very, very thankful
I wasn't able to.
Apparently at this house, some people say this happened before the house was even built
there.
That this house was built on his grave.
Other versions of the story said this happened in the villa house.
But this young boy had a horrible father, horrible, horrible dad.
And one day the dad was like, "I'm super crazy today."
And he tied up his son, stuck a funnel in his mouth, and poured gasoline down the boy's
throat.
And then, you guys kind of know where this is going unfortunately, right?
No one's like, "Oh, I'm done.
You're full of gasoline."
He poured gasoline down this kid's throat, poured gasoline all over this kid's face,
and he lit the boy on fire.
Burned him up.
And so that's why he's standing there holding the funnel in this house.
Other people say that at this house sometimes when you're in the bathroom, of course, I
hate bathroom, ghost is the scariest.
When you're in the bathroom, you know when you shut the light off and there is that moment
where you hit the switch and it goes from light to dark.
There's like a brief moment in between that it's never instantaneous.
In the moment as the light is going off, but before full darkness has enveloped you, you'll
see the boy standing behind you in the mirror.
I would rather be walking around the house the whole time than that.
That's just terrifying.
I guess if he was walking around when I was taking a shower, that's the worst of both worlds.
But funnel or no funnel, this boy may have died in this house.
Again, I couldn't find any proof that this horrible crime actually happened.
One of the reasons why I wanted to highlight that one, and we'll move on to the next story
in a second, but I want to highlight that one because we'll see this from time to time.
We'll see ghosts holding their instrument of destruction, the way that they died, they
will continue to have it in the afterlife.
It's not super common, but I wonder why that is.
Because not everyone who gets their head chopped off walks around with an axe, not everyone
who gets hung walks around with a noose, but every show often we'll see ghosts like this,
where they are holding something that killed them.
I have another story coming up that also has that characteristic of it.
It's fairly rare.
The boy walking around holding a funnel for the rest of his life.
For all I know, he loved funnels.
It was his favorite activity, and his dad just got tired of it and put a funnel in his
mouth one day.
I don't know.
I don't know why some ghosts have this.
I also don't know why some ghosts have gory, bloody heads chopped off.
And then there are people who died in the Civil War who were like walking around their home
in a crisp uniform, even though they got gangrene and their leg was sawed off on some table
in the middle of Charlottesville.
I don't know why some ghosts appear whole and some don't.
Why some ghosts hold the way or carry the way that they've died into the afterlife.
But just a fascinating story.
Gertie, Gwyn Inor, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the world famous Carpenter
copter we are leaving behind Delaware.
We are headed all the way out to Richmond, Virginia.
The year is 1982.
We're in Richmond, Virginia.
We're at a Sheraton hotel.
Actually we're working there.
We all got jobs as bell hops and maids and I'm the manager.
I'm Mr. Moseby.
Oh, second Cody, you stop it.
We're all working at the Sheraton hotel.
And I was like, you guys better keep those rooms spick and span because the band The
Kinks is coming here soon.
And you're like, yes, sir.
And you're like marching around and you're cleaning stuff up and brushing things.
And I'm sitting there and I'm like, my favorite band, The Kinks.
They're the ones who have that song.
You really like me now.
Or what is it called?
Yeah, you really like me now.
And I'm like sitting there and I'm humming it to myself and you're just like, oh man,
what a lousy boss.
That's not even the name of the song.
Did he not write down the name of The Kinks number one song?
I'm just sitting there and listening to The Kinks on my record player and I was like,
dude, I can't believe The Kinks are coming to this hotel.
And then I hear a bunch of girls outside the hotel screaming.
And I was like, oh, that must be The Kinks.
And sure enough, I walk outside the office.
We're all standing in line like we have like basically when the emperor was on the Death
Star where all standing in these lines.
And The Kinks are walking in the Sheraton hotel.
You got some guys that didn't write down their names, but the one we're going to look at is
Dave Davies.
This 35 year old dude, he's the member of The Kinks.
And I'm like, Dave Davies, you're my favorite one.
The reason why I only wrote your name down and they're like, what?
I'm like, The Kinks, you're so good.
I love all your music.
I love that one song especially.
And I'm shaking their hands and we're all like shaking the hands of all these.
How many people are in The Kinks?
I don't know.
But Dave Davies, he's like, oh, Bollocks, another hotel in the old colonies.
Yes.
I'm used to playing music over here because I'm in The Kinks, but something's wrong.
And we see him kind of wander off.
So we're like, we don't care about the other members of The Kinks.
So we're kind of following Dave Davies.
He's walking through the hotel and he's like, why does my body feel so weird?
And he walks into his room and he lays down on his bed and we're hanging out.
We're just standing over him as he's laying in bed.
He's like, oh, my body.
Why do I not feel like me old self?
And then, beamed into his nose are the strongest smells he's ever smelled.
He sits up straight and goes, ah, lie me.
That is pure frankincense.
Oh, is that a bit of rose vinegar?
Ah, yes.
Lilex in the spring.
So why am I smelling all of these smells?
Why are they, he described these things as being so fragrant.
It was like you could scoop them up with a spoon.
He smells all of these smells just obliterating his nostrils in a good way.
It's that good kind of obliteration.
And what he comes to realize is he is being contacted by five mystical beings.
Is not just from another world, but from another reality, another dimension.
A place so unlike what we know as reality, they have truly ascended over all reality.
He says that these smells are actually the way that these five mystical beings are talking
to him.
He's able to decipher the smells to receive these messages from the ascended ones.
Now I know what you're thinking.
He's having a stroke, right?
He's having some sort of serious medical complication that's causing him to hallucinate these smells.
Now I've mentioned before on this show when I get really, really, really stressed out,
I will hallucinate smells.
That's when I know that I need some rest.
I'll actually start to smell raw sewage.
It's not because I'm walking by a Taco Bell.
It's not because I'm walking by a Taco Bell dumpster.
I can smell raw sewage wherever I go.
And that's when I know I'm too stressed out.
That's when I kind of got to take a step back.
So I mean you would think maybe this guy's having a stroke.
Maybe this guy's under a bunch of stress.
But no, he's not having a stroke.
He's actually smelling these smells that don't exist.
He's actually able to decipher what they're telling him.
Then, while he's on tour in America, all of this stuff is going on, he feels himself float
outside of his own body.
The thing that is truly Dave Davies has now left his physical form.
He's floating around the hotel room.
He's like, "Oh, this is kind of weird."
But I'm not having a stroke.
This is totally fine.
Remember the kinks.
He continues to smell the smells.
He continues to feel like he's outside of his body.
And as this tour is going on, at one point he feels like a bow constrictor.
A unseen bow constrictor begins to wrap around his forehead and starts to squeeze tighter.
And tighter.
He can feel the immense pressure inside his brain.
He feels like his head's going to crack open.
My Jesus, this guy's clearly having some sort of medical emergency.
All this stuff is happening in a matter of days.
I think it happens over the course of a month or two.
And he's hallucinating smells.
He's floating outside of his body.
That's never a really good thing if you do it accidentally.
He feels like his head's about to pop open.
Well, luckily it's not a medical event.
Luckily, because the voice is in his head, starts to tell him, "Hey, no, no, no, it's
cool.
We were tickling your nose with descents.
We were communicating with you that way."
And now are these voices in your head.
So we can talk to you directly.
But, be careful what you say about us.
Be careful what you say about us.
Don't reveal everything we're going to tell you.
Now he was at the time dating a woman named Nancy Evans.
And he started telling her what was going on, but only certain parts because the five
ascended ones were telling him, "We're going to say this, but don't tell Nancy.
Don't tell Nancy this part."
Now that is super typical with schizophrenia.
That is super typical with hearing voices, right?
The voices may actually, they know that these outside people exist in your life, these family
and these friends and these loved ones, and they will try to get you to deceive them.
Oh no, everything's fine, everything's fine, they'll tell you not to tell them they exist
or they'll tell you certain things and they'll say, "But don't tell Nancy I said that."
Again, it sounds like a serious medical event.
All of these things, if you went to a doctor, you would get diagnosed with some, you'd
probably be hospitalized.
Now I've been using the term the ascended masters.
He uses the term the intelligences.
That's what he calls these five mystical beings that are communicating with him and they begin
to reveal truths to him.
They say humans exist in a sea of energy.
What we see as reality is not truly the reality.
We're actually just swimming in this wide open ocean of nothing but pure energy, much
like fish, right?
When you say you're swimming in energy, he compares the intelligences and pair us to
mental fish swimming unaware through the ocean.
It is also revealed by the intelligences that nearby Earth there is a massive spaceship
that has computers on it and in these computers there is information about every man, woman
and child who have ever lived on the planet Earth.
I don't know if that includes mutant babies and Delaware, but every single person who has
ever lived on Earth, their information is stored in these computers.
These aliens or these intelligences also tell him that they want to help him evolve to a
higher vibrational level.
They want to help him ascend.
And the way to do that is to stop having sex.
He's a rock and roller.
He was with a band called the Kinks, right?
They got to live up to their name, but he is told no more sex.
And almost like they could tell he wouldn't be able to stick to that one, the aliens numbed
his entire genital region, actually his entire pelvis.
And he goes, "Listen, I could walk totally normal.
I could walk, I could do a little dance, I could play the guitar and put my leg up on
one of the speakers.
Wano, no, no, no, no, you got me going."
But I couldn't feel my junk.
It was completely numb.
Now listen, when I was reading this I go, "This guy's clearly had a stroke.
If not a stroke, an aneurysm, or some sort of medical condition.
These all could be explained away by underlying mental illness finally coming to the surface,
a physical illness coming to the surface, leaving your body feeling parts of your body
being numb, very least a really bad pinched nerve, but also a stroke like he can't feel
parts of his body."
But it's funny because when I read the story, that's what I was thinking.
I read a bunch of different sources on this because Dave Davies is really, really open
about this.
And I think that's fascinating too.
He ended up writing a book called "Living on a Thin Line," which I guess is the name
of one of his songs or a line from one of their songs.
He's written two autobiographies and in his second autobiography he talks about the story
and he goes, "Yeah, I was going through all this stuff.
These intelligences were communicating with me."
And at the time in 1982, when they're on tour, he's giving press interviews.
He's talking to radio DJs.
He's talking to newspaper.
You know, as you're coming into towns, the local media does a story on them to talk
about, "Hey, the kinks are coming here.
The kinks sell more tickets to their concerts because people are going to go see them because
they're writing about the newspaper, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
Davies was able to take a look at reality and madness.
Dave Davies was able to take a look at these amazing messages
he was getting from the intelligences
and compare it to the day to day life,
the day to day reality we all live.
He was able to look at those two and tell the difference
between the madness and the sanity.
But tomorrow we'll take a look at a man
who couldn't tell that difference
and truly innocent people
ended up losing their lives.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great day guys.
[Music]