Can a deadly drug actually be a cure?
Then we travel to Greece to take a look at four different encounters with bizarre humanoids.
Are they ghosts, aliens, demons?
Who knows?
But you'll find out today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
Let's go ahead and get started with the episode.
First off, let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, Eli Rack.
Eli Rack, round of applause.
Eli Rack doing a little bow over there.
You are going to be our captain this episode.
Whatever vehicles we take, you are going to be in charge of.
If you can't support the Patreon, totally understandable, just help me get the word out
about the show.
Spread it online.
Spread it in person.
Spread it as if it was a communicable disease.
That also helps out a lot.
But maybe don't use that as a, as if you're just coughing on people.
"Dead Rabbit Radio."
Maybe not that far.
Eli Rack, let's go ahead.
Let's start off in the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're going to take a little flight.
Across the nation, we're going to Stockton, California.
Meth, capital of the world.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's another meth story.
So just be prepared for lots of references to meth andphetamines.
This one I actually found on Reddit.
Like I always, I find all this stuff on Reddit because I go to the meth subreddit.
It's a guilty pleasure of mine.
I'm on the meth subreddit and there's a user named TeddyNobs, which this is why I go to
the meth subreddit.
Not because there's people named TeddyNobs, but this was popped upon on the meth subreddit.
Tell me you cannot click on this.
Here was the headline or post or whatever you call it.
I honestly believe, okay, coming from a meth, from one meth addict to another.
I honestly believe doing meth daily.
Okay, you just can't be an occasional meth user.
I honestly believe doing meth daily prevents you from catching COVID-19.
Hear me out.
Which I love how he adds that at the end because he obviously knows most people are like, "What?"
He's like, "No, no, no, no, no.
Hear me out."
And he goes on to say that he doesn't know any tweakers who have COVID-19.
So that's scientific proof right there, right?
But he goes, he goes, "Listen, tweakers," which is, if you don't know, tweakers, someone
who's super high on meth and they're working on cars, they're working on your car by stealing
the stuff out of it.
Come back here.
He goes, "Listen, tweakers don't have any of the safety precautions that are put in place
with COVID-19 stuff.
We don't social distance."
I mean, we pass a pipe around, right?
That's the worst thing.
We have this little pipe, we're smoking meth, and then I hand it to you and you're smoking
my meth and stuff like that.
We're hanging out, we're breaking into people's cars.
He didn't say that breaking into people's cars thing and stuff, but you know what I
mean.
Basically, they're repairing starter engines at three in the morning and then someone tells
them they found some springs in a dumpster.
So you ride your bicycle because you can't have a car, because you took it apart, you
ride your bicycle over to the dumpster and grab some springs because you'll want to need
them for that project you're working on.
That spring-powered car.
Basically, there's no social distancing or anything like that.
So at the end, then he goes, "Listen, if you know someone who has COVID-19 who's a daily
user," see, it's again, not you tourists, not you people who just use it on the weekend,
daily users only.
If you know someone who smokes meth daily, who's got COVID-19, let me know.
He posts this and people start going, "You're an idiot."
In the midst of people going, "Oh, no, no, no, I know people who smoke meth, but do they
do it daily?"
I would ask, but people would go, "I know people who smoke meth who've gotten COVID-19."
In the midst of all of that, somebody posts an article.
Meth may fight flu virus, steady suggests.
This was from covid19data.com.
It's written by Chino Contreras.
Ellie Rack, let's take this dirgeable and leave behind Stockton, California.
There's a couple bullet holes in it, so we got to get fast and got to refill it.
We're headed out to Taiwan.
We're going to land.
We're going to put on our lab coats.
We're going to walk into the National Health Research Institute in Taiwan.
This was back in November 6th.
They published the study, November 6th, 2019.
This study does not speak specifically about COVID-19, but let's go in there and we see
the scientists standing around and they're in their lab coats.
There's a lump of lung cells.
There's just a big old gross lump sitting on a table.
Looks like a slab of meat and the scientists are like, "Are you ready for tests?"
This is our first test.
We don't have a number for it.
They're like, "Yeah."
They expose the lung cells to meth.
I don't know how they did it.
I don't know if they brought in Johnny and he walks in.
He's like, "Hey guys, is it time?
Is it time?
I've been smoking meth anyways."
They're like, "Oh man, you're not supposed to smoke yet."
I don't know how they did it.
He smokes in.
He has this little meth pipe.
He smokes it in.
He smokes it all over the lung cells.
To be fair, they can't get in the article.
They said lung cells.
I don't know if they had a clump of lung.
I don't know if they had a human's lung just sitting there and a guy's blowing
meth into it like he's playing the bagpipes.
But let's just pretend.
The fact of the matter is they exposed lung cells to influenza A and then they infused
it with methamphetamine.
Then 30 to 48 hours after the infection.
So you've got the scientists sitting around calmly looking up the cells and then the meth
dude's like all bumping into him.
He's taking apart the laboratory.
He's like, "Oh dude, you know how many cool things I can do with this microscope once
I've taken it apart?"
They're like, "Ah, we need that."
They realized that the meth treated cells had a much lower concentration of the virus
than the control group.
What's more, this reduction occurred in dose dependent manner, meaning the more meth, the
less the virus reproduced.
What's interesting, so the doctors, they do see a correlation.
So this guy actually is onto something.
But they're saying, "We're not telling people to smoke meth.
We're definitely not telling people to smoke meth daily."
We're not saying that.
But now scientists are starting to look at this and they go, "If we can take something
that's structurally similar to meth, if we can take meth and modify it some way, take
away the tweakiness, take away the damage, take away all the bad stuff, take something
that's structurally similar to meth, we could actually prevent or possibly cure influenza
A."
So we're leaving behind Taiwan, Elirac.
Let's go ahead and hop in the carbonicopter.
The durgible has been stripped for parts at this point.
Johnny's already completely dismantled it.
There's just a balloon and a couple cinder blocks holding up the balloon.
Everything else is gone.
We're in the carbonicopter.
Elirac, we're leaving behind Taiwan.
We are headed out to good old Greece.
Okay, Elirac, let's go ahead and put that carbonicopter in a holding pattern actually
before we get to Greece because I'm going to give you guys a little meta commentary here,
a little behind the scenes thing.
This is 10 hours later I'm recording this part.
I did this thing about humanoids in Greece.
We're still going to do that segment because I think it's interesting.
But originally it was an interactive adventure.
It was horrible.
I recorded the whole thing.
It was bad.
It was funny.
I had a good time recording it, but it's really, really bad.
What's interesting and this is my tip to you for you artists out there.
You always want to do your best obviously, but you're never always going to do your best.
And I can get, whoa, that was like the best episode I've recorded.
That's great.
My first 50 episodes, there's some stinkers in there because I didn't know what made a
good Dead Rabbit Radio episode.
The key to actually like being an artist, not a lot of people talk about this.
The key to being an artist isn't always about putting out the best material.
It's about knowing when you've sucked, knowing when you've missed the target, knowing when
it's bad.
It's weird.
You want to do your best obviously, but every time you sit down with a pen and paper to
write a story or to start drawing a picture or to make music, it's not always about putting
out the best product possible.
It's about the craft.
It's about creating product.
There's artists who just dream and dream and dream and never do anything.
There's artists who labor so long trying to get the single best novel they can that they
never get past the world building phase.
They've written stuff down, but nothing as a narrative.
Or they start writing stuff and then they rewrite that first chapter, start writing
stuff, rewriting the first chapter.
It's not until you start actually putting out books, putting out stories, releasing
artwork to the public that you can start to go, "This is a good picture.
This is a bad picture."
It's part of that craft.
Kanye West.
Kanye West famously said, someone asked him about being a producer.
He says, "Make three beats a day every day for three summers."
That's how you become a great producer.
It's about the craft.
It's about building things.
If he just labored over the same beat over and over again or the same 10 beats or 20 beats
or whatever over and over and over again trying to perfect them, you have to build body of
work.
That's my motivation to you guys out there.
And also to let you know why I'm so much more subdued as I'm recording this part at
9.30 at night.
It's not always about creating the best single thing.
It's about working your craft over time, releasing stuff, releasing stuff and realizing what
works and what doesn't.
That is a not often things that about art.
And I think a lot of people just don't do that.
They just tinker, tinker, tinker on something for a long time.
Like I am with this introduction.
But I wanted to share that with you guys because I know a lot of you guys struggle with that.
Eli Rack, let's come out of that holding pattern.
We are headed finally to Greece.
Second time for me today.
First time for you.
First off, let's head back to the year 83 BC.
Helicopters flying over.
There's like pantheons and stuff.
Big old marble pillars in the middle of nowhere.
Yeah, we're like going in between them.
Nice flying Eli Rack.
We look back, there's rubble everywhere.
Not so nice flying.
But we are going to meet a dude named General Sola.
And he's like, has his army and stuff like that.
He's marching on Rome.
Second time, by the way, he originally took control of Rome, established himself as the
ruler and everyone's like, "Oh yeah dude, hey why don't you go out and fight that war
dude?"
And like us, the senate, we will make sure nothing bad happens.
And he's like, "Ah."
The way everyone's eyes is shifting back and forth at the same time makes me a little
suspicious.
But he ends up going, taking his army out to Asia Minor, which I believe is Turkey
nowadays.
Anyways, it obviously, he gets overthrown while he's gone.
The senate's like, "Yeah, we don't like that guy.
We totally lied to him."
They take back over to him and he's like, "Oh great, so now he has to walk all the way
back to Rome to show him who's boss."
And he eventually does, but before he does, he's actually moving with his troops through
a place in Albania called Dyratc.
That's apparently the modern place where it's at is Dyratc, and originally was the
Illyrian Apollonia, which I believe was one of Prince's backup singers that are, "This
is better than the original version!
This is better than the original version!"
As General Sola is moving with his troops, according to a dude named Plutarch, he was
like a historian, old-timey historian and stuff like that, he says that he heard a story.
That's how history was back in the day.
You just heard stories from people.
Someone was like, "Hey, you won't believe it.
I was out doing this stuff with General Sola and this happened."
And Plutarch goes, "That is going to go great on my blog."
Plutarch tells the story as General Sola was moving through the area in Albania.
They're walking through this place, it's just nothing but all green trees and meadows and
stuff like that, aka everything back then, right?
You either had a small town, everything else was untouched of urgent nature.
But anyways, so he's moving his troops through this area and General Sola is sitting there
with his leaders and stuff like that and they're trying to figure out battle maneuvers and these
soldiers run up, they're all sweaty because they've been running because they don't have
cars.
Everyone sweats because they're constantly running.
They're like, "General Sola, General Sola, you won't believe what we found."
And he's like, "This better be important."
And so he walks out of his tent and he sees this sader being restrained by his men.
"General Sola is like, "You're right, I do need to see this.
This is quite interesting."
You remember that movie Hercules?
This is the best example I can think of.
Remember Danny DeVito and Hercules?
That's a sader.
It's like this little dude, he had generally had horns on his head and then he had horse
legs to be specific.
And this guy, they're holding him and General Sola is like, "Hmm, the beast.
I've seen this beast before."
He actually said, Plutarch actually says, "This sader looked like what you would see
a statue of."
He actually wrote this, said, "Here they say a sader, such as statuaries and painters represent,
was caught asleep and brought before Sola."
Sometimes his names use this Sola, but I've seen Sully, I've seen all different names
for this dude, but...
So Plutarch's saying, "This is exactly what you would think of.
This was a little Danny DeVito goat man that they have in front of him."
And General Sola's first thinking, he doesn't say this out loud, I wonder what he tastes
like.
I wonder if this man creature is delicious, but he shakes the idea from his head.
He's not a barbarian, although he is a little curious.
Little man, horse legs, little horns on his head.
General Sola's like, begins to question this creature, like, "Where are you from?
How delicious are you?
What spices do you think would work best on your legs?
No matter what, soldiers are like, "What is going on?"
No matter what questions Plutarch asks this guy, he's just not responding.
He's giving off these grunts and these growls and all sorts of stuff.
And eventually Sola, as much as he is mystified by this whole thing and a little hungry, he
thinks this is a bad omen.
One, I'm not getting any information from this guy.
Like, it's not like this guy can actually have a conversation.
Two, this is a creature from beyond the veil.
Like, basically, I'm getting ready to march on Rome and talking to this goat, horse, whatever
he is, man, with little hooves, little legs, little hooves, is probably not a good thing.
So he bade his soldiers to just let it go.
And he's like, "Let it go into my kitchen."
And they're like, "Oh, that's weird."
And then they have like a giant pot boiling.
But that's not what happens as far as we know.
They just let it go.
And it's funny because you read that and you're thinking, "Who nowadays, like, imagine General
Schwarzkopf?"
And he's like going into Iraq during Desert Storm because I'm a boomer and that's my reference.
General Schwarzkopf is like, "We're moving troops through here and then like, we'll move
a tank over here."
And they're like, "Sir, sir, sir, look what we found."
And it's like a goat man, right?
I don't even have to make up another creature.
It's just a plain old sader.
General Schwarzkopf would be like, "Call the Pentagon."
And they would like put him in a Pentagon.
The Pentagon's like, "Hmm, I wonder what this guy tastes like."
They're running taste analysis on him.
And back then, one, if you captured him, you'd have to like take care of him and stuff like
that.
And then if he died, maybe it's a curse.
It's an omen.
They let him go.
So an interesting story, an interesting sighting of basically what would be encrypted nowadays.
Back then you could say with some sort of like nature spirit or things like that.
But let's take a closer look at this story.
In the early, early versions of the Sader myth, they had horse legs and horse tails
and then the upper body of a human, little horns on their head.
But by the 6th century BC, the legend had actually changed.
So even though Plutarch says this looks like you would see on the statues and you'd see
in the paintings, we don't know if he's talking about the paintings for before Solas time.
Because remember, Solas make in this March in 83 BC.
So for the past 500 years, a Sader was described as something different.
The top half's the man.
The bottom half is a man as well.
The point is regular human legs.
By his time period, Saders were described as just being all human but covered in hair,
bigfoot maybe, covered in hair.
Horse tails, tail of a horse, that's still weird.
And super ugly, which I guess is kind of implied with the horse tail coming out of you and
covered in hair.
Super ugly, big naked dude, giant horse sized boner.
So this is what's interesting.
The story says he captured a Sader and we're like, oh that's interesting.
But what he probably really found was a fully erect, ugly, hairy man in the middle of nowhere.
It's possible that he actually saw an ancient looking Sader from the old, old periods.
And that's what he saw.
Or he just saw an ugly, naked man with a big boner in the middle of the woods.
We don't know, but this is historical record, really.
About as close as to historical record as you could get back then.
There's always these weird little tidbits in the middle of these stories and you're
like, what?
Because it's all about him marching on Rome and someone would be like some dusty historian.
Historians not dusty.
A clean historian going through a dusty book, reading about Roman history would be like,
what?
Kind of naked dude with a big boner in the middle of nowhere.
Are you trying to eat him?
Oh, that's weird.
And then you just go on to the next paragraph because it's just too weird for those nerds
to comprehend.
Ellie Rack, let's go ahead.
We're taking that carbonic copter.
We're going a little bit farther in time.
We're going to go to the period of time before World War II.
Shortly before World War II.
Technically, that story was pre-World War II, but you know what I mean.
We're going to a place called Pentilichen Mountain in Attica.
A bunch of people in Greece just shook their head.
That's not how you pronounce it, bro.
But before World War II, there was a woman walking down this mountain pass and there's
this old, spooky house.
The house is known as the Planktacea Palace.
It's still around.
Apparently it was just an old house.
At this time, it was abandoned.
This woman's walking down the road and we're going to be walking down the road as well.
We're walking down the road.
Streets as dusty as a researcher.
As this woman's walking down the road, a little 10-year-old girl is coming the opposite direction.
She's not singing a creepy song.
She's walking down the street, right?
She's walking down the street, but this is kind of in the middle of nowhere.
So the woman's like, "Hmm, interesting.
That girl must be lost."
But before she can really comprehend what's going on, the little girl starts to...
change.
Her hair begins to start standing up straight.
Almost like a magnet is being brought over her head and her hair is metal.
Because otherwise a magnet wouldn't do anything.
Her hair starts standing up straight.
Ding!
And now she looks like kid.
Kid in play.
She already is a kid.
So her hair standing up straight and the woman's staring at this little 10-year-old girl.
Now as the girl is walking, she's still walking.
That doesn't deter her.
She's like, "I don't care how straight my hair is.
I'm going to keep on walking.
Nothing's going to stop my locomotion."
But once she crosses the path, so the woman's walking out one side of the road and the little
girl's walking towards her, the house is in between them.
And then as she's getting closer to the woman, she gets sucked into the house.
Now the woman obviously does not go after the girl.
She's not like, "I'll save you."
She beats feet.
Because what would you do in that case?
The question is this.
Was that girl real?
There's a couple different ways we can look at it.
We can look at it.
If the girl was real, she probably should have went to go find her.
But it's possible the girl was real.
She's walking on the street.
Her hair sticks straight up and she gets sucked into the house.
She's now a prisoner of Plaintasia Palace.
And she can never get rescued because no one can pronounce the name of that house if that
woman goes, "Oh, oh, I just ran into a horrible thing at Plaintasia Palace up in the Pentechalean
Mountain."
The authorities are like, "Those places don't exist, ma'am.
That's not how you pronounce anything in Greece.
We won't be able to help you."
And the woman's like, "No, it's possible."
Or here's an even creepier scenario.
I don't know.
The girl getting sucked into the house is kind of creepy.
Ghost activity, right?
And this ghost is actually trying to escape the house.
Every day it's getting a little bit farther out.
Maybe not every day.
Because then she eventually should be in downtown Athens.
But she's constantly, this little girl is trying to escape the grip of the house and
she's getting farther and farther away.
But whenever she passes a certain threshold, she gets sucked back into the house.
You can live there now.
I actually think people live in that house.
It is a real place that you can visit.
So if you decide to go visit this place, first off, I would recommend learning how to renounce
it.
The locals will not take kindly to you if you're calling it whatever I called it.
Secondly, I shave your head before you visit because you never know.
You know that's a bad idea because you'd want your hair to stand up that way you would
know you were about to get abducted into a house.
Let's go ahead and move on to the next one.
Eli Rack is flying the helicopter away.
Let's move on to this other place in Greece that I don't have a name for.
Eli Rack is like, "It's June 24th, 2001.
It's 1.50 a.m."
There's a university professor who's sitting at home.
He's the only one up at this time and he's watching some television.
Now this college professor goes by the initials GP.
He'd actually had two previous encounters with the paranormal.
Once in 1974, a woman comes knocking on his door and asks him for money.
He's like, "Well, it's kind of weird, but yeah, sure mate."
And before he can finish his sentence, she vanishes into thin air.
And he's like, "Well, that's a relief because I didn't really want to give her any money."
Also, in 1986, he was right.
He's riding a bus through town.
And he sees his mother-in-law on the bus.
That's not the weird part.
His mother-in-law was dead.
Not like...
Okay, it's not like she was a corpse on the bus.
And he's like, "Someone should do something about that.
Probably me because this corpse is sitting next to me."
Let me rephrase that.
So what 500 episodes does to you?
His mother-in-law had been dead before.
She'd already died.
And so was his ghost on the bus.
And he said, "Not only did I see my dead mother-in-law on the bus as a ghost, again, not as a corpse,
but she was there for five minutes.
It was on a fleeting glimpse.
He was looking at this ghost for five minutes, which is an extremely long time for paranormal
activity."
So June 24th, 2001, GP is watching television.
His wife and his son are sleeping in their respective bedrooms.
And his daughter is not home.
So her bedroom was unoccupied at this time.
And he's sitting there and he's watching television.
And then he's like, "Yeah, television's done.
Click.
Shut it off."
And he starts doing that routine.
We all do is we're going to bed.
You know, you kind of get up, make sure everything's shut off.
He's walking around his house.
He realizes the kitchen light is on.
He walks into the kitchen, shuts the light off, and he goes, "He instantly feels a cold
chill crawl over his skin."
He turns around and he sees this almost indescribable thing.
It's six foot two.
And he sees that all of its limbs are very lanky.
He sees a face devoid of any facial features, but where the eyes, the nose, the mouth should
be, there were just bumps.
He said it looked like computer graphic.
It looked like it was artificial, not artificial in the sense of it being robotic or plastic,
but artificial in the sense that it doesn't belong in our reality.
Everything mimicking our reality.
Trying to get a human face, trying to get a human body, but failing at it.
The limbs were too long.
The face knew where the features should be, but couldn't generate them.
It's standing there in the kitchen with him now.
Lights are off and he sees this thing standing there.
And then it begins to move.
But even that seemed like a mimicry of human movement.
He said it moved in large leaps, but it was in slow motion, like an athlete jumping a
hurdle but painfully slow.
The feet wouldn't touch the ground.
There was no noise as this was going on.
Right before the foot should touch the ground, it simply leaped again.
He watches it jump out of the kitchen and go into the bathroom.
The GP immediately follows it, goes in the bathroom, throws the light on, it's gone.
He turns around and sees that his daughter's bedroom door is open.
And this creature leaps out of his daughter's bedroom, slowly jumping, silently, back into
the kitchen.
He goes into the kitchen.
It's empty.
He turns and now it's jumping out of the bathroom, jumping through the house.
It leaps into the middle of the living room and completely disappears.
The whole encounter, he says, took about 30 seconds.
He's just watching this thing bound around his house.
This was very, very interesting.
GP said he got the impression that the creature was running from something.
He felt like the creature was hunted by something and wanted to avoid any contact.
So while this man is sitting in his house and he's watching this truly alien phenomenon
happen, he's not really scared.
And he senses fear from this creature.
Not afraid of him, but afraid of something.
They didn't belong in this man's house.
It didn't belong on this planet.
So if tonight, when you sit at home, maybe you're reading a book, maybe you're watching
television, maybe you're just lounging about listening to your favorite podcast, when it's
time for you to go to bed, you're gonna get up, do your little ritual, make sure your
lights are shut off.
But when you shut off that last light, don't turn around.
You may feel that cold wind on your skin, but don't turn around.
You may feel those eyes that aren't quite eyes staring at your direction, but don't
turn around.
Because even though GP had a bizarre experience and was able to report it to us, there's a
chance that this is more than just a one-off thing.
This thing was being pursued by something.
It was in fear of its life.
And it got away.
But who's to say that the next time this lanky, featureless creature appears behind you?
That the predator chasing it won't appear as well.
If you turn around and look, you may become a participant in this ghastly game of tag.
You may find yourself not retelling the story to appear in some weird podcast.
You may find yourself waking up in a world that you don't recognize with no eyes, no
mouth, and a predator right behind you.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)