A man is stopped at a DUI checkpoint, and what they find in his car is terrifying.
And then we take a look at a story that is often forgotten when we look at the life of
Ed and Lorraine Warren.
The Conjuring movies are based on them.
They were at the forefront of major haunting stories.
But did you know that they also once had an encounter with Bigfoot?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Karpner, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
It's funny, the story we're going to start off here wasn't the story I originally had
planned for today.
I just read about it in the news today.
I'm doing it for one or two reasons.
I think it's a good follow up to our Ouija board episode, especially the ending.
Yesterday, you don't have to listen to yesterday's episode to follow this one.
But yesterday, I ended that episode with saying I don't know what's scarier.
The idea that a demon can possess someone via Ouija board or simply that people can
simply snap under the smallest provocation.
Is that a word?
Underneath the smallest of circumstances, someone could just snap and start murdering
people.
The story actually really gets me worked up.
Now I have an unofficial rule that I try not to cuss on this show.
They do slip out from time to time.
I'm going to do my best because this story actually really gets me worked up.
It's kind of depressing too.
And that's another reason why I want to cover it because I almost need to just tell it and
get it off my plate.
I can't let it be sitting in my notes.
And you're like, Jason, why are you telling us this story?
It's so depressing.
Because again, I just think it's an interesting story and it's an ongoing trial.
And you guys can follow as well.
It's September 2014.
There's a little DUI checkpoint in the state of Mississippi.
Board police officers sitting there.
Cars are coming.
Stopping the car.
Have you had anything to drink tonight?
No.
Yes.
How many drinks?
This routine.
This DUI checkpoint.
And this van pulls up.
There's a man in it.
37 year old man.
The cop's like, oh, he's either drunk or he's not.
Maybe he'll be smuggling some coke and it'll be a cool Miami Vice moment.
But the cop knows.
Listen, guys are either drunk or he's not.
The guy either keeps driving or he gets out of his car, breathalyzer, all this stuff.
Just a routine stop.
But as the car pulls up and the man rolls down his window, the police officer recognizes
a smell.
It's a smell that only people in certain professions know.
Morticians, military, doctors, cops.
It's the smell of death.
That was the officer's exact words when he was filing the report.
I smelled the smell of death.
Now the guy in the car, his name is Timothy Jones Jr.
He's a 37 year old dude.
And he's just kind of chatting but the cop just smells the fact that there have been
bodies in here.
Animal maybe?
Human maybe?
He doesn't know.
But he begins kind of looking around the car with his flashlight, checking it out.
And that's when he notices three things you never want to see in combination.
Maggots, blood, and children's clothing.
Timothy Jones Jr. and his wife were married.
They had five kids.
So this is going to get grim, guys.
So again, you can just jump ahead ten minutes and get to the funny story or just keep hitting
that skip button if this isn't the way you want to start your day.
Seven, six, two, and one were the ages of his children.
They had a divorce.
He got sole custody of the kids or at least most custody of the kids.
I don't know if it was sold but they spent most of the time with him.
And he had a really hard time dealing with it.
Had a really hard time dealing with it.
Now we've talked about this before on the show.
There's good ways to deal with stuff and there's bad ways to deal with stuff.
The way that he dealt with stuff is that when his kids misbehaved, he made them do push-ups
and sit-ups and do physical training.
There was this way of kind of like breaking them down.
Very bully-ish type behavior.
But anyways, he said, "Child protective services have come out to his house because they noticed
the mark on his kids.
They actually visited his house two weeks before this incident."
And they're like, "Yeah, he does make them like run laps and stuff like that, but the
kids actually seem to be well fed.
They're clean.
They're well groomed.
The house is clean.
It's nice."
But what people didn't really know was that he was hearing voices.
At least he says he was hearing voices.
Now his mother had done 20 years in a mental institution for schizophrenia.
He says that he was self-medicating himself that he was hearing voices.
And at one point, the voices told him to kill his kids.
And he's like, "What?
Nah, I'm not gonna do that."
But one day he comes home.
It was August 28th, 2014.
He comes home and the electrical outlet is blowing out.
And he accuses his six-year-old son of blowing out the electrical outlet.
And the kid's like, "I didn't do it."
And the dad's like, "Yeah, you did."
And they started having this back-and-forth argument.
So he started making his son do push-ups and sit-ups until he admitted that he blew out
the outlet.
And the boy was adamant that he didn't.
So then Timothy, like a real man, starts smacking his six-year-old son around.
This one, his story's really pissing me off.
He starts smacking his son around.
And then he sends the son to bed.
And then later on he checks on his son and his son is dead.
So this is all his version of the story.
We don't know exactly what he did to the boy, but the boy ended up being beaten to death.
He says he just smacked him around a bit.
The kid goes to bed.
But the boy, when he checks on the kid later, the six-year-old kid is dead.
At that point, he said the voices came--the little spoiler alert here.
He's trying to get insanity.
That's why I think all this voice is nonsense is in this story.
Timothy was hearing voices, maybe not.
I don't know.
I really don't care.
But anyway, so he's sitting there and he's looking at his dead six-year-old son in bed.
And he says the voices came to him and that the other kids were conspiring against them,
so now it's the time to take them all out.
He goes into the eight-year-old's bedroom, strangles.
I think the eight-year-old was a girl.
They were mixed.
So some were girls and some were boys.
I didn't even want to really picture the genders of the kids.
But he strangles the eight-year-old.
He strangles the seven-year-old.
He then goes into the room where the two-year-old and the one-year-old are sleeping.
And in a particularly brutal detail, he said their necks were too small for his hands,
so he used the belt to strangle them.
He throws all of them into the car.
You know what's funny?
The element that I think really kind of got--that is when you deal with true crime and stuff
like that, you read stuff like that.
That bugged me, but the detail that I think really bugs me the most about this story,
honestly, is you get immune to the death type of stuff.
He throws the kids' bodies in the back of his van.
He drives around for nine days.
He doesn't really know what he's going to do.
He's thinking about, well, maybe I should melt him, maybe I should cut him up, and maybe
should I ground the bones to dust and just scatter him somewhere so no one will ever
know what happened to the kids.
Now, obviously, cops will figure out that his kids are missing, but as he's on this journey
to dump these children, his children, wherever he's going to put them, they have video surveillance--I
don't know why this pisses me off so much, but they have video surveillance footage of
at one point him going into a convenience store and buying cheese sticks and curly fries.
I don't know why that bugs me so much.
I think it's because the--it's--this is going to sound so weird, but you don't deserve a
treat, dude.
You don't deserve your favorite food, okay?
You don't get to take a break.
You don't get to go to your--the place where you want and get some food you want when you've
got murdered kids in your backseat.
You don't get to do that.
You don't get to have a fun summer day.
At one point he goes to the store, he buys a saw, acid, goggles, candy, and Gatorade.
And I can just imagine this asshole sitting in his car in some parking lot, eating a Snickers
bar, drinking a Gatorade, and just having a good time as his kids are rotting in his
backseat.
You know, it's so bizarre.
It's so bizarre because, again, when you read a lot of this stuff, when you research a lot
of this stuff, you do become immune to a lot of the super grisly details.
But when you read the mundane stuff, it gets to you.
It gets to you.
I've lost track of the amount of people that I've seen--I've probably seen about seven
or eight people die in real life, and I've lost track of the amount of people I've seen
die in video.
Like, absolutely.
Which couldn't even give you a rough estimate of how many people I've seen blowing up, or
accidentally electrocuted, or get their brains blown out in some sort of Syrian war video.
I've completely lost track of that stuff.
But this detail, it's just so--when you look at the horribleness of these crimes, the mundane
details are what tend to haunt me.
I remember--I think it was the Zodiac Killer.
I remember reading a long time ago, there, I think it was the Zodiac Killer.
There was a guy who was like 50 years old, he was one of the victims of the serial killer,
and I can't swear that it's a Zodiac Killer, but it was in San Francisco.
There was a guy who was like in his 50s, he worked at the Coke bottling plant, and every
day he got a free bottle of Coke, and that was his favorite drink, and he would walk
home with his bottle of Coke, and he would sit at home and watch television and drink
his Coke.
And when he was walking home that night, he was shot by the serial killer, and they found
his body and the Coke was spilled next to his body.
That detail really stuck with me for a long time, because that's me.
I'm the guy who enjoys the little things in life.
I'm the guy who enjoys walking to the store, grabbing my three favorite items.
I got my drink, I got my favorite snack, and then I walk home and I enjoy them.
That was me getting gunned down.
Those mundane things are the things that always stick with me.
It's not necessarily the grizzliness of the murders, but it's the mundane stuff that really
gets to me.
So he's on trial right now, and he's confessed to it.
He's totally confessed to it.
The question is whether or not he's insane, legally insane, or if he just snapped.
He said to in his police interview, "If Nathan," that was the name of his six-year-old son,
"if Nathan had admitted that he'd blown out the outlets, all the other kids would be
alive.
He's the one who caused me to do this."
You've...
On the Ouija Board episode, I said, "I don't know what's scarier, the demon creeping through
the darkness or people just snapping."
I have my answer.
It's people just snapping, because you really can't predict it.
This guy didn't have a Ouija Board.
By all accounts, he seemed to be fairly normal.
Child Protective Services came out two weeks before this happened and talked to him.
They felt he was normal.
The wife never thought he was a dangerous person.
She felt comfortable with him watching the kids.
He just murders five of them in one night, because one kid doesn't admit to blowing
out an outlet.
Far, far insanity.
People snapping is far creepier than a demon.
Because demons may or may not be real, but insanity, and I'm not using a legal definition.
This guy's guilty.
This guy needs to go to prison, not some hospital.
Yeah.
Far creepier.
Far, far creepier.
Okay, but enough of the...
That story.
I went to...
I was like, "I'm gonna get some and eat."
It just kind of left a sour taste in my mouth.
But again, it couldn't be because I just read it right before I was recording it.
Didn't really have time to digest it.
I haven't listened back to that segment yet, but you might be able to tell that my voice
is a bit different just because...
So like two hours later, I'm recording the rest of this.
Let's go ahead and change gears here.
And right now, we are going out to Tennessee.
Now, Ed and Lorraine Warren were the people the Conjuring movies are based on them.
I believe they were part of Amityville, I'm pretty sure, and they might have been part
of the infield haunting, but really the Conjuring universe is all built around the life and
times of these two investigators.
Ed passed away a couple years ago, and Lorraine Warren just passed away this year.
We always hear about them being connected with these hauntings, but not a lot of people
know that they also had a run-in with everyone's seven-foot friend who's covered in hair,
Bigfoot.
Now, apparently, so I found out about this because I was reading this article.
So there was a book that they wrote back in the 80s called Ghost Hunters, back when they
were still kind of just starting to become super popular.
And I'm reading an article about the book and about their Bigfoot adventures, and I
came across this passage.
It said, regarding the book, this is what it says, Ed and Lorraine Warren lay out some
of their most terrifying cases.
Which include elements like disappearing Nigerian priests, judo chop, martial arts murders,
porno theater demons, and possessed biker gangs.
Just to name a few.
So yes, I did buy the book.
I went and I bought that book.
I was like, "I gotta read this thing."
And the author of this article says it's actually probably one of the craziest ghost books story
collections out there.
He goes, "It's just kind of all over the place, but in the middle of the book," written
by Ed and Lorraine Warren, there is an eight page chapter simply titled Bigfoot.
So Lorraine and Ed were on a lecture tour in Tennessee.
Reporter comes up to him and goes, "Hey listen, I need your help."
Well I don't need your help, but I know a bunch of hillbillies who need your help.
I'm a little, I question this reporter, was his beat the hillbilly beat, or did he have
family members who were hillbillies?
Like how were they so easily able to get a hold of this reporter and being like, "Hey,
we got a scoop for you, Bigfoot, still in kids."
Actually that is something a reporter would want to hear.
But anyways, the reporter goes to Ed and Lorraine Warren and says, "There's a bunch of hillbillies.
They're being harassed by a Bigfoot."
And Lorraine says, "I never believed in Bigfoot.
It was something that I never really paid attention to.
It was just kind of whatever."
You know, and that tends to be the case.
A lot of criticism, I get two big criticisms about this show.
One, my voice is too sexy.
And two, they go, "Jason, the only thing you believe in is ghosts.
You're always like poo poo and everything else."
And both of those criticisms are quite valid.
But I get where she's coming from.
You do tend to just kind of focus on one particular form of freakish beliefs and then you kind
of poo poo the rest.
So that's how she was with Bigfoot.
But for whatever reason they do decide to go.
I think it was just kind of like, maybe they just want to see hillbilly people in their
natural environment, the suns of the soil.
They just wanted to really see what they were like and maybe catch the sighting of a Bigfoot,
a creature that they don't really believe in.
Also, it probably helped the reporter ask them to because they seem to be a bit on the publicity
pound kind of side.
They seem to really like publicity.
They go up there, so they go to the hillbilly village and everyone's just kind of like playing
on their banjos and stuff like that.
Lorraine and Ed are, I imagine, like dancing around doing a traditional dance, a traditional
hillbilly dance, which is just a drunken stupor.
But the people in the hillbilly village were like, this is like, I should say, this is
like in the mid-70s, early 80s.
This isn't like, when I keep saying hillbilly village, this isn't like the 1880s.
Anyway, so they're in the hillbilly village and the grand chieftain of the hillbillies
comes out in his headdress made of a Paps Blue Ribbon cans and he's like, I am the leader
of the hillbilly clan.
This is what happened.
Many moons ago, no, he's like, so this is what happened.
One day we were sitting here, minding our own business, not making meth, not making any
meth whatsoever.
But there's a little two-year-old boy kind of hanging on the outskirts of town, town
being where the caravan stops, where the mobile homes only reach out to.
And we saw a giant monster come out of the woods, giant bigfoot, try to take the boy
and the boy started crying, the monster ran away.
So we want your help finding this thing.
Now again, according to the book Lorraine and Ed were like, because they didn't believe
in bigfoot.
But again, she's like, fine, let's do it.
Now, after a certain point, after a couple hours, she's thinking this is a waste of time.
As far as she's concerned, they're not looking for, what they're looking for doesn't exist.
So it would be like if you were hiking for four hours and you knew nothing was going to
be found.
Let's imagine you were looking for forest fins treasure.
That's what she was going through.
They were looking for something that just flat out didn't exist.
So she's in the woods, they're walking around.
And then all of a sudden she gets a psychic blast.
Oh, oh my head.
And she sees bigfoot.
I guess they're just saying, because she didn't know Lorraine Warren is a psychic.
She was reportedly a psychic, allegedly had the psychic powers.
She just wasn't walking through the woods and she's like, oh, these new found abilities.
This was her gift.
Anyway so she's like, oh my head, Charles, go save Logan.
Cyclops is in need of help.
But actually no, she doesn't do that.
That would have been cool.
But no, bigfoot's there instead of Charles Xavier.
And he goes, oh, why humans follow me?
And she's like, she starts talking with it.
And she goes, well, you scared.
What's so bizarre is that, again, I haven't read the exact chapter itself because I'm
getting the book, but I'm basing this off what the article said about the chapter.
And she just kind of like goes into a conversation with this thing that she didn't really believe
existed.
She said it was about 40 yards away from where they were at.
She knew it was very, very close to where this hunting party was and she's psychically
connected.
She tells everyone in the party, shh, shh, shh.
I'm talking to bigfoot with my magic brain.
You've got to be quiet so I can concentrate with my magic brain.
So the hunting party falls quiet.
She's talking to bigfoot.
And he goes, me, hurt.
Me, foot, get scratched on ground point thing.
She's like a rock and he's like, whatever.
It's, my foot's all cut up because you chase me.
And she's like, well, we're chasing you because you were trying to kidnap a little boy.
He's like, no kidnap, no, me understand crossing state lines with individual, his federal law,
me no do that.
Me want to play with baby.
And she's like, well, okay, that's all well and good.
And you have an understanding of federal law regarding kidnapping.
But he's like, yes, bad experience back in '60s.
No talk about it.
And she's like, okay, we'll table that for later.
But the kid was scared.
Your giant, giant Harry monster, you're coming out of the woods.
He's like, yes, yes, I am.
Potuitary gland problem.
And they're having this conversation.
And she's like, she's mentally, she said at this point, she's mentally bandaging his
foot like she's giving him visions of her like physically helping them.
And then in true hillbilly fashion, let's say I'm assuming that oddly enough, I'm assuming
this story is true in the sense that I'm assuming that a bunch of people walked down
the woods and she might have imagined the conversation.
I don't think she made the whole thing up.
I don't think she made up the hillbilly party or anything like that because it's such a
brief section of this book.
And if you took it out, it wouldn't matter.
So I'll say that she probably did go in the woods with a bunch of hillbillies, a bunch
of rednecks and imagined that she was talking to Bigfoot.
Maybe she was really talking to Bigfoot.
I don't know.
But whatever the case in true hillbilly fashion, if she made this up, she definitely knows
her hillbillies.
In true hillbilly fashion, while she is talking to Bigfoot psychically, after telling everyone
- hey guys, be quiet, I'm talking to Bigfoot psychically - they invited her out here to
talk to Bigfoot psychically, a guy, uh, hillbilly, starts honking his horn.
He's honking the horn and it's quoted in the article as a joke.
So imagine you're in the middle of making first contact with a Sasquatch, a creature
that is a legend all over the world, and some hillbillies all "Yuck, yuck, this will be
funny, na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
funny" - you know, like, honking and just playing on his horn.
And of course the psychic connection was not only broken, but then Bigfoot took off through
the woods so they heard this huge noise running through the woods.
And Lorraine says she took off after it.
This part of the story is probably 100% made up this indie, but anyways, Lorraine says she
took off after it and she sees blood that is described as more viscous.
Is that how you pronounce that?
Viscous and more redder.
Is that a word?
Redder?
This was the quote.
The blood trail was both redder and more viscous than a human blood.
So anyways, that might have been - actually I might have missed - I might have added in
the "A".
So I'm not going to put that on the article, "Redder" or Lorraine.
Anyways, she's following this trail that has a human blood on it and the other - the hillbillies
are following behind and then Ed is like barely walking after.
He's like, "That's all made up."
I don't believe - I don't even believe my wife has these psychic powers.
She's just really hot and good in bed.
So I just play along.
I don't care.
I think - I know it's all fake.
I've been faking hauntings for the past 20 years just to keep my hot wife interested
in going to spooky hotels with me.
That's not true.
That is 100% an allegation.
It's a joke.
I don't assume a state of the warrants.
Anyways, they follow this viscous trail of a human blood to a cliff and then nothing.
So the idea is that Bigfoot either killed himself, jumped off the cliff, or was running
so hard and his foot hurt so bad that he just really wasn't paying attention to where he's
running and accidentally ran off the cliff, like Wiley Coyote.
And I guess the story has an afterword as well, where Ed Warren says, "I think Bigfoot's
not real.
I think it's a tulpa.
I think it's a thought form.
I think it's something that so many people have believed in.
It has become something that's real and that's Bigfoot."
I think that it probably just ran off the cliff and then just magically disappeared,
which raises a couple of interesting questions.
One, we've talked about tulpas before and I've talked about Bigfoot's being tulpas as
well.
So me and Ed were in the same vein.
But you know, I think that's kind of a common sub belief among Bigfoot followers.
Not Bigfoot followers because that's like they're super into Bigfoot being real.
But people who kind of just look at it every once in a while go, "It could just be people's
imagination have made it real."
But here's the interesting question about that.
If that's true, can you have a psychic link to a tulpa you didn't create?
Because you can have psychic links to tulpas you did create if you listened to my episode
about the guy creating the cartoon character and having sex with it and it's screaming
in his brain for the rest of his life.
We don't know if he killed himself or not.
But can you have a psychic link with a tulpa that you didn't create?
If you can have a psychic link with a tulpa that you didn't create, then a tulpa really
is technically life at that point.
If there's a tulpa that can be released into the world and it's indistinguishable from
any other life form and it has its own inner thoughts, it has basically its own soul, then
it's its own life form.
And then in that case, do tulpas, well where do tulpas go when they die?
Does their soul go somewhere?
Do they deserve rights?
Do these imaginary creatures that become real deserve rights?
Those are all huge rabbit holes that I don't want to jump into.
At the end of an episode like this, maybe we'll do it on a future episode.
But I think it's interesting, the reason why I wanted to look at this was you have someone
who's made all of their money telling people that ghosts are real and houses can be haunted
and Annabelle is dolls running around and Annabelle too is dolls running around in the
olden times and the none and all this stuff is based off these stories and legends from
the Warrens.
And the Conjuring Universe is really the only other big cinematic universe is the Conjuring
Universe.
You have Marvel Universe and Conjuring Universe and that's about it.
Other ones like Fast and Furious is just kind of a franchise but Conjuring Universe has
all these interconnected movies and it's funny because even they're like I don't believe
in Bigfoot.
Like until they have that encounter they can see dolls running around and all sorts of
crazy stuff but when someone brought a Bigfoot to them they're like I don't believe in it.
I think that's a pretty normal thing.
Plus, James Wan, I know you listen to this show, you gotta do this Bigfoot movie.
You have to include a Bigfoot reference in at least one of the next Conjuring Universe
movies.
Gotta put a Bigfoot in there.
It would be a deep cut for the true Warren worshippers out there.
So that is the story of Lorraine and Ed Warren meeting Bigfoot which is similar like stating
something like the Mummy meets Frankenstein.
You have these huge paranormal investigators, these heavyweights in one world and then you
have this heavyweight in the world of cryptids actually meeting.
I'm surprised this story isn't more popular but it's not, I would assume it's not more
popular because it's fake and they knew it when it stand up to scrutiny if they were
constantly questioned about Bigfoot so they just kind of wrote it in a book, kind of tossed
it away.
I could be wrong on that though.
I'm kind of harsh on the Warrens just because of their, some of their cases turned out to
be fraudulent.
Not them but the people behind the cases it turned out not to be true.
So you know, I'm a little more harsh on them but they did good paranormal work.
They kind of brought that more into the whole like haunting stuff and they're part of the
big boom.
With that, but Amityville was a hoax, Enfield Haunting was a hoax and they were kind of
involved in these things.
I think, I think.
I don't know what their level of involvement was but yeah, you know, that's the problem.
You get caught up in a couple different hoaxes.
You could really run into Bigfoot and have a psychic conversation with him in the woods
and then eventually Hillbilly hunks the horn and Bigfoot kills himself.
That could be the one true story you tell but you know, how many times do I have to
believe that Annabelle the doll got raised by the nun and then the Amityville house and
then they moved to Enfield.
Like, at what point do I have to say, I don't think that's true and they're like, no, no,
no, we really saw Bigfoot.
Here's some of his blood.
It's so viscous and I'm like, you know, what can I say?
Could be the one true story out of all the nonsense.
Could be more nonsense and a story of nonsense or they could all could be true.
But one thing's for sure, I'm gonna read this book because I want to find out about porno
theater demons.
And once I do, we'll have to talk about it on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Bye.
(upbeat music)