Dolls. A multi-billion dollar industry that's been going on since the beginning of time.
Every civilization has had their own form of dolls. Whether they are the fertility statues
they made out of clay a long time ago, or today's pussycat dolls, they've existed since the
beginning of humanity. But for some people simply saying the word dolls feels them with
fear. There are some people who listen to this show who won't even click on this episode
because it is called Haunted Dolls. What is it about dolls that people find so terrifying?
Can dolls actually be haunted? And I just ordered a haunted doll off of eBay today on
Dead Rabbit Radio. Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm
your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day
too. First off I want to say thank you so much to everyone who sent me birthday wishes.
All day long I was getting them via email, YouTube comments, Twitter. It was awesome.
It was really really cool to just be walking around my phone like do do do and it would
be like happy birthday Jason. It's a really really cool feeling so thank you everyone
for making me feel loved. That was just awesome. Totally awesome. I really appreciate that.
If you'll see my cover art for today's episode it was a birthday card that Veronica's son
made for me. Little Finn. I don't think he probably wants to be called Little. But he
drew me this. It's a Halloween/Birthday card. It does say him 45 on there and Veronica thought
that was funny. But all she did was guarantee me. Guarantee me three extra years of life.
No jokes on you. And then very briefly non-spoiler Joker review. It's alright. It's alright.
It was good. It wasn't great. But I enjoyed it. It was really entertained. It flew by.
It seemed like it was only like an hour long. Didn't have a lot of fat to it. It was really
good but it's not one of those movies that you oh no no I know you don't like comic book
movies. You gotta see this one. It wasn't like that. If you want to see it go see it pretty
quickly because otherwise stuff's going to get spoiled for you and there's some weird
twists and turns. And if you don't want to see it I don't really think you're missing
much by not seeing it. That's my review. So I enjoyed it though. I really really enjoyed
it. But let's go ahead and start our descent into the madness of dolls. Little doll people.
It's funny because there is so much to cover in this episode and it's frankly stupid. Not
the idea of haunted dolls. That's idiotic. But the idea that there's so much stuff written
about these dudes. It's really really bizarre. And I have some interesting thoughts and conspiracies
regarding that but let's go ahead and get started with really what started this whole
thing last night on online. I'm like oh my god I got an episode tomorrow. Just typing
random words hoping something spooky shows up. No I'm going through and I go I've never
covered haunted dolls before. I think I've talked about them here and there. But I've
never actually like done an episode on them. Which is weird because they're kind of like
a horror mainstay. Let me tell you a personal story. So when I was probably like 20 something
23 maybe. Living with my grandma. Chilling with my grandma. I come home from work one
day or I was probably just out messing around with my friends but I came home to my grandma's
house and there was this dirty busted up doll sitting in one of the chairs. And my grandma
was in the other chair watching the Drew Carey show or whatever. And I walk in I'm like
hey guys what's up. Hey grandma. And then I look and I'm like what's that doll doing
there. My grandma looks over at this house was the one where all the shadow people were
chilling and all the creepy stuff was happening. My grandma was watching Drew Carey show. She
turns over she looks at the doll she goes oh the dog brought it in. And I go did the
dog put it in the chair. And she doesn't respond. Now you could say oh she's possessed by the
spirit of the doll. Let us come. Now she probably just is too busy watching the Drew Carey show.
She knew I believed in all sorts of creepy nonsense. She probably didn't want to entertain
the thought. Because obviously I was saying did the doll walk in here. So I went out and
I talked to the dog. So it was weird because I thought the dog never brings first off my
grandma never let the dog inside the house unless it was like a rainstorm too. He never
brought in stuff in three. You're telling me that doll was sitting in the backyard this
whole time. The dog's like ten years old at this point. But anyways so the doll was super
spooky and covered in mud and had like an old fashioned dress on it and its hair was
all matted. Basically looked like a girl had picked up from a bar except more age appropriate.
They are usually quite filthy. I think they just come home with me so they can use my
shower. But I take the doll and I go to I don't think I did it immediately that night. I think
I just kind of like kept an eye on the doll. I was like I'm keeping an eye on you and the
doll just sitting there. The doll won that staring contest but later like the next day
I believe I took the doll over to my friend Josh's house. So you got Josh and Jackie and
Joanne and they've all shown up in other ghost stories that I've told. Personal ghost stories
I've told. I was like hey guys look I got this haunted doll. Now Joanne wanted nothing
to do with it at all. Josh was playing in PlayStation 2 but Jackie was like haunted
doll haunted doll. And so we gave it a bath and we took it into the bathroom and we started
like cleaning it off and like washing off the dirt. And then we're like she, Jackie
was I think like 13 or 14 so she had dolls of her own. So she goes and she gets little
doll hairbrushes and she's like here you go she gives me it's a piece of pink plastic
with little prongs on it. It wasn't like from the doll set soon but anyways we both have
these doll brushes right? And we're running the doll under the water and we're like brushing
the doll's hair. We're just brushing it. And we're doing it and a good amount of time
is passing. We hear Josh in the other room beating up the undertaker on the PS2. The
undertaker hadn't actually shown up. Give me my doll kicking down the door. We hear
him he's doing his PS2 thing. Joanne's doing whatever. And me and Jackie are just in here
washing this doll off. And at a certain point Jackie turns to me and she goes I can't stop.
I need to get this doll clean. And it was weird because maybe it's just her saying it like
put it in my head and I hadn't thought of it before. But I was feeling the same thing.
Now sometimes that happens. I can walk in a room and it feels fine and then someone goes
this room's kind of creepy isn't it? And then I will retroactively believe that it was creepy.
Human mind is very easy to mess around with. But she goes I can't stop doing this. I need
to clean it off and I turn to her and I agreed. It was really weird. So either she put that
thought into my head and I hadn't thought about it or in the moment I felt like I was
also having a hard time stopping. Like we had to get this doll clean. And eventually
we did. And then I thought it was hilarious because I would put the doll in the passenger
seat in my car. I took it everywhere with me. I thought it was so funny because people
knew that that doll was super creepy. They knew it's Providence. So they knew like it
had appeared in my grandma's house. And me and Jackie couldn't stop cleaning it. And
so on and so forth. And then the doll I remember one morning I woke up and I was like time
to go to work. I'm putting a little uniform. I'm putting a little Godfather's Pizza uniform
on the doll. I'm like oh you look so precious. Carrying it everywhere. People's pizzas
are covered in muddy footprints. I remember one day I woke up and doll was gone. And I
wasn't like oh the doll must have walked away. I thought oh I must have put it somewhere.
I looked all over for that doll. Couldn't find it at my place. Looked in my car. Couldn't
find it. I ended up going to Jackie's house and I go hey Jackie where's the doll at? And
she's like what? I go where's... I wonder if we ever named it now that I think about
it. I go where's the doll at? Where's the doll? And she's like I don't know. Your doll you
should have been the one who had it. And we looked all over her house. Never saw that
doll again. It hung out with us for about six months right? This doll was on these adventures
with me. Now do I think the doll was haunted? It was creepy and it magically appeared and
disappeared. Not magically. I was pushing it a little too much. The doll was creepy. It
appeared one day and disappeared a couple months later. Never to be seen again. Does that mean
it's haunted? No. Does that mean it's magical? No. Does that mean that I never cleaned up
after myself and it's very possible that the doll, if it did become animated, fall into
a pile of dirty clothes, got thrown into the washing machine and just dissolve? Possible.
More likely. I guess except for the walking part. But that's really been my only interaction
with a quote unquote haunted doll. A creepy doll would be a better term for it and possibly
possessed us so we would brush its hair and clean it up. And then it went on its own way.
The doll could have been wanting to possess us and take over our bodies until it realized
all we did was play PS2 and eat Pop John's. The dolls like this will not end well for
any of these people involved. I'm researching last night and I go, "Yeah, I want to do a
story about haunted dolls." So I started looking up like the most haunted dolls or the most
dangerous haunted dolls and there's not a lot of them. I honestly thought there would
be, there's basically two levels of haunted doll stories. There's the ones that people
know and then there's the ones that happen to your aunt when she's six. And you go, "Jason,
that's the same thing with haunted houses. You have the Amityville Horror and then you
have the haunted house in your neighborhood." But generally the difference is that haunted
houses, abandoned asylums, creepy roads, they're shared experiences. The haunted house is there
and it lasts through generations. Your grandfather was scared of the house, your father was scared
of the house, you're scared of the house. It's generally a generational thing. You know
the house at the end of the lane that the old lady like chopped up a bunch of trick-or-treaters
and then handed out their body parts to other trick-or-treaters. The story gets passed on,
mutated and things like that. But haunted dolls are a family story and it's quite an interesting
phenomenon. Let's look at some of the famous ones. Now Annabelle and Robert the Doll are
the two most famous ones. Annabelle, briefly, because I think that I, let me go ahead and
say all the stories I'm about to tell you are completely ridiculous and stupid. Annabelle
involves the Warns, which I've talked about them before. You have the psychic woman who
believes she can talk to ghosts and Bigfoot and then her husband who probably didn't believe
in any of it but just liked being in a rich chick who made money scamming people allegedly.
And then so Annabelle was a doll that some girl, a raggedy end doll that some sorority
girl bought. And then at the same time the house was haunted and they was of a little
girl and the sorority girls go, in my version they're sorority girls, I think they were
just in college but I want to make it a little sexier. They said, "Hey, you can jump into
the body of this doll." And then the doll started moving around. It wasn't like doing
the robot or like, you know, doing the chicken dance or nothing. It was just like you'd
come in one day and the doll would be in a different room. Which when it's you and two
roommates, everything moves all of the time. Oh no, where did I put this last slice of
pizza? I don't know, it's a girl with the pizza-stained face and you're like, "Ugh,
it's a ghost." So stuff will move when there's three people, three college-aged girls living
in an apartment. Things are gonna move around. That's just, oh and the doll's so evil that
now it's in some laboratory, not laboratory, it's in some museum or something like that.
But hey, here's a question. If Ed and Lorraine Warren were really good at this ghost stuff,
how come their ghosts haven't shown up yet? Because they're dead. They've been dead for
a couple months now. Where are their ghosts? Like shouldn't they be on talk shows and stuff
like that? Shouldn't they be inhabiting dolls? Anyways, so that was kind of rude. They've
lost their lives and I don't like it when people die, but if you were a parapsychologist,
you'd think they'd be making the rounds right now. Zach Baggins should be walking around
with the EVP reader talking to these dudes. So Robert the Doll is a doll. He's just some
creepy looking doll who was that the guy, Robert the Doll, if I remember correctly, was the
dude in the Rocky chair that his face changes or like they actually have video footage of
his head moving. So you know, there's that. I mean you're like Jason, that's kind of
a big detail to gloss over. Here's the thing. If there is actual video footage of an inanimate
object moving its head, and it was 100% legit, it would be studied in every single science
laboratory, biologists would be getting rid of their equipment to say how is it possible
that this inanimate object moves. So it either has, and it is the biggest discovery in human
history that an object that was crafted by humans that was made to not move moves on
its own, proving either life after death or that inanimate objects can come to life.
That would be the biggest news ever. It would revolutionize the rocking chair industry.
It would revolutionize every single ping pong table out there because you would have to
wonder, am I picking up a sentient object and hitting it against another sentient object?
We would be paralyzed as a nation. Now I know that's a stupid analogy, but could you put
your shoes on if you knew your shoes were alive? So there's that, there's that part of
it, or if it was actually proof that there is life after death, which is what everyone
wonders. Some people believe they have the answer, but I think everyone is a little
doubtful in those dark moments. Like is this right? If there was video evidence that this
doll moved on its own, it would be the biggest news story in human history. This is what
Robert the doll does. He has a bunch of different origin stories, either he was some voodoo
stuff or some girl went into the body of the doll or whatever, but this is what this doll
is supposedly capable of doing. Car accidents, broken bones, job loss, divorce, and a cornucopia
of other misfortunes. That's from Wikipedia. I normally don't use the word cornucopia
in what I'm talking. And then museum visitors, because he's chilling at a museum now, have
post-visit misfortunes for failing to respect Robert. So considering I've been talking trash
about this dumb doll for the past 10 minutes, who knows what's going to happen to me, but
the doll doesn't cause car accidents. And then this is where I'm going with this. We
have these like super dolls, these dolls that have all these magical powers that are able
to do stuff. Because here's the truth. Would you go to a museum to see a doll? Because
these dolls you have to pay to go see Robert the doll. Would you pay to go see a doll that
if you walk by to make cut the brake lines to your car or it makes your wife leave you
because she's finally realized that for your vacation you wanted to go look at a 100 year
old doll or just walk into your sister's bedroom and there's like a creepy doll. Like most stories
of dolls, of haunted dolls are super mundane. Super mundane. And then you have these mega
ones. You have, here's some of the ones that are less known. I found some other ones here
that are less known. Let's look at these guys real quick here, these haunted dolls. We have
Peggy. These are supposedly famous. Peggy, it's a little girl doll, a little cute girl
with blonde curly hair. She's known to cause nausea, dizziness and heart attacks. So it's
Taco Bell in the form of a doll. It can also is known to drive you mad. Now you go, how
can a doll give you a heart attack? Ah, non-believer. If you just look at a photo of Peggy, you can
have a heart attack. When you, there's a YouTube video that starts off with a warning saying
you've been warned by, look, watching this video you may have a heart attack. We're about
to show you a picture of Peggy the doll. People take this stuff quite seriously. This doll,
apparently, according to scam artists, say that this doll is possessed by the ghost of
someone who died during the Holocaust, which is bizarre. This story was eventually retconned
because that's just good. Listen, man, you can make your scam artist, right? That's how
you make your money is telling people that their pipes are haunted and stuff like that.
There's certain things that you don't say ghosts come from. You don't want to say the
Holocaust for one. Here is a haunted box. Ooh, if you open it up, bad things may happen.
Ooh, the person who had that died during a horrible, horrible, worldwide genocide. I
don't want that. Don't include genocides in your fake ghost origin stories. I would
say that is a bad one. Come on, do you want... Here's a pair of haunted shoes. Fine. I found
them in the rubble of World Trade Center. Like, there's certain things that you're making
it up, so make up something less horrifying. Chew it up by an escalator. Okay, I'll buy
those. That's terrible, but they're haunted. Shoes, right? You're gonna have somebody die.
You're gonna have a Holocaust? Seriously, bro? So, this one died on the Holocaust, apparently.
And the psychic who was taking notes on trying to figure out what it was, what was in Peggy.
Peggy the doll stole the notepad. So then the psychic was like, "I don't remember what
other stuff I made up. I mean discovered during our saiyans." You give me some time to think
about it, and she's like pulling out her book, a fiction writer's workshop book. I'll
remember it, sure enough, and it's like Chapter 4. But anyway, so that's why we don't have
much information on Peggy, other than the fact that she can give you a heart attack
if you just look at her. We have Harold. He's a scuffed up baby doll. He's like a little
baby doll. His head's all jacked up. But, so it's funny that his head's all scuffed up,
because this doll... I think it's funny, because it's not funny. It's actually quite tragic,
but this doll, his head's all scuffed up, right? And he was passed from haunted doll collector
to haunted doll collector. So anyways, I mean that's a whole other thing we'll get into,
but this dude buys it, buys this stupid plastic doll that's supposedly haunted, and then he
invites his buddy over to see the doll, and his buddy comes over and then shortly afterwards
is diagnosed with a brain tumor. Therefore, the doll gave him the brain tumor. But here's
the question. What about the dude who actually bought the doll? Where's his brain tumor?
Like I come in contact with a haunted object, right? And I have 30 friends. One of those
friends gets in a car accident. Is the doll cursed? Now, I would leave out, if I wanted
to say that, I would leave out the other 29 people who visited me and saw the doll and
focus on the guy who got in the car accident. So this is total cherry pick and stuff. Yes,
when you have 30 friends, one of them is going to have a health problem or a broken bone or
a heart attack or something like that. We live in a mortal universe where things unfortunately
break down. Also with Harold, we did have an owner have some unfortunate luck. One of
the original owners of Harold got it, and his cat died, and his girlfriend left him for,
according to this article, his girlfriend left him for the pool man. What's a pool man?
I understand the word pool boy, but if we become that sensitive in society that pool
boy is, is there actually a like an age range? Like let's say you're 18 to 25, you're a pool
boy. But after that, uh-uh-uh, pool man. I've never heard that term before. Pool man. Anyways.
Okay, that was a weird rant. Last one we're going to talk about here is Letta. These are
the famous ones, Letta. It's an old marionette doll, some dude, some bloke in Australia, found
it under the floorboards. Don't believe that story at all. Totally made up. It's convenient
because he doesn't have to really show any origin story for it. Apparently it's 200
years old. Don't believe it. It has real human hair possibly. I, I, I, that is a more believable
detail than a 200 year old piece of wood underneath an abandoned house in Australia. And he throws
it in his car and he's driving away. Why he was in this house in the first place, he was
just like a scavenger. So basically he's a war pup. He just escaped Mad Max's assault
on his fortress. He's digging through a house and finds a doll. He's a scavenger again. He's
not like some meth head breaking off copper pipes to recycle them. He just breaks in houses
and looks for garbage under the floorboards, totally made up. He gets the doll out of there,
throws it in the trunk of the car and as he's driving away, here's a voice go, "Let
him me out!" So very, very stereotypical Italian ghost. That's why it's named Letta,
because it said, "Let him me out!" What? Totally fake, totally made up. Now, I'm not
saying that again. He wouldn't keep the doll. I think most of us would keep the doll because
it was spooky, but I would try to see if it repeated itself. Not kept saying, "Let me
out!" because then it's just Teddy Repskin. I would be curious to think, is this doll
actually talking? I'd have video cameras and tape recorders around it all. I probably want
to sleep for the first couple days to try to see if I was going insane, which to be honest,
not sleeping for three days is a sign of insanity, but I would want to know, and if it didn't
say anything else, I'd just must have heard it. It's not doing it again, but anyways,
people go around it, they get sick, dogs and kids hate it. Supposed to supposedly be a
gypsy doll, I don't know why it's speaking Italian, and it may or may not move, depending
on the person. Some people say it moves around the house, some people say it doesn't, but
the people who say it does move around the house at least scuff marks on the floor, so
it's kind of a dick because you just wax those floors and then you got little wood feet going
chchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchchch
and obviously, easy way to scam stupid people out of their money, and I'll get to that in
a second, but easy, easy way to get money from people. eBay actually initiated a rule saying
you can't sell haunted stuff, so when you buy stuff on eBay it says, "We're selling
this item as is, we can't make any guarantee that a ghost is actually going to show up
at your house," because it is such a scam, obviously, but people are buying these things
for tons and tons of money. You know me, I'm not one who normally make fun of people's
names, I've never done that on this podcast, but there's a haunted doll specialist. Can
you imagine putting that on your resume? So what do you do? You're at a bar. Actually,
to be honest, that would be a good pick-up line. Saddle up to a girl, be like, "Yeah,
you know, I just got back from day at the office investigating haunted dolls." I think
that would actually be a really good pick-up line. I should actually try that, but don't
listen to this episode, girl, that I pick up. There's a woman named, there's a woman
who is haunted doll specialist. Her name is Cat. This is very, very juvenile, and I'll
have to admit it's juvenile, but her name is Cat Blowers. Cat, Cat. No, I'm assuming
she's married, apparently. I guess her husband's name is Nick Blowers or something like that,
which is a little better. But imagine you're a girl, you're the boy of your dreams, your
name's Cat. You're the boy of your dreams, you can't wait to fall in love. The only problem
is you know when you guys get married, your name's gonna be Cat Blowers. Cat, Cat. Cat
Blowers. But anyways, Cat Blowers, she buys these pieces of junk on eBay, and then she
has this test, she locks them in a phone box with a tape recorder to see if she can hear
them talking. She says, "Sometimes I record music like from them, and it's weird, right?"
And then she realizes that it's always the song that she happens to be listening to in
the living room. She's like, "That's weird. This 300 year old doll loves pink." So anyways,
she does that, she throws a tape recorder in her phone box. She also sets an EMF reader
out for three to five days, so like, "Doooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
in the room. She's like, "I'm not gonna do that. I'm gonna do that." And then she's
like, "I'm gonna do that." And then she's like, "I'm gonna do that." And then she's
like, "If your house is haunted, you go, "Hey, my house is haunted, dude. Let me out."
And then they're like, "No, no, no. Your house is haunted because this dude like, blues brains out."
And now he's like, floating around. His brains are floating around too, so be careful where you step.
And you would assume that's the same thing with dolls. But no, because this stuff is so
made up and it's so such a scam, because the people just kind of make stuff up as they go along,
they go, "No, this doll is haunted by a leprechaun. So it brings you good luck." So buy this doll
and you'll get good luck. We're selling this item as is. We can't prove there's a leprechaun in here.
That's a scam. You can say this doll is haunted, it makes noises late at night. It's still probably a scam,
most likely. But it's a believable scam. Don't sell me a 30-year-old doll and say that the goddess Artemis
left some nymph in it and it will give me like sexual energy. Like, that's a scam.
When I keep using the word "scam," it's mostly in regards to that set. Obviously, here's a piece of
plastic, pay $30 for eBay on it, it has a ghost in it. It's most likely just a piece of plastic.
But by then telling me that it has some sort of benefit for my life, that's a scam. It's absolutely a scam.
Because if it worked, you'd keep it. If I had a doll that had a leprechaun in it, I'm not selling it to anybody.
No. It has a leprechaun in it. There's no amount of money that I can get on eBay for a leprechaun.
For a live leprechaun? Well, this is a ghost leprechaun. It doesn't matter. It's a leprechaun.
Anyways, let's get back to Kevin Kane. He's telling the story. This woman buys this doll that was supposed to have a happy spirit in it.
But one night, she woke up and she felt tiny little hands around her neck.
Now, she doesn't wake up. The doll's not actually strangling her. She just feels a sensation of ten little tiny fingers around her neck.
Which could not kill you ever. A doll cannot. The thing about how tiny them little hands are, they can't even move their thumbs.
We've gone from the point of dolls that may or may not walk and may scuff up your floor to full digit manipulation able to choke you.
Why would a doll need to choke you? How could a doll choke you?
But if the doll was trying to kill you and you woke up and the doll wasn't there, he just felt the tiny hands on you.
So it would be assumed that it was the spirit of the doll trying to get you. One of the spirit of the doll had normal sized hands.
The ghost in the doll was a normal sized human. The doll itself doesn't have a doll sized ghost.
Actually, now that I think about it, if you were a ghost and you haunted a doll, it would be extremely cramped in there.
Anyways, luckily, here's a quote from this article. "Luckily, he," this is Kevin Cain, "Luckily, he knew how to..."
He, he's an expert at this stuff, "Luckily, he knew how to bind the demonic spirit, ultimately sealing the doll in a box."
Like just regular old boys from the factory, cardboard box will do.
"Ultimately sealing the doll in a box coated in holy water and storing it on the highest shelf in his home where it remains."
You can't really coat a box in water. Now, assuming the box, and I'm nitpicking now, but I'm getting really kind of irritated at this stuff, box?
If it's cardboard, you put water on it, it is no longer a box. And the ghost, the monster easily escapes. The doll gets out.
But if the box is made of wood, I guess you could coat it. You had a wood, you put water on it, but eventually the water dries evaporates, stuff like that.
Whatever, holy water on a box. I love the line. "He stored it on not just any shelf, the highest shelf in his house."
That'll show you demon. That'll show you creature who can manipulate the body of an inanimate object.
You're on the highest shelf, and it's like, "Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
All of my Patreons are giving me the ability to spend money on useless stuff.
I had a choice. I had a choice between these two dolls. Let me explain. This episode is going to go long. Haunted Doll Special. It's Halloween.
Also Dead Rabbit recommends, because I want to do one every day, Child's Play. The new Child's Play movie. It's going to be really brief.
Check it out. Chuckie is an extremely bizarrely sympathetic villain in that movie. It's a very, very well done horror movie. It's dolls. It fits the theme.
I just watched the other day. It's not the best horror movie I've seen, but it has some really good kills. And the way they portrayed Chuckie in the movie was very, very well done.
You really, really feel bad for his journey. So check out the new Child's Play.
But let's go ahead and get back to Dead Rabbit Recommends today. Let's go ahead and talk about the dolls that I had the choices from the one I bought.
So I'm on eBay and I find these. We have Coco the Doll. It's a Harlequin doll. So it has like the big old long arms and legs. Not like a marionette, but it kind of looks like a clown with like the puffy clothes on.
Coco the Doll. $30. Here's the description. Coco the Doll has been part of my collection. Not my collection. I'm reading this.
Coco the Doll has been part of my collection since I've started to collect haunted objects, i.e. waste my money.
This porcelain tiny vessel, not just a doll, it's a vessel, seems to be inhabited by the spirit of a mischievous young boy.
He is highly active and has been known to pull girls' hair and hide objects. So at this point I'm thinking I'm leaning towards this one.
Pulling girls' hair. That would be hilarious. And hide objects, especially when guests are over. There have been occasions where the doll has been, that's not, I'm correcting it, that's not what they wrote, but has been in a different area of the room than I had left it.
Shadows have appeared around the doll as well. Coco isn't harmful, however. He just seems to love the attention. I'm the only attention whore here, Coco.
We'll think about it. We'll think about getting you. Let's move on to the other one that I had a choice of. Veronica, a rubber baby doll toy. So, may or may not be more creepy, but rubber doll toy.
$30. Veronica is a vintage rubber doll. She actually has a squeaker. I would compare it to a dog toy sound. The doll itself does have an old haunted look. This again, I'm reading this from eBay.
I collect haunted dolls. I'm currently downsizing my collection, i.e. I want an episode of hoarders coming up and I want to make my apartment look a little bit nicer.
Veronica is an active spirit. Active, so apparently, eBay terminology, you have very active and active and then just haunted doll. And active means stuff happens quite often.
Very active means it happens so often it's bordering on annoying.
So, when you're searching for a haunted doll, you want to look for the words active or very active. If you're a beginner in this collecting, you might want to start off with a few active ones before you start getting to Dennis the Menistals.
Veronica is an active spirit. I've experienced vivid dreams that's completely useless to me. Doors opening and closing, flickering lights, perfume scents in the room she is located, a woman whispering hello.
She's like, it's weird. Whenever I pick up the phone and it's my mother on the line, I hear a woman say hello. It's so weird.
I believe her to be an active yet positive spirit. She has scared me a few times with her whispers or opening a door on me.
Like, opening a door. She's like walking the doors or slamming her face. Life turns into the naked gun.
She's scared me a few times with her whispers or opening a door on me. Put, I think she meant but. I hope she did. Opening a door on me but she is not a negative spirit.
So I had the choice between those two and I thought I got one of them that pulls girls hair which is awesome and it walks and moves around the room and it makes shadow people appear.
Or shadows appear around the doll. She's like it's so weird whenever a light is pointed at the doll I see a shadow behind it. What?
And if you move the light, depending on the time of day, the shadow moves. So I have that choice and the other one is an old rubber doll that sounds like a squeaker toy.
She doesn't move. Doors open and close, lights flicker and you can smell perfume and then a woman says hello every once in a while.
I bought Veronica. I bought Veronica for $30. Show again guys thanks for supporting my Patreon. Because I would have never spent this money.
I would have never spent any money that I ever like earned in my life to buy a rubber doll from the internet.
And somebody's saying it's haunted. The reason why I chose Veronica was because I don't like stuff moving around my apartment.
And I don't mean like if I woke up and there was a doll walking across the floor it would scare me but I'd be fine with it.
I don't like it when I can't find my keys. That was the deal breaker. Like I was like that would be so funny.
A girl comes over to my apartment and she's like dude who keeps pulling my hair? I kind of like it.
And I was like yeah yeah Coco giving me a high five. He's always there to like test me if a girl likes her hair being pulled.
And I'm like go go he's my ultimate wingman. But I didn't want to deal with some dude moving my stuff.
You go to sit on the toilet there's no toilet paper. You go to sit on the toilet there's no toilet. It's in the bedroom.
I couldn't deal with that. So I went with Veronica which is funny because I have two friends who both go by the fake name Veronica for different reasons.
They use fake names but I got two Veronica's and now I got a third one.
And this doll I'm wondering we're going to get it. It'll be a guest on an episode. We're going to set it up.
But in front of a microphone I have an extremely sensitive microphone and we're going to go ahead and we're going to see if we get a hello.
Now here's the thing. I've been trash talking haunted dolls the whole time and really let me circle back to that.
I got two more things to say. I know this is a long episode but I got two more things to say. One.
I believe in ghosts obviously. I've been very very clear on that but that doesn't mean I believe in every single ghost story.
Whenever people are more into the money side of it the more you are into selling me stuff other than like I can read a book about ghosts.
I'll pay you for the hard work putting that book together. But when you try selling me junk and telling me it's haunted I'm very very suspicious.
Now there's a chance that Veronica, this Veronica doll is haunted. That this is one of the authentic ones. It is. It's possible.
Anyways we're going to get it here and let it hang out in my apartment, show it around, we'll record it and then I think it'll probably just end up in the corner of my room or something like that.
To scare people when they come over. I mean I don't really expect anything to come out of it.
The idea of haunted dolls is very very interesting to me because it really comes out of nowhere.
Like why are people scared of dolls? It's interesting because it's a very very recent fear.
People go oh you know haunted dolls have been around since the days of Ramses. All these articles quote a Wikipedia page and they mention this fact with really no attribution but apparently Ramses the second had these dolls made of his enemies and they would like kill the dolls and the enemies would suffer battle.
That's not a haunted doll. When people think of haunted that's a voodoo doll. It's something completely different. When people talk about haunted dolls it's kind of a narrow definition. It's a pretty narrow definition.
A ghost or a leprechaun or something is inhabiting a doll and that doll is capable of doing things or just being creepy. Or both.
So haunted dolls are actually very very recent phenomenon. People being scared of dolls. When we look back I had to do a ton of research for this. For this absolutely ridiculous subject but probably one of the most well researched topics recently.
When we look back we didn't see haunted doll stories really start to appear until the Twilight Zone's episode of Talking Tina. Or Talking Tina apparently. I always thought it was Talking Tina.
But anyways you would have a short story here and there about a haunted doll. You had Talking Tina though and then you had Prey which was from the trilogy of terror. I think it was called Amelie or Amelie or something like that in the television show.
But you had a short story about a little Zulu doll. It had a spirit in it trying to kill a woman from trilogy of terror. One of the scariest movies ever shown on television. If you haven't seen trilogy of terror watch it. Watch the last 30 minutes of it.
The third story. But anyways you had that you had the Twilight Zone episode and then there seemed to be an explosion of fear of dolls. And I'm not saying there weren't haunted doll stories or people talking about haunted dolls going back farther than that.
But it was not a phenomenon like it is today. And even when you look at like there was a movie like in the... I was looking at these movies that came out like in the 40's and 50's that are about haunted dolls. And again they weren't about dolls being possessed by spirits.
They're about people being turned into dolls or people being controlled by dolls. And then after the Twilight Zone and after the trilogy of terror there's a huge explosion in haunted doll movies.
I think this is the reason why I keep pooping all over haunted dolls as opposed to other ghost things. Is I think it's 100% a cultural creation.
Now again you could probably find a myth of a haunted doll or a story here and there of a haunted doll. But to explain now why kids don't like walking by their sister's bedroom because she has a bunch of dolls.
And that's the kid who drew me that drawing Finn. He's like "Oh I hate my sister's American girl dolls. They're super creepy." But the reason why they're super creepy is because of movies and television that make dolls creepy.
I don't think it's an innate fear. An old abandoned house on the end of town is an innate fear. It's the fear of the darkness, the fear of the unknown. It's a fear of dogs and hobos and a fear of ghosts.
Creepy Woods, same thing. There are certain fears that you can go "Oh I get it, like you just add ghosts to an already creepy location." But dolls themselves.
And you could say "Well they look like tiny people." People aren't scared of haunted GI Joes or haunted Tonka trucks. They don't look like people.
But people aren't scared of other toys. Like if you walked by a room that had a bunch of GI Joes in it you'd be like "I would be like "Oh dude this is totally awesome. These are like Generation 1 GI Joes."
But I would never be scared to go in there with the lights off. But if there was a room full of dolls I would be like "Ugh dolls are creepy." Even though I know that they're just plastic.
But because you're told that dolls are creepy it's reinforced. I read this thing before and they said "Kids find skeletons creepy because parents tell them that skeletons are spooky."
But before skeletons are used in Halloween decoration kids don't find skeletons creepy. Because it's kind of a goofy figure.
But once people go "Oh and then the spooky skeleton came out of the jungle then kids start to find them creepy."
So I think it's a learned behavior. I think it's a phenomenon, it's a haunted phenomenon that is 100% created by society.
Which is really really bizarre. Because I have a printer here that I haven't fired up in a long time and I had to so I could scan in Finn's picture for the cover art.
I'm gonna play this for you and tell me that this doesn't sound like some sort of haunted printer.
[Sounds of the printer]
Now what's interesting is it has all the hallmarks of like tension. You have a repeated "denenen" "denenen" "denenen" "denenen" noise.
And then it does it again "denenen" "denenen" "denenen" and then it does it a third time. And then when you expect the pattern to be repeated it makes a whole new set of really loud noises.
There's like those awkward kind of creepy silences where you hear "mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
There's like those awkward kind of creepy silences where he had going on. It's obviously not haunted. It's obviously not haunted. But it sounds creepy. I remember when I was first trying to do it I was like "Dude who previously owned this jigsaw? Like why is it making such weird noises?"
But if you were like six and your dad's printer like every time you walked into his office, his little den, and you were six and every so often you'd be like "Hold on honey I gotta print this out." And it made that noise.
It would probably be unsettling because it's quite loud. But let's say you're six years old and you hear that noise and your older sister goes "Oh no that means that it's hungry and it's going to eat your hands. You better leave."
The noise takes on a level of menace to it because it definitely has this weird tone to it. It doesn't sound like a normal machine doing something. It definitely doesn't sound like a normal printer. I gotta get a new printer.
But by adding a story onto it, it makes the noises more startling. If I had just played the track normally and didn't say "Here's my haunted copier" you would be like "Why is this noise happening? It sounds like a broken printer."
But if I say "Hey let me play for this." I think I said it was creepy or haunted or something like that. It adds a layer to it. Now imagine if there was a movie about a haunted printer and it made that noise.
During the trailers people were running down the hallway and the printer. You hear the noises and you hear the noises.
And you see it hiding in the closet. This office building has a closet you're looking through the gap and you hear the noise and it's getting louder and louder.
And then it crescendos and then it just title card and it just says "Printer 300 DPI. Deaths per instant." Coming July 29th.
And obviously people would laugh and they'd think that was hilarious but the movie is a success. It actually makes a printer terrifying. People would start believing their printers were haunted.
That's really what I'm getting at. You can make anything creepy. I know there's kind of a long about way to do that. I don't think dolls can be haunted. I think that 99.9% of them aren't.
I think that if you looked at haunted houses, houses that were believed to be haunted, I would say it's probably 50/50.
I would say that people, a lot of times the house is just derelict. It's creepy. There may be something going on there. There may not be something on there.
If someone says this house is haunted and it has this ghost and it'll give you 100 bucks if you spend the night, I'd be like "No, I'm good."
Maybe a thousand. But if someone says this doll is haunted and if you look at it, it'll make you feel like you just ate three Taco Bell meals.
I'd be like "Let's do it!" Not eat the three Taco Bell meals. Bring the doll over. Bring them all over.
I think the chances of you stumbling across the haunted doll is incredibly rare. Incredibly rare.
I think it's something that people, I think it's something that society has said was creepy and created a phenomenon.
The woods are naturally creepy. Haunted houses, abandoned houses are naturally creepy. Dark hallways are the light flickers.
I think that's another thing that was created by this society, by media. It's creepy because it's affecting your vision.
But again, I think that's also because of horror movies and stuff like that. But you start to get, and I think dolls are completely from short stories horror movies and your big brother or sister being jerks.
I think that's where all of the fear comes from. Clowns, kind of in the gray area. I think part of it's because you can't see their faces.
But the idea of the creepy clown, 100% the invention of the media. Even what's his face? That stupid John Wayne Gacy guy. He wasn't running around in a clown outfit.
That was like his side gig. He had a bunch of them. Killing boys was one of them, but he was like a general contractor was really his main job.
Creepy clowns, killer clowns. Complete invention of the media. You can say it's because you can't see their face. It's creepy.
Yeah, I guess. I guess. I've always wanted a bang a chick that looked like a clown. Not like she had giant feet and a big red nose, but like girls, like hot girls in clown makeup, I find extremely attractive.
Like there's photos online of like hot girls, but they're like wearing clown makeup and I'm like, "Ugh."
Anyways, that aside, I think there are things that are naturally creepy because it's an evolutionary thing. Dark, run-down places where humans used to be and now you don't know what's in there.
That's something, it's basically the evolutionary equivalent of a cave. We didn't go into unknown caves when we were cavemen, so you don't want to go into unknown houses as a, who we are today.
Dolls completely made up. I have no problem with haunted dolls. So Veronica is on its way. We're just going to chill. We're going to hang out, put a microphone in front of it.
A quarter-couple episodes, I'll have Veronica nearby. We'll see what we pick up. I will either be completely vindicated and prove that this doll, this $30 doll, which I'm not going to be mean to and throw it down the river or do anything stupid like that,
it's not haunted, I'll put it with the rest of my dolls, I'll have a funny story to tell people when they come over that I spent $30 from my Patreon on this doll that's supposedly haunted.
I'll either be completely vindicated or I'll be wrong. Doors will open, lights will flicker.
But I've got to be honest, the thing that does kind of make me nervous about the doll isn't the fact that, oh, you know what, if the lights flicker, okay, I don't care.
I've already talked about my apartment being haunted in real life, I've done episodes on that, and I've mentioned that I kind of feel like there's a peace treaty between me and the ghost of the old man in my closet.
But I bought the doll last night and I went to bed. And when I woke up this morning and I was shutting the lights off in my apartment because I leave for work quite early,
the sun hasn't come up yet, I'm shutting the lights off, it's pitch black in my apartment.
As I was walking to the door, for the first time in a long time I felt uneasy in my own apartment.
I felt like I may have a truce with this thing in my closet, but what happens if I bring something else here?
This doll does happen to be legit, and I have one spirit in my apartment, and now I'm introducing another spirit, willingly bringing it in.
What is possible?
God admit, that part of it makes me a tiny bit nervous. And as I was walking through the darkness to get to my front door, this morning I walked just a little bit faster,
because I felt it was a little more tense and a little darker than it normally was when I leave in the morning.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address, you can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast, you don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great one guys.
[Music]