What would you do if you finally met the woman of your dreams?
And then we travel to Lisbon, Portugal to take a look at an extraordinary event that
has us ask the question, are fictional characters the Antichrist today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys are
having a happy whatever day you're listening to this. It could be 3000 AD, who knows, but I hope
you guys are having an awesome fight against the Zentradi in the future. As we're watching the
future war unfold, in comes today's Legacy Patreon supporter. Give it up for Adam Carter.
Everyone give a big round of applause for Adam Carter coming in, cartwheeling into
Dead Rabbit Command. I'm sure he hears that joke all the time. It's like no, no one has ever
confused Carter with a cartwheel. Adam, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand that. Just helps read the word about
the show. That really, really helps out a lot. You have no idea how much it helps getting the word out.
Adam, I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the oars to the Dead Rabbit robot. We're gonna leave behind
Dead Rabbit Command. We're gonna row all the way out to Poland. Splash, splash, oh I have to come
up with a better sound effect for that one. But Adam is brilliantly guiding us out to Poland.
Specifically, we're going to Swinno Juicy Poland, and we're going back to some olden times in
Swinno Juicy. We're talking like pre 1848. So by the time we get there, the world's all CP atone.
It's like log cabins and I don't know a bunch of geese probably running around the town. They just
elected a geese as mayor and he's bringing in his people. We're in Swinno Juicy and there are these
two farm workers and they share a room and it's like the whole house is just one room. Imagine
this like a fairy tale, but it's not. I'm not reading fairy tales again. Even though the story
will sound like a fairy tale, just hold on. They're in like a gingerbread house. They're in
a gingerbread house and the roommates are constantly eating the walls. Ah, we've been exposed to the
elements. The big bad wolf is going to blow it down now. They're in like one room shack and
that would suck, right? Having roommates isn't the funnest thing in the world. Imagine if there
were no walls between you. You're just all laying in this house together and it's even worse because
one of the guys, we're going to name him Tommy, Tommy is plagued with horrible nightmares. So,
get off of me. Ah, the geese, the geese, not again. No. And in this time period, they called them
marts. Maybe the tea was silent, but it doesn't matter how they pronounce them. They were nightmares
and they actually saw it as the version of like the old hack. So what it is is a nightmare wasn't
just you having a horrible dream. Something was coming into your house and sitting on your chest
and making it hard for you to breathe and giving you these horrible visions. So, you know, like,
just all that basic old hag type of mythology. This happens every night and Joe's like, "Bro,
we got to work on the farm tomorrow. Can you please stop screaming at the top of your lungs
at three in the morning?" "But that's the spookiest time," Tommy says. What's happened so often?
That finally they get together and they're like, "We have to catch this." Because they're thinking
that the nightmare is a physical entity or at least some sort of energy they can control.
Nowadays, if you have nightmares and your roommate goes, "Did you try catching it?"
You're getting a new roommate. But back then, the other guy goes, "Oh, that's a great idea.
Why didn't I think about catching my nightmares?" So what they do is they come up with this plan.
Tommy goes, "Okay, the next time I'm asleep, when you hear me moaning,
I'm asleep. If I'm just laying in bed with the covers over my body, don't do it then.
But if I'm actually asleep, it's your cue to jump up and cover up the knot hole in the door."
That's how old this house was, that you just have holes in your house. You try to get like a door.
If you were really rich, your door had no holes in it. But this one is like, "So you're going to jump up,
you're going to plug the knot hole in the door because I bet you have this nightmare.
I bet you that's how this nightmare is getting in here. And then wake me up. Wake me up and
I'll grab onto the nightmare." And Joe's like, "That is foolproof. How did we not think of that?
Also, we should just plug the hole in the door anyways. Let's just do that. Not gonna be better
if we captured this nightmare." So what happens is, of course, that night, he starts having this
nightmare again and Joe, he runs and he plugs the hole up in the door. And then the dude,
Tommy, wakes up and he can feel the forces. He's grabbing onto something. "Oh, you're not getting
away from me. He's grabbing on to me. He's grabbing on to me. He can feel it. Try to leave." But he
won't let go and then eventually he feels the energy kind of dissipate and he realizes it must
be gone. We must have caught it, but maybe it got away. So homeboys, so the two dudes fall back
asleep, right? Because what else are you going to do after you've struggled with the supernatural
entity that broke into your house? You still got to get your Zs. The next morning though, they wake up
and they hear something in the house. "What, huh? What's going on?" It just woke up.
They see a beautiful woman crouched down behind their stove. Oh, geez. A little peek of blonde hair
sticking out there. I'm assuming because they said she was attractive, so of course she's a blonde,
right? She's looking out, looking out. And they're like, they look at each other and they realize
this must be the nightmare. So they get up and they're like, "Hey, we know that you've been
breaking our house all this time and giving me nightmares. Is that true?" And she says, "Okay,
listen. As crazy as this is going to sound, I am the physical manifestation of a nightmare,
but before you guys do something absolutely horrible to me, I'm a human. I'm an actual,
like, normal human girl who got turned into a nightmare." And Tommy and Joey kind of look at
each other and go, "Oh, that makes sense." Because the lore, again, if someone said that to you
today, he'd send them off to the loony bin. But the lore states that there are different ways that
a human can become a nightmare. If a human is born on a Sunday and... I didn't finish writing the
sentence in my notes. All it says is... Okay. In my notes, it says, "If a human is born on Sunday
and their eyebrows, they become a nightmare." I don't know exactly what their eyebrows are
supposed to do. You're like, "Jason, that's your only job is to research this stuff." I think it's
if their eyebrows... It's one of the two. If their eyebrows touch or if they have no eyebrows. I'm
pretty sure I was supposed to have written, "If a human is born on Sunday and they have a unibrow,
then they can become a nightmare." You can also... If you're one of the seven... If your family has
seven boys in a row and you're the seventh boy, you might become a nightmare. And the same thing is
there are seven girls. You're the seventh girl in the nightmare. You're the seventh girl in a row.
You could become a nightmare. There's all these different ways to do it. So she goes to that.
One of those happened to me. She goes, "My eyebrows." They look at each other and they
nod. They're like, "Oh, yeah, the eyebrows. You do have those eyebrows." And they wink because
they know the secret. Now that they've established that this young beautiful maiden is a nightmare,
but she's actually human, now the most important thing between these two gentlemen comes up. Who
gets her? Because at the end of the day, they've captured a beautiful woman. As horrible as that
is, that's the way they're looking at it. They're like, "Well, we have this captive. Who gets to marry
her?" So they start fighting because the one guy goes, "You will... You know, she plagued me night
after night for a long time. I had these horrible visions of death and misery." And then finally,
I grabbed onto her and held onto her so tight that the ethereal energy of her was not able to
leave my grasp. And I brought her to this reality. And Joey knows I put up some cotton in a hole.
So I should get her. And the guy's always like, "No, no, you didn't even have any nightmares."
So they fought over this girl. I'll put you through that, not whole Joey. If you keep complaining.
So he married this girl. We'll call her Elizabeth. So he marries Elizabeth the Nightmare and they
end up having children, which now Joey must really feel like the odd man out because now he's
basically just living with his family. And it says in the story, this German folktale,
quote, "They had children and lived together quite happily."
Unquote. And I thought, "Huh? What? Like, she's trapped. Like, she's still in servitude, right?
At a certain point, she's trapped." And you go, "Well, maybe they went on day trips and maybe they
went to see the site. Maybe they toured plague-ridden Europe." Who knows? But she was happy. But every
day, the victor writes the story, right? Because Tommy's like, "Oh, dude, no, she's totally cool."
Every single day though, she goes, "Hey, Tommy, I was wondering, could you show me where that
knot hole was that you plugged up with the thing?" Remember that whole time when you pulled me out
of the shadow realm and you plugged up that hole? Can you show me where that's at? And Tommy'd be like,
"Nah, it's maybe tomorrow, but I'm kind of tired right now." He's like sitting two feet from it.
He's like, you can easily point at it. He's like, "I've been working. My arm's hurt. Let's go have
more kids." And every single day she'd go, "Can I... I was wondering if you could show me that knot hole?
Hey, Joey, remember you and me used to hang out?" He's like, "What? We never hung out. You're just my
friend's wife." And he goes, "Oh, I still think you're pretty cool. Can you show me where that
knot hole is?" And Joey's like, "Nah, I don't really feel comfortable with that." If she's constantly
asking... If she's constantly... If every single day she's asking for something that pertains to the
way she was captured, I don't think you can include the line, "She was quite happily living with him."
Anyways, after a long time of this, and I don't know if she ever left the shack.
I don't know if her kids were basically like, gave babies and they never saw the sun.
I'm imagining they did, but she needed to have that knot hole released.
And she kept pushing and pushing, and then one day she goes, "Listen, I can hear my mom calling for me.
I can hear my mom calling for me. She's in England and she wants me. And if you just show me the
knot hole, maybe that'll make her stop." And she's still going on about this knot hole. She's had
like four kids at this point. She's still going on about the knot hole. And Tommy finally goes,
"You know what? Tell you what? I'll show you where the knot hole is." And he points to it,
and she instantly flies out of the knot hole and is never seen again. And now Tommy's raised.
He's a single dad. With these kids, he became a sitcom on Fox. It's a folk tale. It's a German
folk tale. It's interesting. I don't know what the lesson is supposed to be about it. It's from
a book called North German Saga's Fairy Tales and Customs. And I don't really know, is the moral of
the story not to wrestle with your nightmares? Is it to not... I think the moral of the story is,
don't tell women where the hole is in your door, because they might fly out of it. But I don't
know how applicable that is in the modern times, because at the end he just became a single dad.
He has all these kids now. He's like, "No, but I think when I read this story, I thought,
what if you could bang a nightmare? Like, what if you could have sex?" And I'm not talking about sex
with a ghost. I'm not even talking about succubus or incubus or anything like that. Like, what if
you could have sex with a nightmare? That's actually the most normal thing I'm about to say.
And then let's say that that nightmare has children. Oh, you know what? That's so abstract.
Let's think of it like, let's say you bang a ghost. This will make it a little more believable.
You're banging a ghost. A ghost is coming to your house every night. It's getting kind of frisky.
First you're sitting there watching television. You feel a little hand on your knee. And then
when you're taking a shower, you feel like fingertips on your back. You think it's just
the water going down your back, but it's not. It's fingertips. And then you get into bed and you see
like the covers move. You think it's just a horrible cockroach infestation. But you throw the
covers up and there's only three cockroaches. You go, "I saw more movement than that." And it's
really this ghost, this frisky ghost, and eventually you're doing the horizontal macarena with a ghost.
And then the ghost has babies, human babies, indistinguishable from other humans. What then?
Like, is it an interesting question? That's just you making up. That might be the most
ludicrous thing. In fact, Jason, I think you actually did an episode
making fun of a woman who had a ghost baby. I think I did too. But if you could have a
sex with a nightmare, we'll go back to that one because I did totally to Swiss ghost babies a
long time ago. If we talk about having sex with a nightmare, what would that do? What I really
want to get at is what would that do to the human DNA? What would that do to that lineage? Like,
that dude now has four kids who are the very, very best or half British and are the very,
very worst or half nightmare. Their eyebrows must be all messed up. And this is just one of those
weird stories because when we think there are so many stories throughout human history that are
about deities, being in humans. This is pretty much the entire Greek mythology is about gods,
banging people. And even when you break that story down, and it's a story of two dudes in a cabin,
and a girl shows up from the nightmare realm, they're still banging her and producing offspring.
Is there something in the human ancestral mind where we constantly are talking about,
not constantly, it's not on the view all the time, but it's something that sparks your interest. It's
half human beings. Like, what is it about that? Like, that is such a common trope. Even before
stories were a thing, that was a cliche. Even before things were being written down and narrative
structures were being formed. That was a thing. Half human, half spiritual, whether that's a
nightmare, whether that's a god, whether that's a nephilim, however you say it, it's so ingrained
into human culture. And I think that, what would that do to the human DNA if this stuff was possible?
Would it be distinguishable? If you were, if this was a true story and you were able to find
the ancestors of these kids, would you be able to tell or because it's so magical and interdimensional,
it would look like human DNA? Or is there a segment of society that is half Atlantean? At
this point, there'd be like one, one thousandth Atlantean, but you know what I mean? Like,
what would be the ramifications of having these people who are half nightmare, half human?
Like, what would it actually do? And that's actually, surprisingly, a great segue that
whole ramblinness was a great segue for our next segment. Adam, I'm going to go ahead and toss you
the keys to the carpenter copter. We are leaving behind Poland. We are headed all the way out
to Portugal. And as we're headed out there, I wanted to do a really quick Dead Rabbit Recommends.
It's one of those movies I really can't talk much about. I think the joy is discovering it for
yourself. I was randomly flipping through Netflix. I came across it. I had no idea what the plot is,
and I watched it twice in a weekend. I really, really enjoyed this movie. It's called The History
of Future Folk. Some people describe it as a comedy. I would describe it as a drama with jokes.
I would actually describe it as a documentary. I'm almost thinking this movie is real,
because as brilliant as this movie is, no one in it went on to do any other film. I'm wondering,
like, is this a true story? It's so bizarre. It's so fun. It's not dark. It's not spooky. It's just a
really, really, really well-made movie. It's the most whimsical movie you'll ever watch
that is about a flesh eating virus. That plays a part in the film. So, really, I recommend checking
out The History of Future Folk, and just put it on. You will enjoy it. It's on Netflix. That's
what I saw it on. It's on. It came out back in 2013, so it's an older movie. But Dead Rabbit
recommends The History of Future Folk. We're headed to Lisbon, Portugal. It's September 17th,
1680. It's 1130 in the morning. And I want to give a shout out to just a random internet user guy
named SoulDrifter. He compiled all of this really cool information on a website. It's a forum called
AlienExpans.com, and he did some really cool work. So, thanks, SoulDrifter, for getting all this stuff
put together. September 17th, 1680. We're in Lisbon, Portugal. And the city is just, you know,
doing its thing. The geese takeover has begun there as well. There's geese. There's a couple
chickens. They're the rowdy ones you got to look out for. And then the people just kind of milling
about town, and then all of a sudden a massive sound cracks across the sky.
Three tongues of flame spew forth. Baaah, baaah, baaah, hitting the ground. Oh no, run! Save the
geese! Lightning begins striking the city. Starting fires. His goose is cooked. So, that's the mayors
laying there. Oh, save me! A black cloud begins to descend from the sky.
And from it, thunder echoes across the landscape.
And out of this cloud emerged a huge hairy creature. And they see it, but it's like a blur.
It's running so fast, they can barely get a glimpse of it, let alone chase it, but people
are trying to chase this thing around. The city's in ruins. There's fires. There's still this horrible
lightning storm. And this monster is running around their fields. They're trying to chase it. They
can't catch it, but they keep running. And when they would get near it, it would be right in front
of them, and then it would be behind them. And then they'd turn around and be in front of them again,
and then it would start running circles around them so fast they could not make out any details.
This whole event, this whole event leads into a storm, a powerful storm, that hits the city of
Lisbon, and it kills 80 people. This is not a good day to be in Portugal. But this creature,
who they saw as this omen of this utter destruction of their city,
they can never catch a good glimpse of. They could see that he had a pretty big tail on him.
But the thing that really stuck out to them was this creature was blue, white, and red.
It's that Sonic the Hedgehog.
Sonic the Hedgehog. Now, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Give me a second. That Sonic the Hedgehog
came down to Lisbon, Portugal in 1680. He's running around. Now, this story was reported,
that the Sonic the Hedgehog part was not reported in this book, but there's a book called Wonders in
the Sky by Jacques Valet. He's a huge UFOologist and Chris Aubuck as well. He wrote this. The creature
is described as being blue, white, and red. And when I read that and I read how fast he was,
and he was running around in circles, I thought, Sonic the Hedgehog. Sonic the Hedgehog came to
Earth. Chris Chan is breaking out of jail right now, just to listen to this episode. Sonic the
Hedgehog came to Earth in the year 1680 and was running around Portugal. Now, that alone would
be an interesting topic to talk about. I mean, obviously a fictional character descending the
planet. Do we know what was Sonic the Hedgehog? No, obviously not. But I wasn't there. But he
does meet some of the criteria of being Sonic the Hedgehog. But if it was just a story that talked
about, and it's a pretty cool story anytime, anytime 80 people die in a city, you know I'm
gonna cover it. It is a cool story. The idea of this super fast creature is cool. The idea that it
could be Sonic the Hedgehog is super bizarre. Super bizarre. I can shock valley is not saying that.
I am. But then and then I thought about it. I thought about it. What if
fictional characters are the Antichrist?
Let me explain this theory. And what's funny is I have, I've seen this pop up in other places online.
I'm not the first person to put this together. But this was a story that I would see pop up on
Reddit or on some forum like, what was the, what's the other one I go to? Not above top secret. I go
there and I go to God like productions. I see it on God like productions a couple times too.
Superheroes are predictive programming. So when superheroes really show up, we will bow before
them. And that conspiracy theory was so nuts. And the people who were talking about it was so nuts.
I go, there's not really a narrative hook here. If you're going to be insane, it has to be organized
insanity. We've talked about that, that on this show, but I've seen other people mention that.
The one I saw specifically on Reddit, I'll see if I can look it up. I actually think it got deleted
was that when aliens invade, they're going to come in the guise of superhumans. And since we
already worship superhumans, we'll worship them. I'm taking it a step further. When we're dealing
with the interdimensional, we kind of talked about this on the Bigfoot episode, but this week,
but when we're dealing with the interdimensional, the average, the normal laws don't apply.
I could not walk out of this closet and become Superman. If I put on a Superman costume, I wouldn't
look like Superman. I would have to work out every day and take human growth hormones and
you know, get taller, all this stuff just to appear to be like Superman. But if I'm some sort of
interdimensional alien or a demon, I could appear like Superman easily, easily. And if you're already
demonic, if you already have these infernal powers or you have technology that can mimic
these things, you could have the superpowers of Superman, right? Think about it this way. Think
about it this way. Let's say the devil shows up tomorrow, right? He makes his presence known,
he's at like some sporting event, he's walking around. I guess I'm just described that scene from
The Dark Knight Rises. Imagine that, but Satan. Satan walks out on the field, he goes, "Citizens
of Earth, I am Lucifer and you, you sure you guys know me? I'm famous for a lot of stuff around.
I'm here, I'm taking over the world and all these demons are crawling out of portals.
People are gonna fight back, right? There might be, there might be a couple weirdos in West
Memphis that are like, "All right, now's our time to rise." But the rest of us will be like, "Yeah,
I think even Saint worshipers would be like, "Oh, I didn't know this guy really existed. Ah!"
We'd all fight back." So that's why the idea of the Antichrist when you read like the Book of
Revelation or even, the Antichrist is mentioned multiple times in the Bible, but he's also mentioned
as being there's multiple Antichrists. When you read the Bible, it's not a singular person,
so that kind of works in my favor. But when you work, look at the story in the Book of Revelation,
Satan takes the guys as like the new Messiah, right? He's coming down. So I always figured he'd
show up looking like Jesus, but when it come looking like a monster, right? He'd come looking like a
Redeemer, like a false prophet. But you would still have people. Now, in the Book of Revelation,
talks about like, you know, people will be confused and people will worship him and stuff like that.
So maybe there is some sort of magical element, like people are getting brainwashed and things
like that. But I don't know, nowadays it doesn't seem to take much for people to start going nuts.
Maybe you don't need magic. But anyways, I think even then, if some dude showed up and he's like,
I'm the Redeemer of humanity, if some guy showed up to you today and said that, you'd be like,
what? What are you talking about, man? I'm on my smoke break. Please leave me alone. And if you
started seeing people talk about that in the media, like all the news outlets are covering this guy
and he's this big Redeemer, he's the matreah, whatever, you're going to have a sizable chunk
of humanity that goes, I not only don't trust him, but I don't trust you because you believe in him
so easily. So I'm not only going to fight against him, I'm going to fight against you. So you want
to have a united front. You want to have all humans united against this demon, because it looks like
a demon in the first example. Now you'd have humanity split in half. And you'd have people
of different religions fighting together against this guy who's claiming to be the Redeemer because
he's interfering either with their economic interests or their spiritual interests or what.
It'd be like any other world leader that's tried taking over, but this dude has magic and
can turn into a seven-headed dragon. That's in the book of Revelation. But what if you could avoid
the war altogether? This is what I'm talking about here. I'm watching this television show called
Oz. It's about prisons. Prisons. It's from the 90s. I'm from the late 90s. There's a scene in it.
There's a young man in a wheelchair and he's been drug-free for about two years and he meets
his idol, his basketball idol, this basketball player who's now also in Oz. He beat up his girlfriend
or something like that. And the basketball guy is doing drugs. And this young man who's one of the
protagonist of the show, and there's not many because it's about prison. It's about corrupt police
and corrupt prisoners and how hats hang on heads and all sorts of crazy stuff. The basketball star
is doing drugs and he offers some to the guy in the wheelchair who we know now. We've known him for
quite a few episodes and he's kind of a moral center. And he goes, "Dude, do some drugs." And the
guy in the wheelchair goes, "No, I'm good." And he's like, "Do some drugs. Do it. Do it. Come on, man."
This young man in this wheelchair who's in prison for killing a cop. He's one of the moral centers
of the show again, by the way. He starts doing drugs. And it's so interesting because I'm watching
that scene and I thought in another television show he would have rolled away in his wheelchair.
That would have been it. And he would have had a moral victory. And we would have seen a difference
between him and the other prisoners of Oz. But he started doing the drugs and I'm sitting there
and I, my mind's processing this. And I thought that, imagine if your hero, because he goes on
and on and on. He idolizes guy. He idolizes basketball player. He's supposed to be like this
Michael Jordan level player scored 58 points in a single game. And now he's in your neighborhood.
In this case, you're in prison. Imagine if your hero wanted you to do something you knew was wrong.
Nothing serious. Not go on and kill anyone. Not go on and torture anyone. Just, you know what?
Maybe have that drink. Have that smoke. Cheat on your wife. Whatever. Your hero says it.
So we don't get taken over by a demonic entity. We don't get taken over by a religious entity.
We get taken over by something disguising itself as our heroes. Spider-Man, Superman,
the Flash, whatever. And that would be universal. You're not going to have everyone believe in the
Marvel or the DC guys, right? You may have people in other countries who have regional heroes.
Well, they show up too. I made that joke earlier about Christian. We did a whole episode on the
dimensional merge and eventually all the fictional worlds are going to collide with ours and it'll
be this paradise. As long as you don't live in Gotham City. What if that is how the world ends?
Not in the field in Israel known as Armageddon, but on every street corner in the world.
We merge with the fictional. We love our heroes. We love our stories.
We tell these tales of heroics. These fictional characters seem real.
You might be able to fight against a human adversary. You might be able to fight against a
demonic adversary, but would you be willing to go to war with the heroes you grew up with?
It'd be a lot harder. You may question, I think it's super weird that all of a sudden the fictional
world is real. That's fine. You would question that, but would you instinctively try to pick up a gun
or a pulse rifle or whatever weapon was lying around in this now fictionalized world to take out
Daredevil or Mickey Mouse or Bugs Bunny? You'd hug them. We have entire theme parks dedicated
to taking the fictional and making it real just so you can hug them. Take pictures with them.
The perfect way to win a war is for your opponent not to even realize the war is taking place.
The forces of darkness are truly as smart as we think they are, as clever, as deceptive
as we've all heard. They will not come in their true form. They won't even come in the form
that everyone's expecting. You look at the book of Revelation. They would come not as a redeemer,
but as a friend. What they appear is someone that nobody knew who has all these miraculous powers
and has to convince the world to bow before him or would Lucifer and his host of demons all just
take the forms of these fictional characters and inhabit our world and we love them already. We love
them when we look at the page or on the screen. We'd love them more if they stood next to us.
And once we are all in the thrall of these means, once we have all submitted our hearts and our
minds to our fictional friends made real, that, that is when the slaughter begins.
That is when we are enslaved. That is when we are broken.
They do have that old saying. The worst thing about heroes is meeting them in real life.
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also put us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great week guys.
[Music]
[MUSIC PLAYING]