Is there life after death? This is the question that has plagued humanity since
the first dude went "UGHH MY GUTS" and fell down and died. Today we're gonna take a
look at two stories that have opposite answers to that question. First off we
take a look at the story of a young family who starts renting a house but
they have no idea this house is already inhabited by a ghost who can make solid
objects appear out of thin air. And then we take a look at a scientist who spent
his entire life skeptical of the idea of life after death until one day he got
sick and died himself only to suddenly be reawaken in a world of endless
jello. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio. Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of
Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. Hope you
guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys are gonna have a lot of fun this
weekend. And this will probably be the last reminder. Next week May 13th I will
be in McMinnville Oregon at the McMinnemins UFO Festival. On May 14th I'll
have a Vinter booth out. We're gonna be handing out stickers and we're gonna
have a ball. It's gonna be a lot of fun. If you happen to be traveling through the
area swing on by. Say hi to me and then all the other weirdos and freaks that are
there talking about UFO stuff. It's really gonna be cool. And the following
week there's only gonna be four episodes coming up that week because I do most of
my production stuff on Saturday. All my research on losing that. To be there
and to be meeting people. Maybe meeting you. Who knows. But someone who I'm
meeting right now because you're walking into Dead Rabbit Command. Everyone on
your feet. Give it up for one of our Christmas livestream contributors.
Sawyer Elliott. Wooo! Yay! He's coming in dressed like a Christmas tree. It's a
couple months too late Sawyer. But come on in. Ring them little jingle bells.
Sawyer you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode. If you guys can't
support the show financially I totally understand. Just help spread the word
about the show. That really really helps out a lot. Now Sawyer let's go ahead and
get things started by tossing you the keys to the Jason Jalopy. We're gonna
leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're driving all the way out to a house in the
middle of nowhere. Now I found this story posted online by someone named
Mandans. And Mandans said you know this didn't happen to me. This happened to my
friend. This was a story that Mandans has heard. And we don't have a year. We don't
have a location which is pretty common for a lot of stories online really. Anyways
we're gonna go a couple years ago is when this story reportedly took place.
There was a young couple and their dog moved on to this rental property.
As they're moving into this new place this young couple they've already had
their own share of hardships. The girlfriend let's go ahead and call her
Mandy had already had back-to-back miscarriages. And the husband will call
him Jack. He probably has some bad stuff happen to him. I mean obviously miscarriages
affect both people and the couple but I don't have anything specific for him.
Maybe he stubbed his toe as he was moving into this house. But this couple
you know they're getting ready to have a nice fresh start in this brand new
rental property and they got their dog. We'll call him Rover.
I don't know why he's trying to talk. He's trying to talk for the very first time.
They looked at Rover they're like what did he just try saying something and the
dog's like nope. They're like oh okay. So you got Mandy, Jack and Rover moving into
this house and almost immediately after starting to live here Mandy starts to
have these experiences. It started off with things like feeling her hair being
tugged. Huh what? Huh? Who did that? And Jack's like in the other room. Rover's all
laughing like that dog from those old cartoons. But it's not him. It's not an
animated dog. It's Rover. Something was pulling her hair and then occasionally
she'd be sitting there and something would tickle her feet. Pretty creepy
right? She starts going up to her husband and me like Jack, Jack you won't believe
what just happened. Somebody pulled my hair and it's not the dog. Very
suspicious of him already. He's trying to build a blimp to enter some sort of
race. It's not the dog and then my feet got tickled and you weren't anywhere
around. I was just sitting here with my shoes off reading a book. Something
tickled my feet and Jack because of the things that they had been through and
the and because specifically because of the things that Mandy had been through
with the miscarriages he starts to think that it's probably just her
imagination. Oh you're just imagining physical sensations on your body. You're
just imagining your hair being pulled so he doesn't put much stock into it but
this happens so much. She starts to say hey we got to move. I'm actually too
scared to be here. It's not just by myself. I'll have these sensations while
you're in the house. Like we got to move. You know they're renting this property.
It seems to be a pretty good piece of property so Jack's like listen we're
not gonna leave just yet. We're gonna wait until the polder guy sets you on fire and
then we'll leave. He goes we're not gonna leave just yet. Let's go ahead and see if
your sister wants to move in with us. Maybe that will calm you down because he
doesn't believe that it's anything ghostly. So anyways the sister does end up
moving in and one night the three of them are sitting in the living room and
all of a sudden the husband and the sister hear a they hear a very loud
slap echo through the living room and both of them look around. I mean it's it
was an audible sound that came into nowhere. The husband and the sister are
kind of looking around like what in the world caused that and Mandy was sitting
there rubbing her forehead and she said as we were all just sitting here an
invisible force slapped me in the forehead and now everyone had had a bit of
an experience. I mean she got slapped. She was the one who got assaulted but the
husband and the sister knew something was in the house now because they clearly
heard the slap and there was nothing there to make the slap. I mean sure
there was sure there were six hands in there but none of them slapped Mandy
and she didn't slap herself. So the very next day the husband calls up the
landlord and says listen. It's gonna sound super weird but my wife keeps
getting tickled and my wife keeps getting tickled. Oh man my wife's getting
tickled and my wife's getting her hair pulled and then you know last night we
all heard a loud slap and my wife got slapped in the face by something so she's
ready to leave. Like is there something we need to know about and then the
landlord on the phone goes "Uhhh... Uhhh... Yes yes I was afraid this day would come."
The tickling, the hair pulling, the slapping of women. Oh it reminds me of a
memory I thought I had gotten past. You see seven years ago I used to live in
that property but I moved away. Obviously I'm not there right now. The landlord
jumps out of the closet and he's like "surprise I wasn't when he slapped your
wife." The landlord goes "I moved away because seven years ago my own son Matthew
drowned on that property. He died and knowing how precocious my five-year-old
son Matthew was I'm sure that's him. He's probably his ghost running around
slapping your wife, tickling your wife, pulling her hair." So... wait wait wait what?
What? You're telling me your dead kid might be here beating up my wife. The
landlord goes "probably like that's that's my best guess right when I lived
there there was no ghosts my son died now there's a ghost it's probably how it
worked out and the landlord begins yelling over the phone and he says quote
"Matthew if you're here stop playing tricks on this poor woman you're scaring
her." The the abuse stopped. Hair pulling and tickling and I wouldn't really
classify as abuse I guess if you didn't want it it would be abuse. Obviously
slapping someone in the head you shouldn't be doing that ghost or
otherwise but after the dad was like Matthew I told you once I told you a
million lifetimes quit slapping people after the landlord yelled at his son
over the phone the physical abuse stopped but the haunting never stopped as long
as they lived there and they lived there for a few more years they begin to
encounter all this other activity. Some of them is pretty benign right and you
could chalk it up to other things like the toilets would flush on their own you
know whatever that's cool like maybe it's like a plumbing issue and or maybe
it's a helpful ghost you're sitting there you're going to the bathroom and
you're like "phew I better flush the toilet" and then before you can flush it
it flushes itself. "Thank you five-year-old boy who just watched me
defigate you've done your duty" and they hear a little voice go "he he he duty"
actually another thing about it that would be quite terrifying I don't know
if it was flesh in the toilet while it's all they're taking a shower and he's
flushing the toilet they're like "ah I don't know if it was flushing the toilet
while they were sitting on the toilet because that would be creepy right to
think that there was a ghost I guess I wait if you live on at house you have to
make the assumption that while you are doing anything there is a specter of a
bloodied woman standing in the corner watching you do it I just I think that's
probably I think it's probably fair to assume anywhere you go so be on your best
behavior even at your home there might be some woman standing there in a
stained old ripped-up wedding gown with her face clawed off by her own fingernails
and she's watching you play Minecraft for nine hours no that that is probably
happening at some point but Matthew is not only flushing toilets he also would
play with their dog so remember Rover he's still a part of the story he rovers
running up and down the hallway sometimes and the two sisters and the
husband would kind of be like what that's weird Rover would run up and down the
hallway and they said the way that he was running was like someone was running
alongside him playing with him hey this way Rover wee
no let's go back the other end of this hallway I'm a dog I'm an idiot even I
think this is boring ghosts is like wee it's just like a three-foot hallway they
just run it back and forth Rover's like and so all that stuff is interesting
right no not really you're like I guess it's mildly interesting I don't know if
it's really worthy of a Friday episode but this is why I really wanted to cover
this the toilets flushing the plane with the dog getting slapped by a ghost this
is why I really wanted to cover this one day the young couple was sitting in
their living room and all of a sudden a matchbox car rolled down the hallway and
Jake and Mandy look at each other and they go we don't own any matchbox cars
do we they didn't have been wondering about a story if they're like oh yeah I
want a bunch of matchbox cars and the sister was playing with them they didn't
have any kids at this time they owned no matchbox cars but here was a matchbox
car rolling down the hallway and I think the implication is that the ghost
manifested it which is one of the most curious things I've always found about
some ghost stories and it seems to always be brushed over there's a lot of
times you hear about phantom coins like people in haunted houses hearing coins
drop and they turn around and there's a coin on the ground we covered a story
like that on the show or I mentioned it on an offhand comment before it's a
weird subset of hauntings physical manifestation of an inanimate object
that remains behind that's magic like ghosts are one thing you can explain
ghosts away in a bunch of different ways but if things are manifesting out of
reality now we've crossed fully into the world of sorcery and you would think how
come we don't look more into that how come that's not a bigger mainstay of
ghost stories physical pennies dropping out of the sky in haunted houses again
that's it's common and you think that would be a place you would just be like
come you know you know you just bring a couple buckets you're like ah now I'm
gonna make all my I'm gonna make my riches one ghost penny at a time and
you figure you could take this matchbox car right I would try to find out like
when it was manufactured like was it like the Batmobile little matchbox car
from the newest Batman movie like because there's so many weird ways you could
look at this like if the kid has access to he's dead right he's a dead kid maybe
he has access to all matchbox cars past present and future because it wouldn't
matter to him right he's just like sitting at home he's like oh that dog is so
boring and he starts floating around and where did he get it from did he go to a
toys RS and he's like you're linking takes them off the shelf and that's why
when this is my new conspiracy when you go to a toy store department store and
you find a package just empty like the package is there but the item is empty
ghost it's ghosts it's not shoplifters it's ghost like where did he get the car
was it a car from his original collection that he played with that he
manifested into reality was it a car that he found in his ghostly travels around
he's not Casper but I don't know how else to explain that he's floating down to
the local Walmart and checking out the toys or was it a car that was even ever
made by matchbox was this car actually produced because the thing is when they
find the pennies pennies are pretty obviously have dates on them matchbox
cars have dates on them as well but you know maybe they didn't pick it up and
look at it if you saw me you look at it it's like the year 3022 who knows I
there's so many ways you can look at this how did the matchbox car get there
why did he choose that car and we're all talking about the reasoning why how did
he make the car appear in ghost stories we all and I've never taken it for
granted I remember hearing about ghost coins a long time ago and I go this is
this should be studied way more phantom coins money coming out of nowhere are
they making the money or are they stealing the money from somewhere else like
did the penny have to be minted and then he's taking the penny from someone's
person dropping it on your head in the haunted house and it really opens up a
whole door to like the law of attraction imagine if you could corral 20
ghosts and some sort of like call center right and you just make them
constantly make matchbox cars you get a bunch of ghosts of kids they're like oh
I just want to see my mom you're like you can see your mom when she dies and until
then you're sitting in my call center and you're gonna make matchbox cars for
me and they're just sitting there like and they're mentally creating toys from
their childhood and then I take them down to like collector shop antique
roadshow stuff like that and they're like whoa how did you get this original
raggedy Andy doll this thing's like in mint condition and then I look at the
camera don't look in my basement there's a lot of dead kids in there be around
and then I get possessed by all the kids my body before that happens for that
nonsense happens I wonder if you could industrialize basically let me let me
say what I want to say but I'm trying to avoid what if you can industrialize
dead children to manifest objects that then you can resell now that I think
about it who wants to buy much stupid matchbox cars I have I have like a
little I have like a little toy stand outside my house and I'm selling the
matchbox cars for a dollar each the neighborhood kids and kids are coming by
to buy them I'm like you don't happen to be sick you look kind of sick they're
like no I'm feeling good you're like oh man I bet you really like matchbox cars
don't you I bet you can make all the matchbox cars in the world they're like
ah running away so yeah it's weird it's weird my weird money-making idea but how
do ghosts manifest though from this fairly mundane haunting right it's just a
poltergeist is just someone who's kind of messing around we have to look at the
theory that ghosts can create things out of nothing and that goes beyond ghost
powers like knocking on walls and flushing toilets and flicking lights and
standing in the corner while you're taking a shower all that creepy stuff
that's creepy stuff but the fact that they can actually manifest stuff out of
nothing who's to say you can't be sitting in your house one day and that bloody
woman in the corner of your room gets so tired of you she manifests the bullet
right into your heart and then she manifests the suicide note what that'd
be super crazy right that'd be insane and then you're standing there next to her
all bloody and stuff like that and you're like and now some other guy moves in
he's like oh what a nice place it's time to sit on my laptop and play Minecraft
for nine hours and you're like she's just gonna keep doing this so Sawyer
let's go ahead and be more profound I don't know why it became my slave labor
camp I was really gonna focus just on the fact that you can manifest stuff but
Sawyer Elliott let's get us out of here get us out of this ghost suicide pact
we're leaving behind this house we're waving goodbye to little ghost kid
we're headed all the way out to Lynchburg Virginia and there's a man his
name is dr. even Alexander and he's a neurosurgeon he works on people's
brains and one day he's sitting there in the operating room and he's like oh do
this guy's brain it's like totally nuts but I gotta heal it give me some of that
needles and thread he's like so he's also in the brain together he's like there
it goes nice and smooth they're like doctor no he's working on people's
brains and stuff like that and he saves this guy puts his skull back on and the
guy sits up goes thanks doc he's like you betcha that's what I do I save people's
brains and then as he's walking out of the operating theater this young nurse
walks up to him she goes dr. even Alexander that was so cool how you
didn't let that guy die the other doctor just loves to kill people that's so
cool how you didn't let that guy die but doctor what do you think what happened
if he had died doctor even Alexander goes hmm I've thought about this a lot
because my job it makes me focus on life and death one wrong stitch one wrong
needle into the brain he's so sad with sewing the brain together one wrong
twist of my wrist and that guy could be dead and I think there's probably nothing
after life right it's probably something that when you die your brain is flooded
with chemicals and you just dream of something that's where all these so
called near-death experiences happen and this was kind of his view for around
25 years he worked in the industry for 25 years but on November 10th 2008 he
wakes up and he's like oh my back oh dude this totally sucks and as he's like
complaining about how bad his back hurts his brain starts to hurt too no I
need that I need that to work and he's has this splitting headache the worst
headache he's ever had in his life severe back pain and he's like oh dude I
must be super sick with like the flu or something right because apparently he's
not apparently he's not a regular doctor knows those aren't flu symptoms he's
like maybe I just have the flu I'm gonna go back to sleep and his wife's like okay
honey but remember you have that brain operation soon he's like I'll do it later
he falls asleep a couple hours later his wife comes in to wake him up for that
brain thing he's supposed to be doing and she can't wake him up she's like even
even wake up bro wake up dude and he's just all and that's when she calls 911
he's all convulsing and stuff and his eyes have rolled back into his head she's
like oh no so she calls 911 ambulance shows up they throw him on a gurney and
he's all convulsing they're like strapping him down they're like I know
this guy this is dr. even Alexander he's the best brain surgeon he's the best
brain surgeon I know and I only know one we must save this guy's life so they're
taking him to the hospital it turns out he didn't have the flu right anyone
would have known that if you have a horrible backache and the worst
take ever probably not the flu he had bacterial meningitis it's this virus
that was eating at his brain and he goes to hospital and they're like dude this
dude is toast like even if we save him this virus has been eating so much on
his delicious brain that he'll probably be a vegetable but we'll try to do that
miss Alexander we'll try to save him and so they put him in a medically induced
coma now on dr. even side this is what happened and obviously this is where you
do get a lot of skeptics to say well you know it's all the chemicals and stuff
they're bumping into your body and all the stuff the body's naturally doing plus
he did have a brain-eating virus that's probably not gonna help your
cognitive skills but what dr. even saw was he was no longer dr. even Alexander
he died and was in this dark underground place his form his his essence was
trapped in Jell-O and he's just sitting there completely surrounded by Jell-O
in a pitch black underground cavern now he says I don't know how I knew it was
underground I just felt that it was underground but I'm sitting there and
I'm completely coiled up in this sea of Jell-O he goes I couldn't talk he says
nothing was in focus I couldn't see I had no memories before being inside the
Jell-O and I had no idea of a sense of self I didn't know I was an individual
I was truly a blank slate I didn't know who I was or where I was or how I was
and none of that mattered to me I was in the Jell-O he said there were these
black roots surrounding him as he's just sitting there in this war I'm trying
to think of another word for Jell-O as he's sitting there in this warm Jell-O
he's sitting there in this warm Jell-O-Ton and he has his quote about it
because he's been telling people about this he goes I died I died and I ended
up in the next life and I had no memories and no sense of who I was I was
just this new thing and people go that sounds horrible you're just like trapped
in this place and you don't know who you are or why you are you have no idea
about your family you don't remember anything and he has this quote he goes
quote people think going through this experience in this state of almost
amnesia must have been very horrific and yet I knew nothing else is a
possibility and therefore to me it all just seemed natural this was existence
that's a really interesting quote because again if I conch you over the
head right now with a billy club and me and that bloody ghost dragged you out
of your house and I took you underground and poured Jell-O all over you and then
you woke up right because you would know oh no I have a family I'm gonna be late
to work and I'm allergic to Jell-O he starts swelling up but if you didn't
know anything other than the Jell-O then why would you be scared you would have
no idea that there was a life outside of this Jell-O prison underground really
really interesting way to look at it and then this is so this is super
interesting so we have I love that detail to this the idea that when you
die you can end up in a place and not know anything of life so there's no
mourning there's no loss you just simply are as unique as that experience is
what's interesting is then it transfers into a very very by the book life after
death experience it's so basic there's a gate that shows up there's this
beautiful music playing and he's like floating through the Jell-O and then
he's taken to a paradise where marshmallow clouds of pink and white are
slowly gliding over a valley and then like there's a bunch of people in
peasant clothes dancing around come on over here over here take a bath take a
bath get the Jell-O off you and then come over here and then he climbs on
top of a butterfly and he's like flying around on a butterfly and then there's
like this beautiful woman sitting next to him she's like you're loved you're
loved here really basic life after death obviously to him this was a life
change and experience I kind of glossed over it because we've covered stuff like
that before and even if you've never listened to that show before that's the
standard life after death story right where you're walking a paradise there's
people in peasant clothes you feel like this joyous acceptance and everything
like that but the opening where he's in the Jell-O I find absolutely fascinating
I've never heard anything like that before with a life after death experience
that I can recall the second the middle part is a little boring it's a little
redundant blowing around paradise with a butterfly but then it ends with all of a
sudden paradise is replaced with pitch blackness an infinite dark void and in
the center of it is a bright pulsating light and he's looking at it and he
realizes that this is the creator this is the person who created everything and
it is at this point when he remembers who he is even when he was in paradise
climb on the back of a butterfly he's like is his family's mourning him he's
in the hospital he doesn't even know his family exists when he's in this black
void that's when he goes oh I have a family like I have people who love me
back on earth and I have co-workers and stuff like that and I have that brain
surgery to do and I have family members and stuff like that and then he remembers
his life on earth for the first time and then he sees five faces appear in the
darkness and they all have this concerned look for him and he wakes up comes out of
this he does have a long recovery it takes two weeks for his brain to even
start to fully function he's just laying there for a while but he doesn't make it
and when his brain is finally fully healed and he's opening his eyes he's
able to interact with the world he realizes because people are coming in to
visit him he realizes that four of the faces he saw in the darkness were family
members you didn't recognize them at first but now that he's seeing them in
the hospital room he's like you were there and you were there and you were
there he goes but there is a fifth face and I don't know who that was and
apparently what he says was he found out later there was a relative of his who
claims to have psychic powers and they were trying to contact him
telepathically while he was in his coma it wasn't there in the room but was
somewhere else trying to telepathically contact him a fascinating story
fascinating story doesn't like the wizard of Oz that's true but we have this idea
the really the most fascinating part was the beginning the rest of this story
about miraculous life after death I'm like boring get back to the Jell-O the
idea of paradise being there we've covered that before find that very
fascinating the idea though of not knowing who you are when you are dead is
infinitely fascinating to me because that goes against what most major religions
preach at least the Western religions right you you are reunited with your
loved ones in the afterlife but if you I mean I guess eventually he was right he
was running around I maybe his loved ones also flying around dragon flies are
playing jobs and you're like a John fly away and you're a little slow butterfly
the idea that you can not know the idea that you exist here and you learn and
you grow as a person and then when you die you basically forget all that stuff
and you're in this such a natural state and everything's wiped clean is
fascinating and a little terrifying I'm not gonna not gonna lie like I think
that's why I kind of glommed onto that that's terrifying state but if that's
all you knew right this is all we know that's what's so fascinating about life
and life after death we don't know what happens after you die I think there's a
common some people go I don't know and they literally mean they don't know like
they don't know if there's life after death but people like me I do believe in
life after death I will also say I don't know because it's such a weird question
if someone asks what do you think happens to us after we die I will say I
don't know but the full answer is I believe we go somewhere but I don't
know what it is or what that experience will be like will there be gravity in
paradise will there be enough butterflies for everyone or will some
people get stuck with caterpillars and they're just going they're just riding
that caterpillar around who knows like that's the thing when I say I don't know
I'm talking about the specifics and I think a lot of people when you ask them
what do you think happens to you when you die I think a lot of people when they
say I don't know they mean the specifics they're not talking about the big
question about life after death this is really fascinating and there's actually
been a big push lately I've been seeing more and more of these articles
psychology today just ran a big article on Monday about how it is obvious that
there is life after death there has been so many accounts of people having these
experiences and you can caught you can keep saying well it's just the chemicals
firing in your brain you can keep saying that over and over and over and over and
over again but that is that really the answer is that really the answer and
what's interesting is they say people who are not religious have these
experiences people who did not believe in life after death before this
experience afterwards said like was like a huge conversion right a huge amount of
people say no it's obvious there's life after death and what I thought was so
interesting they did this study and that's what this psychology today
article was referencing one of the things that constantly popped up in this
study was when people die and have these experiences these near-death experiences
they almost always say the world I went to was the real world like it felt more
real than anything I've ever experienced here that was a common refrain when I
died it felt like I woke up it felt like that was reality and this is a place
we're at while we're learning things or a place that we're at while we're
killing time together that's so interesting that that was a common
statement when I died I went to the real place I was home there that's where
I'm supposed to be as they're doing the interview they're like you have any
cyanide on you or maybe I don't know like is this building on the tenth story a
lot of people are saying that that was realer than anything here in reality
fascinating way to think about it and again tying it in with the ghost story
and we'll wrap it up like this which one is accurate how can you have both how
can you have a soul die like a young boy drown and then his ghost trapped on
earth and then this doctor have a brain disease and go to paradise like how well
how do the physics of ghost work we've talked about that a lot on this show and
it's a question that I'll always wonder not gonna talk about slave labor camps
for kid ghosts again but I'm talking about why are some people ghosts and
some people go to paradise I don't understand I mean you can look at it
from a religious perspective right you could say well maybe Dr. even Alexander
followed this religion maybe the five-year-old boy was a dirty heathen
but I don't think it's that because you do have people that of all religions that
end up as ghosts and then you have people of all religions or no religion go to
paradise have these visions or go to these places a place realer than the
real world how do you get slotted into what how do you I think it'd be dope to
be a ghost honestly for a while but I want to want to do it for like six seven
thousand years right but to be honest I think paradise would get a little boring
after six or seven thousand years fascinating story what happens to you
after you die my answer is something happens to you but whether you become a
ghost or you go to paradise or what paradise is like whether you're reincarnated
or sit next to the creator I don't know I don't know the specifics I it's so
bizarre to me that you can either end up in an endless sea of jello and then
dance with other joyous humans in this lush verdant valley and then hit your
ride on a butterfly wing on your way to meet the Creator of the universe that's
one option the other option is you're a lonely ghost a little boy in a house just
sitting there that when a young couple moves in you get so excited you start
teasing the mom you just want some affection you just want some love why is
the little boy ghost trapped here and Dr. even Alexander went to paradise and
came back a true mystery it's the one question the one mystery that someday
we will all solve on our own we will all know the truth of life after death sooner
or later dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address you can
also at us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio tick tock is at dead rabbit radio
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true friend
podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today
have a great weekend guys
[Music]