A bizarre new holiday tradition has started, apparently.
I guess from now on, Kevin Spacey is going to put out mysterious videos every Christmas.
And then we travel to Hood River, Oregon, where Bigfoot was spotted on the freeway.
Or was he today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had a great Christmas.
I did.
No snow.
Stayed at home, watched some movies, got caught up on the Mandalorian, played some video
games.
It was a fun Christmas thing.
But speaking of Christmas.
Oh yeah, and also dude, you want to talk about like aggressive bots?
Here's a little behind the scenes stuff.
If you listen to the Christmas episode, it's still up on YouTube.
They haven't gotten that yet.
But if you listen to it on the podcast for in the first hour, I sang quote unquote saying
"Sleigh bells, sleigh ride."
It was some Christmas song.
And within 40 minutes, the video was taken off of Facebook for a copyright claim.
So when I say "sing," I sang like the first two lines of a song, a Christmas song, and
I messed the one of them up.
And yeah, within 40 minutes, the video got taken out from Facebook, which is fine, whatever.
I didn't know the song had a copyright.
I thought it was a super old Christmas song.
I had to go and re-edit the podcast.
The YouTube version still has me singing that song, but it's only a matter of time before
they think.
It's weird how quickly the bot can find that.
Because I don't think someone working for NBC, which is the copyright holder, was listening
to the podcast for maybe.
If it's a bot though, I'd like to say just hear this next episode of this podcast we're
going to have, because I think it would be great.
I wonder if how many notes it takes to trigger the bot.
Who knows?
I guess we'll find out if it gets me when I go just hear those stories that we're about
to talk about.
The first story is a new Christmas tradition.
So let's all cuddle around the fire.
Come here.
I'll hold you.
I'll swaddle you.
I've been swaddling you guys lately.
Come here.
Yeah, get on my, come on.
I put a little blanket.
We got a shared blanket.
We're drinking cocoa.
I'm drinking keto cocoa, which is just water.
It's just brown water, toasting to each other.
We're sitting around the fireplace.
It is time for a new Christmas tradition.
Apparently this is a thing now.
We're going to sit right here.
Hold my cup.
Hold my cup of hot cocoa.
My cup of hot brown water.
Hey, let me get my YouTube video set up here.
We are going to watch the newest Kevin Spacey Christmas video.
This is so bizarre.
So last Christmas, he released a video called Let Me Be Frank, and I did an episode on it.
It's one of my most watched episodes on YouTube.
And it was just people who were like, "What?
You're an idiot.
Kevin Spacey's member of the Illuminati."
Yeah, yeah, sure.
But anyways, I was just like, "This guy's a lunatic.
He releases this video like five, six hours later.
He gets charged with sexually assaulting some 18-year-old dude in New York, and we'll get
into all that."
But anyways, so that was weird.
That whole thing was weird.
And then this pops up.
And also heads up to Chris Kay.
He's the founder of the Golden Rabbit Brigade.
I was wondering whether or not to cover this story, because I just thought it was a weird
thing.
And he's like, "Hey, you know, here's some weird details."
So I looked into it a little more.
So thanks, Chris.
This is the video.
This is the transcript, because I don't want to get demonetized.
Here's the video.
This is him.
So we're sitting in front of a fireplace, and it's very meta, because we're watching
Kevin Spacey sit in front of a fireplace as well.
And this is what he says.
You didn't-- and the only reason I'm reading all of this, because I think there might be
some clues to what I don't know.
This whole thing is so bizarre.
Let me just read it to you.
"You didn't really think I was going to miss the opportunity to wish you a merry Christmas,
did you?"
And you're like, "Jason, that's the worst Kevin Spacey impression possible."
I'm not-- he's doing his character Frank Underwood from House of Cards, who has this
weird southern drawl.
It's still a bad impression.
Not excusing it, but don't-- I don't want you to think that's how I imagined Kevin Spacey
talking.
Okay.
"You didn't really think I was going to miss the opportunity to wish you a merry Christmas,
did you?"
"It's been a pretty good year."
Okay.
That's important.
We're going to get into that.
It's been a pretty good year, and I'm grateful to have my health back.
And in light of that, I've made some changes in my life, and I'd like to invite you to
join me.
As we walk into 2020, I want to cast my vote for...
More Good in this world.
He does start doing these pauses at key points here.
Ah, yes.
I know what you're thinking.
Can he be serious?
In this point, he pokes at the fire.
There's another pause as he's poking at the fire.
Ah, yes.
I know what you're thinking.
Can he be serious?
I'm dead serious.
And it's not that hard, trust me.
The next time someone does something you don't like, you can go on the attack.
But you can also hold your fire and do the unexpected.
You can kill them with kindness.
And then that weird musical cue you just heard is in the video.
That wasn't a joke.
That wasn't something I edited in.
The weird creepy evil musical cue happens right after he says "kill them with kindness".
So I...
That was not a funny gimmick that I was doing.
Now, let's...
So this is super bizarre.
So when he came out with the first video, people thought this was the thing.
He was releasing it to let the elite know that if you have me thrown in jail or if I
get punished, I'm going to spill all my secrets.
It was a warning shot to the Illuminati.
In the video, he was holding a mug that he got from the Tower of England gift shop.
Anyone can buy these, by the way.
But it was a sign that he was threatening the Queen of England.
If he goes down, everyone goes down all this stuff.
And it's funny because now we know that Prince Andrew was tied up into Epstein.
And that wasn't...
People who followed Epstein knew about that back then, but now that's public knowledge.
So that can be tied back into it.
All these people that knew of him, he knew of stuff, Kevin Spacey.
All the people he knew about Kevin Spacey's dollyances.
He knows about them.
And if I go down, you all go down stuff like that.
People saw it as a threat against the elite.
Now he says in this, "It's been a pretty good year."
And it actually has for Kevin Spacey.
Now Kevin Spacey, all the charges against them are alleged.
But he started off the year in not a very good spot.
Because in 2017, he was accused by actor Anthony Rapp of sexual assault when Anthony was only
14 years old.
And this was really one of the big gets for the Me Too movement was Kevin Spacey.
And funny looking back, they didn't get many.
You got Harvey Weinstein.
You got Spacey.
And then Bill Cosby.
And now R. Kelly.
Stuff like that.
But it's kind of winded down since then.
Matt Lauer.
That one was creepy.
With the door.
He had the door.
He'd press it.
But these guys are like super villains, really.
Women would come into his office and Matt Lauer would hit a button.
Allegedly.
And the door would shut behind him.
Charlie Rose got caught up in this.
So there was a lot of big dudes who got netted up in this.
But for the most part, maybe what like 5, 10 people total went down.
Kevin Spacey I think was the only one who was gay who got caught up in this.
George Takai came real, real close.
But people were like whatever.
People kind of dismissed that.
Which sucks for the guy who accused George Takai.
So I just want to get all that out of the way.
Let's get into the actual interesting conspiracy stuff in it.
So it has been a good year for Kevin Spacey.
When he released that last video, like I said, that same day he got indicted for sexual assaulting
this 18 year old dude.
And those charges have been dropped.
Because what happened was the dude wouldn't turn over the cell phone because the defense
lawyers wanted to see what was on the cell phone because they were texting each other
back and forth.
Allegedly Kevin Spacey groped this dude.
And so they go we want to see your cell phone.
We know you were texting throughout the night.
The dude throws the cell phone away.
You can't find the cell phone.
The mom admits when she goes to the police that she had personally deleted text from
the phone.
Kevin Spacey denied it when the young man took the stand.
He took the fifth.
And so all the charges were dropped.
So it was that part of it was a good year for Kevin Spacey.
He's been charged.
He's had like 20 accusations in one theater group alone.
Young men coming forward and saying, so he was kicked out of his theater in England and
all that stuff.
But this was really the only charge, like legal charge that he was facing as of right
now.
Anthony Rapp when he reported it.
And so this happened to me when I was 14 years old.
That was it.
He didn't have any charges or anything like that.
He was just coming forward.
He felt that it was time because all these other people are coming forward with all those
experiences with older people in power.
So this was the only criminal charge he was facing.
So it has been a good year.
However, there's been some other odd things that have happened this year.
Now for one, the biggest, the one that everyone obviously probably knows about at this point
is he released this video on the 24th and on the 25th, one of his accusers committed
suicide.
So a day after he released the video, one of his accusers committed suicide, suicide
like Epstein.
We'll explore that in a second.
We'll explore that in a second, but check this out first.
That's not the only Spacey accuser to die this year.
Let's go back to September 2019.
An unnamed man who accused Kevin Spacey.
It was a masseuse who accused Kevin Spacey of kissing him against his will and forcing
him to grab Kevin Spacey's genitals was currently involved in a lawsuit with Kevin Spacey.
I don't believe it was a criminal charge, but was currently engaged in a legal matter
with Kevin Spacey.
September 2019, this unnamed man dies.
And within like a couple weeks, Kevin Spacey's lawyers motion to have the suit dismissed.
And people are kind of like, yeah, we get it, you can do that, but you know, generally
it's up to 90 days you can do that or whatever.
They moved on it really quickly.
That was done.
Now the question is, was how did this dude die?
Now on Wikipedia it says this young unnamed man died of cancer, but I read article after
article after article that just said this guy died.
The only thing I could find saying that this guy died of cancer was a variety article.
And if you look in the comments and all this stuff is in the show notes, when you look
in the comments of the variety article, it says the original version of this article
did not mention cancer.
It was added later.
That's what one of the commenters said.
They were saying they were on the article earlier and it didn't say how he died and
then was updated.
In the variety article it says a source tells variety he died of cancer.
It's odd because it says on Wikipedia he died of cancer.
Every other article I read just said he died, he died, he died, he died.
It wasn't until I typed in "Kevin Spacey, lawsuit, cancer, was I able to find an article
that actually specified he died of cancer?"
That's how hard it is to find that.
So it almost is like the only people who say that he died of cancer is variety.
It's weird because you would think if you had cancer, this might be bizarre, I've never
had cancer, but if you had cancer you would either record all of your testimony up ahead
of time.
So if you died of cancer the lawsuit could still go through and then your family could
reap the benefits.
Or if it was a criminal trial, cops definitely want that information before you pass away.
That should be enough.
If you are dying of a disease and then you die they don't just go "pfft" trials over
like you can leave evidence.
So if he really died of cancer, which I mean it's not like you wake up one day and you're
like "ooh my back hurts" and then you just die of cancer that day.
It's a progression, it might be a couple weeks, but so that's weird.
But it's possible he died of cancer, even though only one person reports that and we
don't know who the person is.
But that lawsuit's gone, young man has passed away.
In 2019 as well, in other, this one was really weird because I didn't know about this one.
I knew about the masseuse and I knew about the guy who just passed away, committed suicide
just a day or two ago.
But I didn't know about this one until I really started looking into this.
2019, May, May 2nd 2019.
So there's a woman or was a woman named Linda Culkin who actually accused him of sexual
assault back in 2009, so way before me too.
And on May 2nd 2019 in Quincy, Massachusetts, she walks across the street while traffic
has a green light and is just ran over, killed on the scene.
Now people were like, she's just like, she just walked into traffic.
Suicide?
Who knows?
Accidental, daydreamin' and listening to music, who knows?
But the fact of the matter is she walked while she had a red light, while traffic had a green
light and she was killed on the scene.
Now you're like, wait a second, Linda, that's a girl's name, why is she accusing Kevin Spacey?
Kevin Spacey didn't sexually assault her.
Back in 2009 she was a nursing assistant.
And one of her patients said, you know, Kevin Spacey sexually assaulted me and she apparently
went nuts.
This is a really, really weird story here.
Never heard any of this before.
2009, she gets this information, I don't know if I'll have time for the Bigfoot story,
we're gonna see, because this is a really, really conspiratorial world we're going into.
So in 2009, she hears that one of her patients was sexually assaulted by Kevin Spacey, allegedly.
And then, alleged everything, alleged everything, okay?
So because we're gonna get even weirder stuff going on.
So what happened was, she hears this story and she begins cyber stalking Kevin Spacey
to the point where she begins calling in bomb threats, harassing him and his associates,
and then mailing white powder to them as well, anthrax.
Basically a terror campaign against them.
She was actually, this whole thing went on back in 2009, she was doing this stuff, she
was harassing him, she gets arrested, taken to trial, found guilty, serves 51 months in
prison because of this.
And that happened in 2014 when she got arrested and went to prison.
So about a five year time span, she was involved in this terror campaign.
Now she gets out, obviously, Cartes and Hitter in prison, she gets out, gets ran over.
Now you'd have to think she's probably pretty validated when Anthony Rapp came forward and
admitted that, and then you have all these other people admitting to the sexual assault
allegations against Spacey.
So she's like, "Oh, proof, but she dies this year too."
So now you have three people who died this year who are connected to accusing Kevin Spacey
of sexual assault.
So when he says something like, "It's been a pretty good year," in his video, it has
been for him, but not for those three people.
But this is an interesting side note to this whole thing.
Let's take a look at the actual, so we know what Linda's story was, we know about the
unnamed masseuse.
Let's take a look at this most recent guy.
This guy's name is Ari Bin.
Was Ari Bin.
And he killed himself on Christmas Day, a day after this video was released.
Now, obviously, that was one thing, Chris K. When I saw that too, I was like, "Well, that's
suspicious," obviously.
Let's take a look at Ari Bin and what's going on here.
So Ari Bin was married to a Norwegian princess.
And they'd been married from, I think, 2002 to 2017.
They're separating.
They had gotten a divorce in 2018.
They had two kids together.
And after this whole thing came out about Kevin Spacey doing all this creepy stuff, Ari
Bin gave an interview with a radio station, a Norwegian radio station called P4.
And this is the story that he told.
He meets Kevin Spacey at a dinner for Nobel Prize winners or Nobel Prize nominees or something
like that.
High-level, high-falutin people, hobnob and doing rich people stuff.
Ari Bin's there.
He's still married to his wife this time.
And here's his quote.
We had a nice conversation.
He was sitting right next to me.
After five minutes, he says, "Hey, let's go out and have a cigarette."
And then he takes me under the table in the middle of my balls.
I got more than I bargained for.
And then he starts kind of chuckling in the radio interview.
And then he says, "Eh, maybe later.
I had black hair back then and was 10 years younger, so was right up his alley."
So first off, that's a burn, basically saying that, yeah, he likes him young and I looked
kind of young back then.
The guy's a total creep.
But the idea of him just being like, yeah, you know, we're sitting there talking.
He grabbed my balls and I was like, no, maybe later and just kind of blew it off as a joke
and went on with my evening.
That's important to this narrative.
So yes, was he sexually assaulted?
According to the story, did Kevin Spacey sexually assault him?
Yes, just because you laughed it off doesn't mean it's not a sexual assault.
Still sexual assault.
The guy grabbed his genitals and was trying to get him to do something sexual and grabbed
him in sexual spots.
Still sexual assault.
So the fact that he laughs it off doesn't make an okay.
Shouldn't be grabbing people in the genitals.
You really shouldn't be touching people at all unless you're comfortable with them.
They're comfortable with you and all that sort of stuff.
In the moment when someone does that or you're telling the story afterwards, you're like,
yeah, that guy was a total creep, man.
He reached down and he grabbed my balls and asked me to go outside.
I was like, nah, that's cool.
And then you laugh about it with your buddy.
You're like, yeah, that guy's a total pervert.
Still sexual assault.
Just because he laughs about it after the fact, even telling the story years later, doesn't
minimize it.
What I think is interesting is classifying this guy as a Kevin Spacey accuser.
I think it's putting him into people who are taking him to court.
So the headlines that are saying Kevin Spacey accuser and most of the articles that talk
about this don't say specifically how he's telling the story.
Again, yes, it's 100% still sexual assault.
I'm not denying that whatsoever.
However, I would not place him in the same category as these men who are taking him to
court or Anthony Rapp.
That sucked.
When I read Anthony Rapp's article about what Kevin Spacey did to him, it was really sad.
That's going to be in the show notes and I really recommend people to read it because it's a
really, really interesting read about a young man who is basically taking advantage of.
And you're reading it first person.
Very, very well-written, compelling, true life story.
And I don't think Ari Bin fits into that.
Yes, 100% sexual assault.
And I'm not saying, oh no, it's okay.
He laughed about it.
I'm not saying that at all.
What I'm saying is that the narrative is being constructed that people who accuse him of a
crime are being killed.
He has, like I said earlier, at least 20 people in one theater company who are accusing him
of this.
Now it's possible they're disappearing like ducks in a pond.
That doesn't make sense.
It could be that they're disappearing, or just disappearing.
Doesn't need a metaphor.
And we're not hearing about it, possibly.
What I think actually happened here is terrible coincidence.
And I know you're like Jason, not again.
You use the coincidence card all the time.
Hear me out.
I think that Kevin Spacey made this, but here's, there's two ways to look at this.
Kevin Spacey made a weird video and a man who's recently separated from his wife of
15 years on Christmas kills himself, which unfortunately fits all the statistics.
Male suicides are higher than women suicides.
Suicides are higher in holiday times.
Men who are suffering from emotional trauma separated from their kids are more likely
to kill themselves and he's a middle-aged man.
All of these things are risk factors for being a suicide victim.
It's only, it would be what, his second Christmas away from his family.
Statistically, if he was 22 years old, totally happily, if PewDiePie accused Kevin Spacey
of sexual assault and then killed himself this Christmas, that would be super suspicious.
That would be incredibly suspicious because he doesn't have those markers.
But this guy did.
It's absolutely unfortunate.
I feel like this narrative is being constructed because the only thing is using that term
Kevin Spacey accuser, commit suicide, is the narrative we're being told.
Now there's two options.
Like I was saying, there's one.
Kevin Spacey releases a weird video and the next day someone who meets all the risk factors
for killing themselves kills themselves.
Or two, Kevin Spacey releases this video and somebody off to this guy, somebody killed
this guy.
That's not impossible.
I'm not saying that it's not impossible.
It's definitely possible, but I think it's unlikely because here's the key to this whole
thing.
We look at this all the time.
They go, "Oh, the movie The Exorcist is cursed."
And people died working on The Exorcist.
Oh really?
Yeah, the guy's uncle, the cinematographer's uncle, died in a car crash three years after
the accident.
Linda Blair is still alive as of recording this podcast.
So if the main players are still around, is there really a curse?
If Kevin Spacey is bumping off people who accuse him of this stuff, who's the number
one accuser?
Anthony Rapp.
Still around.
Still has a career as of the recording of this podcast.
So the fact that these secondary or titiuary, is that the word?
Because in this game, doesn't really play into the narrative.
I personally think Kevin Spacey made a weirdo video and then this guy killed himself.
I think that's the most likely scenario.
Obviously, I could be wrong if they could be connected.
Kevin Spacey could have been behind Epstein's murder.
I'm sure Kevin Spacey and Epstein knew each other.
Can't prove that.
I'm sure they ran on the same circles, along with all these other open secret weirdos and
Hollywood and things like that.
I think a more suspicious thing is the woman who accuses Kevin Spacey and then gets thrown
in jail for 51 months.
And you have to wonder, was she really going crazy or was she actually onto something and
the powers that be made her look crazy and have her thrown in jail?
Now again, the most logical answer is the woman was crazy.
The most logical answer is she heard this allegation, she actually did these things,
and she went to jail.
However, a conspiracy theorist could say, "Oh no, no, she was totally sane."
She found out that these allegations were true and on a quest for justice, the powers
that be to cover up for Kevin Spacey's crimes had her thrown in jail.
My answer to that, again, is then why didn't the same thing happen to Anthony Rapp?
Because he easily could have disappeared.
He could have easily gotten a cocaine charge the next day and then that would have been
it.
Or heroin charge before he even came forward.
He submits the article to the website that it was originally published for.
That editor is plugged into the powers that be, calls somebody up, someone says, "Don't
publish that article."
And then Anthony Rapp ends up in some rehab center.
If these people are as powerful as the conspiracy theorists believe, because they are either
all powerful and control Katy Perry, you do this song, you put this in your video, or
they're not.
They're either scared of Kevin Spacey revealing this information about the Queen of England
and they have the ability to start pulling the levers of justice to make sure that he
gets off.
They're either that powerful or they're basically just ordinary businessmen who can maybe make
a phone call to a judge in Iowa.
It's one or the other.
So if they can have this woman wrongfully accused or in a jail, why did Anthony Rapp's story
ever get out there?
If they can kill a member of the royal family, married to a Norwegian princess, if they can
have him executed on Christmas Day, why is Anthony Rapp still running around?
Or any of these other people?
Or Harvey Weinstein, like you can't tell me that Kevin Spacey has more political power
than Harvey Weinstein, or more political power than Matt Lauer, who would be far more
connected into politics than some actor who played one on television.
So the conspiracy theorists are either works or doesn't.
I find the story fascinating.
Oh, and I have to say this too, Chris Kay pointed this out.
I don't know how he discovered this, but apparently just to put this all in a bigger
bow, no pun intended, there's an ornament on the set for the Kevin Spacey video and
there's a little piece of tassel in front of it, so it makes it look like the letter
Q.
So pulling this all into the Q mythology as well, where you have Donald Trump.
supposedly has an agent or an ally, somebody named Q, and maybe Trump himself, and maybe
his son Barron, and maybe someone in the administration.
I know almost everyone's been rumored to be Q at this point.
Basically someone who, the story is this, that Donald Trump is going to throw all of
the child-listing Democrats in prison and like the impeachment and the Mueller report
and all this, like the Mueller report was supposed to be this, and now we're getting
into all this nonsense.
The Mueller report was supposed to be really, Robert Mueller was investigating the Democrats,
it was a cover, see, and when the report came out it was going to indict Hillary Clinton
and Barack Obama and all these people for like child-listing and human trafficking and
all this stuff.
That obviously didn't happen.
And then, could you imagine if it had, if it had, but anyways, drain the swamp, Q is,
Trump's really going underground trying to root out all the corruption in America.
He has done a lot of stuff into human trafficking, trying to shut down human trafficking and
stuff like that.
So, but Q really builds into this whole thing, like there's an inner war going on in Washington,
D.C. and to that, there probably is honestly, we see little blips of it pop up here and
there in the news.
I don't really believe in Q being an individual or a movement.
He originally started off posting stuff on 4chan or somewhere and it was floating up
to 4chan, clues and codes and all sorts of stuff.
That stuff's still around.
But anyways, so now Kevin Spacey's video is getting brought into this Q mythology as well.
So is he Q?
Is he sending a message to the actual Q to say maybe I'm on your side?
Because he does say that thing about what I'm going to do in 2020 is my vote is to be
nicer or something like that.
Is that him throwing a bone to the Trump administration saying yes, Q, see this little Q and I'm saying
I'm not going to be anti-Trump this year.
You and me will work together, help drain the swamp.
I know who the Chalmolisters are.
You know who you think they are.
I can give you proof.
Is it a message to them?
Let's kill them with kindness.
Let's work together.
All of this stuff from a one minute Kevin Spacey video.
It's horrible that a man died on Christmas Day and obviously millions of people died
all over the world on Christmas Day.
It's not just because this guy's famous and in the news makes his death more important.
I'm just, it's suck.
Maybe not millions, 100,000.
What I'm saying is that, it's not the point how many people died on Christmas.
That's depressing.
It sucks that this guy passed away.
I don't necessarily think Kevin Spacey had anything to do with it.
I'm not going to say 100% he didn't, but I would, if I had to bet money, I would assume
it was just a man who would spend his second, maybe even his first Christmas away from his
family and he saw a future of him not with the woman he loved and the kids that he cherished
and he killed himself, which is unfortunately very, very, very common for men and women,
but the risk factor is a lot higher for middle aged men.
It's middle aged single men.
It's much, much higher.
So, terrible tragic story.
I personally, and I've talked about this before, whenever we have stories where people kill
themselves and it gets wrapped up into conspiracies, Anthony Bourdain was the same thing.
I think we look at, I think to look at them and go, "Oh, it's because of this, that or
the other thing."
It's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that
it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that
it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just
that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's
just that it's just that it's just that it's just
just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's just that it's