Thomas Hanks, a man whose name is normally associated with great films like Big, The
Burbs, Dragnet, and Joe vs. the Volcano.
I'm sure he wants some Academy Awards, but those are his best ones.
But nowadays the name Tom Hanks is synonymous with Adrena Chrome Parties, and being executed
just a few days ago.
And then talk about the ramblings of a man man.
While I was on vacation, I got so sick.
I was on Death's Door, I went on a "unintentional spirit quest."
I blacked out and journeyed through the void.
And while I was walking through the endless eternal darkness, I found out that two Mexican
people live in my esophagus.
Today, on season 15 premiere of Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are okay with that unusually long intro.
It's season 15.
It is the start of a brand new season.
I do apologize.
I'm a day late.
I thought I got mixed up with- I did almost die.
I did almost die on my vacation.
So you'll have to excuse me.
My date keeping skills aren't up to par yet.
But yeah, I'm sorry.
So we're only gonna have two episodes this week and the next week.
We're gonna start doing the normal weekly.
Sorry, I apologize for that.
It took a little bit longer than I had planned to do.
But I know someone who will always allow me to take as long as I want.
It sounded weird.
One of our newest Patreon supporters floating into Dead Rabbit Command.
It's Morphous Gas.
Everyone give a round of applause to Morphous Gas.
This little cloud's floating into Dead Rabbit Command.
Morphous, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just helps read the word about the show really, really helps out a lot.
Ask yourself, what did I do to promote Dead Rabbit Radio today?
And then do something.
Don't just ask yourself that question.
Do something.
Also, quick behind the scenes note, we are gonna be doing a lot of stuff on TikTok going
forward.
So subscribe to my TikTok @DeadRabbitRadio.
It's gonna be a lot of the stories that you've heard in the past, but a minute long.
So if you haven't listened to every episode, that's a good way to catch up.
And there will be no dancing.
If you're afraid that I will be dancing, I guarantee you there will be no dancing on
my TikTok.
Just lots of cool, old stuff.
And some new stuff.
There's gonna be a lot of true crime that I don't really want to talk about on the podcast.
I don't want to talk about on the podcast.
So I'll pollute my Dead Rabbit Radio TikTok account for that.
So, but TikTok dancing or no TikTok dancing, it's time to get today's episode started.
Morphous Gas.
I'm gonna toss you the keys to one of our brand new vehicles, the Dead Rabbit Dropship.
Go, go, go!
Everyone's running on it.
You're just sitting there.
You thought you were just listening?
You thought you were just gonna sit and listen to a podcast?
No way!
You gotta get up and run.
You got all your military gear on.
We're running onto the Dead Rabbit Dropship.
And there's like a sergeant on board and he's like, "We're moving in with first wave.
You kill anything that looks like Tom Hanks?"
And you're like, "What?
That's so specific.
Why don't you just say we kill Tom Hanks?"
And he goes, "No, we're gonna smash the entire area.
If it looks like Tom Hanks, you get him.
What if I were supposed to kill him?
He's a really bad sergeant.
Cause you don't like where he's supposed to kill him?
Are you arresting this guy?
Dead Rabbit Dropship.
Leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're headed out to Milan, Italy.
It's June 12th, 2021.
Super recent story.
I'm surprised this isn't getting more play in the lame stream media.
This is too busy talking about the Olympics and medals and stuff like that.
When the real medals should be put on the chests of the 173rd Airborne Combat Brigade,
because those are the heroes that recently arrested no one Adrena Chrome Smuggler, Tom
Hanks.
I know you guys have fond memories of Tom Hanks starring in all of those movies.
All those childhood movies you watched.
Like Philadelphia and Saving Private Ryan.
All those Saturday afternoons.
Watching a man's face get blown to pieces.
But maybe you're like me before he started doing all this ultra violent and depressing
stuff.
When I was a kid, Tom Hanks was hilarious.
Tom Hanks was so funny.
He was in Dragnet, which is very, very interesting, and the Burbs.
You know the Burbs is a very, very famous movie he was in and it was about a conspiracy.
It was about a man who believes there's like a satanic, cannibal cult in his neighborhood.
And when we talk, Tom Hanks is such a fascinating character outside of his whole acting career.
Outside of the stuff that's real.
Because he's been embroiled in this huge Pizza Gate, pedophilia, Adrena Chrome scandal for
a couple years now.
And the COVID thing first started.
When those lockdowns first started, he was in New Zealand, I believe.
And he was one of the first casualties of this war where people go, he's not really
in, because he said, I have COVID.
And he was one of the first like famous people who got it.
And he goes, I got COVID and then the conspiracy started.
No, he doesn't have COVID.
Well, he may have COVID, but he's not in a medical facility.
He's not locked down in his hotel room.
He's actually in prison.
You guys remember that?
We covered it a little bit back then.
So weird.
But Tom Hanks has been embroiled in these weird conspiracies for quite a while.
But when you go back and look at his filmography, he actually had two movies that dealt with
secret satanic societies trying to take over the world or take over the city or the neighborhood.
The Burbs, most famously, but Dragonet was a remake of the old television show was him
and Dan Ackroyd.
And there was a satanic cult in Los Angeles.
Like it was the powerful and elite people of Hollywood trying to sacrifice virgins and
drink their blood and all this stuff.
Fascinating because when you look at the Tom Hanks conspiracy theories, a lot of people
bring up the Burbs.
A lot of people kind of say that maybe he was trying to warn us or maybe that was predictive
programming.
No one brings up Dragonet.
And I spent 30 years since I watched Dragonet, but I remember I watched it a lot as a kid.
I thought it was super fascinating.
Now I wonder if there is a connection between people who were fans of the Burbs and the
one person who apparently saw Dragonet me and people who do or went on to be conspiracy
theorists because there is a really interesting Venn diagram between people who believe that
Tom Hanks is an Adrenaline Chrome addicted freak today and who also enjoyed the movie
the Burbs.
But all of this information, quote unquote information, is coming from us from one of
my favorite websites.
Real raw news.
It is a website that's right.
I can't even describe it as like a journalism website or a news website because neither
of those words really fit it.
It would be closer compared to like Wattpad, like a straight up fictional website.
But people believe it.
People totally believe that what this guy's saying, most of the articles are written by
an author named Michael Baxter if that's his real name.
But he's been going on and on about body doubles and Nancy Pelosi.
You can pull her head off like it's, don't try, don't try this.
Don't actually go to Washington DC and go, oh dead rabbit radio.
I can do this and start yanking on Nancy Pelosi's hair.
But apparently if you see Nancy Pelosi, there's like a 50/50 chance that she's actually a
Scooby-Doo villain and it's a body double and a mask.
And Joe Biden is either hologram or he's a body double who was in the movie Curse of
the Komodo.
We've covered all of this stuff.
We've covered all of this stuff because I find it so fascinating.
But now on June 12th, 2021, the chickens have come home to roost in the story of Tom Hanks
because a lot of people do believe he's highly tied into this Adrenaline Chrome smuggling,
pedophile horrible stuff.
He was arrested by the 173rd Airborne Combat.
Let me back up.
According to Real Raw News, according to this website, I don't want people to be like,
"Whoa, Jason said it."
According to Real Raw News, all of this.
He's sitting in his private jet with his longtime friend.
This is what I don't understand.
You can eat.
Tons of people are saying that Tom Hanks is an Adrenaline Chrome addict and a pedophile.
And those are both horrible accusations to make.
But whatever.
Like, that's horrible and people make those accusations.
This is what I don't understand about Real Raw News.
Because they add details that are so superfluous to the article itself that I think they're
joking at this point.
I clearly think they're pulling everyone's leg and the audience doesn't realize that.
So Tom Hanks is arrested at his private jet.
He's also hanging out with his buddy Peter Scalarri from Buzzing Buddies, which is interesting.
Peter Scalarri, for you Scalarri heads out there.
You're like, "Oh my God, is he tied up in this Illuminati Plateau?"
No, it's weird.
Michael Baxter reports that even though Peter Scalarri is a longtime friend, half of you
are Scalarri heads, the other half of you is, "Who the hell is Peter Scalarri?"
Why are you kidding me?
So back in the 1980s, there was a show, this is the height of sitcoms, right?
Like high concept sitcoms.
There was a show, I loved it, as a kid called Buzzing Buddies.
It was about Tom Hanks and Peter Scalarri.
Future Adrena Chromatic Tom Hanks and his longtime friend Peter Scalarri.
They were dudes whose house was demolished on accident or on purpose, I don't remember.
And they had to then live at the woman's dorms on college so they dressed up like women
and pretended they were women on this whole sitcom.
They ran for like two or three seasons.
And they're constantly spying on their sexy roommates.
Buzzing Buddies, best theme song for a television show ever as well.
Second best.
The gummy bears theme song is really good too.
You should have taken a couple more days off, you're clearly not up to this job again.
What I can't figure out is that Michael Baxter goes through the detail of adding this saying
that Peter Scalarri was on the plane.
Most people do not know who Peter Scalarri is.
I'm sure even Peter Scalarri's listening to this podcast, he's like, "Huh?
Who's this guy?
Who's this guy he's talking about?"
And then if you do know who Peter Scalarri is, for the rest of the article you're singing
the theme song to Buzzing Buddies, because it's super catchy.
He says that Peter Scalarri's on the plane and then you go, "Oh no, Peter Scalarri must
be wrapped up in this Illuminati Plateau."
No, the 173rd Airborne Combat Brigade lets Peter Scalarri go.
Which doesn't make any sense because if he...
How...
Let me ask you this, dude.
Let's say you have a buddy.
Let's say you have a buddy you used to dress up as the opposite sex with and you used to
peep on women.
Or don't do that.
Let's not imagine that.
But imagine your best friend.
You're hanging out with your best friend for past 30 years.
And that friend also injected the adrenaline.
That friend who you're like, "Hey buddy, what's up?
What are you doing this week?"
And you hang out with them.
What are the chances that that guy, without your knowledge, without you knowing it all,
also injected the adrenaline of dead children into the base of his neck?
How long do you think your best friend could get away with that?
And you not know.
Because we apparently know this is being talked about all over the internet.
But even forgetting that, like, if my...
Every so often I saw my friend, he had a big black eye and he seemed a little hyper than
normal, I'd start to suspect he must be injecting the adrenaline of dead children into the back
of his neck.
I don't think you could get away with it that long.
So anyways, long time Tom Hanks friend, Peter Scolari, is free.
So if you are a Scolari, don't worry about him.
But Tom Hanks was arrested and was taken to like a military tribunal.
You know, he never served in the military.
Saving Private Ryan was not a documentary.
For some reason, he's brought before like a...
Three generals have to review the footage against him.
Like all the evidence against him.
But apparently, there are hundreds of videos of Tom Hanks engaged in heinous acts against
children.
Also according to Real Raw News, the judges watched snippets of four of the clips and
said, you know what, that's it.
You're guilty.
We just watched four snippets.
And that made me think.
Is that how trials work?
Can you present a bunch of evidence?
And then someone just watch a little bit of it and go, I'm good.
Because you think...
You think I'm someone who came to you with 500 videos of Tom Hanks engaged in horrible
acts?
Like would you be like, I've watched the first 470, but these last 30 may change my
doesn't mind.
They may change my decision.
Would you just be able to watch snippets?
Because you wouldn't want to watch all of it, right?
And then I started thinking, if you're in a jury for like horrible stuff against kids,
they don't make you watch that stuff, right?
I'm assuming they don't.
I don't know.
Like, I can't imagine they would subject a jury to that.
And they would ask the jury, are you comfortable with watching this material beforehand?
And anyone who said yes, well, they're just going to get arrested anyways.
So maybe they wouldn't have to watch all 500 videos.
I'm not saying that they should, but anyways, apparently there's 500 videos of Tom Hanks
doing this stuff.
And again, the weird details that they add is always so fascinating to me.
Not only are there a bunch of videos of Tom Hanks supposedly doing horrible stuff to kids,
we have this quote from Real Raw News.
"One video showed Hanks and Songstress."
That's a word.
That's a word now.
Did you not know that?
She's not a singer.
She's a Songstress.
"One video showed Hanks and Songstress, Lady Gaga, injecting each other with the Drina
Chrome, injecting each other while an unseen child screams," echoed in the background.
"That video doesn't exist.
That video does not exist at all."
So why would Michael Baxter make that up?
I don't, that's what's always so fascinating to me.
Like, why does he add that creepy element into it?
Did he, does he think that video exists?
Did someone tell him this video?
That's always a weird thing.
Someone's feeding this information, but imagine, like why is he imagining that and putting
it in?
Who knows?
But anyways, according to him, that exists.
And oh, I'm sorry, I misspoke.
I said there were 500 videos.
I'm looking further down on my notes.
That's incorrect.
There's 50 videos.
Big difference.
But I also left this part out.
There's not 500 videos.
There's 50 videos and 2000 photographs.
So I think actually I kind of met him in the middle somewhere, but that was all the evidence
that the military tribunal needed.
They watched a couple clips.
They're like, "Gros, you know Lady Gaga?
Guilty, guilty of all charges."
And so he has been executed, death by lethal injection.
Quite ironic for a man who's most famous, not for saving Private Ryan, not for getting
big or forced gump in it.
No, he's the man who will always be known as the Adrenochrome addict.
Tom Hanks.
It's so funny because the reason why, I'm not going to go really into this.
I've touched on it in different episodes.
You know why Tom Hanks is tied into this?
Two people.
Two people really started the whole Tom Hanks thing.
There was a woman on Twitter named Sarah Ashcraft who said her father, when she was 12, sold
her as a mind-controlled slave to Tom Hanks.
That was one of the big accusations.
There was a random account on Twitter that's been shut down now.
A woman named Sarah Ashcraft says she was mind-controlled monarch slave type of thing,
sold to Tom Hanks.
And then Isaac Cappy, a actor who's done bit parts his entire life.
And then he started making accusations that he knew about the Illuminati pedophile control
of Hollywood.
And then he killed himself.
The conspiracy theorists say that he was, uh, suicided.
That he was actually killed.
And he publicly accused Tom Hanks of pedophilia.
And this is such a weird thing.
Tom Hanks has a hobby of taking photographs of lost items.
And a month before, I, this isn't weird because of the coincidence.
It's just weird that Tom Hanks has this bizarre hobby.
A month before Isaac Cappy died, Tom Hanks took a photo of a glove on historic Route 66
and titled it Roadkill.
And then a month later on Route 66 actually was Interstate 40 where he killed himself
or was suicided.
Isaac Cappy jumped or was forced off of a bridge and then got hit by a car.
It was about 2,300 miles of Route 66.
So, but people have said that the origin, the story behind the photograph has changed.
Some people say the photograph now was taken days before Isaac died.
Some people say it was at the same location.
That's it.
That's how Tom Hanks got wrapped up in all this stuff.
And people, it's now part of pure Illuminati, Adrenochrome conspiracy theory that Tom
Hanks is browning.
Imagine if two people made allegations against you.
Two people.
And for the rest of time you're tied into that.
That's really what this is.
I find the whole Tom Hanks getting wrapped up in this conspiracy theory so fascinating
because it's really two people and it's tragic that Isaac Cappy died.
It is tragic that Isaac Cappy died.
But yeah, even Isaac Cappy's origin story, he does, there are pedophiles in Hollywood.
See that's what always clouds this thing.
There are pedophiles in Hollywood and they are powerful and they do protect each other.
That's real.
But it's when you get into the Satan worshipping and they eat the babies and drink the blood
and the Adrenochrome and stuff like that is when you actually stop looking at the real
pedophiles and you start looking for the imaginary ones.
And you start to think who's the one who's actually propping up these conspiracy theories.
Because if more and more people are looking at Tom Hanks and trying to figure out if he's
really in prison, are you looking at the actual pedophiles in Hollywood?
And you're not.
You're absolutely not.
So it's all very fascinating.
Isaac Cappy, what happened was this is really his Illuminati awakening origin story.
He was hanging out with Seth Green and he was being shown a tour of Seth Green's house
and Seth Green pointed to this door in his house and he goes, "That's where we keep the
children."
And he goes, "Edgy joke."
And Isaac Cappy took that joke seriously and thought that there are actually children
behind that door and that really kind of started his Illuminati, trying to expose the Illuminati.
And again, I go back to the thing.
Think about an edgy joke you've made in your past or maybe you were going to make later
this afternoon and someone hearing that and taking that joke as truth and then spreading
that throughout the internet and then that person killing themselves.
And you for the rest of the time will be accused of being part of this conspiracy theory.
You made this racist joke or the sexist joke or just this out of place edgy joke and now
you're tied into this conspiracy theory.
It's fascinating stuff how these conspiracy theories develop.
And then I was watching a music video Isaac Cappy did because Isaac Cappy was a struggling
actor.
He was trying to make it in the industry.
He made a music video with this guy from Bander Plump Rules.
And in the music video, Isaac Cappy uses a device to mentally control women and have
sex with them.
In the music video that Isaac Cappy himself decided to make uses monarch mind control and
Illuminati symbology.
It's fascinating.
It's fascinating stuff.
See, that's, I'll put that video on the show notes, but that's been completely, oh no,
he's one of the good guys.
He's trying to expose the Illuminati.
I remember, and the reason I want to say this too, the reason why I love covering real
raw news is this episode is going to go long.
It's first episode of the season.
One of the reasons why I love covering real raw news is you have to remember I used to
believe in this stuff way more than I do now.
Nowadays, believe in aliens, ghosts, demons, stuff like that.
But I used to, and some conspiracy theories, but I used to really, really believe in conspiracy
theories.
I was 100% a 9/11 truth or I was 100% believe.
I want to say 100%.
I was like 90, 80% that the powerful people in Hollywood and in the world had to make
sacrifices and have to be part of the secret society and all of these things.
I believe that stuff.
I'm sorry, I had to take a break there.
Someone started power washing, power washing their house right next door.
Three weeks.
I don't record an episode.
Everything's fine.
And then I start recording someone starts power washing.
But what I was saying, and I'll wrap it up like this, I never believed in conspiracy,
I always believed in conspiracy theories and things like that to varying degrees.
But the idea of a powerful cabal controlling Hollywood and you have to be on the inside
to really make it and that they gave, they Illuminati gave you commands and they had to
put certain things in your video.
He had to do certain rituals.
I believed that and I never believed it more than when I was a struggling musician.
Because you're working your butt off trying to make it.
And you start to think, why is this dude making it?
Why is this super attractive guy with tons of talent and connections?
How come he's famous and not me?
This little shrub from Orangevale, California.
You start to think, how come I'm obviously better than this dude?
What is this old Michael Bolton?
I'm like, what?
I'm totally a better singer than him.
You start to think, how come I'm not good?
I never believed in Illuminati conspiracy theory more than I was a struggling musician.
Like nowadays, I believe that there are people trying to rule the world.
I believe there are multiple groups, not just one.
I believe there are multiple groups trying to rule localities, cities, the world.
If they're super rich and they really want to try it, but I don't think it's any one
group in particular.
I think it's a lot of other groups fighting for control.
But the idea of this one group controlling everything and you have to be an Illuminati
mind control slave or you had to like bow down to the Dark Lord.
Michael Bolton, you had to sit there and you had to be like, please, please let me be famous.
I believe that I never believed that more than when I was a struggling musician.
Nowadays, I believe that, you know, there are groups like that out there, but I don't think
it's the end all be all to success.
And I think that's what Isaac Cappy, you'll see reviews and info wars.
Alex Jones said he's a pretty big actor.
People refer to him as a Marvel actor because he was he was the pet shop owner in the first
Thor.
He and I'm not knocking extras.
I'm not knocking people who are working the industry.
But he was by no means a successful actor, more successful actor than I am.
But you know what I mean?
And I think they try to build it up.
And I think his origin story was he's struggling actor.
Seth Green made that joke about that's where we keep the kids.
He starts thinking what it maybe that's why Seth Green to be fair.
I don't know why Seth Green is famous.
I've been watching him my entire life growing up.
I'm sure he's a really nice guy.
But I don't mean to throw shade at Seth Green.
I'm sorry if I lost some green ads.
I'm paid transport or some sure he's a great guy.
But I've always been like huh what?
So anyways, maybe Isaac Cappy thought that because he's like really this guy's famous.
Struggling actor and he starts to think and and because he is an actor in any way shape
or form and when he starts saying the Illuminati controls Hollywood and Tom Hanks as a pedophile
and Seth Green has kids in his basement.
People outside the industry who all read I think the Illuminati controlling Hollywood
I think that attracts a lot of struggling artists.
I think that does attract a lot of people who are writers and musicians and filmmakers
and they are really trying to be creative and their professional and their private life
and they can't be.
And I think they start to go maybe it's because the Illuminati.
Mark Marin one of the most famous comedians now.
He was a struggling stand-up comedian for decades.
And I was listening to his podcast, BETF podcast years ago and he said there was a time period
and when he believed the Illuminati existed because he was struggling in Hollywood for
so long and he thought started thinking maybe they do exist.
But you know now that he's interviewing President Obama now that he has like what the number
one maybe in the top five podcasts in the world he doesn't believe in anymore because
he's not a member of the Illuminati but when he was struggling no matter what he did he
couldn't make it.
I think that that's where this Illuminati controlling Hollywood conspiracy theory really
flourishes and I think that's what happened with Isaac Cappy and because he was in Hollywood
if he was just a plumber making these YouTube videos people would people he would just be
one of many people who were making these comments.
If he was a plumber at a Hollywood producer's household the presence would go up then he
could go aw you won't believe it this producer one day he took a big dump and I went to go
fix his pipe and I saw Tom Hanks injecting Adrena Crome and you'd be like what well maybe
because he has more access than I do and at the end of the day it's still a man just
saying things.
And the guy who played Butzer Pie from Clown Camp Massacre does he really have did Isaac
Cappy in roles like that he was in Breaking Bad as Rowdy Prisoner did he really have access
to these Illuminati secrets because then you figure everyone would what about the other
ten clowns from Clown Camp Massacre.
He was in the cast of Lemonade Mouth as Mel like you start to think like if someone at
this low level knows all these secrets and does everybody because I have friends in
who in the Hollywood machine and they haven't said anything but again maybe they are Illuminati
agents I think the story of Isaac Cappy is tragic because he passed away but I think
it's it's made him more famous than he would have ever been and I'm not saying that him
passing away made him more famous but the saga of because he was getting famous while
he was alive the saga of he's exposing the pedophiles and the Illuminati control of Hollywood
has made him more famous than he would have ever been if he'd continue to work his entire
life in the industry.
And Tom Hanks for a huge segment of the conspiracy theory society there's a minister named Pastor
Greg Locke who's becoming more and more famous he's doing all these sermons against wearing
masks and don't get vaccinated and stuff like that and he's kind of starting to become a
viral no pun intended a viral video minister if he's really taken off there's a video
of him I'll see if I have a copy of it I don't know actually where I got it I got it off
like YouTube or something like that but I'm trying to think of anyways there's a video
of his private video of that Greg Locke's sermons no no he's doing this thing and he's
doing the sermon and he starts going off about Tom Hanks and Oprah Winfrey and I'm
thinking if you went to his church just thinking oh you know what I wonder what Jesus is up
to today I haven't heard from him in about 2000 years I wonder what Jesus is doing you
go to church and then he starts screaming about Tom Hanks you'd be like what and the
audience's congregation is like yeah yeah boo Tom Hanks you're like what did he do he's
not he's just in the okay fine saving private Ryan wasn't that good of a movie but I don't
think he should be listed up there with that horrible war criminal Oprah why it would totally
boggle your mind why someone was going off about Tom Hanks in church but if you know
the code if you know the story Tom Hanks is a pedophile but to 98% of the world they're
like what fascinating story and again I used to believe I didn't believe this conspiracy
theory specifically because I was out of it by the time this was growing up but I believed
in all of these conspiracy theories that Hollywood was taken over by the Illuminati St. worshiping
groups and you know and I that's what I love about real raw news it's not far from what
I used to believe these totally insane conspiracy theories to me it's like looking at a fun
house mirror and you got to remember where you came from it's okay to mock people but
sometimes you got to admit that that those people used to be you let's go ahead and move
on to our last story for the day and this one is a little more personal myself as a
horrible conspiracy theories back in the day man I was cool back then I was one of the
cool conspiracy theories don't think I was some big old dork but yeah no I totally believe
in all this stuff. Morphous gas let's go ahead and toss you the key we got to dust this bad
boy off because we have not used this in a while let's toss you the keys to the carpenter
copter we are leaving behind Milan Italy Peter Scalari's like can I get it right home we're
like no you might be complicit in the crimes against children we're flying away. Morphous
gas take us in this carpenter copter we're leaving behind Milan Italy we are headed out
to Sacramento California Sacramento California my hometown anyone trying to hack my passwords
and they ask what city were you born in Sacramento California my hometown the place I visit every
show often that's where I've been after the past three weeks lounging taking a vacation
from the show taking a vacation from work just chillin playing video games which is something
I don't get to do anymore because I'm so busy watching movies hanging out with my mom a
lot of fun but I almost died I almost died we talked about this briefly on the July 18th
Alien Abduction Special I'll put that on the show notes you guys should listen to it I
had a lot of fun during that a lot of fun with them but right before that happened so
I recorded that on Sunday July 18th I was horribly sick for the week previous to that
from Sunday the 11th pretty much right when my vacation started I got a really bad air
infection really really bad sore throat it got to the point where I went four days without
eating and over the course of those four days I had maybe a liter and a half of water spread
out over those four days it was bad it was super super painful it was the most ear pain
I've ever had in my life I get ear aches I get sore throat all the time hands down the
worst but finally I was able to survive this is not a ghost this is not a clone doing this
podcast I was able to survive and I was able to get better through the help of my mom my
mom taking me to the doctor my mom is not a doctor herself but you know got mama's love
keeping me going and then she then when that ran out she's like oh you know more refills
on this you got all the love possible then she took me to a minute seven clinic and I
ended up getting antibiotics and prenatal zone for the pain and everything cleared up
but the reason why I'm talking about this on a paranormal conspiracy and true crime
podcast it's not a conspiracy that I got horribly sick I had a spiritual awakening in my sickness
it felt like a vision quest and it's such an interesting thing so I have tangled with
ghosts and witches and demons and shadow people but having this vision having this hallucination
I ever want to put it in it's interesting because I it happened multiple times over
the course of a few days and it put into perspective when people talk about shifting to other realities
and people talking about going to different planes of existence stuff we cover on this
show because what would have a nutshell my pain was so intense and not only could I not
drink or eat my body didn't want me to my body had basically given up like I was still
hopeful I was still like maybe we maybe we can be this I was actually still doing my
normal vacation stuff I was still playing some Far Cry 5 I was watching movies with
my mom that's what we do when we go down there I'm watching slacks about killer pants I'm
watching carousel about a killer killer carousel horse floating around poking people with its
unicorn horn virus shark big freaking rat slash or ret party all great movies still doing
the normal thing but my body was breaking down my body had given up as much as my mind
was wanted to hold on my body's like we're just not even going to get hungry we're not
going to get thirsty and I had to force myself to drink she can only go three days really
without water before you die and so I was forcing myself to drink that water my body
wasn't thirsty but I was forcing myself to and every time I took a swallow it felt like
someone was taking a toothpick and sticking it in my ear and pushing as hard as they could
for 45 seconds I timed it and you don't know how many times you swallow throughout the
day until you feel every time you swallow because you're constantly swallowing just a little
bit of saliva and as some sort of horrible side effect to this whole thing I was drooling
and sessently I was just drooling making me swallow even more so but that's all just gross
disgusting stuff we talked about that stuff on Dead Rabbit Radio too but what would happen
was periodically I would just be sitting there playing Far Cry 5 or hopefully just doing
that sometimes I'd be walking through my mom's house sometimes I'd be in the shower and bam
I'm in the void I'm in the void it's this endless dark expanse oddly enough wasn't
pitch black how you would picture an endless void because I'm sure we often do it reminded
me more of the black that you see on black construction paper had a bit of a grain to
it but it was endless with no ceiling no floor no walls it went on forever the only reason
you had any orientation in the void was there were other people in the void with me let me
back up here too before I go into that the void was not some other place the void was
inside of me the void was inside my upper body I'm in this place endless darkness inside
this place are two Mexican people standing there as well as a man and a woman they're
both wearing like peasant clothing like 1800s clothing you would see if you're watching
like the three amigos or reading history book doesn't have to be from a movie it's just
very traditional like peasant garb in Mexico so standing there and I'm looking at these
two Mexican dudes and realize that I'm in my own body and I read that what's so weird about
this whole thing is that it didn't feel weird at all when we've reported on stories about
people going into voids or standing in these UFOs that are more than just a UFO metallic
but like an endless expanse of like red lights showing from nowhere I always say dude one
of that be so weird one of the be so weird to be there but the fact is when you are in
some sort of hallucinatory state it doesn't feel weird at all I wasn't like whoa where's
the ground bro the walls they go on forever it's just like okay it's like standing in
the middle of Macy's like it's just a location but I'm in this endless void that's inside
me there's two little Mexican people standing there they're completely silent they look
really stern they look like they don't want to be there I mean it doesn't want to be in
the endless expanse and in between this man and this woman there's a donkey head an oversized
donkey head the donkey head was about as big as they were it was just from the neck up
and the donkey wasn't making any noises it was just sitting there and they had a rope
around its neck and I would shift in and out of this and I really wouldn't even go like
whoa dude it just hallucinated I think I knew it was some sort of fever dream or some sort
of side effect to the dehydration or the pain or both but I kept going back to this place
and this is what it's again fascinating I can't say they spoke to me telepathically
or a sign appeared or anything these are just things that my brain constructed the two people
inside of me were completely benign they neither wanted to be there nor didn't want
to be there they were neither invaders or inhabitants they were simply there the donkey
however was an interloper what I came to realize in my adult state is that the donkey symbolized
a piece of mucus that was stuck in my esophagus a bacterium factory post nasal drip dripping
down into my throat had formed a piece of mucus in the shape of a donkey's head and
was stuck inside of me and the message was very clear remove the donkey head from your
body and your illness will leave my mom loves me I'm probably her favorite I'm not going
to be after she gets her water bill because I took some of the longest showers there that
hot water just hitting my back and breathing in that steam I could feel everything loosening
up and what would be weird is as I would continue to go in and out of this state of semi consciousness
however you want to put it the void the void was always eternal in all directions but remember
because it's oriented because I can see where the people are standing there's a floor you
can't see it but there's obviously a floor there as time goes on the floor moves up
because the mucus is moving up through my esophagus this is happening over a matter of
really a day and a half this these visions and I remember feeling that the mucus was
moving up through my esophagus my quest to get this out of my body to expel this out
of my body was working and the image of the two Mexican people and their donkey that they
have in captivity is moving further up my body expel the donkey and you'll be fine I
don't know if the little tiny people told me this I don't know if the donkey introduced
himself I don't know if it was just a joke my brain was playing on me but at one point
I came to learn that this donkey was known as Lucas this mainly happened so I got sick
on Sunday got really bad on Monday and got worse on Tuesday this is really happening
Tuesday night Wednesday all day most of Thursday when my mom gets off work Thursday she can
tell I'm about to die she can tell that I have been a brave little boy of an mommy strong
little soldier but she can tell that I'm obviously as much as an act I wasn't trying to let on
how sick I was she could tell I was way sicker than she thought because I was really just
being like oh no it's no big deal let's keep watching capsized blood in the water movie
about people going through extreme pain as sharks are circling them and I'm watching
and it's like oh man it'd be so nice to have water splice on my body I'd be drinking up
all that saltwater she takes me to the med 7 they go you have an air infection you have
a raw red throat gaming antibiotics I ended up getting prednisone which is a steroid which
really really helped the anti inflammation and then by Sunday I did a what an hour and
a half long July 18th alien invasion special which was really like up until that morning
I did not know if it was gonna happen and I did get to share a story that I had forgotten
about for 20 years about the drill the drill squad at my old high school confronting me
and telling me what an awful person I was it was such a fun memory to rehash and I'm
glad I'm glad I was able to share with you guys but the story is so interesting and
and it's the it's interesting on a couple different levels one it made me think about
when we cover stuff that's unusual when we cover stuff that's unusual that I've been
through when we talk about demons and ghosts and things like that I do kind of have an
attitude like yeah no I understand what they're going through but now I think I understand
stuff like the void like what it's like to be in a place that is endless it's like being
it's like being in a macy's it's simply a location and it's scary when you step back
and think about it but when you're in it it's as real as any location to it started to make
me think about this idea which I don't really talk about on this show but I find very fascinating
and it's pretty well known that's what I'm talking about but this genetic lineage this
idea that all humans are connected in the sense I am from I'm Basque my family came
from Spain about a hundred years ago I have family members who are from Mexico extended
family members I have friends from Mexico but I have no genetic link to anyone in Mexico
so it's so fascinating to me that in my darkest hour when I'm in this horrible place of pain
because I like I said my brain was still hopeful but my body was just shutting down it just
didn't care about eating or drinking that my spirit is being protected my body is being
guarded by two little Hispanic people in peasant clothes from like the 1800s so interesting
right it's no one of my genetic code that's super interesting and I'm wondering why that
it why that was the image that my body projected I understand why I had the image of the donkey
is because I think there was a giant piece of phlegm in me that was in that weird shape
of like a donkey head and my body could only describe it and my body was basically sending
signals mean you need to get this out or you will die my body your body doesn't know that
medicine exists your body works at a basic eight level by day four of this your body's
like listen there's something in your body you need to get it out you are only going
to get sicker as long as it is in because I did have to take antibiotics I had an infection
there was a bacterial invader in my body but why the little Mexican people I mean I don't
have anything against them I just am curious as to why that was the image my body created
or my mind created or my soul created but then let's put out a conspiracy caps and wrap
this episode up wrap up this extra long episode I think I haven't edited it yet but you can
obviously say where are they now most likely were figments of my imagination or maybe they
were spirit guardians maybe I'll run into them again somewhere once again in the dark
void they're like Jason you take better care of yourself they're holding like a whole
zoo back and they're like guy we can't keep doing this I say I think about this from time
to time I think the gut is such an integral part of a human body or really any living
things body but we dismiss it all the time we'll say stuff like oh I have a gut feeling
but for the most part we think that the soul resides in the brain we forget about how powerful
the gut is I remember a long time ago I read this article and they were talking about head
transplants and I don't know if I can find it for the show notes but the guy and I might
have mentioned this before on the podcast but this guy goes if you ever truly transported
a head you'd be sent and seen someone to the worst insanity they ever suffered because
there everything doesn't reside in the head if you transplanted ahead it the gut biome
is so radically different it would be like they're living in a different universe so
our guts are everything our whole biology is so important to who we are but with our
conspiracy caps firmly on let's take it down this path we hear a lot about simulation theory
they go statistically statistically the chances of this reality being the real reality is
infatessimally small that there is most likely throughout creation there is a society that
is created computers advanced enough to run super advanced simulations and once that happens
and you have a population of say seven billion people on that planet and half of them are
playing this game the chances of us being the real reality and not one of these four
point five billion simulations that are constantly being run is super small so most likely we're
in the simulation and we're not the real reality what if we're in the gut of somebody here man
you've already shut off the podcast you're like I'll turn back in season 16 let's see
hopefully he's less insane how do we know that we're not little microbes living inside
some other creature's stomach that we're just amoebas and we're in a pitch black darkness
sitting next to a puddle of acid waiting for him to eat some Cheetos so then I can land
on one of the Cheetos and eat up just a little enough of a resource so I can last another
day I'm gut flora your gut flora and we have created this entire existence around us we
are really born into darkness it's constantly hot and bubbly and we're just this goo living
inside of this organism we've never truly seen the sun or heard music or felt the touch
of a friend's hand on our back in time of need no we're just an organism in some creature's
gut and this is all an imagination all of reality is something we have crafted to deal
with the fact that if we knew what reality was we wouldn't want to eat that Cheeto we
would rather just die off but the biological imperative doesn't allow us to die off it
makes us march forward it makes us live longer to eat just that other piece of scrap to live
a little bit longer and everything is just an illusion that is actually statistically
far more likely than any simulation theory because if you say there's a society that
has 4.5 billion simulations running at any given time the chances of us being the real
world versus one of the civilizations there are countless living creatures on earth alone
99% of those have guts and have digestive enzymes and little bacteriums and little flora
in their guts just on earth there are more living things with gut biomes than there are
of even the highest level of simulations running in theory and in each gut flora there's tons
of different little the chances of us actually being something inside a fox's stomach is
far more likely than you being a simulation and it's 10 times as scarier it's probably
more than 10 times scarier at least if you're in a simulation you figure maybe you're entertaining
as someone if you're in a simulation at least you were special enough to be coded into it
if you're in a simulation at least there's a sci-fi future for someone out there if not
for you but what if we're just flora what if we're just bacteria living in a sperm whale
stomach and eventually despite whatever we do whether we are the greatest author whether
we are a lowly hobo whether we are Tom Hanks or Isaac Cappy that's sperm whale will die
and its body will sink to the bottom of the ocean and we will just cease to exist with
it even in the big bang you can figure eventually the universe sure expands expands expands
and then it begins to contract but after a certain amount of time there's another big
bang reality is back but what if none of that is real not even the sperm whale is real we
imagine what sperm whale is but we're just something in eternal darkness in something's
gut our only mission is to help it digest food and everything else has been made up
to make it more comfortable for us to accept the fact that we are eternally locked in
darkness our only mission is to help some unknown creature we don't even know exists
eat is far more likely than simulation theory it's far more likely than reality according
to simulation theorist we may be nothing more than a digestive engine and everything we
dream everything we hope everything we create everything we are is an illusion we're just
a chunk of bacteria inside another creature and one day that creature may die one day that
creature may begin trying to expel us and realizes that it no longer needs us someday
that creature may take medicine that rapidly kills us off it's a beautiful world out there
we think full of hope and promise maybe and someday we may realize in our final moments
that all of reality was an illusion everything we knew everything we loved was nothing when
it is finally time for us to pass from this life we see what is truly real some people
fear death because they are afraid it is just eternal darkness but then you realize we were
always in eternal darkness we just didn't know it you're not chasing is this depressing
is this how you're starting off season 15 darn tootin dead rabbit radio gmail.com is
going to be your email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
tiktok is at dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day I'm glad you listen to it
today have a great one guys hope you guys are back for tomorrow you're like now I'm not
going to be come back you love it have a great day guys
(upbeat music)