When police are investigating a horrifying crime, they instead uncover a sickening conspiracy?
Then we travel to Arizona to meet a pair of rock collectors who travel out into the wilderness
looking for the shiniest of rocks.
Instead they come face to face with a mind-bending experiment that will end their lives today
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
We are having a short week this week, only three episodes because I just got back from
the McMinnemins UFO Fest in McMinville, Oregon.
I'm telling you guys, it was a blast.
We're gonna do it again next year.
We brought out our haunted museum.
We stood out there, we were handing out stickers designed by Adam Carter.
We just had a blast.
It really was so fun.
So we're going to get next year and some of you guys came out to visit me.
That was really awesome.
You know, I was hoping.
I was hoping.
And you did not let me down.
So you guys are going to be the pilots this week.
First off, everyone give a round of applause for today's captain, today's pilot.
We're going to give it up for Joel from Arizona.
Woohoo, Joel's walking in.
Yeah, giving him high fives and stuff while we're clapping.
We have quantum hands.
We can do everything at once.
And I got to say this, Joel, I forgot to, he had his girlfriend there, maybe his wife.
I forgot to write her name down, but she's there too.
She's equally important.
But Joel, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't meet me in real life, that's fine too.
Just helps rid the word about this show.
That really, really helps out a lot.
Now Joel, we're going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy we're leaving
behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed all the way out to Mill Plain, Washington.
It's October 30th, 2021.
The day before the spookiest day of the year.
Halloween.
In case you're bad at math or don't have a calendar.
It's the day before Halloween and kids are already picking out their costumes.
I'm going to Spabiota, says one kid.
Well, I'm going as Snuflufagus, says another kid who's apparently as big as a mammoth.
But while they're deciding whether or not to be Freddy Krueger or Jason Voorhees or
Paw Patrol, Pet Man, whatever those dogs are called.
While everyone's trying to pick their costumes, nobody realizes there's a real monster in
town.
He has a costume.
This monster has a costume.
It's an Arby's uniform.
This man works at Arby's restaurants.
Long time listeners of the podcast know Arby's are the grossest fast food restaurant out
there.
They really are.
Like just even, I feel like I'm some sort of like having these PTSD flashbacks when
I mention Arby's.
I can taste that sauce.
I can taste it.
I can still taste that tangy sauce rolling down the back of my throat.
I haven't had Arby's in 20 years.
But if you gave me a taste test of sauces, I'll totally do that taste test by the way.
If you'd like to meet me and have different sauces for me to taste, yummy.
But when I go to the Arby's one, I dig my blindfold off and go "You sir are no friend
of mine.
I'm taking the rest of these sauces and leaving."
Arby's is disgusting.
Arby's is a disgusting fast food restaurant.
And I hate to say things like I told you so, but this story proves that this story that
happened to this one Arby's proves that they're all disgusting.
From October 30th, 2021, there's a manager at a Arby's in Mill Plain, Washington named
Stephen S. Sharp.
He's a 29 year old dude.
And while he's watching all these people getting ready for Halloween, he walks through Walmart
and the costumes are quickly disappearing from the shelves and he's like, "You know what?
All of these trick or treaters are constantly saying they want trick or treat.
Well what if I gave them a trick in their treat?"
He's all talking.
He's talking out loud at the Walmart.
People are like, "Stay away from that guy.
He's obviously a lunatic and gonna do something grotesque."
Stephen Sharp's plan is this.
I don't know if he actually came up with this idea the night before Halloween.
Oh the trickiest treat ever!
Back at the Arby's restaurant, he was the only one there, there was a bag of milkshake
mix.
I guess it's like some sort of powder that they put in there.
It's this milkshake mix and he opened this bag up and he urinated in it.
I don't know what he even urines like.
He urinates in this bag of milkshake mix.
This is actually, you'll see a lot of headlines for this.
Some of you guys may have read this, but this is just the tip of the story.
That is just the tip.
This is out and about in the news cycle.
You'll see headlines like "Fired Arby's Manager Admitted to Urinating" at least twice in
a milkshake mix.
It would have gone into the machine and the police looked at the receipts between October
30th and October 31st.
There was one root beer float sold and 30 to 40 milkshakes.
Now that's the headline.
That's the headline you'll see, but when you read the articles, it's far more disturbing.
So you see the headline.
You see these headlines and the big question you have is how did they figure this out?
Did he get ratted out by someone?
Did someone go, "Oh, I've had an Arby's milkshake a day since the end of World War II."
I know what they taste like.
This one tasted like human urine.
No.
The way that they uncovered this is incredibly disturbing.
This is insane.
What happened was the local police got a tip that someone in Mill Plain was trading and
collecting child pornography, child sexual abuse images.
And they figured out who it was.
It was this guy named Steven Sharp.
Yeah, the local Arby's.
So when they arrest him, they get his phone and they start going through it and of course
they find what they're looking for, a bunch of child porn.
And then they came across a video of him urinating in a bag.
And these are vitriol police officers taking all sorts of horrible stuff, right?
But this one, they're like, "What in the world is this?
Like, what?
This is so weird.
It's surrounded by all of this disgusting child porn.
Here's a video of a guy peeing in a bag."
So they asked him, "Hey, what's this video of you peeing in the bag?"
So that's how they found this guy.
He was being charged with child pornography.
And I didn't know this.
I didn't know this.
So he was being charged with possession child pornography, which right there.
He's looking at like 20 years per image or whatever it is, 5 years per image and he has
a bunch of it.
Whatever.
Doesn't matter.
He deserves the jail time.
When peeing in the bag is food tampering, that's against the law, luckily.
Otherwise people would be peeing in food all the time.
But I didn't know this.
During the interview when the police were like, "Why did you pee in the bag?"
He says, "Oh, because it got me off."
Like I got sexual enjoyment from peeing into this powder.
So now he's not just charged with food tampering.
It's another sex crime charge.
If you do something sexy, and it's not saying, I'm saying that this is sexy, but if you do
something for sexual reasons, that's different.
So if you were robbing a bank, everyone get down.
Give me all your money.
And you have like a big old boner that's too charged.
You're going to get charged with robbing the bank and you're going to get charged with
having sexual gratification during it or something like that, which would be super awkward.
Like if you robbed a bank and there's like a really hot bank teller there and you're like,
"Oh, don't look at her.
Don't look at her.
Don't ma'am.
Go into the back room and don't hit the silent alarm.
I can't look at you.
I don't want to get a second charge."
As the security guard is choking on his own blood and I want to get charged with a sex
crime.
Yeah, that's it.
He got a new charge.
Now here's the thing.
I guarantee this was not his first rodeo.
Guarantee it.
I mean, he got caught with the videos of him peeing in the bag.
But remember, this guy was a manager here.
He worked his way up.
I'm sure he did this a ton of times and never videotaped it.
I don't know much about, by the way, perverts think, but I don't know.
It would have pervert just go, "Hmm, I'm bored.
I'm going to pee in a bag of wine."
Obviously this guy did, right?
But what I'm saying is he probably did it a bunch of times and then he goes, "You know
what?
I have such fond memories of peeing in that milkshake mix.
I'm going to videotape it this time so I can enjoy it at home.
Like I bet you he's done this a lot."
And now that he knows he'll get a separate sex crime charge for every time he did something,
then he's just not going to say anything.
There could be hundreds.
There could be thousands of milkshakes out there.
One day he takes a trip to corporate office.
They're like, "Steven, really like the cut of your jib.
Why don't you come down to corporate office and see what it's all about?"
And he's like walking through the milkshake mix room where they're making the powder.
He's like, "Ha ha ha."
So it could be like the end of cabin fever where that water truck was driving down the
road and the water was full of fleshy new bacteria.
That could be, there could be semi-trucks of Arby's milkshake powder mix driving through
your city right now.
Insane, right?
It's one of those stories.
You see the headlines and it sounds gross and then you dig into the story and it's even
worse.
A child pornographer peed in people's milkshakes.
There's a lot of people I wouldn't want to pee in my milkshakes.
I don't want to pee in any of my milkshakes.
I had to pick between milkshakes and like this one, a serial killer peed in this one,
a bank robber peed in this one, and a child pornographer peed in this one.
I know which one I'm not choosing.
Gross.
Like that's even worse and the fact that he got off on it.
Imagine him just being at work that day and seeing people come up and they're like, "One
milkshake.
You know what?
It's Halloween.
I'll have three milkshakes."
And he's like, "Oh yeah.
I don't want to pee in the counter.
Okay, I'm done.
I'm done with that segment.
I'm done.
Joel from Arizona, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Carbindercopter.
You and your lovely lady friend can take us up and out of this Arby's.
We're leaving it behind, although Steven Sharp may be a recurring character.
Let's leave behind Washington.
We're headed all the way out to the Arizona desert.
The year is 1938.
We're in this unnamed Arizona town.
It's near a train station.
There's this train headed towards town and on this train is a young man named Steve Brody.
Now, Steve Brody's coming out to the area because he loves collecting rocks.
It's a passion of his.
He just walks around and goes, "Whoa.
I've never seen a rock like that before."
And he picks it up, looks at it, and puts it in his pocket.
Maybe a backpack doesn't say exactly what he used to collect them, but somehow he collected
these rocks and he had a buddy of his.
He doesn't give a name for his buddy.
There's some interesting details to the story we'll get to in the end, but he doesn't give
a name to his buddy.
We'll call him Jake.
So Steven and Jake are on this train, headed to this unnamed Arizona town.
And when they get out, they begin to quickly figure out their plans.
Where they're going to go collect these rocks, where they're going to stay, stuff like that.
They probably should have figured out before they got there.
They find out there's no hotels or no rocks.
It's underwater.
So they get out there and they start talking, "Oh, you know what?
I saw a really cool place as we were coming into town on that train.
There's that bluff over yonder," Steven says.
I think we should go over there and Jake agrees.
Jake goes, "Yeah, let's go out to that bluff.
I'm sure there's tons of rocks down there.
I mean, what is a bluff already?
But a giant rock."
The townspeople get word of these two strangers in their territory.
And they don't care, right?
It's a normal town.
They're a bunch of wrong-term mutants.
But they do warn the young men, "Hey, yeah, we overheard you guys wanted to go to the
bluff.
Don't go to the bluff."
A lot of people have gone missing out.
They're even locals.
Even people who know the area, they've gone out to the bluff.
They've never come back.
But Steve and Jake kind of just figure there are local superstitions, right?
There's what could possibly go wrong out in the middle.
What could possibly go wrong in the middle of the Arizona desert?
So they go out there against the wishes of the townspeople.
They go out there and they're out at the base of the bluff.
And they're not there for that long.
Really.
They're just got there.
They're kind of looking around.
When out of the shadows surrounding the base of the bluff, a man steps out wearing a solid
black cloak and a black hood.
This man stepped out of the shadows totally cloaked.
Stephen could not describe what this guy's face looked like.
But it's not really what he was worried about.
The face just cared if he was handsome or not.
The dude stepped out of nowhere.
He stepped out of some sort of void.
And then another cloaked figure stepped out of another nearby shadow.
And at this point, Steve and Jake are like, "Dude, we gotta get out of here."
So they start to run and they get maybe a couple feet when all of a sudden one of the
men in the cloaks seem to be holding some sort of weapon and a beam.
The beam about as wide as a pencil shot out of this and struck Jake in the back.
Eugh.
And when that beam struck Jake, Stephen said that his friend fell over and laid on the
ground completely motionless.
The air was thick with the smell of scorched skin.
Stephen sees his friend laying motionless on the ground and he stops.
Either he stopped because he didn't want to leave his buddy behind or he knew there was
no way he could outrun these guys over this vast expanse of desert.
He comes to a stop and these two cloaked figures walk up to him and they put something
on his head.
He said it was basically just like this device that had these two metal discs that fitted
over his temples.
And once that device is securely around his head, he passes out.
The next thing he knows he's regaining consciousness and he's somewhere in the dark.
He passes out again and when he comes to he's still in that same dark place but he realizes
he must be underground somewhere.
Blacks out again.
He comes to, he realizes he's not just in a hole underground, he's in a cell.
He can actually see bars.
Passes out again.
What happens is he's constantly coming to for brief periods of time and each time he's
able to take in a little bit more information.
He realizes after multiple times of regaining consciousness and passing back out, he's somewhere
underground either in a dungeon, like a literal medieval dungeon or a cave system.
There's bars separating him from a chamber area, a place that he could leave this cell.
He's not alone.
There's other humans in this cell and they are all in this catatonic state.
They seem completely brainwashed and he starts to think, "Is that what I'm like when I'm
unconscious?"
Because he keeps getting knocked out and what he realizes is that every time he regains
consciousness one of these cloaked figures walks up and jolts him with some sort of device
and he passes back out.
So whenever he's able to start to become aware, it's cut short.
He keeps waking up though and he sees these humans just standing there.
He's put back under.
He can't even formulate a rescue plan.
He has no idea what's going on.
Eventually he is awake at the same time someone else is awake.
A young girl.
And she tells him we're being held captive.
These men in the cloaks they're known as the Dero.
That's all the information she has as well.
And she also was able to piece that together from multiple awakenings and then getting
knocked out and awakenings and getting knocked out.
Until one day he regains consciousness and he's standing in the outdoors.
"Tingle, tingle, tingle, tingle, tingle.
Get your French fries here.
French fries."
And he's like, "Oh, I'm so hungry."
And someone says, "French fries?"
He wakes up.
He's actually standing in New York City.
He's standing in Times Square watching these old cars drive by, you know the world famous
New York French ride vendors.
Best French fries in the world.
He's standing in New York City.
He has no idea how he got here.
The last thing he really knew was he was outside of that bluff in Arizona.
And he begins walking through the street kind of unsteady.
He doesn't know where to go or what to do and he catches a reflection of himself.
He has a beard, which he never had before, and long hair.
So he knows there's been a passage of time, definite passage of time he has no memory
of.
He goes to a newspaper stand and he looks at the date on the newspaper.
Two years have passed since he was standing in that Arizona desert.
Steve made his way back to Arizona.
Apparently that's where he lived.
This is really interesting because we have a lot of information and not a lot of information
at the same time.
Apparently he didn't live in that region of Arizona where he went rock hunting, but he
did live in Arizona.
He makes his way back to the town he was originally from.
He never saw his friend again.
He never saw his friend in the cell.
He never mentions his friend again.
After this he goes back to the town that he came from and he kept his mouth shut.
Apparently he didn't have any family.
No one was really looking for him.
He didn't tell anyone the story until somebody, a friend of his, was visiting him a couple
years later.
Was visiting him and this friend had a copy of the Amazing Stories magazine with him.
Like sticking out of his back pocket, which was a fictional science fiction magazine.
And on this issue they talked about inner earth.
And they talked about this idea that there's an advance civilization underneath the surface
of the planet.
And when Steven saw that issue he started going "Dero, Dero!"
And he freaked out.
His friend was like "Dude, whoa, what is going on?"
He was able to calm Steven down and Steven was like "I've never told anyone this, but
I'm going to tell you this story right now.
I've told the story that I just told you."
And this story apparently was first recounted in a book in 1967 that was published in 1967
called The Shaver Mystery in Inner Earth.
It was specifically talking about a researcher named Richard Shaver, who I believe we've
talked about on this show before, Richard Shaver, who believed in the inner earth philosophy.
So he didn't come out and voluntarily tell this story.
He saw a magazine cover and freaked him out and he told his friend this story.
And as proof that he could show, because he wouldn't have a lot of right, he wouldn't
be like "Look at my beard!
They're not giving me a proper beard at any time."
Apparently this friend had this conversation with him back in the 40s and it was in 1967
when it was published.
So he couldn't be like "Look at my beard!
Look at my long hair!
Anyone can grow out in the time."
He did have two silver dollar sized scars behind his ears.
And he says "This is where they attached the device to me."
Because the first one was attached to his temples.
This one was behind his ears.
This must have been a device they attached to him during his imprisonment.
But he had that.
He had those scars.
He had those burn marks.
But he never told his friend what town it took place in.
He never told his new friend the name of his old friend.
He goes "I just don't want to even talk about it, but I'm telling you the story right now."
And he said "Don't ever tell anyone this story.
I'm telling you.
I'm never recording it on a podcast."
He told his friend "Please don't tell anyone this story.
Everyone will think I'm a lunatic."
But it happened.
It totally happened.
The reason why the friend felt comfortable telling this story was because eventually Steve
went missing himself.
Steven was last seen riding on a train in Arizona.
And another man who knew Steve saw him and was like "Hey Steve, what's up?"
And Steve didn't respond.
He was just staring out the train window.
The train was chugging down the tracks.
This guy knew Steve and he thought that seemed out of character.
He seemed drunk.
He seemed like he'd be in some sort of stupor.
He was just staring out the window and I even put my hand on his shoulder and was like "Hey
Steve, are you okay?"
He still wouldn't respond.
Still was staring out the window.
This man said the train came to a stop and I got off to use the restroom and when I came
back Steve was gone.
And I figured he must have got on off on that stop.
But I was a little worried for him, right?
You know I'd never seen him like that before.
But I just never saw him again after that.
I didn't get back on the train and I did and the train took off.
I imagine he went somewhere.
But the hypothesis that you'll see pop up in a lot of these stories is he was under their
mind control again.
He got free and he said he goes "I don't know if I escaped or what.
I don't know how I got out."
I was just in New York City all of a sudden.
Did they call him back home?
Did they finally reconnect the mental control over him and he was in that stupor like he
had seen all those other people just standing there like mindless zombies?
They finally get him again and control him to get on the train, to head out there and
to walk out into the Arizona wasteland to rejoin them underground.
It's an interesting story but I want to wrap the episode up like this.
What I thought was really interesting about being kidnapped and being taken prisoner
by inner earth creatures with laser guns is the fact that they dropped him off in New
York City and as I was reading this I thought what if that's why there's a bunch of crazy
homeless people in major cities?
If you had to drop off somebody who is going to weave a tail no one will believe you would
drop him off in a major city.
If you had a town of a thousand people and some dude just showed up in the middle of
town and he's like "they took me, they took me, they took me away, they got all these
other prisoners, help me, what day is it, what day is it, Tuesday, what year?"
They're like 1940s sir.
That would make the news right.
Lunatic bearded lunatic shakes may or asks date.
That would make the news right and people with local police would come out and they
throw him in the drunk tank and he's like "I'm not drunk, I'm telling you, they're underneath
our feet, they're under the ground."
And then you know what I mean?
It would be more noticeable.
I'm not saying they would believe him, I'm not saying they would believe him, I'm not
saying they're like "he's our new mayor, we're my crazy bearded guy, the new leader of our
town."
I'm not saying they would believe him but it would stand out more.
If you took him back to that Arizona town and that guy came wandering and he's like
"you're right, don't go out to the bluff, my buddy got totally blown up, I think, I never
saw him again and they got all these people trapped underground."
Then obviously instead of the town people just going "maybe you might not want to go
out there" they'd be telling people "definitely don't go out there, there's people trapped
underground, maybe they'd go and try to rescue them."
I think that's aliens biggest fear is humans finding out about them.
100%.
I think they're terrified of that.
I think they're absolutely terrified of that.
We would beat them into a pulp.
So that would be their worst fear.
But if you took a guy, a blathering idiot or not, and dropped him off in a small town,
people are more likely at least going to hear him.
Maybe not believe him but they'll hear him.
But if you dropped him off in the middle of New York City, no one would believe him.
You'd be like "they're underground, they're underground and they're kidnapping people."
And right next to you there's a guy screaming "they're in my skin, they're kidnapping my
white blood cells."
There's so many crazy bearded homeless people in these big cities that it would just get
lost in the mess.
It would get lost in the chaos.
So it actually makes sense that they would drop him off here.
I wonder how many of those screaming homeless people you see as you're driving down the
road are telling the truth.
Not that their car broke down and they just need some gas money to get to the next city.
Not that.
I'm talking about the crazy people screaming at the top of their lungs.
Maybe they were just dropped off there by aliens.
They were dropped off there by aliens.
After the aliens use you for two years they're like "here you go sir, we're going to teleport
you in front of a Chevron gas station with this cardboard sign that says help I need
gas."
Who knows, right?
The story is already bizarre enough without adding on our homeless people actually ailing
abduction victims.
Which will probably be the name of this episode.
But you would have to think that some of them might be.
Some of them might be.
So the next time you see a guy screaming in the top of his lungs outside of a 7-Eleven
you should stop and listen to him.
You should go "hmmm" you should sit there and listen to him prattle on.
Because it's possible, it's possible that he's telling the truth.
It's possible that as he's talking about lizard men underground and young people being taken
against their wills maybe he is privy to the dark secrets of the Dero.
It would be the perfect place to hide your mind control victims.
Hide them among the drug users and the mentally disabled.
Hide them among those who are already invisible and ignored by society.
Because when these people come forward the truth tellers come forward and they're screaming
at the top of their lungs till their voice goes hoarse spittle flying out of their mouth,
hair, crazy, long scruffy beard as they're screaming the truth.
You'll never hear it because it is drowned out by the lies of a million madmen.
[Music]
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]