You're riding in your car with your family and you see a massive UFO in the distance
But you're the only one who sees it and no one believes you but will they believe you when a gray
breaks into your house and
Then we take a trip around the world to discover a disturbing connection between
unwanted children and
Killer ghosts today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*Music*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day, too
My day was actually quite rough and they did something I don't normally do
It was such a rough day and my back has been killing me that I took a shot of vodka
Probably about 15 minutes ago
Well, it was actually more than shot and it was inside of a diet coke. So let's go ahead and start it with the episode
I don't know how this is gonna turn out. I don't think I've ever I've done the show with hangovers before
And I might have once done it with a buzz
So we'll see how this works because right now I'm buzzing pretty hard when you're on keto
Alcohol actually hits you a lot harder because your pancreas is functioning differently. Let's go ahead and get started here now
This first story I mentioned briefly yesterday
But we're gonna go ahead and really delve into it today. The year is
1994 the place is
Lapierre, Michigan. I always think it's so funny when people go my hometown's in an episode. It's funny how many
Weird stories have happened in people's towns around the world and they're just completely unaware of it
But I can guarantee at least one listener either lives in La Pierre or knows of La Pierre
I didn't know about it. So I'm not one of those listeners, but someone's gonna go well golly. That's where I live
I'm not seeing everyone from La Pierre is Tom Sawyer because I don't know anything about the town
It may be completely urban city. It may be a suburb of affluent people
I don't know or it could be full of a bunch of Tom Sawyer clones. I don't know golly
They have a huge their biggest import is single stalks of wheat so they can put between their teeth
They walk around but anyways in La Pierre, Michigan in 1994 this kid tells this story
Well, he's an adult when he's telling the story, but this happened to him when he was a kid
I know that's confusing but that's just the way I phrased it an adult
Back up here. This episode is already going off the rails an adult tells a story about what happened to him in
1994 when he was younger and that's important because the way people interact with adults and the way people interact with kids is completely different
For for many reasons one kids are generally stupid and two kids are prone to making stuff up
But as an adult he tells the story his mom was driving him and a friend back from bowling
Which now that I see my nose the fact that the best thing they could do on a Saturday night was bowling really makes me think
I'm on point with the wheat stalk imports
But anyways, so mom was driving this boy this unnamed boy will call him Tom
We'll just call him Tom because it fits he's right. She's driving because he doesn't say his name
She's driving Tom and his friend Huck back from bowling right and they had another guy who they hung out with the bowling alley
But I'm not gonna say his name so anyways
Otherwise this will get banned from YouTube so Tom and Huck and we'll just call him Jim
We're all hanging out at the bowling alley and so Tom and Huck are like bye and the mom's like who's that?
Who's your nice friend again?
And they're like we don't say his name in public even in 1994
But anyways the mom's like let's that's odd so they all hop in their car
They hop in the mom's car. They're driving down the road and he's looking out the window and there's a big empty field
And he sees in the it's like dark. It's late at night. They're coming over from the bowling alley
He's looking out the window as you're driving by this big field
He sees a massive
Actually what he sees is he sees all these lights and his first instinct
He says I thought a football game was being played out in the field like I thought it was a stadium game
It was that light out but as I continued to look at it
I realized that it wasn't a football game. It was a giant triangle with lights on it
So he's seeing this triangle out there now. He starts pointing it out. He's flipping out
He's like mom. Huck look he's pointing out the window at this massive triangle and they don't respond to him
The mom is just staring straight ahead driving and Huck in the back seat is not making any motions
Not looking not making any any reference to this massive UFO that's out in this field and then the vehicle just
Darts away super fast which again is typical of UFOs. It just you know and after it leaves
He's this is what happened. He's like mom Huck look look out the window. Come on guys
Look look and they're not responding and then it flies away
And he's like look look you got a look and at that point both the mom and Huck look out the window and see nothing at all
Almost like mid-sentence as he's imploring them to see what he's seen after it zips away
Then they're unfrozen and they see nothing and they start making fun of them
They're like ah Tom always with the tall tails and he's like no no no no. I'm not making this up
I actually saw this massive UFO
Triangle flying out in the field, but since they didn't see it
They basically made fun of him until he got home
He said that he saw it two more times now
I'm a little iffy on that detail because it just says he said he saw it two more times
I don't know if he saw it two more times on the right home, which if that's the case then the info is just kind of
Being a dick. It's like flying around keeps freezing his friends
He's but or it could be that he saw it two more times before this last event
But again, he says I saw it two more times when nobody else saw it
So I still imagine this UFO is a dick like he's at high school. He's doing his homework
He looks out the window UFOs stand in the front yard. He's like guys look look the whole classroom is frozen
He's at prom everyone's taking prom photos his day gets replaced with the giant triangle
He's like guys look look no one pays attention to him at that point
UFOs just kind of being a jerk because it keeps appearing in front of them and
Freezing everyone no one else can see it
So either this UFO has is totally trolling this kid or this kid has some sort of brain damage
He hallucinates triangles, but the story wraps up like this
So Tom goes over a while later. It doesn't tell us how long but Tom goes over to Hux House to have a sleepover
He's over at Hux House. He's having a sleepover and they're sleeping in Hux basement in the middle of the night
He wakes up something
Just startles him and he comes out of a deep sleep
He sees
The stairs leading into the basement so he wakes up and he's able to have a clear view in the dark of the stairs that lead
Down to the dark basement now. I'm assuming they're not in a dark super spooky Freddy Krueger basement
But technically all basements are super spooky Freddy Krueger basements
He's sitting there in the dark and he's looking at the stairway and he starts to hear something walking down the stairs
Not the most healthy thing not the most healthy thing, but he hears it walking down the stairs
He looks up and he sees peering between
The banister so you know how you have a staircase and you have like the banister and then you have like the rungs in
The middle you guys have seen staircases before
But in between the slats of the staircase he see he hears something walking on the stairs and he's looking
He can't really figure it out
Then you see something holding on to two slats and with his face pressed between
Banister thing, you know, I'm trying to build a visual, but I don't know the terminology
You've been to stairs before you've seen stairs in your life
Imagine being a kid looking in the darkness and seeing someone peeking through the staircase
There's a great alien just staring at him
little three-foot tall creature
Looking at him in the darkness and then Tom is looking at this thing and he says I see you
Which is an interesting thing that he said because he has had so many encounters with these vehicles
And he's constantly telling people he sees it and nobody believes him
But now he's face-to-face with this creature from another world and he says it plain as day
He's finally stating it. I see you and in that moment the alien
Vanishes doesn't run up the stairs doesn't run down the stairs doesn't hide in the washing machine just blinks out of existence
Now that's where Tom's story ends
But I don't necessarily know if that's true
Because Tom saw the UFO and it zipped away and no one believed him
The UFO was able to appear in plain sight when to his prom took his virginity and was able to
Deceive everyone that there was no UFO there and when he looked at that alien that gray and said I see you and it vanished
Did the alien go back to its mother ship or did the alien finally figure out?
Which human kept noticing it?
Moved out of his field of vision moved out of his ability to see and still followed that boy around
cloaked
hidden out of sight
But always right behind him
Let's go ahead and move on to that was creepy enough little gray alien like as you're listening into this podcast
You're driving in your car. She'll gray alien behind you
Just looking and you turn around
He's not there
Or even better if you're listening to this podcast in bed God help you if you do I know a couple people do I wouldn't even listen to
This podcast in bed you're listening to the podcast in bed
It's you're laying on your stomach so your back is to everything in the room and while you're listening to it
You feel those large black emotionless eyes on you actually maybe more than one gray alien
He's watching you right now
Sorry sorry guys, sorry guys blame that one on the vodka shot claim that one on the vodka shot
Well, I just lost 50 subscribers because of that description people like I'm gonna listen to your podcast anymore
Now you're intentionally scaring me jerk
So let's go ahead and move on to our next story. Now if you thought that story had a grim ending
You have no idea what's coming up none and I will say this this particular segment is quite
insensitive so
I'll see you guys. I'll see a good chunk of you tomorrow once I start talking about this feel free to just skip ahead
Whatever move on till tomorrow because this episode this gets a little dark here. We're gonna travel around the world
We're gonna look at some interesting
Cryptid spirits ghosts what whatever you want to call it first off. We're gonna start off. You know what?
Because we're traveling all over the world. We haven't done that in a while and because this is actually if this is an episode 250
I think it's like 249. It's close enough guys
It's back in action. Let's hop on board the carpenter copter get on
Take your bags get all your stuff and you might want to carry a back brace and some knee braces
But go yeah, put them on strap them on hop on the new improved carpenter copter because we are going to use this
Brilliantly designs device. It's actually just a helicopter. It's not space-age material or anything
But I might be over hyping it get on the copter. Just come on get on the copter
I'm not gonna sell it anymore carpenter copter is back in action. We have it repaired
We're ready to go. I actually meant to bring it back a couple episodes, but I forgot I was gonna do I did some UFO episode
And I was gonna have that carpenter copter to show up totally forgot it was in my notes, but it's here now
It's here for the story of ghost babies now ghost babies is a
Quote-unquote legitimate phenomenon and you'll understand what I mean in a second, but if you have a problem with
If you have a problem with infants like being left in the way everyone has a problem with infants being left in the wood
but if you have a problem with stories about
Babies being left in the wood and again everyone has problem with trying to figure out the best way to put a disclaimer on this if you
Don't like stories of infants in peril
I'll see you tomorrow, but know that the carpenter copter is here
So when we mentioned in a later episode you're like where'd that come from it must have been the episode
I skipped the ghost baby episode
How about the carpenter copter we are taking a trip to Scandinavia is that a place is that Scandinavia is a
Like a language right? I know it's a folklorist system. Is that just the Nordic countries anyways you get in the carpenter copter, dude
We're going to Scandinavia. We're just flying around until we see a country called Scandinavia
You're like dude. We're gonna be flying around for an awful long time. I'm like shut up. Just get inside
You're like dude, didn't you just say you drink vodka? I'm all fine
Okay, anyways
Carpenter copters are gonna probably crash this episode too, but we're going to Scandinavia and in Scandinavia we land
We eventually find it might actually be a real country and that bit didn't work at all
but we land and
We meet these villagers and they're like a
Why they're rostafarians we meet these villagers and they're like hello good travelers
Welcome to our fictional country or it may be true
I am norvish. Hey norvish. How you doing? He's like yeah, yeah enough of the introduction
So norvish tells us this story. So norvish says you guys can do whatever you want, but don't go for hikes alone
like why not he goes because
of the myling
The myling is what you got to look out for. I'm like, what's a myling norvish is like. I'm glad you asked
I'm glad you take a seat by this fire
Because I smoked this alien marijuana
And tell you the story of the myling now the myling is also known as a
ut bird and an
ut bird ut bird
so
Myling comes from an old Swedish word that means murder
So you're like we're off to a good start some sort of murder ghost
But ut this word starts to get dark ut bird means that which is taken outside
So you would call garbage ut bird. I don't know if I'm pronouncing that right, but I like saying it
But it means specifically the ghost imagine having a ghost
Nothing to think about it ut bird means something to take outside i.e. garbage
But this ghost is also called an ut bird. Imagine if you were a ghost and your name is just garbage
Trash you have like a phantasm. You have a poltergeist
You have a specter and then you just have trash trash ghost
That'd be the worst way to die even a garbage man would be like this sucks
I don't know why I don't know why I assumed garbage. I'm in love trash
I'm I think the alcohol is kicking in more now anyways ut bird means thing
That which is taken outside and so the story is this in Scandinavia. They have these folk lorish legends that unbaptized children who die
And that can include all sorts of stuff more specifically children who are left in the elements to die
It's been done all over the world. You have a baby that you don't want
You don't need or has some sort of deformity
You would basically take it out into the middle of nowhere or actually just take it at three feet from your house
And leave it there and eventually it would die of cold it would die of heat
It would die of wolves
Barret eat it a bunch of crows would carry it away. Whatever now oddly enough. It wasn't 100 fatal
Sometimes people would find it sometimes animals would raise it like mogulie
So it can have a happy ending but for the most part the babies just died
So dark episode here dark episode. So these spirits are
Dead dead babies
There are the spirits of babies who specifically have been left in the woods or left anywhere outside
Or inside just neglecting babies is what i'm trying to say or unbaptized babies who die
Now the legend goes like this these creatures in the scandinavian regions they will haunt the area where they died
So there are huge problem for hikers and travelers and stuff like that because if someone took their kid and left it in the woods
And then bounced and then a couple days later it dies or a couple hours later it died. Oh my god. So so dark
And then a couple months later you are hiking down the woods going man
What a beautiful day look at those squirrels are hanging out and they're playing chess and look at birds are singing and making cinderella's dress
That rhymes and then there's like a dead baby 10 feet away from the trail
You're not going to know about it. So these things can haunt areas. They're not spooky like graveyard hauntings or
abandoned castles or mental asylums and stuff like that. They're just like landmines sitting in the middle of fields
So you're walking down the trail late at night and you hear the sound of a crying baby
And you're like that's where to middle of nowhere. There's no babies around you check your pockets
You don't have any babies. You didn't bring any babies with you. Where's that sound coming from?
At that point the myling jumps on your back and demands to be taken to a cemetery
It needs to go to hallowed ground to be buried to be at peace
So you're like, whoa chill baby chill chill. Yeah, dude. I'll totally take you to a cemetery. No big deal
It sucks your parents left you out here. I will take you to a cemetery now in a rational world
That's how it would work the mylings the ute birds don't work like that
They jump on your back and they demand you take them to a cemetery and almost as kind of the ultimate dick move
They don't let you take them there. That's where they want to go
But what happens is the closer you get to the cemetery you closer you get to hallowed ground like a church yard or whatever
It gets heavier and heavier and heavier to the point where you imagine, okay
It will get so heavy you will begin to sink into the earth. That's impossible
If a steamroller rolls you over you don't sink into the earth
Like you just flatten but anyways, so you're walking and you're like, yeah, dude. I'll take you to the cemetery
No problem. It's just hot. Oh, he hops on your back. He's like, yeah, I guess that's a good way
I was gonna put you in my pocket, but we're all my other babies ago
Anyways, you're walking to the cemetery, but the closer you get the heavier he gets to the point that very rarely do they get to the cemetery
Most of the time travelers will collapse and die before they get there or they'll be smushed into the earth
But sometimes they do get to the place where they're going the myling hops off their back. The dude's like, oh, thank god, man
Oh my back and the myling is now
Fine it is now fan hallowed ground and can be a piece
Also, if you can't make to the cemetery and you don't get crushed they just rip your throat out
So the creatures are quite vicious. Even though they are the victims of a horrible crime
They they stop you from getting to where they order you to go
And if you don't get crushed or sink into the earth, they just rip your throat out
So that's the story of the mylings or the ut birds different names for different regions
But the same type of creature
But let's go ahead and hop back into the carpenter copter
And let's go to germany and you're like jason are we just going to germany?
So you can tell me another depressing story about abandoned kids
Kind of pop in the helicopter. Just get it. Just get it
We're going to germany and that is where we meet the the wider ganger and in german that means one who walks again
So it is either a reference to a zombie or just a lazy person who's always on the couch and they're like, oh
Look at the wider garden as you get up off the couch to go get some more cheetos
And then you go back to the couch
But anyways in general it is a reference to a zombie one who walks again a dead person who's come back to life
And within the wider garner there is a specific subset of it known as the off-hacker
What's an off-hacker you ask? Well, good question. Good question
An off-hacker will literally the name off-hacker means
leap upon
Because it jumps on people's backs
You're like, oh, that's kind of weird. We have Scandinavian myths when this is a german creature
So fairly close
Maybe some cultural contamination both creatures jump on your back, but let's keep going here
The off-hacker is a shape shifter that can shape shift into a werewolf
Or anything else
And when I read that I thought why would you want to shape shift into anything other than a werewolf?
The werewolf might be the most badass cryptid on the planet. A werewolf could take on 10 bigfoots. No problem
I really don't think outside of a god level cryptid like the Groot Slaying which we covered in like episode 53 or something like that
I think the werewolf might actually be the most vicious of all cryptids
So this thing can become a werewolf a houseplant a telephone
Norvish a carboner copter, but why would you become anything other than a badass werewolf?
I don't know but this is the off-hackers
MO this is what they do late at night when a lone traveler is walking through the woods
This creature will jump on your back as the name says off-hacker and
Demand you take it to hallowed ground
That's kind of weird
Now the regions are fairly close
But this creature will jump on your back and demand to be taken to hallowed ground
But as you get closer to the hallowed ground
He gets heavier and heavier
and heavier
And if you didn't get crushed by the weight it would rip your throat out
Now the fact that we have two similar
Demons cryptids spirits however you want to describe them
Within a northern europe is basically where both of these myths come from you could say
People from germany went to scandinavia and people from the scandinavian countries went to germany
cultural contamination
maybe
Most likely yes, you're right
The first one had to do with little babies. This one is just some sort of creature that likes to jump on people's backs
It's not connected to infants
So there's enough of a difference between those two
Maybe it's just an idea of people playing telephone with folklore and the myth grows
So are you trying to say because there was a similar myth in germany and a similar myth in the scandinavian countries that
There's some reason to think that there really is some sort of spirit that haves some people's backs
And they get heavy and heavy and heavier until they crushed until they're crushed
And if they're not crushed to death they get their throat stripped off and they both want to go to hallowed ground
Are you trying to tell me there that this thing might be real because you've made a connection between these two?
Let's go to japan
In japan, there is a creature known as the konaki gigi
which literally means
old man crying
So you can talk all you want about cultural contamination and folklore between germany and scandinavia
because there is going to be a
Source of that but when you're looking at folklore, we're looking at old old stuff and yes
You had germany working with norway. You had german not working. They didn't have a business together
But the germans and the norwegians and the swedish people and all that stuff. They knew each other from way way back
They were bros
Back from when they were just a bunch of barbarians running around. I'm sure that there was cultural contamination
But when we look at similar time periods in japan
This is what they tell us a konaki gigi is
It's a shape shifter
But this one actually can only shift between two forms. No one of them is not a werewolf
It can either become an old man who sounds like a baby when he cries
Which is its natural form. Actually. It's an old man who sounds like a baby when he cries
Or it can just be a baby. It can be try to choose between an old man who sounds like a baby or a baby and
To even make it even more weird sometimes the old man has a baby face
And sometimes the baby has an old man face and i'll leave it up to you to decide
Which one is creepier if you're walking down a city street and you turn down an alley, what would be creepier
seeing a
one-year-old baby with the face of an old man like benjamin button or
An old man looking at you, but his face is perfectly smooth and round and he looks like
John candy he looks like a baby john candy, but the rest of his body is like a 90 pound old
Like weak frail man. I'll give you
You guys can decide which one's creepier. I know half of my audience is like who the hell's john candy
It's a dated reference. I know I know who's a new fat actor
Um who looks young. Uh, what if you turn around the corner and you saw
Chris I would say chris farley, but you always look like he was on a bunch of drugs
He never looked like a baby
Who would you turn around and i'm spinning way too much time on this
But you turn around a corner and you see an old 90 pound man
with the face of
Melissa mccarthy, how's that melissa mccarthy? Sorry melissa. You've lost a lot of weight
I've congratulated you on your weight loss, but melissa mccarthy
From that terrible television show she was on that face on
Old man that took way too long to describe anyways, so
It's a shape shifter
He become two things an old man who sounds like a baby or a baby and you're like jason just get to the
Just tell me the tell me the creepy boy. Okay. Okay. Anyways, this is his mo in japan
They have this legend
You walk in your lone traveler walking through the woods. You hear the sound of a baby crying
You go and you pick up the baby and if you don't the baby just hops on your back
You don't have a choice
The baby then turns into an old man
And this one just crushes you immediately
He doesn't say take me to find peace. He doesn't go take me to be buried
He just crushes you the second he's on your back. The weight of him is so heavy
You get crushed into the earth
There's different versions of how a konaki gg is created
But one of the versions is if a baby is left in the wilderness to die
It becomes this
vengeful spirit
I find it interesting that across the world and you could say the first two are northern europe
But I find it and i'm sure there's more variations of it. They're all fairly specific
Let's look at the similarities between these things. They attack lone travelers
They use deception to get a hold of you. They either shape shift. Well, they almost always shape shift into something that you don't expect
They jump on your back and they all crush you now
You can say like there's not even that many similarities
There's more similarities between these three creatures and ghosts in general
Some ghosts float through walls. Some ghosts wear clothes
Some ghosts you see some ghosts you don't like there's not a lot of similarities between ghosts overall
That's why they've had to categorize them like poltergeists or phantasms or specters like I was mentioning earlier
but you have these different legends of creatures around the world of
something that
disguises itself as something jumps on your back crushes you
Two of the versions they tell you to take them to hallowed ground
Two other versions both basically state their babies left in the woods
And those are the two farthest apart the Scandinavian one we can take the germany one and we could say well
You're close enough to scan an avial will lump those together, but the northern european one and the japanese one
Still have enough similarities to make one think that at some point this phenomenon was real
That at some point in human history there was some sort of vengeful spirit that would
Jump out of the woods jump on your back and kill you and may have been related to an abandoned baby
Now the skeptic of me says what's happening is people are finding lone travelers just flat on the ground and they were having heart attacks
And they made up this story
But even if that's true, I find it weird that the story they made up in northern europe is the same story they made up in japan
But all that being said
The truth of the matter is when we see similarities between these stories across the world
It does give it a hint of something real
And what's even more frightening generally?
Infants around the world are considered the most precious thing
They are so innocent and untouched by the evils of the world and you have what makes these stories scary
Is you have the families that are responsible for leaving these kids out on the wilderness?
Unpunished
It is the lone traveler walking through the woods
that basically
Triggers this
vengeful spirit
It's not a creature that goes after and slowly takes down everyone who was mean to it. It gets you
Who had nothing to do with it who doesn't even know it's there?
It gets you and kills you
For the simple mistake of walking by where it died
It may or may not be real
And to be honest it most likely isn't but that doesn't mean that when you're out hiking by yourself
You shouldn't
be
aware
Of what may be in the bushes just beyond the field of view
Because we live in a wicked world
And where you walk every single day the roads you take the alleys you stroll down the woods you hike into find peace
You don't really know what happened there before
Because the world
Can be very very cruel
So when you think you're alone in the woods
And you think someone's watching you
Just walk a little bit faster
Because what is watching you?
May be something that has long been forgotten
In the mists of folklore
You may be able to avoid being found in the middle of the trail the coroner's report
suffered a heart attack very young for their age to have died like this
Couldn't breathe
fell down
They're dead
when in reality
you made the
simple mistake
Of walking past somebody else's sin
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadratheradio
Twitter is @deadratheradio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]
[MUSIC]