Which one would you choose? To see a ghost or to not see a ghost but know that it
sees you? And then we traveled to Coffee County, Tennessee to take a look at the
story of a local weirdo. Everyone in town knew this guy was nuts but they had no
idea how deeply his dark desires went until the police arrested him for
cannibalism. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host
Jason Carpenter or I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna go ahead and get started right away.
First off let's give a shout out to one of our Christmas livestream
contributors. Christmas, I know what's happened six months ago. I got a big list
I'm trying to get through all of this but there's no rush because all these
people are awesome right now walking into Dead Rabbit Command is Creole
Cosmopolitan. Yeah come on give you a big round of applause as you're walking in.
Sweating, still this heatwave going on. Sorry we'll kick off the AC in Dead
Rabbit Command. If you guys can't support the Patreon I totally understand. Just
help spread the word about the show. That really really helps out a lot. Creole
Cosmopolitan. Let's go ahead and toss you the bunny bicycle. I like this new
thing. It's very eco-friendly. It's a good workout. Creole Cosmopolitan.
Let's give you the bunny bicycle and we're gonna sit on the handlebars. We're
gonna sit on the handlebars. We'll sit in the little basket. Got a baseball card
stuck in the spokes. Pedal us all the way out to Tempe, Arizona in this heatwave.
Pedaling us on out. I need to come up with a better sound effect. It's always just
the sound of someone panting. Tempe, Arizona. We're going back in time. We're
in the early 1900s and back then on 24th West Fifth Street and Mill Avenue was
the Mountain Bell Phone Company. This building still exists today. You don't
have to have a time machine to enjoy this story. 24th West Fifth Street and Mill
Avenue was the Mountain Bell Phone Company. It was a two-story building and
phone company, right? So back then like phones were just invented. It would be
like working at Google nowadays. You're like, "Whoa dude this is so awesome. This
is brand new technology." You're plugging stuff in and listening in on people's
phone calls like you're the operator from He-Ha and I'm sure it was more
professional than the He-Ha lady. But the reason why we're at this building is
because the story goes this is how this legend starts. Do we know this young
woman's name or any of the details? No. But back in the 1900s when it was Mountain
Bell Phone Company a young woman reportedly killed herself. She took her
life on the second floor of this building near one of the restrooms. Now
fast forward, fast forward over time it stops being the Mountain Bell Phone
Company. The building changes hands and it becomes a retail shop called Trail. Now
when it's this retail store called Trail, now we're in the modern days. We're no
longer in like sepia-toned cowboy hats and He-Ha operators. People have cell
phones and people drive cars and stuff like that. We're in modern times. There's
a retail store called Trail and they only use the first story of the building.
They had no use for the second floor but you know you're not gonna just be like
"I'll never go up there guys, knock it down." People reported hearing someone
walking around upstairs on this abandoned second floor. You'd hear
footsteps. Now there was still a staircase leading up there and sometimes
people would go up there. I'm assuming you I'm surprised they didn't use it for
some sort of storage area and they may have put some stuff up there because
people did go up there from time to time to get stuff but it doesn't say that
they're up there every day or didn't say how often people are going up there but
you'd hear footsteps coming from up there. At times you knew there should be
nobody up there. Then people would go up there occasionally and they would see
her ghost. They would see her ghost kind of wandering up and down the stairs
which is terrifying right because this is old building it's not like you can take
the elevator. I don't know how many staircases they have. Probably one and
you're walking up the stairs. Imagine that's so creepy. Imagine walking up
the stairs and getting a box or something like that and then as you're
walking down you see a ghost walking up the stairs. Where are you gonna go?
You can run around in the second story but that's where she's going. You're
trapped. You can't go down the stairs because there's a ghost there. I consider
myself fairly brave when it comes to paranormal. You're the biggest
scaredy cat. Monday you said you were afraid to turn into a tree. Well that's
because that's spooky but if I was walking down a hole what would I do if I was
walking down a hallway because I've seen shadow people and demonically
possessed people and all that stuff. If I was walking down a hallway and I saw
okay that's why I would turn around. I would probably observe it for a while and
then I'd get out of there. I don't think I would try walking past the ghost. Maybe
if it's a sexy ghost I might like walk up to it and start hitting it up. Hey what's
up? Where are you going? But even in those cases I probably would run away
because it's super spooky. It's a ghost. It's spooky. So full body apparition.
Walking up the stairs. You're trying to walk down the stairs. You are now trying
to figure out a way. You're looking for a fire escape to get out and then imagine
if someone sent you to go upstairs and you open the door and you saw her at the
top of the stairs walking. I'd be like dude I will go get whatever you want up
there but we're gonna have to wait a while because I'm pretty sure I just saw
a ghost at the top of the stairs. She might turn me into a tree. This happened
a few times over the course that Trails was a retail store. Trails is no longer
there. Now it's a restaurant called Sunbar Tempe. You'd have this staircase
and you would be walking up the stairs or walking down the stairs and you'd see
you're also walking stairs but there were also times that's creepy enough
right because that's affecting you. This is where I get to would you rather
see a ghost or know a ghost is watching you. A couple times people were upstairs
getting stuff doing whatever they needed to do there and when they were coming
back down the stairs they saw the ghost of this woman is standing at the bottom
of the stairs staring at the door that leads into the first floor. Just staring
at it. And this happened so many times and this was reported so many times they
just boarded up the door leading to the second floor and then completely covered
it up. Apparently it was just a wall at a certain point because you would have...
that's terrifying to me. Like as I'm recording this you know I have all these
doors around me. I'm recording this and imagine that there's a ghost in my
bedroom staring at me but I can't see it. Like what is really creepy or if I turn
in my bedroom door is open and I can see a ghost standing there. It's a sexy ghost
and I'll be there in a second honey. Or to know that it's trying to get to me but
it can't. It's just like waiting and watching. Imagine if behind a closed door
near you there's a ghost. I can hear your voices you're talking and it's waiting
to get to you. Like it's observing you. And this this was so unsettling
before you know the ghost is walking up and downstairs they're like "Larry you
still got to go there and get the new stock. Got to go up there and get those
boxes." But when the ghost is just staring at the door downstairs like
plotting or planning or waiting who knows who... see that's the thing you don't
know they boarded it up. Now I did go... I didn't actually visit it in person but I
did look up Sunbar Tempe online. I like went to Google Earth to kind of take a
look at it. It doesn't look like it has a second story anymore. It actually looks
like it's a one-story building but that's the same address. So I mean this
building was built in the 1900s and now it's like a hip dining spot in
Tempe Arizona. I don't think they wanted to have a big rectangular building that's
the color beige. So they may have actually eventually torn it down but one
thing we've learned over the course of this show is that just because you tear
down a location doesn't mean the ghost goes away. There's tons of reports of
mansions being burned down. We've done stories where a second floor of a
building it was like a college. I think it was the third floor of a dormitory was
knocked down and people can still hear the ghosts but it's like 10 feet in the
air like above the roof of the sea. If you're on the roof you can hear the
voices coming from above you somewhere. Just because the phenomenon... just because
the building is destroyed doesn't mean the phenomenon is gone. However I did not
see any online ghost reports about Sunbar Tempe. But if you're in the Tempe
area we got listeners all over the world and I'm always so grateful for that. You
guys are amazing. And if you do happen to be in the Tempe area go to... this was a
stealth ad. This whole thing was leading up to Sunbar Tempe, the hippinist
hoppinist place in Tempe Arizona. If you want to be like me dead rabbit hop on
over to Sunbar Tempe and order the new drink. Order the possessed
the goblet. It's all smoky and stuff. You'll drink it and it's so strong you'll
wish you were dead. Sunbar Tempe in Tempe Arizona. I've never been there. Their
food makes suck. I don't know. Maybe it's the best place to go but anyways go there
and see if there's ghosts. That's what I do when I go to places. I go "hey is this
place haunted?" I do it all the time. And people with me are like "oh my god" because
they know I'm gonna bring it up and people are constantly like "yeah there's a
Thai house restaurant called Thai house here in Hood River haunted. There's like
a little girl upstairs because it used to be a house. Then they turned into a
restaurant. Andrew's Pizza downtown. I have a bunch of friends who worked there
haunted. They named the ghost Tabatha. Used to be a dance studio which we know
again in the world of paranormal. Very very common. Very very common to have
theaters and dance studios and places of the arts to be haunted. I actually want
to start doing some on the ground ghost hunting with my friend Molly in town
again. It's been years since I've done on the town ghost hunting but that should be
fun. We'll talk more about that when I'm actually doing that but yeah. I ask when
places are haunted "hey is this place haunted?" So yeah I do that. I mean even if I
don't know anyone who works there like as they're bringing me my check. Like "hey is
this place haunted?" It doesn't hurt to ask. They've already served you your
food. They can't spit in it. But yeah so if you happen to be in the tempe area
check out Sunbar Tempe and ask "hey is this place haunted?" and then your waitress
is like "no of course not" and then you tip her and then she walks away. She walks up
a set of invisible stairs and then your real waitress shows up. She's like "uh
where's my money?" and you're like "nooo!" Sunbar Tempe the only place where a ghost
will steal your tips. Creole Cosmopolitan let's go ahead and toss you the keys to
the carboner copter. We're leaving behind Sunbar Tempe. We have full bellies from
their delicious meal be it breakfast lunch or dinner. Sunbar Tempe the only
restaurant you should ever go to. Fly us out of here. We're headed all the way out
to Coffee County Tennessee. Don't actually go there for breakfast. I don't know when
the place is open. You're like "what Jason told me you guys served breakfast?"
Breakfast. Breakfast. They're like "what are all of these people coming here all of a sudden?"
I traveled from around the world. I'm from El Salvador just to eat some
staking eggs. We're headed out to Coffee County Tennessee. We're headed back to the
year 2014. It's June 6th 2014 and there's a liquor store in town and waiting for a
ride is Lisa Marie Heiter. She's 36 years old and she's a mother of six. Her
life has not been easy. Things have been really hard. She struggled with alcoholism
for a long time. That is not only a debilitating mental strain but a
debilitating physical strain. She's having all of these emotional problems
and alcohol problems and like what often happens in the world of alcoholics is
that the family loves you and they will always love you but at a certain point
they got to back off. They got to say "listen I love you and I'll always be here
for you but I won't be here for you. This is just too much of a strain on us."
That's what's kind of going on in her life. She's married to a man named Charles
and she'd been married to him for six years and in this time period June 6
2014 he's like "I can't do this anymore. I can't be a part of an
alcoholic's life." To make things worse she worked at a liquor store which I
just I mean that just sounds like the worst combination and recently she had
been told by her doctors that she had ovarian cancer. So she has ovarian cancer.
She has six kids to take care of. She's recently gotten divorced.
I've married that last for six years and she refuses treatment. She tells the
doctors "I don't want to do any of the chemo. I don't want to do any other
treatment." The doctors say "listen you got six months to live like that's our
estimate." Sometimes they're wrong right? Sometimes they're wrong. It's not like
they actually can see a expiration date on you. It's kind of a guess. Some people
live way past that. In her case though the doctors do say "you have six months to
live if you're gonna refuse treatment and you know they understand why people
don't do the treatment because it can be very taxing on the body." She's making
her peace with this right? Even though her and Charles are divorced
Charles said "you know I still helped her out." Because he loved her right? They
still loved each other but they just couldn't be together. Charles couldn't
do it anymore and you I understand that. I think most of us can understand it.
Well on June 6th 2014 Lisa called up Charles and says "hey I need to ride home.
I'm at the liquor store. I need to ride home." And Charles is actually in another
state. I'm doing a job but I'll be there around 4 30. She's calling pretty early
in like the mid morning. He goes "it's about a five-hour trip. I'll be there by
4 30 p.m." And she goes "yeah sure okay you know I can wait. You can come pick me up."
Well later that afternoon Charles calls her cell phone and it goes straight to
voicemail. Is the phone turned off? Did she shut her off or something?
Again when you're dealing with someone who suffers from alcoholism they can be
a little erratic. But she's not at the liquor store. She's not there to be
picked up. And again maybe she walked. Maybe someone else gave her a ride. I
don't know. And the fact that Charles was a couple hours away. The fact that he
couldn't get there until 4 30 p.m. that day haunts him to this day. He said quote
"I still blame myself because I didn't go get her. But I was down in Huntsville,
Huntsville, Alabama. I was down in Huntsville unloading my truck and I wish
I could have been there a little bit faster. Usually I rescue her every time
something goes wrong." Let's take a look at another resident of Coffee County,
Tennessee. A man everyone knew in town is a big old weirdo. This wasn't one of
those "oh he was a nice quiet guy and never suspected it." This is one of those
"oh yeah that that makes sense. This seems like the type of guy who would do
something like this. This man's name is Gregory Hale. Back in 2014 he's 37 years
old. He's living with his parents. His parents had they were both retired. They
owned this house and Gregory Hale lived with him. Had a girlfriend, had a kid, and
had very very bizarre hobbies. To put it lightly. He worked at a local meat plant.
A local meat packing plant. So he's like sitting there and there's like meat
coming down a conveyor belt and he's like stamping it and wrapping it up and
touching it rubbing it all over his skin and they're like "Gregrie you're supposed
to be in this part. You're in human resources. Why are you in the
meat assembly line?" He worked at this meat packing plant and everyone there
knew he was a total freak. Everyone there thought this guy was a weirdo. He
would smuggle just from the way that he talked. Just from the way that he looked.
He's one of those guys that has a large collection of knives. He would take
Facebook photos of him like dressed in all black with a red tie and a bone
sword and then he had the same outfit. He's like wearing like new balance shoes
and black jeans and a black shirt and then a slipknot mask and he's holding
this bone sword. He's standing in front of like a garage. Like not a cool spooky
garage from Dead by Daylight. Like your grandma's garage. Like the garage on a
house. Just like a normal tract house. He's lame right? He did all this stuff. He
would post stuff on Facebook saying "I like to hug the people I hate so I know
how big to dig the hole in my backyard." You know what's so funny is that I've seen
stuff like that a hundred times from a hundred try-hards right? People are trying
to be like all goth and edgy and stuff like that. I will say this guy does turn
out to be the real deal. Even though I'm kind of rolling my eyes at whoa look how
edgy that is man. He actually does. The reason we're talking about an archery
crime podcast is because he does walk the walk. He posts jokes like "If you ate a
vegetarian would they taste..." This is actually kind of funny. I've been trying to read it without laughing.
He goes "If you ate a vegetarian would they taste like soy? Like soy meat? Like
impossible burgers?" Okay that's kind of funny right? I would have given that a
little thumbs up or laughing emoji but he would talk about stuff like that. He'd
post pictures of Richard Ramirez the night stalker with captions that said
"Wish I could have met you." And the biggest crime there is that he spelt you.
It's just the letter you right? I don't think Richard Ramirez was into emoji
talk. But anyways wish I could have met you. He talked a lot about Richard Ramirez
the night stalker serial killer back in the 70s. California late 70s. He would
often get caught stealing from the meatpacking plant. Now you could imagine
some people are like "Oh dude I really need to eat today. I'm gonna take home
this pound of prime rib." You probably get fired for that. He was stealing bones
and eyeballs. And I'm sure that the manager was kind of like "Well it's not
like we're gonna use those anyways. That's Oscar Meyer plant down the road.
That's how they make their hot dogs." But here what am I gonna do with an animal
bone or an eyeball? So sure if this guy wants to take home a bag of eyeballs each
day I mean it's weird right? They knew it was weird but I don't think they're
really punishing him. But he does get fired eventually. The manager does get
tired of this dude's antics but not for stealing animal waste. Not for posting
bizarre stuff on Facebook. Not for worshiping Richard Ramirez. Worse!
Everyone knew about all that stuff and he's still gonna get fired. One day this
is a fireable offense. And maybe in America you could have probably, well this
wasn't America. He probably could have had a civil rights lawsuit over this for
the First Amendment. One day the boss walked in to work and there is Gregory
Hale with animal guts performing a satanic ceremony at work. And the boss
is like nope I'm done. If he still wants to take this lawsuit I'm willing to fight
that battle. I'm not gonna allow you to try to summon the Dark Lord at work
using all this blood and animal guts that happen to be laying around. You're
fired. You are no longer working here. Now you can imagine like this must have been
his dream job right? This dude loves serial killing and he's in a place like
his Willy Wonka Chaka Factory. He walks in there's blood everywhere. He's like
dancing on a pile of eyeballs. He's juggling them. He has a cane made out of
a bone. This would be awesome for a sicko. There's a bunch of people listening to this
at a meatpacking plant right now. They're like shut it off. He just insulted our
entire profession. They're throwing blood at the Bluetooth speaker. Gregory Hale is
fired from the meatpacking plant. And you know what he's whatever he's just kind
of gliding through life anyways right? Well on June 6th 2014, Gregory Hale pulls
up outside of a liquor store in Coffey County, Tennessee and sees Lisa Marie
standing there. And they chat for a while and she talks about waiting for a ride
and he goes you know what I can give you a ride home. Not a problem. She's like
sure he's like yeah yeah hop in. Take you on out there. June 9th 2014. So three days
later. And just to show okay so she has now disappeared and it doesn't really say
in the article that there's a big manhunt for her. She was supposed to be picked up
on June 6th. It's three days later. She's disappeared. And this is one of the
problems with someone who has like drug and alcohol problems right? Is because
they act in erratic ways. When they go missing for a couple days it's not the
same thing as if you went missing. Like let's say you go you have like a good
attendance at work. You're always there on your Monday starting your shift at a
meatpacking plant. You're like oh I want to get the freshest eyeballs. I got to get
there nice and early. When you go missing when I go missing I have like
really good attendance right? And so when I stop showing up to work I get a phone
call. Like where are you? The search for me would start almost immediately. But you
know when you have someone who's suffering from it she probably has just
not shown up to work and things like that. They may have been looking for her
but we don't know about that. And the reason why that's important is because
there's a chance that Gregory could have gone away with this. Because it was
completely random that he drove up to that liquor store. And random crimes are
very very hard to solve. I'm not saying that he never would have got caught but
it's possible. But on June 9th 2014 now we're near the town of Manchester, Tennessee
Gregory Hale is chatting with his neighbor. He's like hey yeah what's going
on how's everything going? They're like oh you're going good with me Gregory. If you
found a new job yet and he's like no apparently I went to the bank hoping it
was a blood bank. I put in my application. It was a regular bank. What do you expect
me to do there? And the neighbors like to it on your Facebook friend. I know what
you post. Maybe you should just try getting a normal job and posting minions
on your Facebook page instead of love poems to serial killers. Anyways Gregory
Hale is talking to his neighbor and Gregory goes hey you know what I was
wondering if he could help me with something. The neighbors like yeah sure
you know what do you need? And Gregory Hale goes could you help me dispose of a
body? And at first the neighbor thinks that he's joking right? People say stuff
like that all the time. But the neighbor starts to realize that oh Gregory's not
joking like he's actually asking me if I can help him dispose of a body. He
contacts the police. It's so funny because if you think about people who would say
that to you in your life hey you want to help me dispose of a body a lot of times
you would think it was a joke. But this guy knew Gregory's reputation and knew
this guy wasn't joking. He's being dead serious. He called the police. The police
show up at Gregory's location and again I don't even know if they know Lisa
Marie's missing at this point. They may have it's been three days but who knows.
They show up at Gregory's house and they find the dismembered remains of Lisa
Marie. And she was chopped up in such a way that there were two plastic buckets
full of different parts of her and her torso was on a burn pile. It's very hard
to burn a body. My dad used to have a crematory. My summer job for a while was
going down there helping him out. It takes a lot. It's an extreme amount of heat. It
takes to reduce a human body to ash. A lot of people think oh you know just like
a marshmallow throw it on a fire. Uh-uh. I know you guys see in those Viking
movies they burn them on the pyre. You're watching the Northman. They're just
constantly burned. Everyone gets killed in that movie. They're constantly burning
bodies and as a religious thing sure but to actually reduce it to ash there's no
evidence left. It just doesn't. You can do it but it takes a lot of heat. Now when
they the police show up like they find this stuff before they're even talking
to Gregory. They show on the property and they see these two buckets of human
remains. They're just kind of like sitting out. This torso on the burn pile
and they go into the house and Gregory is taking a nap. He was completely
unconcerned that he asked his neighbor if he could help him bury a body. He's
like oh well guess he doesn't want to be buried in a body. That made me sleepy. And
it is after the police wake him up from his nappy time. He confesses that he
killed Lisa Marie and he fully reveals to the officers that not only did he
kill Lisa Marie not only did he dismember her but he ate parts of her as
well. Now he says that during this whole time the kidnapping, the murder, the
cannibalism, there was a satanic ritual performed and there's no details in any
of the articles of what the ritual was. I have a feeling this guy was a YouTube
Satanist. So he's one of those guys that just watches a couple YouTube videos
and thinking those all of the esoteric knowledge out there that involves
Satan worshipping and Lucifer and the dark ones. I don't think he really knew
what he was doing. He probably just painted... I don't know why he painted... I'm painting this
guy as a tryhard loser but and he is not saying that. He's exceptional because he
murdered someone. He's not. He's a monster but there's a lot of tryhards out there
in the world of Satanism. Really in every religion but they kind of stick
out in Satanism because they're just doing the tryhard type of stuff. Dressing
in all black clothes, they got it Kmart and holding a bone sword. They bought
online and it's somehow that's supposed to make them these edgy people. So I don't
know if this guy actually performed the ritual that was written down in the dark
grimoires from the 1500s or if he just saw something on YouTube and thought
that looks cool and painted a pentagram. Again, it doesn't really matter. He did
murder and eat a woman and yeah he just... there's a classification the FBI
uses for serial killers. Now this guy's only killed one person but it's... he
probably would have killed more had he been a little smarter. It's called... they
have an organized killer which would be someone like Ted Bundy who plans
everything out and then they have a disorganized killer which is someone
like the Vampire of Sacramento who was walking around breaking into people's
houses. He actually wasn't really technically breaking in. He'd walk up
to your house and if your door was unlocked, this is back in the 1970s, if your
door was unlocked that was God giving him permission to murder everyone in the
house. I had a really good friend of mine in college. He was in the neighborhood
where the Vampire of Sacramento had eaten the baby, walked in and killed a
woman and the woman was babysitting and ate a baby, drank all the baby's blood
and he said that happened. He goes, "I actually... it was... if I remember correctly
there was a babysitter and her son..." like I'm trying to remember the details.
There was a babysitter, there was like a six-year-old boy that was the babysitter's
son and that woman was watching an infant at the time and my buddy went over to
the house to see if the kid wanted to go play because it was a friend of his. "Hey
you want to go play?" and he knocked on the door and no one came into the door and
he goes, "I guess my friend's not home." And he left and it turns out that while he
was knocking on that door, the killer was inside the house and when the cops get
to the house, they find a dead mom, they find her dead kid and they are not even
looking for a baby at that point. Someone came up and goes, "Oh my god, is my baby
okay?" and the cops are like, "Uh... because there was no baby there. He was
actually the vampire of Sacramento." I forgot what his name was. Let me look it
up real quick. Richard Chase. Richard Chase, if I remember correctly, he was caught
like walking down Watt Avenue covered in blood and he had the remains of a baby
in a bucket just like sitting in his house and and the FBI has steadied him
as a disorganized serial killer because he didn't plan anything out and he
really wasn't thinking, "Oh, I might get caught." So he just walked around covered
in blood, walked in and out of houses and he took the baby with him and ate it,
ate a good portion of it and drank his blood and all that stuff. So that's what
I would classify Gregory as well, a disorganized serial killer because he
just had the body... he was trying to dispose of the body. He had the body
parts just in buckets and Lisa Marie's heart, he threw it over into a neighbor's
yard and landed in her garden. Like obviously you're gonna find... I mean
obviously you're gonna notice that doesn't belong here. That looks like a human heart.
So very very disorganized in his way he was doing. I mean luckily, right? Luckily
he was an idiot and it turns out, right, this wasn't a spur-of-the-moment thing as
the police are investigating him and all that. He revealed that for a long time he
had fantasized about killing and eating someone. This guy's a father too, remember?
The beginning this guy lives with his parents or lived in his parents' home.
Maybe they weren't there. I think they probably would have been a little alarmed
at his antics but he lived at his parents' home. I believe they all live
together but that... some of the details on this story I couldn't verify. But he
does have a child of his own. He has a girlfriend. He had spent years fantasizing
about killing and eating somebody and he had actually practiced stalking women
before. He would follow women around and he would fantasize about how it would be
to capture them and kill them and eat them. That was always his desire. And when
he drove up to the slicker store and saw Lisa Marie waiting for a ride, it was
just a crime of opportunity. He goes, "Here's my chance." She got in the car and
he didn't take her home. He took her back to his house.
So he's been sentenced to life without the possibility of parole. He's already
in the prison system. They'll never let him out. That's the story of Gregory Hale
and his victim, Lisa Marie Heider. What a terrible tragic story, right? I mean, she
knew she didn't have much longer to live. She knew that she had only been given
six months but that's six months she could have spent with her kids. That's
six more months on earth. But she never would have guessed that she wouldn't die
from cancer but that she would be eaten. She would be killed and eaten as part of
a satanic ceremony. And the scariest thing about this story is we know. We know
that Gregory Hale, although rare, is not one of a kind. I mean, I just off the top
of my head were rattleing off facts about the vampire of Sacramento, Richard
Chase. People who fantasize about eating people and doing it. People who fantasize
about killing people and eating them and getting away with it. You know, this guy
luckily got caught. But how many others are out there? Not only already doing
this and getting away with it, but just also the young men sitting around
fantasizing about this. How many cannibals have we covered on this
podcast? A lot! A surprising amount of cannibals. I'll put the episodes in the
show notes. I don't want to hear those. I don't want to hear this one. Insane.
Absolutely terrifying to think that there are other people out there like him
right now fantasizing about eating people and some of them may have already
taken that step. How do you protect yourself? How do you protect your loved
ones against the man who has spent years fantasizing about killing them? Killing
you? Like we just go about our day and we have our safety radar on, right? We're
kind of aware of our environment to a certain extent and watching for trouble.
Maybe we keep some sort of self-defense item on us, but there's someone behind me
who spends day after day after day after day of what it would be like to kill and
eat me. Someone who's run every scenario through their head, if the person does
this, I'll do this. If the person says that, I'll say this. If the person tries to run,
I'll do this. If the person runs and falls, I'll do that. And they've played out all
these scenarios in their head and they're sexually aroused by it. I'm expecting to
fight insane homeless people and dumb kids who don't understand that they
shouldn't pick a fight with an adult. Some teenager malden off. Like that's where
my fight experience comes from basically. Drunks, stupid teenagers, and crazy people.
Like just, you know, like not this crazy. Random violence is the type of
fights that I've been in and that's the type of fights that I expect and that's
the type of fights I know how to, if not win, survive. But I've never gone up
against someone who spent day after day after day after day trying to eat me,
stalking me, observing me, and then going home and sexually fantasizing about
what it would be like to eat me. Right now there's a listener on this podcast. He's like,
"Oh man, you totally, we have a soul bond. That's exactly what I want to do." It's
like, how do you fight against something? How do you fight against someone who's
obsessed with this level of depravity? It's terrifying to think about. So we don't.
We try not to think about it. We just go on with our lives. But people like Gregory
and people like Richard Chase exist. And while those people have been caught, how
many more are out there watching you, stalking you, fantasizing about you, and
each day their hunger grows. And at that point you're not fighting a man.
You're fighting a monster.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also go to
subbedfacebook.com/deadrabberradio. TikTok is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]