mysterious fortress in the middle of the desert. Crows can't tell the difference
between the living and the dead and we take a quick look at some mysterious
footage shot in the catacombs under Paris today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Carpenter. Hope you guys are having a great day. I'm having a great
day. It's really really hot but you know I'm just staying hydrated drinking a
bunch of water. I used to hate drinking water. I just couldn't you know I was I
don't know what it was. I know a lot of people complain that water has no taste
and it doesn't have a taste. It's funny because it technically has to have a taste
but maybe the taste particles are so spread out. It's like one taste particle
per million or something like that. But yeah I'm not a fan of water but I've
recently been drinking it a lot and it is really good for you. You guys are
probably like of course it's good it's good for you but as an adult male who's
gone most of his life without drinking water it's a I have to admit it's pretty
good for you. I don't sweat a lot and I was telling that to someone the other day
and they go oh you're so special I was like no I don't sweat because not because
of anything special because I'm constantly dehydrated. I don't have
enough liquid in my body to come out of my pores. My body's like a laptop with
the fan not working. I think it's constantly overheating. So now that I've
been drinking more water I've been getting a little bit of sweat a little bit of
sweat going on you know on my forehead. No CNC music factory level but it's a
bit different. It's a bit different for me. I used to drink a gallon of Kool-Aid a
day and when I in let me when I was 35 years old not when I was a young kid
which I drank Kool-Aid back then but probably from about 35 to around 38 I
drank a gallon of Kool-Aid a day. I actually have a Kool-Aid man poster in my
apartment just because I love to Kool-Aid so much and then once I went to the
doctor and we were talking about weight loss and I told him I drank a gallon of
Kool-Aid a day and he laughed not just at that and I kind of realized I was like
that's kind of weird that he laughed at that and he caught himself really
quickly after we talked and did the whole visit thing. I wasn't there for the
weight loss or something else going on but we were sitting there talking he
goes hey you know I can tell you're kind of a funny guy you can take a joke I'm
gonna go ahead and tell you what I was laughing about earlier. Now at the time
my hair was real my hair I have is I kind of have crazy hair if I don't do
anything with it if it's not like shaved down it just kind of grows in every
direction and he goes when you said you drink a gallon of Kool-Aid a day the
reason I laughed was because you reminded me of the Hawaiian punch guy and I
laughed because that was funny and it was pretty true so yeah and it's you know
it's always good to have a rapport with a doctor like that he's not my regular
doctor unfortunately but I think he's moved on a lot of times the doctors at
little clinics end up getting better paying jobs at hospitals so good for him
good for him I hope he keeps his sense of humor and I hope he runs into a lot of
other patients with their sense of humor probably not because they're seeing them
because they're really sick. So the first story we're going to cover tonight is
recently made the news but the study had been going on for maybe two years so
there was a case of well it's no one in science that crows will often hold
funerals for other crows and they've always kind of wanted to understand the
phenomenon now crows are incredibly intelligent they've done so many studies
on crows where crows will remember you as an enemy for like up to two years there
was a guy and I think it was even longer than that there is this professor who was
throwing rocks at crow for whatever reason for science I guess and then the
crows would attack him and he ended up leaving going to an eye you know what's
funny I'm gonna tell you the story and I honestly probably can't back it up I
don't know if I can ever find this article again but the scientist was
throwing I'm assuming he's a scientist was throwing rocks at crows on his
college campus he ended up getting a job in another college campus he came
back years later to visit some friends he got attacked by crows he'd gotten
attacked by crows the whole time he was working there which made him want to
throw more rocks but even after he left and came back the crows remembered him
and continued to attack them they've done studies where people have been mean
to crows and then other people have had worn worn masks of the person who was
mean to crows and the crows attacked them again I'll see if I can find those
links to prove what I just said I'll see if I can find that information but if
you don't see the links then you'll just have to take my word for that but
anyway so they have observed crows holding funerals and one of the one of
the hypotheses is that the crows aren't necessarily mourning the dead what it is
is they know that there's an enemy in the area so they're trying to figure out
what killed it they're trying to do a little bird CSI for cause scene
anyways there's there's anyways so they try to figure out what killed it so they
won't die themselves so they don't necessarily know if it's like a funeral
like releasing the bird spirit to heaven so this scientist got together with this
film crew and she's like oh we're gonna have this I'm gonna run this experiment
you guys can be there and you can record the birds having the funeral so the
camera crew gets there and they put out this fake what's a real bird but it's
dead and it's stuffed they put it in the road and another crow flies down looks
at it and begins to hump it begins to try to dry hump it and the scientist is
like that is not what that's not what they're supposed to do so for two years
she was taking these stuffed crows and leaving them around the Pacific Northwest
I think it was in Portland actually maybe Seattle but anyways and out of 4% of all
the case she does like 200 times or something like that out of 4% of these
cases the bird had sex with the dead bird and in one case the dead bird was there
and then two birds came down and started banging each other in front of the
dead bird and what her hypothesis is that it's tends to happen during mating
season and she goes it's not because there's not enough mates to go around
she even saw one time that a bird's mate was in the area and the bird still came
and banged the dead body so it's like cucking with a dead bird which has to
be the ultimate form of cuckoldry but she says that when they're mating system
their brains actually aren't working right because in some of the cases the
birds would attack the corpse and in most of the cases the birds would go down and
try to figure out what's going on so she thinks that when mating season comes
around the birds the wiring is mixed up in their brain and so they don't know how
to react they want to figure out the danger they want to attack it as a as
a interloper into their area and they want to have sex with it like all things
are coming together yeah so now it's part of crow science that four percent of
these dead birds will get molested at some point and it just you know four
percent is such a small percentage that it probably wasn't seen and if somebody
did just see it you know a lay person would be like oh that birds just kind of
jumping around that other bird because birds don't have penises I guess they
just like rubbed their vents against each other it was funny too because this
scientist she got the cops called on her a couple times because all the people in
the neighborhood would see is a woman go and set down a dead crow and then
retreat to the bushes with a pair of binoculars so people in the neighborhood
were quite nervous of why she was doing all of this stuff but I just thought that
was an interesting story it popped up oh and the pun obviously is I didn't make
this up it was in the scientists actually put this in her paper which was
great putting the crow in necrophilia that's if you if there's no if there's
a Nobel Prize for great great scientific phrases that's the one that might
have even actually been the name of her paper honestly the second story was an
interesting one because I was researching something off the conspiracy
list called Colgate forts and I actually found out what that was we're gonna do
another story on that and it's the Colgate forts itself well I just tell you
right now it's Russian soldiers went to Siberia and to they were like soldiers
fleeing the purge the purges the Stalinist purges and they actually made
forts out of Colgate toothpaste to live in and I you're thinking okay well
that's the end of that story the story actually gets more fascinating than that
but while I went and we'll say that for another episode but while I was researching
Colgate forts I came across just this mind-boggling mind-bogglingly weird slash
like it's like this weird mystery that not only doesn't have any answers but it
seems like nobody wants any answers this is a real place you can find it on
Google Earth it's historical place it's called and I might be getting the
pronounciation pronunciation pronunciation wrong and it's called
Rani Kot fort or Rani Kot or a in in I'm not gonna spell for you but anyways so
this is in Pakistan so you're thinking oh you know there's a fort in Pakistan
what does it have ghosts is it full of cryptids no it's known as if not the
largest fort ever constructed on the planet Earth it's like in the second
place there's been some dispute over whether or not this one in Pakistan is
bigger or one in India is bigger and of course there's a dispute because they
hate each other but this fort and using the fort is kind of a weird phrase
because it's actually a 19 mile long perimeter of these massive walls and it
goes up into this hill range and it comes down it's because it's on people say
it's the it's like the Great Wall of China it's just this massive fortress in
Pakistan and so it's just sitting there in the desert there's been a little bit
of restoration work but not recently and it's free to visit here's the thing no
one knows when it was built no one knows who built it and no one knows why it was
built so you're going oh you know okay fine some Mesopotamians built some stone
structure you know 10,000 years ago big whoop you know of course we're not
gonna know this structure was built any time between the 9th and the 18th
century they don't know and their people are going as probably built in the 17th
century 17th century we have documents still from the 17th century you're
telling me one of the world we're just gonna call it the world's largest fort
the world's largest fort was built in the 1700s and we don't know who it is at
first I thought okay we don't know who it is it was probably some like a Syrian
warlord no and I know those groups aren't in Pakistan but those are just
the ones I know off the top of my head and I can pronounce because the names in
these articles I can't pronounce 1700s they built a 19 mile long fort
white's perimeter fort and nobody knows why who built it no documents no poems
about it no legends about it it's simply there they don't know who built it
their theories ranging from this group I can't pronounce to that group I can't
pronounce to Greeks to the here I'll try to pronounce this one because this is the
most recent one the talpers yeah the other ones are okay the parthas
Parthenons yeah I can't say most of these but anyways so most recent evidence
says that it originated under the talpers it costs 1.2 million rupees to
build these are all things that they can estimate just from like the size of it
there's three little forts inside of it and it was just massive undertaking
it's in the middle of nowhere people go there's nothing defensive in that area
that word would require someone to build such a massive fort it's not a
strategic choke point it's not a resource point it's not near anything
here nowadays so why was it built why was it built and if it was built so
recently how can we have no information the one theory I could find was that the
reason why we don't have much information on who built it and you know
it's just sitting there and it's been named like a World Heritage site
Pakistani government's really not doing anything to keep it up all the rest last
of the restoration happened in the 18th century so even then they were still
working on it still fixing it up they're still massive doors it's amazing but
the theory is is that the group that they believe built it or think built it
is a different religion or a different royal dynasty from the current one and
they want the current one wants to seem like they're the greatest and they don't
want to give any credence to other groups and that's possible I mean people are
petty like that but I just think it's amazing that something could be built so
recently that we have no information on if this thing had been hundreds and
hundreds of years old I can understand we don't have any information we come
across that like we'll find mounds in America we'll find structures and
scientists are like we don't really know who built it we think it's some sort of
burial mound but we're not entirely for sure it could be this tribe it could be
this tribe but they didn't have any written records this was far past the
this was far past the time where people are having rented written records people
have having printing presses people have already at this point circumnavigated
the globe 17th 18th century is far far far too recent to have no information on
this thing and the weird thing is this no one's out there steady in it the
articles I read said it seems relatively safe there's not a lot of bandits in the
area but there's no police but we have scientists going into the Middle East
going in you know in war zones that have just started to cool down to look at
artifacts and this place is just sitting there who knows what's there who knows
what to find now that being said I have a theory why would you build a fortress
in the middle of nowhere zombies I have a theory and it's I have nothing to back
this up but what if we had a zombie infestation and early human history and
I'm thinking like bubonic plate times dark ages times and this is kind of my
kind of my guess to that in all over the world when we look at royal soldiers like
the high-level soldiers a lot of times they had padded armor but in Europe the
soldiers were decked out in metal the knights the knights that we all know of
if you're fighting zombies what do you want do you want padded armor that maybe
they can bite through or do you want to be encased in steel I don't know if it's
actually steel but do you want to be encased in metal what if hear me out
what if the bubonic plate existed but it was actually a zombie virus and that's
what caused one-third of the world's population to decline and the only thing
you could do to stop it was to send knights out to just bash in infected
peasants heads and the thing is it's like any writings of that of people dying
of this horrible disease and coming back and and moving throughout this
civilization of northern Europe and people fighting these things all of
that stuff would just be chalked up to religious superstition they'd go no no
no no that was just an actual plague and look under a microscope and this is
what a bug looks like and blah blah blah maybe the bubonic plague because we
still have the bubonic plague around again I just realized that we actually
know what the bubonic plague is because it's still an issue and like but anyway
so we don't have zombies that we know of but what if that was the core reason
why knights were encased in all metal now as much as I love that theory I do have
to throw a little assault on that fire I don't know if that's a phrase but you
know the knights did exist long before the black plague came into town but but I
did find out that in 100 AD 15 million people died in Europe and they don't
know why they they think it's because of like global cooling or global warming
and the crops all dying but maybe it's zombies so how does this play into rain
caught for it in the 17th century maybe there are zombies out in the middle of
desert maybe someone opened like a gin or a some sort of I jins don't exist in
Pakistan assuming they exist at all but maybe there was some sort of unholy
force that came out and they had to build this giant fort to fight him like
that movie the Great Wall which nobody saw I don't think anybody saw that movie
but I think it's in the tristitory and honestly that theory okay they built that
fort to fight zombies or to some sort of supernatural force a that theory is
just as valid as any other one because actually okay it's not as valid as any
other one but it's the only theory put forward most people are like yeah we
don't know why it was built and I've read multiple articles on this and it's
frustrating because it's a mystery I think could be solved they could go out
there and say oh this guy thought the land was holy and built this fort or
this land actually was some sort of strategic choke point at that time but
it's just nothing there's no investigation into this fort at all
that's what makes it such a huge mystery you know we cover a lot of stuff on the
show that just can get easily debunked but I can't find anything for why this
fort exists or really anything to say why people aren't researching it science
it's just stuff's coming up and they're like yeah scientists aren't really
interested why not archaeologists other people who study old stuff so look that
up look up rainy caught fort and if you're an archaeologist you're looking
for a thesis subject maybe you just found one we're gonna wrap this up really
quickly you guys may have seen this before this video originally got deleted
and now it's back up it's super bizarre on a couple different levels but it's
fairly short so I'm gonna keep this part short there's a video of a man in the
lost cat and the catacombs of France so underneath they had such a oh my god
they had such a problem with people dying in France they had so many bodies
they had to put them in caverns what if that was the victims of the zombie plague
bam wrap around anyways they had such a problem with all these dead bodies they
didn't know where to put them they put them in all these catacombs underneath
Paris and so this guy is on a video camera and he's walking through the
catacombs and this footage was broadcast on ABC family of all things so here
let's play a quick audio clip of the Paris catacombs thing you I mean obviously
you're gonna want to watch the video to get the full effect but I'll just play
a little clip of it here we hear his breathing get louder and louder as though
something was scaring he was he's frightened he's frightened occasionally
stops perhaps to try to decide which way to run among all the many different
corridors he's running faster and faster and faster and deeper and deeper into
the catacombs and all of a sudden
so I just wanted to include that because it I think it's just such a creepy video
and people have said oh you know it's fake and blah blah blah but I you know I
and it may be I mean the guys definitely in some sort of tunnel system people are
like well if a monster was chasing him why don't we see the monster on film and
I'm like well maybe it's not a monster maybe it's a ghost or maybe something
crawling on the ceiling or maybe it's fake or maybe he was just having anxiety
attack I mean those are probably the two most likely ones because he's underground
and there's a bunch of dead bodies around him but I think it's an interesting
video I hope you guys check it out I remember seeing it years ago and
thinking it was creepy and then I had to find it again because now that I'm doing
this podcast there's a couple of stories and stuff that I remember coming across
early on you know years and years ago and I'm like oh that would be cool to put
on the podcast a video is probably not the best thing to put on a podcast but
this one has some pretty cool audio too I think you can kind of get a gist for it
but check it out yourself as well dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is our
email address you can always hit me up there contact me let me know if you have
any story suggestions we have a lot of cool ones but I'm always looking for more
I just love research and stuff and reading about it Twitter is @jasonOcarpenter
my Facebook is facebook.com/dead rabbit radio you can hit us up on there as
well you'll get the links to the newest episodes and you know we always post on
YouTube as well under dead rabbit radio a lot of times we take clips out of the
shows all of those venues are places you can get the podcast if you're
listening to it on any sort of podcast service like iTunes, Stitcher, Google Play
make sure to subscribe make sure to leave us a review too that really helps
and also share this podcast with your friends if you have a good time if you
have a laugh if you learn something share with your friends that's how we keep
the show going this is a daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime
podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it
today we're gonna be back tomorrow with some other great stories and I hope you
tune in have a great day
[Music]