Was there really an internet game that encouraged its players to commit suicide?
And can magic help you get the life you've always dreamed of today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to Dead Rabbit Radio. My name is Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too. Episode 72. This is crazy that it's actually lasted this long.
And not to be fair, no, no, no. Now that it's lasted this long, that I've kept doing it this long.
It's awesome. I'm very, very proud of myself. We're actually, which you know,
you should always be proud of yourself, but we're actually doing great. Thank you so much
for everyone who's downloading the show, listening to it. It's doing, it's phenomenal.
We're hitting the tipping point where now it's just getting subscribers and getting new downloads
every day. So I appreciate that. And really, that plays into our second story. So I currently have
a friend who's having trouble with mice in her house. Now I'm not going to say who it is because
she would beat me up. But you know, the traditional answer is you have mice in your house. People
say we'll get a cat. Cat, well, either mice or cats, however many mice you have. Apparently,
she has a lot. That actually works with other species as well. I used to eat a ton of rice,
pounds and pounds of rice. It's really cheap and it's filling and I love it. And I always like
mix it with chili or a Taco Bell or whatever. Turns it's basically just a filler food. What I didn't
know was that in rice, and correct me if I'm wrong, I probably am. I don't know if this is
exactly where they came from, but in rice, there are little bugs called rice weevils, like eggs,
basically. So if you and again, people are like, that's not how it works, Jason. That's not how
it works. But this is what I was told happens. If you cook rice and don't eat all of it and you let
it sit out for a while, the rice weevil eggs hatch. And so you get these little bugs that fly
around your apartment. Now that sequence of events happened quite often where I would cook rice and
wouldn't eat all of it. I would leave the bowl out and these bugs, these little rice weevils began
to infest, not this apartment. This was years and years ago. I don't want people going, I'm never
coming over to your apartment again, Jason. Anyways, so I'd get these rice weevils flying around.
They pretty much limit themselves to the kitchen or wherever there was rice before. Maybe they
showed up to eat the rice. I don't know. That's not the point. Anyways, I had rice weevils everywhere.
And then one summer, the rice weevils were gone. But my sanitary habits didn't change. So I was
like, "Oh, I wonder where all those rice weevils at." But I had an infestation of ants, not an
infestation, but I had a lot of ants in my kitchen because again, not cleaning up. And so I was like,
"Oh man, I got all these ants. Oh man, I just, no peace of course. I could have just cleaned up." But
it's like, "What are we going to do with all these ants?" So finally I got some bug spray
or just cleaned them up. I think I just like mass extermination of all these ants. And then maybe
like a couple days later, a week later, the rice weevils came back. And I thought, "Wait a second.
The ants, the rice weevils were here. The ants showed up. There was no more rice weevils to get
rid of the ants. Rice weevils show back up." So then I realized that the ants must have been eating
the weevils. So what I did, again, rather than clean up, I coaxed a bunch of ants into my apartment
by leaving sugar out for them in lollipops and candy.
The ants showed up in droves. Never had another rice weevil problem. Now, when I say rice weevil
problem, let me tell you this story for an example. I was dating a girl at the time. She was over at
the apartment and she was complaining about something or whatever. I'm sitting on the couch and she's
just like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah." And she had something in her hand and she hit the top of the trash can.
So like the lid would pop down to throw the thing away. She's looking at me because she's complaining
to me about something. And she hits the top of the can and she drops the thing into the garbage can.
And right when the candle is open, a bowling ball size of rice weevils just silently flew out of the
garbage can. I was almost expecting them to make the shape of a mallet and hit her on the head.
It was like a cartoon amount size of rice weevils. And they just flew right by her. If she had seen
them, it would have been over right there. Absolutely. She would have crucified me and
broke up with me, which technically happened later on. But I saw it like, and my eyes go
wide because I'm thinking if she just turned slightly to her left, she is going to piss her
pants. And they just fly up and then they just kind of like are buzzing around the ceiling of
they're happy they finally got free of their garbage can jail. And she didn't see them. But so that was
the level of rice weevil infestation. So I ended up coaxing the ants in, they took care of the rice
weevils. And then as a reward to them, I built them an amusement park. I built them a little,
I built the ants like this little like walkway. And then I had like this little thing of rubbing
in alcohol. And it was like, if they fall on that, they die. So that's not really an amusement,
but it was amusement to me. And I built like these little bridges they could walk across and I put
sugar everywhere so they could eat it. I love ants now. I don't have them anymore. Sadly enough.
Well, I guess that's good. But I always liked watching them like eat stuff, be like put out a
lollipop and then you'd see them eat little little holes through them and stuff like that.
So thank you ants for giving me entertainment and saving me from rice weevils. Let's go ahead and
get started with the episode. So this is an interesting story because there's a lot of
disagreement over whether or not it's real, which isn't surprising on the internet. But for the amount
of impact this has had, it is weird. What we're going to talk about here is the blue whale game.
Now the blue whale game started back in 2017, 2016, 2015 actually. So started back in say 2015.
And what that is in an overview, an umbrella view of the blue whale game, you, it is a series of 50
tasks that get increasingly more dark and violent. So the first, I finally found the list. It took
me forever and see again, there's not a ton of concrete information on this. So we're going to
go over a couple of the quick, we're going to quickly go over a couple of these tasks. So day
one, you're supposed to carve a phrase on your arm. Day two, you wake up at 420 and you watch a
scary video. You just keep going through. You have overcome a fear. You write an online status on
social network about being a whale. You listen to music that the curator sends. And so what it is,
is that you sign up for to be part of this blue whale game and you get an advisor and they walk
you through these 50 tasks. And if you don't complete them, you get like berated, like you're
not doing these fast enough. Where's that picture of that guy's name carved on your arm and stuff
like that. And the end result is kill yourself. And some of these tasks are set up to overcome
objections to killing yourself, like climb up a crane and go to the edge of a bridge,
stand on the edge of a building and basically it's baby steps to get you to that point.
Now supposedly it started in Russia. So it's been linked to like hundreds of suicides.
And there is all these, it was an international thing. Governments were saying,
parents, you have to monitor your kid's social network. There's this game going around that's
taking young, vulnerable, depressed kids and talking them into committing suicide.
There are people online who are trying to get your kids to commit suicide.
One of like Egyptians former government officials, his son killed himself. They
believe it was linked to this game. They had a big outbreak in India. The biggest was in Russia
where they're having a ton of these. And what's weird is the pushback was no, this is a modern day
witch hunt. This is just like the satanic panic of the 80s, which is where, you know, supposedly
everything was, everything, they went wrong with saint worshiping. You could play albums
backwards and there were preschools with saint worshipers running them. And that's almost
like a, it's own episode, but it's kind of like this moral panic. The pushback was none of these
suicides because kids were killing themselves. The question was, is it linked to the blue whale
game? And they can never find, according to the online sources, they can never find definitive
proof. What we know in this time period is kids were killing themselves, which is nothing new,
unfortunately. And that there were websites dedicated to getting people to kill themselves.
The question was, were the two things linked? So there was a really interesting article written
in Cosmo where a young female reporter went undercover pretending to be an even younger female,
and she got a hold of one of these groups because it wasn't incredibly hard. And she met a guy who
was saying, you know, follow these steps. Why aren't you doing these things? And it's an interesting
read because she talks about kind of the mental anguish she was going through because she was
going in as an undercover reporter. But the way he kind of groomed her actually was making her
feel depressed and lonely and things like that. Now again, the pushback is none of this stuff is
linked. None of this stuff is linked. In Russia, they arrested a man. They arrested him for inventing
this game, basically. And he was being held in charges of inciting suicide. And he's like,
oh, these people want to die. And I'm just cleansing society. They're biological waste,
which is funny because that's a lot like we talked about yesterday with Satoshi Umamatsu.
He figures he's doing the world a favor. And again, the pushback, the debunking is, oh,
there's really no proof this guy was arrested. That was first reported in this tabloid type
website and things like that. It's totally made up. It's overblown. What I honestly think is
going on. It doesn't surprise me. There are people out there trying to talk other people into committing
suicide. Maybe it's their fetish. Maybe it's a power move. Maybe it's their way of being a serial
killer. I think the pushback is the thing saying this isn't true. These kids are just
unfortunately killing themselves. It's not linked. I think the pushback is coming from,
and this is my conspiracy, coming from tech companies. If the governments of the world
could prove a conclusive link between Facebook, between Instagram, between Twitter, and a suicide
game that's causing hundreds of kids to kill themselves, it was like 230 kids or something
like that, you would see massive regulation on those sites, massive. They would say Facebook,
you have to vet every single comment that comes online because people are dying because of it.
So what would Facebook and Google do? They would basically lobby to say this isn't true.
They're going to favor search results that are like, well, there's no conclusive link.
They're going to favor stories where they're like, yeah, but this didn't really happen this way,
and we think it's just a made up thing, and this didn't happen, and this didn't happen,
because otherwise, their survival would be in jeopardy. If the governments, and again,
moral panics do happen, and stuff can get over-regulated because of that, but if the governments
of the world could prove these things are actually happening, these sites would be shut down.
I think that I believe that people are still enticing young people to kill themselves online,
and I believe that young kids are doing it, and I believe it's a problem, and I believe it's a
problem that's being covered up because there's just way too much at stake to let that information
get out. We're already talking about regulating Facebook and Google because they're demoting
conservative websites. Could you imagine if we could prove that they were encouraging suicide,
or not necessarily encouraging it, but not stopping it, that people were using their sites
for young kids to kill themselves? It'd be a disaster. Absolute disaster. So we'll see. Again,
it's an odd story. There's tons of articles on it, but all of them say there's no conclusive link,
and maybe there isn't. Could also be that, you know, when a young person takes their life,
family is always going to look for answers, and maybe it's the easy answer to go,
"Oh, they were coaxed online part of this blue whale game," but again, I think the truth may be
half in the middle. Even if half the kids was linked to this group, that's still a problem,
and it's a problem that would need to be addressed. I'm not a huge fan of Facebook and
Google, honestly, but I just think that's an interesting story. Now it's kind of come back
with the Momo challenge, which is kind of the same thing. It's this creepy figure that encourages
kids to commit to suicide, so the game is still going on. It just will change its name, and because
these creeps are always out there. The next story we're going to talk about is far more uplifting,
so I don't want to end on that one. When I was about 18 or 19, I got this design in my head.
I was really into metaphysical stuff back then, and I remember I saw this image, and it wasn't
magical. It wasn't like it was floating in front of me in fire and talking to me in
Inoki and or anything like that. It was just this glyph I got in my head. I can't really explain it.
I can draw it easily. And it was basically when I saw it, I knew what it was. It was the symbol of
my life. I was like, "That's how my life will be charted out. That's the symbol of my life," and
I knew about sigils and things like that. So a sigil is basically an inscribed - I'm reading the
definition here - is an inscribed or painted symbol considered to have magical powers. So it's basically
like a design that is infused with magic, magical thought, magical vibration. So I had this image
in my head, and I've drawn it out. People who know me may have seen it on me before, and usually I
draw it when I'm bored, but it's always been very comforting to me because it's a symbol of hope,
and it shows the good times and the bad times in my life. It kind of just charts the whole thing out.
And I'll see if I can draw a picture of it and throw it up online. I need a scanner. But so
that was - I had that sigil. What's interesting - so then we're going to skip ahead to what
the story is about - is not the magical drawings, but something known as a hyper-sigil. So a hyper-sigil
is not just a drawing of a symbol, a magical symbol, but it is a living magical work. It is
basically a sigil that has its own - it's a sigil in story form, I guess is a good way to put it.
People have made hyper-sigils out of things like poems, of comic books is a really popular one,
movies, and things like that. And what it is is it is basically taking your life
and turning it into a narrative. You live the hyper-sigil. Grant Morrison is a comic book writer.
He's very, very well known in the comic book community. Not real name recognition, but he
had a comic book that came out quite a while ago called The Invisibles. You probably know what
better is the matrix because the matrix ripped off a lot of the plot, the overall plot of The
Invisibles. But for him, The Invisibles was his hyper-sigil. To him, that's his hyper-sigil. That
is the life he wanted and he lived through the story of the comic book. And he said, "I wanted to
live in a glam, futuristic world, so I created a glam, futuristic world and enveloped myself around
it and now I'm living the life I've always wanted to live." Now sure, being a successful comic book
author is part of that because he has the money to buy those things. But you create and so imagine
what your life is like right now. Now I want you to imagine if going forward, you had to cut a movie
trailer for your future life. So you're where you're at right now, but you go, "You know what? I want
to be this. I want my life to have these elements. I want it to be exciting or exotic or passionate
or dangerous. Imagine a movie trailer of you waking up tomorrow, the life you want. Imagine a story,
a narrative, where you are the main character and really put your mental thought into that. You
are creating a hyper-sigil by doing that. I've done that with Dead Rabbit. When I was putting up flyers
for the show, I imagined, I go, "This would be a scene in the trailer for this story of my life.
Of me just going out and doing the groundwork to get this ball rolling." I remember specifically
thinking that as I put the flyer up on the community board, I thought, "This is a scene in the trailer
of the story of Dead Rabbit Radio. This is me taking that first step to get it known to the wider public.
And that's how I live my life. I've created this narrative for me. I've created this character. That
is me." When people meet me in real life or people who know me listen to podcasts, they're like, "Ugh."
It's just like talking to you. But at the same time, Dead Rabbit is part of a separate space, part of
like a magical thought space, a future that I want. And that's how I envision it. My hyper-sigil is
Dead Rabbit. And I think about it and I put it out there. And it comes, that's the weird thing. It
works. It absolutely works. If the show fell apart tomorrow, you could argue it didn't work.
And I'd say, "Yeah, there is a, you know, convergence of factors and something happened,
the show couldn't continue." But that's not going to happen. The show's going to keep growing and
growing and growing because I've seen those parts of the trailer. I've already lived those parts of
that story. I may get curveballs. I may get plot twists that I don't see coming. But the overall
story is the same. If you listen to the early episodes, and I don't know if I necessarily
said it on the episodes, I'm pretty sure I did. I did say in real life. I would tell people,
"We're going to wait 50 episodes and then we're going to evaluate the show and see where we're
going to do that in the future." Just two episodes ago, I was talking about five years from now on
the show. Like, this is the growth of the show over the next five to 10 years. Like, I keep
fixing that narrative to go farther and farther into the future. I don't want to preach to you guys.
But I think this works. And I think this can work for everybody. And the beauty of it is, it's free.
There's no seminar you have to go to. There's no book you have to buy. I will say this, all the
information I've given you on Hypersidials is kind of all the stuff that I found. There is this quote
and this is a quote from Grant Morrison. This is how he defined Hypersidials.
The Hypersidial or SuperSidual develops the sigil concept beyond the static image and incorporates
elements such as characterization, drama, and plot. The Hypersidial is a sigil extended through the
fourth dimension. My own comic book series The Invisibles was a six-year-long sigil in the form
of an occult adventure story which consumed and recreated my life during the period of its
composition and execution. The Hypersidial is an immensely powerful and sometimes dangerous method
for actually altering reality in accordance with intent. Results can be remarkable and shocking.
You don't have to believe me. It sounds completely foolish. I think it works. I've seen it work.
Is it possible? We talked about this with the Despair Code episode too.
You know, you hear stuff like The Secret, which is, I've looked into The Secret. Positive thinking
is definitely good. There is actually an older book from the late 1800s called The Science of
Getting Rich and you think it's a book about like how to do well in business. It's a book about the
metaphysics of gaining property and money and it is fascinating. It's kind of, it predates this
obviously and it's basically that the universe is full of a formless substance and when you think
of becoming wealthy, the universe wants to provide to you that wealth. But you've got to work for it.
It's super bizarre. Basically, the premise of the book is there are no natural limitation on
natural resources. There is no limitation of money. Anyone who wants money can get it. But not just
through hard work, you also have to visualize yourself becoming wealthy. And the William Waddles,
I think, or Wallace Waddles wrote it. It's fascinating because he goes, you're going to have
two hard workers next to each other and one person is rich and one person is poor. You're going to
have two people with the same business. One person is rich, one person is poor. Two houses on the
street, one person is rich, one person is poor. And he's like, if it was strictly because of
socioeconomic factors or strictly because the business you are in, everyone on that street
should be poor, everyone in that business should be poor, or reversely, everyone on the street
should be rich, everyone in that business should be rich. He said the people who are wealthy are
people who already believe that they're wealthy and they act accordingly and the universe recognizes
them living that life and then rewards them with it. It's really bizarre. And it has the guy, the
author was a Christian socialist and it has this weird Christian theme running through it. And
the basically is like, God, the universe, everything wants you to be wealthy because you can't truly
live life if you're poor. That's almost its own episode. But I mean, again, I think that it's
your thoughts dictate your reality. And you go, well, Jason, what about the kid living in the
Sudan? You know, his hypercigill could just be to get a meal the next day. I don't know. I don't
know that they answer that question. The same reason why I can never answer the question like,
why would a God or any higher deity let children die of cancer? I don't know.
But I do think that there is a power to your thought. And if you can create a new reality
around it, just try it. That's what I would say. And again, the beauty of like a system like this,
you know, you're not no one's selling you anything, it just simply exists. I know it works for body
builders. If you talk to any bodybuilder, Arnold Schwarzenegger, any of those guys, they'll say,
I visualized myself being muscular. And that is how I got to this point. Well, let me rephrase
that. They also had to work lift a shit ton of weights. But if you're just lifting weights and
you're not visualizing yourself, you haven't created that story, you're not living that character
as a monster of a human. You're just lifting your weights, there's a disconnect between the
mental and the physical. Imagine your life as a movie, create a plot around your life.
Think of that, focus on that. And see what happens. I could be wrong.
But I think hyper sigils work. And if they do, and we have the ability to reshape our own lives,
you could say, well, Jason, I want to be a superhero, I want to fly around a building,
can I use a hyper sigil for that? I don't know. I don't know, I do have a theory about that,
though, actually. I think that if that was, if you really, really wanted to be a superhero, and you
imagined every day you become a superhero, again, I have no proof of this, but I think that you would
basically create an alternate reality where you are a superhero. You would still live in our reality.
And I wouldn't like if my best friend every day wished he was a superhero, and he created this
hyper sigil where he could fly around. I think, in theory, in my reality, he would still be Joey,
but an alternate reality would open up where he got superpowers. Does that sound insane? Absolutely.
Absolutely. Does this whole thing sound insane? Absolutely. Absolutely. If I'm wrong, I'm wrong.
I'm not, like I said, I'm not selling you anything. And I don't really know. I believe that it works.
Have you seen it work for me? But if I'm wrong, and a bunch of people want to say that was your
dumbest story ever, because you're trying to convince me that if I tell myself a story, it'll
come true, what do you have to lose if you don't do it? Like I said, the only thing you're losing is
time and thought process, which we're going to spend anyways.
I've said this before, I will sit at home and I will imagine getting new listeners to the podcast.
But at the same time, I have to work on my podcast every single day. I think that's part of it too.
I think part of the hyper sigil is you create the life you want in your head. But if the life in
your head is to be a Major League Baseball player, you got to practice. You got to put that work in.
That's kind of what Wallace Waddles was saying too. If I sat around and said I want to be a
super successful podcaster and release an episode once a month, that's not going to work. But
I put in the work to do the podcast. I was up till four in the morning recording stuff yesterday.
And then in my free time, I imagine the future I'm going to have with this podcast.
Hyper sigils. It's on the conspiracy iceberg. And it may be one of the truest things on there,
honestly. We'll find out. Let me know how they work for you. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going
to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. One of my
hyper sigils is not to be invested with ants by the way. I should put that out there. Twitter is
@JasonOCarvander. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast. You
don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]