A cuddly cryptid, a woman washed away returns to the same place she was swept from a year
and a half later, and then we take a look at the terrifying story of Texas' own Candy
Lady.
Was there a woman leaving candy on children's windowsills?
And did her trap work today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
You are listening to the only podcast that will not discuss the Mueller Report this week.
I repeat, the only podcast.
The only podcast.
They are.
You don't have to worry about that at all.
This is your refuge from politics.
Dead Rabbit Radio.
We're gonna go ahead and get started here now.
I kinda cheated in the beginning when I said it was a cuddly cryptid.
Let me go ahead and get started here.
So, I was sent this link the other day.
I'm gonna read this to you, and I want you to see if you- this is such a bizarre description.
I'm gonna read this to you, and I'm gonna see if you can guess the creature we're talking
about.
Its appearance is character- and I'm leaving out a few key details.
Okay, 'cause otherwise it gives it away.
Its appearance is characterized by dark blue hair, a huge mouth devoid of teeth, large
bulging eyes.
His voice is serious and abrupt, and his speech is simplified, using an abundance of infinitives
and emitting other linguistic compliments.
His diet includes muffins, donuts, apples, bananas, lettuce, as well as other inedible
items such as salt and pepper dispensers, traffic signs, towels, pins, typewriters,
telephones, motorcycles, Peabody awards, a truck, a safe, a Volkswagen Beetle, and the
letter of the day.
So that's the description of Cookie Monster.
That's the Spanish Wikipedia description of the Cookie Monster.
Now the English version of Cookie Monster does not have any of this, which I think is absolutely
hilarious.
The English version of Wikipedia is just like, you know who we're talking about.
It's Cookie Monster.
But the Spanish version decides to create this horrifying image of this creature with
no missing all of his teeth and a huge mouth, bulging eyeballs, and I guess those are accurate
descriptions of Cookie Monster, but they're terrifying nonetheless.
The reason why I came across this was because in the previous episode I did about shape-shifting
women who eat men.
I think it was the title, something like that.
It was maybe four or five episodes ago.
I forget very quickly.
I described there as one of the cryptid women, one of the shape-shifters, who was described
as having cookie-like hair.
And I actually had two listeners chime in on that.
Both of them kind of said it's probably a translation error.
On YouTube, Edward...
Edward Baez?
Baez?
Anyways, Edward said maybe they meant like empanadas.
Like it's the hair was flaky.
And then Jimmy emailed me and he said maybe it's like churros.
Like dreadlocks.
I think it is a translation error.
According also to this Spanish Wikipedia page, Cookie Monster's best friend is Gustavo Frog.
That's just weird to me.
I always thought Kermit the Frog was fairly...
I know more about the history of Cookie Monster now than I ever thought I would know.
Definitely more than I ever learned on Sesame Street.
He started off stealing cereal.
His original name was the wheel.
His original name was the Wheeljacker because he stole the wheel-shaped cereal.
And then there he...
His best buddy was a guy named Flute Snatcher.
Now I don't...
Because he ate fruit...
Because he stole flute-shaped cereal?
Now again, those might be translation errors as well.
But that's a little bit about...
Who are we talking about again?
Oh yeah, Cookie Monster.
Cookie Monster.
Also known as Mostro de la Galetes.
So I think that's like Monster of the Cookies or something?
And in Latin America, he simply goes by the name Lucas.
And I guess when Disney bought...
They used to have different names everywhere.
When Disney bought them up, they said, "Nope, it's Kermit the Frog, it's Cookie Monster,
they didn't...
They used to localize everything."
So now if you grew up with Gustavo Frog and Lucas running around, they're like, "Who
is that guy?
Who is the Cookie Monster?"
Om nom nom nom nom.
That might have gone on a little longer than I originally planned.
I don't know, I found that fascinating.
And thanks guys for your explanations of cookie-like hair, they're probably pretty likely.
Now we're gonna go on...
You know, it's actually been a really interesting week.
Conspiracy and weirdness-wise, I got a lot of stories that are fairly recent coming out.
But one of the ones that popped up, like maybe in the past few days, was really bizarre.
And from the first thing you hear, you're like, "That's absolutely impossible."
And then you go, "But...
Weirder things have happened."
And then you keep reading into it and you're like...
Yeah, I don't know.
So we are going back a year.
We're going back to January 2017 and we're traveling to the island of Java, the tastiest
sounding island other than Cupcake Island.
We go to Java Island.
And we're sitting on the beach.
We're enjoying the nice weather.
It's beautiful out.
There's sun, there's hot chicks walking around in bikinis.
And we're just drinking a Mai Tai.
I don't know what they drink there.
We're drinking an alcoholic drink.
We're drinking iced Java with some liquor in it.
We're just hanging out.
And we see this woman with her sister and I think one of their sons.
She was with two other people.
I'm just making up family members.
Oh, it was like her eighth cousin.
Now she was out there with at least her sister.
I know that for sure.
The woman's name is Naining Sunar-sir.
Nairing Sunar-si.
We'll just call her Naining.
That probably pronounced that wrong as well.
But anyways, Naining, she was a 52 year old woman.
She's out on a beach vacation with her sister and an other family member.
Could be anyone in her genealogical tree.
It's her great ancestor.
They're out at the beach.
They're enjoying the fun.
They're enjoying the sun.
The Daily Mail.
And I did read that article, by the way.
Was it Sexy Spice?
But anyway, it doesn't matter.
They banged.
That's the point of that.
So The Daily Mail is a tabloid, but it wasn't just in The Daily Mail.
It's in a lot of paranormal websites.
It's in a lot of like regular news websites, because it's such a bizarre story.
Here's the kicker.
So I started looking into this because I was like, "That's absolutely fascinating, if true."
And it's kind of fascinating if it's not, because it just shows how quickly rumors spread.
So I watched the video.
I didn't understand a word of it.
But I watched the video.
And the video is purported to be her being taken off the beach and taken home.
She's not wearing a yellow dress.
She's wearing a blue top.
So immediately I said, either she was taken somewhere else and they changed her clothes,
or the videos fake.
And it's being attached to this story.
And sure enough, I found when I was continuing to research this, one of the articles said,
"Here's some photos that are being purported to be Ninning, but these are actually photos
of someone being let out of a mental hospital and taken home."
And what's weird is that this footage and these photos are being used in almost every
article, but only one pointed out, people on WhatsApp have identified that those photos
are from a totally different news story in the same area.
So that's not Ninning.
Has nothing to do with this story.
So right off the bat, the video evidence is not true at all.
And then I go, "Okay, well that's a big spoiler."
And now I'm thinking the story's false.
And here's the thing.
To me, this is the detail that stuck out.
I will accept that someone can get swept out to sea and washed away and go into some sort
of magical portal land or something like that and come back.
I don't believe it off hand.
I kind of did this one, but I guess not really, I didn't believe it, but I thought I'm open
to the idea of dimensional portals and stuff like that.
What I thought was weird, so let's say that the story is true.
And she begins giving her dad instructions to come to the beach and find her.
And I guess I should have said this earlier.
She was found at the same location that she had gotten washed away.
That actually was the original story.
But then the story evolved that it wasn't the same spot, it's 500 meters away, whatever.
So if I'm trying to get someone to come to my location, I'm not going to start asking
them to come out two months before I show back magically up in reality.
Because it's very, very likely.
Because she had been coming to her dad in the dreams for a long time.
And then he still had to go out there every day for a couple weeks to find--every day for
a couple weeks.
At any point, he could have just been like, "Ah, I'm having these nightmares."
Here's a pro tip.
Whenever a ghost or trapped in a magical realm and you need to send a message, don't send
the message too early.
Because then they're going to go out, get discouraged, and go back, or people are going
to start thinking they're crazy.
Send them the night before you leave Oz or whatever.
So I thought that was a weird detail too, the dad going out there every single day looking
for her.
They could have said he had the dream and then it was so vivid that he went out the next
morning and she was there.
That would be a little more believable.
But really, I think at this point, none of it's believable.
I would be surprised if Nainin actually exists at all.
Oh, and here's another thing.
This was something weird.
She's 52 years old.
How old's her dad?
In his 70s?
He would be in his really--he would be in his late 60s minimum if she's 52.
And she had a sister, so yeah, he was probably like, if she's 52 or 53, whatever, he would
have had to--I look back over at my notes--if he would have to be, let's say he had the
kids when he was like 20.
So he's like, and you have this old--you're harassing this old man.
You're trapped in another dimension and your ghost keeps waking up a 70-year-old man saying,
go to the beach today.
Go to the beach today.
And he's like, oh, my arthritis.
And she's like, I don't care.
So that detail was kind of weird too, that she was so old.
But I'm thinking that they may have made her that old to match the photos in the video
that was going to be attached to the story.
Weird, weird story.
Don't think it's true, but there's definitely either someone concocted it on purpose to
play some sort of prank, or it was just a--or I wouldn't be surprised to find out if this
is--legends have been going around for a long time in that area.
This story and it's constantly being updated every 10, 15 years, and this time it actually
just went viral, which is a possibility as well.
But that is actually a good segue to our last segment, because we're going to talk about,
again, another urban legend that it kind of--it stands in the same categories as this one
where we don't know whether or not it's real, but far, far more sinister.
Far more sinister.
The year--well, the decade?
The early 1900s.
The place, Texas.
Somewhere in Texas.
The year in the 1900s.
The location someplace in Texas.
The biggest state.
Oh, that's the second biggest state, but a giant state somewhere in there.
There's a little kid sitting in his room.
It's nighttime.
He doesn't have comic books or video games or anything.
He's probably just looking at wood carvings of Spider-Man.
Has a little candle under his bedsheet to read.
House goes up in flames.
But then they move to another house and this little kid sitting in bed, no candles this
time.
And he hears a noise at his window sill.
And he sees a shape kind of move away in the darkness.
The little boy opens the window and out on the sill are little pieces of old-timey candy.
To him, new candy.
He's like, "Mmm, sass, spirula.
Mmm, molasses-flavored jolly ranchers."
And he begins to eat the candy.
And he notices in one of the wrappers.
And it's so funny, I'm talking like he's delicate.
He's probably like, "Gah, gah, gah, gah, gah."
Cookie monstering that.
He was lucasin it.
The next day after his sugar coma wears off, he notices one of the wrappers has a message
on the inside of it.
And it says, "Come play with me."
And it's signed, "The Candy Lady."
So the Candy Lady story, what we know about the Candy Lady is this.
There was a woman named Clara Crane.
And she was born in 1853.
She was born in 1853.
She was married to a drunk man.
He was a farmer.
And one day he was out drinking and running the farm stuff.
And their daughter was out there as well.
And due to his alcohol-induced negligence, the daughter is killed in an unspecified
way.
The mom is just completely just toast over this.
Her mom can't believe, Clara Crane can't believe that her husband killed the daughter,
even if it was an accident.
She then poisons some candy and gives it to him.
And he's like, "Mmm, sasperilla, my favorite.
Ah, ah."
And dies.
She is arrested, but she's found insane.
So she is put into the North Texas Insane Asylum.
And it is there where her man is truly shows, I mean not just killing her husband.
She makes a new daughter.
She makes a new daughter out of a bedsheet.
So she takes a bedsheet and she rips it up and binds it together.
And now she has like a Blair Witch, like effigy, style daughter.
But she carries around the hospital with her.
And she talks to it like it's her daughter.
And I don't understand the, like did she feed it?
Was it all like completely, was it all like covered in gross pea soup as she's trying
to feed her daughter?
Like, but I guess insanity is insanity.
And she probably imagines it's eating the pea soup, but in reality everyone else is
like, "Can you wash your daughter?"
She's like, "I bathe her every day."
They're like, "No, wash your machine, please."
But anyways, due to overcrowding, there's talk about letting Clara Crane go because
she's such a nice woman.
The doctors are like, "Yeah, she's pretty cool."
I mean, other than that disgusting creature, that disgusting golem she's created that she
carries around and tells everyone it's her daughter.
Other than that, she's trying to get it to date other bedsheets in the hospital.
She's like introducing it, takes it down to the laundromat and she's like, "You are the
queen of the ball, my daughter."
She ends up writing a letter to her sister, Aggie, which is a great name.
This is the letter that was written, "Dearest Aggie, I am elated.
I have been informed by Dr. Matthews."
I almost read that as Dr. Mattress.
"I've been informed by Dr. Matthews that Marcy and I," Marcy's the bedsheet baby, "that
Marcy and I will be returning home in less than three weeks."
As you can imagine, Marcy can barely contain her excitement.
Every night she asks, "Is tomorrow the day we go home, mother?"
Very soon I will be able to tell her, "Yes."
The idea of the talking bedsheet is bizarre.
Like if someone was actually carrying around a bedsheet baby, that's weird enough.
But then to imagine it's having conversations with her, because in conversations with the
kid, I mean, does the mattress go, "Why is the sun in the sky?"
Well, because it is.
Why?
Well, that's where God put it.
Well, I mean, kids can be quite annoying.
So I guess if you had a mattress baby, it would actually be a little better than a real
kid because then it wouldn't keep annoying you.
But anyways, Marcy, the bedsheet, and Clara Crane do get let out of the North Texas insane
asylum.
And then about five years after that, kids go missing.
So let's go back to the herb and the legend part of this.
This has an interesting wrap up.
So in this town, apparently in her hometown, her unnamed hometown in Texas, children started
getting candy put up on their window sills.
And a kid goes missing.
And the cops are baffled.
Again, we're back in the 1900s here.
The cops are baffled as to what happened to this kid.
He snuck out in the middle of the night.
Couple weeks later, another kid goes missing.
And now the cops are really, really concerned about what's going on.
And it is then that the parents learn about candy being left on window sills.
Kids had been eating it and not telling their parents because they're not supposed to eat
candy.
They're not supposed to eat candies from strangers.
And more importantly, they're not supposed to eat in bed.
But they did all three of those things.
So parents started to warn their kids, do not eat candy on your window sills.
Don't do it.
You're going to get snatched by the candy lady.
This all came to a head when a boy who was previously found missing, there was a farmer
or a rancher or somebody was walking along a goalie.
They found the body of a 10-year-old boy with his eyeballs gouged out and his pockets full
of candy.
Now the interesting thing about this story, every piece of evidence that makes you think
it has proof seems to be fake.
But you don't know.
And there's basically two separate stories here.
So let's look at the story of Clara Crane first, because that's the one that has the
most specific stuff.
Clara Crane in Texas, as far as I could find, on Ancestry.com there was a Clara Crane in
Texas, but she was born five years before her mother.
So the story of her being born in 1853, or however the word, I might have misstated it
earlier in 1953, but she was supposedly born in 1853, or in that time period, the only
person listed having a daughter named Clara Crane was born after that.
There used to be a place called North Texas Insane Asylum, so that place did exist.
And there was a short news article about Clara Crane being sentenced to prison for the murder
of her husband, but the article is not sourced, it doesn't say what newspaper it comes from,
it's like a blurry scan of a presumable newspaper article.
So it could be fake, we don't have a way to track that back.
In the story of Clara Crane, it does not list where she's from, it's just a small town
in Texas that takes place in Texas.
We have a newspaper article that specifies, she was 28 years old, this happened in Ellis
County and she was tried at the Hattuck Street Courthouse, so we get more details from the
article.
So that makes me think that the story of Clara Crane existed before the story that people
tell their kids about, "Ooh, watch out, she could get you," but you end up being on the
far, far north of Texas, that's left vague for a purpose.
The article that's being purported to be true specifies this was in Ellis County.
So the fact there's a discrepancy between the two makes me think that either this, Clara
Crane actually did exist and the details have kind of been wiped clean to make the story
more universal, or someone came up with the legend of Clara Crane and then someone faked
the evidence and when they were faking it, they're like, "They just can't put in the
news article somewhere in Texas that this court happened, whoever created this article
had to give more detail."
Chicken or egg, chicken or egg, we don't know.
But like I said, the person who's supposedly Clara Crane, I could only find one on Ancestry.com,
but that doesn't really mean anything because not everyone's listed in Ancestry.com, so
I'm back to square one.
Is it square one?
Or is it square, yeah, I'm back to square one, I'm back to the beginning of the board
game, that's where that saying comes from, Jason, don't be an idiot.
So I think that's where that saying comes from, but anyways, did Clara Crane exist?
We don't know.
It's super bizarre.
It's such an unknown urban legend conspiracy theory, I think outside of Texas, that not
a lot of people have delved into it.
I've found a lot of resources on it, and a few of them were very like, tried to dig
into it, but since there's not a lot of information to go on, it's rough.
So then let's jump, so did Clara Crane exist?
Who knows, this woman may have actually existed at some point, but did she make a bedsheet,
baby?
And the right letters to her sister, we don't know.
We don't have any of that information.
And then let's go to the crimes, missing children in Texas, possibly Ellis County, Texas.
Kids going missing, candy being left on windowsills, a young boy found with his eyes gouged out
in his pockets full of candy.
Did those incidents happen?
Again.
As of now, we don't have any proof of any of this stuff.
The crimes are at this point over a hundred years old.
It is quite possible that this urban legend came out of something.
Either Clara Crane is true, and they created the story of the Candy Lady as a warning towards
kids, you know, don't take candy from strangers is really the point of the story.
Or the Candy Lady crimes are true that three kids went missing when one was found dead with
candy in its pockets.
And the Clara Crane story was a retcon to kind of give this madness some sort of face
to it.
Or most chilling that both parts are true.
Both parts are true.
There was a Clara Crane that was sent to North Texas.
It was actually North Texas lunatic asylum, whether that part of the story is true.
And then later back in Ellis County, kids went missing with candy on their windowsills.
There's been a lot of stories we've covered on this show that are only like four or five
years old that are completely horrific.
Like the guy who held up, who did the school shooting and the sexual assault at the same
time.
That's been pretty much a race from the social consciousness.
We have the speargun murder story that's been erased from the social consciousness.
So there are stories even recently that you think, man, how can people forget about this?
And when we're going back a hundred years, it's very likely, or I should say it's possible,
that these series of incidents played out.
The idea of not taking candy from strangers is something that I think most parents, if
not all parents, really worldwide instill in their kids.
What's interesting is that if this case is real, this may have been the origin of that
saying, don't take candy from strangers.
It's weird to think that the phrase, don't take candy from strangers is used so commonly.
It's like a trope.
You can have a television show called Strangers with Candy.
Like it's, you get it.
You get that saying.
Basically, it's ingrained in our consciousness.
And the crazy thing is, is that saying may be based on a real set of disappearance and
murders.
That saying we all use could have started in a little county in Texas.
When a boy unwrapped a piece of candy, it said, come play with me.
He crawled out the window to the dark shape standing in the field.
And that was the last thing he saw before his eyes were cut out.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
There is @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]