An alien reptilian creature is spotted on the side of a road and it stirred up some interesting emotions in me.
And then we take a look at some haunted hitchhiking roads in California.
Yes, yes, it's an interactive adventure. Yes, yes, it's from Backpackerverse, but some of these stories creepily enough are true today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We've got a lot of stuff to cover so we're just gonna go ahead and get started.
Or two, this is our second episode of Alien Week. I said in the last episode I know each episode will have a story that since chills down your spine and then I talk about Trump saying aliens don't exist.
And I was like, I didn't really think that one out. This one doesn't send chills down your spine. It had a very curious effect on me though, very curious effect on me.
So in 2015, the year 2015, on December 6th, a 63 year old man, I've never been jealous of a 63 year old man before, but a 63 year old man is driving through the back streets or like around Oklahoma City.
It's 430 in the morning, he's driving around. Now if you want to go here, you may know the area because I want to go here.
He's driving down Southwest 29th Street and he's driving through 430 in the morning and he's on his way to work.
And he sees a bean, some sort of figure, jump up on the side of the road, out of like a culvert.
So there's like a little ditch that has water that goes through a little tunnel under a road. I had to look up what a culvert was.
So I'm telling you, if you don't know, I had to look it up. Anyways, he jumps up out of a culvert, or she, or it, we're going to say she,
she jumps up out of a culvert and she stands there for about 60 seconds looking at this man as he's driving his car.
And he's freaking out because he sees this thing. This is how he describes it.
It had large eyes and small pointed ears. Its eyes were orange with no glow when the headlights hit them.
It had a small mouth with a nose similar to a cat. It had three toes curled over the edge of the curb with heels like a human.
Extremely large thighs that matched the base of its tail. Its tail was extremely long with the huge base tapering down to no bigger than a matchstick.
He said it was about three feet tall and its skin, it was a reptilian looking, even though that sounds fairly feline.
He got the idea that it was a reptilian looking because it had like scales, had like lizard skin, but it was like a creamy white, almost iridescent skin,
pearl you could say. And it's looking at him and he takes all this in in a brief moment.
And he said it looks like he was trying to figure out if it could cross the road before I hit it with my car. And all of a sudden it darted off and jumped into the other side of the road.
He said that this thing appeared to be very intelligent, very intelligent creature.
Now you're thinking, okay Jason, reptilian maybe, you know, kangaroo escaped from the zoo that also has scales and stuff like that.
But reptilian, reptilian creature, you're not a huge fan of reptilians. You're always poo pooing over all the humanoid reptilian.
That's true. That's true. Until I saw a picture of this thing.
Now before you get excited, it's not a photograph, but he drew, somebody drew, a drawing of what he saw.
I fell in love. I fell in love with a reptile.
This thing, it's a girl. It's a girl, creamy white skin, iridescent scales that shine underneath the headlights.
Thick thighs. These thighs are three times thicker than the rest of its body.
Let's get it on. Let's get it on, reptilian girl, because okay, here's the thing.
I don't like reptilians. I don't even really like reptiles, but this thing man has a little cat face, little like pearl colored scales.
And before you think I'm into like some creepy stuff, he said it was intelligent, so that means it can consent.
It's not bestiality. This thing is like smart and why can't it talk and figure out whether or not it can cross it.
That's not true. Dogs get hit by cars all the time. This thing, he said, seemed extremely intelligent.
You would never say that about an animal, so you know you can have a conversation with her to go out to dinner, you know, talk to her for a bit.
This thing, I am now coining the term kilf. Cryptid I'd like to have sexual relations with. It's a kilf.
This thing is hot dude. You know me man, I like thick thighs dude. I like you know, and like it's all fit.
It's like can run across the, it's like thick, but it can like run across streets before cars hit it.
Dude, and I know you're thinking Jason, you're just doing a bit. I want you to go, I know you're like Jason, listen to me podcasting my car.
I can't keep clicking on links. When you're at home, by yourself, you have some private time.
Click on the link below. Look at the photo of this kilf and tell me you don't want to cuddle up next to it.
Now I have to admit, three feet is way too short. That's not something that I'm into other than the height thing, which I can overlook because everything else is so, I mean, if it was a dude, I guess that's a deal breaker too.
But even the way it's drawn looks like a chick. So creamy reptilian woman, hop on over to Hood River. I'll show you a good time.
I'll take you to my leader. So anyways, let's go ahead and move on. That's our alien story for today. So that didn't send chills down your spine. It sent chills up mine.
Okay, so now you're thinking Jason, your alien week is not off to your good start. Trust me, I like those stories, but if you're looking for spooky alien stories, next three days are quite chilling.
You're like Jason, you already said that yesterday, and you talked about Trump and UFOs. And now you're talking about banging an alien that might not even be an alien. It could be an escaped kangaroo.
Anyways, it's intelligent. It can consent, right? Extremely intelligent. Extremely intelligent. Anyways, let's go ahead and move fast my kilf story. Let's move on to Backpackerverse.
Now, Backpackerverse, quick introduction, is a website that is notorious for just making stuff up out of whole cloth, which is quite entertaining in and of itself.
And the comments are always hilarious because people go, "That place is haunted." I don't even know why they have comments on their page because people are always like disputing the fact that places are haunted.
But I had such a good time covering them. And this one, some of the stories are actually true. Shocking, aren't they? Shocking. And we'll cover those as well.
But first, I want you to pick a number between one and five. Okay, you got it? Okay, remember that number.
Now, we're going to go ahead and hop in the Jason Jalopy. We're going to go for a ride. Now, as far as the story is concerned, I'm simply, I'm the AI. I'm the kit. I'm the little whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
That's a dated reference. And it, kit, I'm not going to explain who kit is. I'm a talking car. I'm the Jason Jalopy because I'm not picking a number. I'm not getting trapped in any of these hellish experiences.
So, first off, we're going to Proctor Valley in San Diego County. So, you're driving me, this is going to get weird. I'm the car, you're driving me around. It's 1 AM. The moon is out and everything's spooky.
Fog drifting across the road. A coyote in the distance. That's a wolf. Wait, no, it's a coyote. Coyote's a wolf, right? Kind of, their dog.
Anyways, there's, you hear, you hear a canine type howling out in the field. And you see a young woman walking down the street holding her thumb out.
A couple of pornoes started off like this. Quite a few horror movies as well. Pick your poison. So, you don't know. It's 50/50, really. Actually, it's like 90/10. 90% you're going to get murdered.
You pull over and you pick up this young woman and she gets into your car. If you pick up a hitchhiker, you put them in the back seat. I picked up hitchhikers. Well, technically, they weren't hitchhikers.
There was this mother and her son or his grandma and her son whose car broke down and I gave them a ride to a grocery store. And when I say son, the dude was in his 20s.
I think the mom said in the front seat, but yeah, I don't know the hitchhiker etiquette. Once I was driving down the road, I used to look like such a, like, I had a big, puffy beard and totally wild hair.
And I was driving around my, I think it was the Ford Mustang and I was full of garbage. I'm driving down Rio Linda, out in Rio Linda, out by Sacramento.
I was driving down the road and I looked like just like a serial killer and no joke. I was driving down Rio Linda, through Rio Linda and I see a hitchhiker on the road in front of me and he has his thumb out.
And he sees me driving and when he gets going to look at me, he puts his hands in his pocket. I was too scuzzy looking for a hitchhiker to get in my car.
But anyway, so, where were we going? Oh yeah, so you picked this woman up. You're like Jason, just tell the damn ghost stories. You pick this woman up, she gets into your, let's say your front seat, because she's an attractive young woman.
And she turns to you and she goes, "Thank you for the ride." And you're like, "Hey, no problem. Where are you headed?" And she goes, "That depends."
"Did you pick number five?" And you go, "Yeah, I picked number five."
So, according to Backpackerverse, the legend of Proctor Valley Road is this, that one day there were these two college boys, they were driving down Proctor Valley Road, and they see the hitchhiker of a young woman and they pick her up.
And they go missing. They go missing for four days.
Friends, family, police are searching the area, can't find them. On the fifth day, one of the college boys appears on the side of the road and he was bawling his eyes out.
And when the authorities get there, they go, "What happened? What happened?" And he said, "It wasn't me who did it. It wasn't me who did it. It wasn't me who did it."
Just catatonic, crazy. The other friend was never found. And the legend goes that a young woman was raped and murdered on this road, and her spirit is now hunting other men who drive down Proctor Valley Road.
Which would make sense why he's saying like this, the implication is that they were obviously taking some sort of hellscape universe, and she was punishing them for her own rape and murder, and he's like, "I didn't do it. I didn't do it. I didn't do it."
Now, there's no proof of any of that happening. I did look up Proctor Valley Road, though, and it is known to be haunted. It's known to be plagued by something. This is what I don't understand about Backpackerverse.
So that story, it's a creepy ghost story, like giving credit. That's a creepy ghost story you would tell your babysitter before you left her alone with your kids.
Proctor Valley does have this thing known as the Proctor Valley Monster, and it is actually like, some people have compared it to Bigfoot, some people have compared it to a deranged cow.
It's a fairly well-known monster in the area, but there's no story of this hitchhiking ghost. However, if you pick number five, you disappear. No one ever finds you again, and you are forever tormented in a hellish dark dimension by a hitchhiker who believes all men are responsible for her crime.
That got a little topical there real quick. But anyways, let's navigate, let's go away from that subject.
And let's go on to Hicks Road in San Jose. Now, Hicks Road in San Jose, it's 2 a.m. It's dark and foreboding. You don't know what you're doing out this late. You don't know why you're driving a car that sounds exactly like a podcast host that you listen to.
And you're trying to figure out why he keeps trying to drive to Oklahoma City. You're like, "Dude, why do you keep changing the GPS cord in this Oklahoma City?" But you're driving down Hicks Road.
And you see on the side of the road a very disturbing thing in the middle of the night. You see a young boy holding a baby. Has his thumb out.
Now, all three of those things are creepy. Little boy in the middle of the night, little boy holding a baby, little boy hitchhiker. Those are all creepy things to see in the middle of the night.
Which you're driving by. And you're not an idiot. Like, maybe you do want to stop and pick this kid up with a baby. It would be questionable either way. I threw you a band and a kid.
And you're just a jerk or you let a possible serial killer possess spirit into your car. I guess really, that should kind of show you how I look at life.
If I'm driving down the road and see a kid and a baby, I'm going to assume it's some sort of spirit rather than like people who have just escaped a canapper or trying to flag down help because their parents are having heart attacks at their campsite.
Anyways, you're driving and you see the little boy holding his thumb up and then he holds up his fingers to hold up the number three. You're like, "Oh, that's the number I picked. I picked number three. What a coincidence."
So this comes from a story, according to Backpackerverse, where a young woman, I have to put that in here. Some of them are true.
This woman was driving down Hicks Road and she saw the little boy holding the baby. Now she doesn't stop for him. She decides to keep driving. And she sees in her rearview mirror standing by the side of the road, the boy still holding his thumb up, but now he's glaring at her.
She's like, "That's kind of weird. Why is that kid so pissed off? I didn't pick him up in the middle of the night."
But then the little boy, you'll understand why I'm doing this story, then the little boy is no longer on the side of the road. He's in her backseat of her car and the baby is screaming at an ear piercing level. And he says to her, "He shouldn't have done that."
And the boy and the baby vanish. But for the next two weeks, the woman heard the baby's piercing scream in her ear, no matter where she went, no matter what she did, and eventually she shot herself in the head.
Now, don't feel bad that none of that happened. A woman did not actually kill herself because of that. Although I do have to say that would be something that I think would be easy to trigger someone to kill themselves.
Like, if you had a baby screaming in your head, I don't moms do, but eventually, you know, moms or parents and stuff like that can like, swat the baby to sleep, swaddle the baby to sleep, rock it to sleep, whatever. I don't have a baby.
This would be a constant baby screaming in your ear would drive you mad. But again, it didn't happen so don't feel bad.
But if you pick number three, you drive past that kid and you hear that piercing "weeeeeee" in your ear as you see the little boy in your back seat going, "You shouldn't have done that number three."
You can't avoid the sound. You can't avoid the sound that's driving you mad. But to be fair, number three, I'll give you the out. You can actually pick up the kid.
Let's say that because you might not be as heartless as me and this fictional woman. You pick up the kid and he goes, "Thanks."
And he gets in the back seat of your car and now you've just adopted a ghost kid and a ghost baby.
So the kid isn't crying all the time in your ear, but you do have to pick up extra hours at your job to pay for them to go to ghost school.
So, you know, pick your poison. One of them you're driven insane by the sound of a piercing baby.
The other one you have a 10-year-old and a baby that never age and exist forever and you have to take care of them.
They're playing Ghost Nintendo. Ghosts and Goblins is their favorite game. Ghostbusters gives them nightmares and they listen to the song "Ghost Town" on repeat every day.
So then you just end up killing yourself because of that.
So let's go ahead and now we move on to San Diego Freeway. And this is an alcohol or near alcohol.
You're driving down San Diego Freeway, it's three in the morning, and you see a hitchhiker on the side of the road.
You're like, "That sounds familiar. Just tell us there's a hitchhiker. You don't have to build a scene each time."
You're driving down the freeway. You see a hitchhiker by the side of the road.
It's a teenager with sunken eyes, hollow cheekbones, and moles on his face.
You're like, "Oh, it's kind of weird. Kind of a weird combination."
So anyways, you stop and you pull over to pick them up.
Because you've learned that that's probably better than having a baby scream in your ear.
You pull over, you pick them up, and he's like, "Thank you. You want to play Magic the Gathering with me?"
And you're like, "Oh great. He's one of those teenagers. One of those cool teenagers."
And you're like, "Happy that you picked up a fellow Magic player."
Anyways, you guys talk about Modern Horizons for a while as you're driving home.
And then you realize that where he wants to go is only a few blocks from your house.
You're like, "That's kind of a creepy coincidence."
He gets out of the car, and then as he's walking away, he turns to you and he goes,
"Hey, what number did you pick?"
And you go, "Pick number one."
That's what I thought, man. You look like a number one.
But it's not me. He just walks away.
And the next day, you wake up and your pet is killed. Whatever pet it is.
Even if you have like a pet, Instructable Rhino, it's killed.
And written in blood next to your pet, it says, "I'm done for now."
Now to be fair, that's fairly tame. You didn't get sucked into a hellish landscape.
You're not tormented by a baby or have to raise two ghost kids that aren't your own.
But this was the story that was told by Backpackerverse, that a woman picked up this creepy kid
that he was dropped off... His house was a few streets over from her house,
and the next day her cat was cut open.
Now, this story does actually have some truth behind it.
Not the ghost part. The real part, which is actually far more terrifying.
On San Diego Freeway, in El Cajon, near El Cajon, 1958, it's November,
there's a guy driving home, his name is... This is 100% true.
This guy's driving home, his name is Thomas Pindergast.
He sees a teenage boy walking down the freeway.
This is what's so funny. This story is far more terrifying than, "I woke up and my cat was killed."
Anyways, he picks up the teenager. The teenager's name was Carl Alfred Eater.
So again, whenever there's three names, serial killer.
He takes the kid home and feels bad for the kid, talking to him for a bit,
feels bad about his circumstances, and says, "You can stay with my family for a while."
One month later, Thomas comes home from work, and his family of five, wife, four kids, murdered.
Carl gets caught a couple days later, and he says, "What happened was the first murder was on accident."
As will happen, the first murder, this kid was making too much noise.
He was crying. That's weird. I didn't make that connection before.
The first one was an accident, it was a little kid who was crying too much.
He ended up killing him on accident, he says.
Then the mom says, "Call the doctor, call the doctor."
Then he turns around and shoots the mom.
Then he cut the throats of two of the kids, and then two of the older kids are at school,
and he waited at the house for them to come home.
When they walked through the door, he slit their throats as well, and then ran, and they caught him two days later.
He ended up going to prison. He was found guilty for multiple murders.
And because it was in California, and the story took place in the 50s and the 60s,
they put him in a minimum security prison, and one day he just walked away.
And they've never seen him since.
So, sleep tight, residents of El Cajon.
They think the guy is still out there, he would be in about his 70s, and that's where this ghost story comes from.
That is far more to--oh, your cat's chopped up. Come on, man.
Really? You just had a guy get sucked into a rape dimension.
If you're not gonna make stuff up, just make stuff up.
Cat. Come on.
This is based on a real thing, and that's the best you could come up with.
A woman wakes up, or a cat's dead.
So, we've had the ghost of a murdered rape victim.
Then we have the two-for-one ghost of the boy and his little baby.
I wonder if it was his baby. That's actually quite terrifying.
And then we just had a ghost based on the true story of Carl Alfred Eater.
So what's next for us, Jason? What's next?
So, here we go. We're driving down Highway 101 in Prune, Dale.
And as we're driving down the road, it's four in the morning, we see a billboard that says, "Are you scared yet?"
"You will be bobsboards.com."
And you're like, "What's that? That's weird."
And that is something we're gonna talk about tomorrow, because it is a definitely weird story.
And I found it when I was researching whether or not these roads are actually haunted.
So, it's a little teaser for tomorrow, bobsboards.com.
But, we passed the board, we passed the teaser for tomorrow's episode.
We're driving down the road.
Now, it says here that I'm gonna read this quote exactly from...
from Backpackerverse. I'm gonna read this quote.
This is from a website. It's like 10 hitchhikers, 10 haunted hitchhikers in California.
I'm obviously cutting out a bunch of them, but this one was just bizarre.
Think about what we've dealt with before.
Now we have, here's this quote.
"Highway 101 has been a hotspot for accidents for several years now."
While some attribute these...
Well, while some attribute these to reckless drivers, several...
Several claim a...
We've dealt with murdered rape ghosts and these hellish freaks and serial killers.
This one says...
Just a black dude. Not a shadow person. Not a...
Not a phantom, phantom with a hat. Just a black dude.
Just a black dude is their villain in this story.
Just a random black guy.
Several claim a black man caused them to lose control of their vehicles.
Like, what is up with... Okay, so anyways.
So, this one actually is kind of hard because the story itself is so funny
that it's hard to slot you into it, but I'll have to do it.
I'll have to do it somehow, because I want to tell Backpacker vs. Actual Version of these events.
In 2009, a woman, so in this one if you pick this number you're a woman,
in 2009 a woman was driving down Highway 101 and she saw a black man hitchhiking
and she doesn't pick him up. She ignores him.
One mile down, she sees what's described as the body of a "large man" hanging from a tree.
Now, what's funny is Backpacker vs. does never specifically say
if the black dude who's hitchhiking is the same black guy hanging from the tree.
They never describe the black guy as large, and they never describe the large man as black.
I feel like the implication is it's the same guy, but I don't think they want to go that far with their made-up story.
I don't want them... I don't think they want to, like, remind us of horrible lynchings to have this stupid website.
So, I don't even know why they're even going this far.
There was... I looked it up. I couldn't find any proof of this.
People do say they do have that Bob's board on there and we'll get to that in another episode,
but I think it's so funny because they want to build up this legend, but they never specifically want to say
she saw a black man hanging from a tree because they look... that's just so gruesome.
So, she sees a, quote, "a large man hanging from a tree." We don't know what his ethnicity is.
She gets out of the car when she sees the body hanging from the tree.
Now, I wouldn't... I've already passed up a kid and a baby.
If I saw a man hanging from a tree, I'm going to assume it's too late to do anything.
I would just drive to the nearest town or I forgot.
In 2019, I'll pull out my cell phone and call the police. I'm not going to get out. He's hanging.
Anyways, she gets out of the car and the rope snaps and the body falls to the ground.
The large body falls to the ground and she runs over but she sees no body there. It doesn't exist.
At that point, she turns around and she sees the black man standing behind her and she says...
She sees the same black man as in "The Hitchhiker." Not the large man.
She sees the same black man with red eyes shining bright and a wicked smile on his mouth.
And he says, "Miss, I need a ride." And the story just ends.
What happens after that? The woman obviously escaped the scenario because she's able to tell it.
Did she go to the cops and she goes, "Yeah." And then I turn around and the black guy and they're like,
"Wait, wait, wait. The cops are like, "Wait, was the black guy the same guy hanging from the tree?"
The woman's like, "Listen, I really don't want to get into the details of it."
But I turn around and the black guy said, "Miss, I need a ride."
The cops are looking at her and they're like, "And then what happened?" And she goes,
"Well, I mean, that's the end of the story." And they're like, "Yeah, but I mean, did he disappear?
Did he turn into a puff of smoke?" She's like, "No, that's just how the story ends."
You got back in your car, right? You came here right, yeah.
Well, then what happened after he said, "Miss, I need a ride." And you getting into your car?
What happened? It's just nothing. Like, I don't understand how the story just ends like that.
But you might. Because if you picked number two, you picked number two, you turn around
and the man looks at you and goes, "Miss and/or, mister, I need a ride."
And then you just give him a ride. You just give him a ride to a local town.
He gets out. He goes to a jazz festival. Has a good time.
So I guess that's probably your best bet is if you picked this dude up.
They come to the jazz festival. It's all good. You guys have a good time together.
That's probably the best ending you're going to get because now we're going to Old Stage Road.
We're going to wrap it up with Old Stage Road. This is in Salinas. It's five in the morning.
Sun is starting to crest. It's not as dark as all the other creepy stories.
But in this story, you have a family. So I don't know if you have a family real life,
but in this story, you do. But you're a single person.
So you get you and your three kids. You're driving through Old Stage Road.
And you see a man smoke a cigarette on the side of the road hitchhiking.
They're like, "Oh, pick him up. Pick him up."
I mean, this is another weird one. So you don't have a choice.
You've got to pick this person up. Oh, and you're number four, by the way,
because that's the only number left. So sorry.
You pick number four and you have no control over the rest of the story.
You're driving. You pick up a smoking hitchhiker to put into your car with your kids.
You're driving down the road and you're having a conversation.
You're like, "Hey, man, what's up? Have you played Magic the Other End?"
And the guy's like, "No, that's for nerds, dude."
You're like, "Oh, sorry. You're putting away your commander deck."
You were hoping to play a game in the car. The car's swarming everywhere.
He looks at you now. He's like, "What a nerd."
And so your kids are coughing. Your kids are like, "Coughing from the smoke."
And you're like, "Hey, man, can you roll down your window?"
Sure, and he rolls down his window, but just more he's smoking.
Now he's smoking even more aggressively because all of the smoke's gone out of the car.
He likes to hotbox himself. Smoking even harder.
Kids are like, "Dad or mom, please."
At that point, you're confused because you don't know if you're a dad or a mom.
This is a really weird dimensional portal you've fallen into.
But your kids are complaining. This guy's smoking a ton of cigarettes in your car.
And eventually you're like, "Hey, dude, can you get out of my car?
Look at my kids are complaining about all the cigarette smoke."
And the dude doesn't get out of the car.
Now, if you think this sounds really random, this is supposedly a story that happened
to a woman who had a bunch of kids in the car. She picked up a smoking hitchhiker.
So if it seems like I'm just making up random stuff, this supposedly actually happened.
But anyways, eventually you are able to convince the smoker to get out of your car.
Which the whole thing is, is why would you pick up a smoking hitchhiker with a bunch of kids?
With a bunch of-- Why would you pick up a hitchhiker with your kids in your car?
I'm thinking when I'm reading it, she was hoping-- Like, back before Tinder,
she was hoping to get some strange. Like, she was hoping that she was going to pick up this handsome--
I don't know if he was handsome, she could have been desperate.
She was hoping to pick up this dude and he wanted to smoke so much
they would have went home and had sex while the kids were playing, I don't know, Rubik's Cube or whatever.
So, but that's not what happened. And that's not what's going to happen with you either.
You kick out the dude and then you're like, "Wasn't that rude?"
And the kids are like, "It was rude you picked up a smoking hitchhiker in the first place, they're all mad at you."
"They're close, smell like smoke now, they're not going to have a good day."
But you take them home and everyone goes to bed.
And you're laying in bed and you're like, "Hmm, I wonder what it would have felt like to be with a hitchhiker for just one night."
"Wonder what his smoked filled kisses would have tasted like."
And as you start to drift off to sleep, you hear your fire alarm go off
and you wake up and there's huge fire in the house
and only you and your youngest kids survive, the other two, die in the fire.
Which is, that's quite grim. Much better than just being told I need a ride to a jazz festival.
So if you pick number four, you've lost two members of your fictional family that never existed.
You're like, "But in this reality they did, I'm so confused."
Anyways, the story goes that the next day the firefighters were like, "We found what caused the source of the fire."
And they hold, they show the woman, they show you a cigarette butt.
And the implication is the guy like, "Showed up at your house."
That's not even really a ghost story. That's just a dude that you piss off, kicking out of your car,
going to your house and flicking a cigarette into your house and killing everybody.
But I think the implication was he was some sort of ghost and it was a ghost cigarette, I'm not for sure.
But if you pick number four, I will send wreaths for your fictional kids who died these fictional deaths on this very real road.
And what's funny is that this road actually is known to be haunted to the point that Zach Baggins and the ghost adventurers crew
went to Old Stage Road and did like an investigation there.
But let's wrap it up with this. I think it's kind of no one not to pick up hitchhikers.
I think it's kind of no one not to hitchhike.
It's probably one of the most dangerous things you can do on the road other than drink and a driving.
I have no statistics to back that up, but it sounds awfully dangerous.
We know it's dangerous because how dangerous humans can be towards each other.
But when you add in the paranormal, when you add in a world of demons and vengeful spirits and malicious poltergeists
also populating the side of the road, also looking for a ride,
you have to ask yourself, how daring do you want to be?
How trusting do you want to be?
Because you never know if you're picking up a person or a thing.
And you never know if you're giving them a ride to their home or to yours.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great day guys.
[Music]