A man is found crucified in South Korea. Is it murder or suicide? And does the all
seeing eye on the back of the dollar bill really is it really a butthole today
on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your
host Jason Carpenter. Hope you're having a great day. I'm having a great day. It's
107. I think this might be a record for Hood River. It says on my phone it only
feels like 101 so I guess that's some sort of solace but I disagree. I don't
know if it necessarily feels like 107 but we're just a little more humid up here
than you know other places I've been in that been this hot. What's up with this
heatwave? It's driving me nuts. The only good thing I like about the heatwaves means
we're going to have a very mild winter and I hate the snow so I'm totally fine
with there being a mild winter. I'm totally good with that. So last night
the play wrapped up. I've talked about being in it before. We just got done with
another play we're doing Spoon River Anthology. It's actually kind of
interesting. I might go back and read it. Oh I mean yeah I see I technically when
I'm doing a play I don't pay attention to anything else anyone's doing on stage
unless it relates directly to me and my character. Just kind of a little method I
have. Also cuts down on people asking me for advice on how to do stuff because I
just go I don't really pay attention to what you're doing. After the end of the
party I'm I'm known for mixing my drinks and not like in the traditional like a
little martini a little grenadier. Stuff like that I took. So we had Coca-Cola
because I was taking a break on the keto. We had Coca-Cola and we had some wine so
I mixed half Coca-Cola half house red. It was delicious. I'm not a big alcoholic.
Well I'm not a big alcoholic but I'm not a big I don't drink a lot of alcohol I
guess would be a better way to put it. It tastes really good. It tasted like
basically cherry Coke and I was very proud of myself and somebody named it
the woke you know like wine and coke but when I woke up this morning I'm pretty
sure that's I'm pretty sure that's when Michael Jackson was giving to kids
allegedly allegedly he gave them something called Jesus juice which was
wine served in a soda can. So provided that the soda can was completely empty
when he gave them Jesus juice I think I'm in the clear but if you ever come
across some red wine and some Coca-Cola you know one time I mixed I got curious
what would happen if you mixed Coca-Cola and Pepsi in together and it tastes
like RC Cola. It tastes almost identical to RC Cola so I'm wondering if the RC
Cola factory is just like two vats of Coke and Pepsi pouring into individual
bottles I don't know but I you know I was funny I never thought of mixing those
two before I wonder how many people have. Try it try mixing other drinks I I
don't know where I'm going with this I'm just gonna go ahead and jump into the
first story because I think that kind of ran out of steam so a while back we did
food-based conspiracies and that's when we did deep soy and fake cabbage and all
of that and this week I wanted to do another theme one so I've decided to
do sex-based conspiracies conspiracies or paranormal events that have to do
with sex and there's a lot of them actually we have some really good ones
this week the first one we're gonna talk about is an interesting one
apparently let's do a quick overview so the all-seeing eye is the pyramid and
the top has the eyeball it's a very familiar logo if you've ever handled
US currency it's supposed to be the the eye of Providence is what it's known as
people have said you it's a Masonic symbol it's a lot of times it's tied
into the Illuminati and it's just kind of this logo like we're always watching
people have said it's like the eye of Lucifer or you know it has all these
negative connotations especially when it gets tied into the Illuminati actually
you know I've seen kids like little kids hold up their hands like a triangle and
they're like Illuminati I'm in the Illuminati and blah blah blah and they
don't know what they're doing but it's still a little chilling still a little
creepy but anyway so this guy on Reddit of all places this was where I could find
the most information on this conspiracy theory I don't necessarily because I
found other sites that talked about it don't think that he came up with it
himself but he's definitely put it in the most I hate to use the word logical
but the most coherent form of this conspiracy theory so the theory is if
he first off starts off by saying why isn't porn why doesn't porn have the
same copyright hounds that every other industry has like if I posted a video of
Pacific Rim uprising on YouTube I'm gonna get hit with a DMCA notice so it's
basically a takedown notice saying that I've violated copyright however when we
look at porn websites they it's all pirated material and he's specifically
saying they'll use major pop songs in those videos so you'll see a video and
it'll just be a compilation video of cream pies or whatever oh I guess I
should say this is gonna be this week's probably gonna be pretty explicit
episodes they're gonna have explicit tags you might want to wear your headphones
I probably should have said that in the beginning but anyways so I'll keep the
cursing low but the subject matter still still gonna be kind of intense so you
have a Britney Spears song said to a compilation of facials or whatever and
he's saying why isn't the why aren't these videos being taken down by the major
companies and that's a fair point honestly it's a fair point we'll get to
that he then postulates saying that the reason why they don't get taken down by
Hollywood is because Hollywood is part of this Illuminati conspiracy to degrade
humanity to make humans feel less feel more isolated from me from themselves
and to basically make us immoral and then goes on to say how come there's a much
a straight anal porn all of a sudden now if you haven't picked up by now this
guy watches a lot of porn and I'm not just saying that it's some sort of
something I've picked out he actually says that he came to this theory quoting
him it was something that just came out at me in a flash in a matter of
speaking while I was watching a girl get plowed from behind by a BBC so he's
watching a ton of porn and coming up with these conspiracy theories he's
saying why is straight porn so anal specific nowadays why is there so much
of it and his reasoning is that the Illuminati and the Freemasons and they're
kind of one in the same and in his view they want to break down humanity and
make us debase and immoral people and the whole idea of the Freemasons is to mock
religion to mock God and his kind of overall point is if you if the pyramid
if the all-C and I is supposed to be a replacement for God it's supposed to be
a parody of religious symbols then maybe the pyramid is a parody of itself
meaning that it's not a pyramid it's actually a it's the backside of a vagina
between the legs with the anus perched atop as the eye of providence and those
are his exact words so basically we're not looking at the all-C and I we're
looking at this butthole now I know you're thinking Jason this is just one
lunatic online why are you why are you doing a segment on this guy well what
was funny is not it's not just him there's other people who believe this
stuff so this other article they're talking about something called AN this
is talking about like Egyptian mythology Egyptian iconography and they go into
say that the AN represents the anus which is obviously associated with
darkness things done in darkness and the darkness in the bowels of office sorry
and the darkness in the bowels of the orifice of perjait purgation
purgation so this isn't just this guy like there are people are making this
connection that the all-C and I is actually supposed to be I have to say
I've looked at a lot of buttholes today researching these articles there's a
lot of pictures of buttholes so all the links are going to be non-safe for work
the thing is is like I know what a butthole looks like you don't have to
do put a close-up picture of it on your website if you're trying to convince me
that first off it makes me less likely of your argument because there's
nothing that looks less than a human eye than a butthole the only thing they
have in common is they're both circles that's ridiculous but you're gonna look
at a lot of buttholes if you click on the links I probably should sit down in
the beginning too so is the all-C and I representative of the human butthole now
he goes on the the guy who wrote the reddit article he starts connecting this
more saying that you know the Freemasons have connections to North Norse
mythology and that Odin is often seen carrying a giant dildo around which I
missed that in the Thor movies but Odin is represented in carrying a giant dildo
around that he penetrates himself with and and you thought it stopped there no
witches and broomsticks the broomsticks were dildos they weren't like broomsticks
they flow around on they're dildos they masturbated with as they thought of
Satan and little known fact the Nazis have taken over the planet since
September 11 2001 and they are using the power of the butthole to control us all
all of that stuff according to this guy is absolutely true now the thing that I
the trouble I usually have with conspiracy theories is they do tend to
cast a wide net he would have done a much better job these people would have
done a much better job convincing me and like I said I go into all these
conspiracy theories with the hypothesis that they are true if he said the butthole
the all-C and I is really human butthole and it's because the Masons came up with
it and the Masons love but sex and they have gay sex all the time or something
like that and they kept it there I would still think it was a little ridiculous
but when you try to tie it into witches and Nazis and North Missal North
mythology and Egyptians and 9/11 and all this stuff it just totally ruins the
point and when you tell me you came up with this theory while watching
interracial anal porn and then he brags also that he never pays for porn oh and
to go back to the copyright thing there are entire companies dedicated to
shutting down pirated and copyrighted porn so his his idea that none of it is
ever none of it is ever taken down because the Illuminati is controlling
the porn industry it's not true there are companies that porn and porn
companies and anyone can hire to go into these websites and give them DMCA's the
problem is is that when you take a video down someone else just uploads it there
is huge money behind porn and I go back to the point I've made a couple times on
the show stop watching porn it's just not healthy for you I don't care about
the moral issues behind it because that may not affect you it actually
physically affects your body you watch a lot of porn it makes you impudent you
stop watching porn you will stop being impudent that's steady after steady after
steady show and it causes erectile dysfunction and then stop watching
porn it also causes you to come up with crazy conspiracy theories but again I'm
gonna circle back one more time is it possible that the all-cni is
representative of something other than the all-cni sure why not it's a it's a
icon is it possible that it represents a buckle you know what honestly this is
one of those things that if it's either or if somebody was able to provide me
more coherent proof that wasn't brought up while they were watching porn and they
go no we actually like if you look at the early text the people who came up with
it thought it'd be funny or no it is like this esoteric symbol that the eye
represents both what sees and what leaves the body I'll be like okay yeah sure as
it stands now I think this guy's just kind of nuts but you know it's one of
those things that and again either way it wouldn't really have any bearing on my
life whether I would laugh every time I handed someone a dollar bill thought of
it but yeah it's one of those weird conspiracies that it's it's possible I
guess it's highly unlikely but it's possible there's other stuff that we've
covered that I'm like no that absolutely didn't happen there's proof that it
didn't happen but this is one of those ones that I mean you get a bunch of guys
together and they start designing stuff maybe they do decide to have a laugh now
what the what the all-cni is supposed to represent they always talk about the the
eye of Providence you'll hear that referred to in conspiracy circles or
the all-cni it's considered the all-cni of God it's supposed to be the eye of
God watching over humanity that's why it's called Providence like it's this
divine providence so I mean it is an old symbol I don't think it was supposed to
be a butthole I think it's easy if you stare at something long enough or if you
watch enough porn and you're thinking about it and you're seeing all these
buttholes quench in front of you and they look like they're winking and I'm not a
big fan of anal anyways but you know it looks like it's winking to make sure
they get an eye whatever I think that the gentleman who wrote the first off I
think he needs to stop watching porn so now I don't think that the eye of
Providence is a butthole I think that kind of went without saying I do think
that like he can weave an interesting story and maybe he should use maybe
should stop watching porn and write I mean like he could write basically say
national treasure meets you know like filthy facials volume 7 and have kind of
this hero going on this quest to unearth this orgy Freemason group that's
drawing these images in our money that makes us want to have butt sex with each
other someone would buy that I think that'd be an interesting story bunch of
Freemasons run around banging each other drawing buttholes everywhere they have to
follow the clues they're looking at like the Constitution and they work out
every other word and it gives you a web address that's on Ex Hamster the you go
to you go to the you go to Mount Rushmore and like if you come on the
four faces in the right order like this vault opens up and it's full of these
it's full it has Odin's dildo in there I mean you know he could come up with
these great scenarios just you using this core idea maybe he actually has
something but no the eye of the Providence the eye of Providence is not
but I'm glad I was able to finally put that at rest that was actually one on
the conspiracy list as well so like I said there's a lot of weird stuff on
there but we that one's done it's settled unless more information pops up
which it probably won't but in but in case it does next story is really bizarre
and it's one that I came across years and years ago it's funny because I used to
just research weird events and then you know find I get books I read websites
and I kind of bookmark stuff and I that was just kind of it I would just
research it and then call it a day and as I started doing this podcast I've been
going back through some moment old bookmarks I came across this story and
it's still surprised me I was still like that's absolutely impossible so this
story is back from 2011 so you know quite old you know news wise so in South
Korea I found this man crucified and crucified in the traditional way his
feet were nailed to the to the bottom of the cross his hands were nailed to the
cross he had a rope around his neck and he had a mirror oh and he had a crown of
thorns just like Jesus you know Jesus did and imagery had a crown of thorns on
he had a stab wound in his stomach where the Romans stabbed Jesus and there was a
mirror in front of his face oh and there was two smaller crosses on the side
those were empty but anyway so some guy finds it and they goes back he
puffs off calls the cops the cops show up and they're looking around and they
see all this stuff they're like okay yeah there's his feet you know they'll to
that and stab wound and the mirror was in his face so he could look at his own
suffering and you're I'm reading this I'm reading the article years ago me like
oh man that's super brutal and I was reading it again last week and I am
like oh man that's awful like was it like a drug deal gone wrong was a day
like some sort of mafia Asian mafia send in a message you get to the last
sentence in the article it says police still aren't sure if this case was a
homicide or a suicide and I'm like what are you what are you how do you
crucify yourself how do you commit suicide via crucifixion I know there's
some crazy ways you can kill yourself but that's
wait for that dog to pass I must have psychic powers right when I said that
oh well maybe I don't that's the way people usually come up they say may have
psychic powers they just think something and something happens and then they're
like I'm gifted anyways so it's a hundred and seven I can't shut the windows
that's the problem but I'm not gonna worry about it he's a happy little puppy
he can bargol he wants I don't care anyway so I read this article and I was
like okay this happened in 2011 they have to have some sort of resolution to
this by now and the cops did finally rule he killed himself and they actually
had to put on a presentation to prove because no one would believe how do you
kill yourself you crucifixion so the police reenacted it listen to what this
guy did so apparently he was this hyper religious guy and before he ended up in
the quarry where they found the crucifix he had emptied his bank account he had
planned they found notes about his crucifixion he canceled his mobile phone
contract according to this now of course you could always say someone made him
I'll do that to kill him and all that stuff but the cops are actually able to
figure out how he did this so they said that and this might sound a little
extreme and go all that sounds ridiculous but this is the cops hypothesis so he
nailed his own feet to the cross first okay then he lifted his back up and put
the rope or the rope is hanging off the cross already he put his head in the
rope now that's Jesus didn't die have a rope around his neck but it takes quite
a few quite a few days to actually die of crucifixion I think he's just beating
that process up anyways then he stabs himself on the side so his feet are
nailed to the crucifix who puts his head in the rope he stabs himself on the side
oh man this sucks and then he drilled holes in his hands and there was already
nails in the cross and he lifted his hands up and pushed the nail like head
through his hand and got him both in there and then just slumped and if they
died of a combination of blood loss and suffocation because when you when you're
crucified even without the rope you can't hold up Jesus wasn't crucified
through his hands by the way that's a misnomer he was crucified through his
wrists but what happens is when you crucified people we know that
scientifically your body will slump and your head will kind of push down into
your chest and you can't breathe so you lift yourself up to get a couple more
breaths but it's you have really no upper body strength it's not like these
people are on a torch now they start to slump again they start to not breathe
again you do that for about two or three days and you die a couple hours
depending on because your lung capacity so it's very torturous way to die you
can you imagine back in the day they talk about these accounts for people
would travel down roads and they would just be crucified soldiers like
crucified prisoners lining the road I mean we complain if we go to Cancun and
there's a head in the pool could you imagine going to Bulgaria and there's
500 people crucified and you're like this isn't where I want to be right now
that was just and but you would just be like oh something was to happen here
well I still got to go do business in this town you know it's bizarre but you
just see that and you can't help them you can't help them because then you'll end
up on there so anyways yeah there was a suicide apparently and again it's
possible that this guy was murdered and this was all an attempt attempt to
cover it up but the neighbors were like he was super religious they didn't really
shock anybody he made the plans if there's a will there's a way as grim as
that sounds if you want to crucify yourself you will plan out how to and
that probably helped them to where they found how he planned they found notes on
his crucifixion the police probably be able to go okay that's how he got his
hands nailed into the cross he drilled his hands beforehand the nails are already
there and he just hoisted it over you know at some point I'm sure he totally
regretted doing that I mean he could have been caught up in some whole
religious fear fervor but after like hour four he may have been like I'll never
see Big Bang Theory again well that's gonna be all we're gonna have today for
Dead Rabbit Radio you can hit us up on email at dead rabbit radio at gmail.com
our Twitter is @jasonocarpenter that's the Twitter account and then there's
Facebook is facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio all of those ways are ways to connect
to us our logo art is done by Ash Black well I hope you I hope you enjoy that
episode I hope you learn a little bit about the
I Providence and buttholes in general I probably could have done a whole thing on
the science of the butthole to kind of like really get you into it so you really
knew what I was talking about but I'm kind of glad I didn't and I think I've
exceeded my orifice research for the day we're gonna keep going along with sex
conspiracies for the rest of the week we've got another couple good ones
coming out and so I hope you keep listening we Dead Rabbit Radio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it
every day I'm glad you listen to it today have a great day guys and stay cool
please stay cool
you
(upbeat music)