Fires burned through the Amazon this summer, and standing in the ashes and the smoke is
the man responsible for it all, Leonardo DiCaprio.
And then we travel to mining country, where a story has been passed around for decades.
Was there really an ancient chamber discovered by simple miners, and when they broke through,
a beast murdered them all.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a great
day too.
Just a quick reminder, this is the last week, and then I'm gonna take a week long break.
I take a week long break every 50 episodes, so these next 5 episodes are leading up to
that.
So thanks guys for listening to the show, but also for the Thanksgiving special, that
was a lot of fun to do.
After that, I did another live stream where we watched Jesse James meets Frankenstein's
daughter, it was like me and about 12 other people for about an hour and a half watched
it, but it was a lot of fun interacting with you guys watching the movie, I was able to
kind of relax.
And then after that, after everyone went to bed, I decided to watch another movie by myself
late at night, it completely ruined my Thanksgiving, absolutely ruined my Thanksgiving.
You know when the Joker came out, when the Joker movie came out, I went and saw that
opening days of the movie theater, all that stuff, talked about Joker a bunch.
Now there was a big push in the media, I saw a bunch of articles saying, "Joker celebrates
in cell culture if you want to see the same movie, but it doesn't celebrate in cells,
it doesn't celebrate," watch this movie called "Cuck."
And I was like, "Oh, okay, so I was vaguely aware of the movie Cuck, I knew it was supposedly
like the Joker, what I imagined it to be was, you know how God's Not Dead is a movie, is
a series of movies now, but basically it's a movie where all the good guys are Christian
and all the bad guys aren't Christian, very, very black and white, to the point that in
the first God, in the first God's Not Dead movie, there is a Muslim girl listening to
the Bible on tape, she has like an iPod, right, she's downloaded Bible verses, and her Muslim
father comes into the, I'm trying not to laugh, this is a horrible thing, but it's just so
ridiculous in the context of this movie, because they're like in the middle of Idaho where
this movie takes place, this Muslim girl's listening to Bible verses on her iPod, her
dad comes in and beats the crap out of her, because like she takes the headphones out
and he hears like Psalms 8, "Let the joy of the Lord be poured upon you," and he's like,
"What?" and he starts beating her, it's completely over the top, there's like all these characters,
and at the end, all of the new Christians meet at some concert for like DC talk or whatever,
Jars of Clay, doesn't matter, very, very just good, that's what I thought, I thought Cuck
was gonna be a good laugh, thought it was gonna be a movie, I thought it was gonna be
a movie bordering on parody, where a kid, a young kid watches like four Ben Shapiro
videos and then goes out and starts like beating up minorities, I thought it was gonna be this
complete black and white, chuckle-fest movie that was totally heavy-handed, it might have
been one of the ugliest movies I've seen since "Gateway Meet," and the fact that I'm comparing
it to a movie called "Gateway Meet" should tell you the level of, the movie is like watching
cancer grow, and you may think, Jason, you're really hyping this up, I'm not recommending
people to see this movie, it ruined my Thanksgiving, and what's really weird, it is the exact same
movie as Joker, it's the exact same movie, you have a guy who's living with an elderly
single mother who's very, very sick, who has delusions of grandeur and a plan to get out
of their current cycle, and just the worst possible things happen to these people.
In Joker, he gets beat up, a bunch of dudes, he's holding up a street sign, a bunch of
dudes beat up, Arthur Fleck, and Cuck, another dude jacks off on him, I mean, the stuff that
the Cuck goes through is so much worse than what Arthur Fleck went through, again, it's
not a movie I would necessarily recommend, because it's probably one of the ugliest movies
I've ever seen, it's just so tough, there's a scene in it, and this might seem like a
bit of a spoiler, if you whole movie you don't, I'm probably talking about this for a little
bit longer than I planned to, but there's this whole thing in the beginning where you
don't know, his father's dead but you don't know how, or why, or if he's not dead if he's
left, if he's just out of the picture, and he wears his father's military uniform, and
he looks like a boy wearing an adult clothes, and it's the perfect way to start the movie,
because he really is a boy in an adult world, he's in his 20s, but just acts like a child.
When we find out, in Joker, we find out, spoiler alert, that he was beaten as like a six year
old, and that's what gave him the laughing, that part is pretty stupid, he gets hit so
hard as a kid, it makes him laugh all the time, that part was really dumb, and Joker,
in this movie, so you're like, okay that's horrible, six year old Joker is tied to a radiator
and beat up, he's hit so hard that he has a laughing disorder, and Cuck, we find out,
again, totally worse, we find out that when he was a baby, when Cuck, when that's his
name now, when Cuck was a baby, Cuck Finn, when he was a baby, we see in a flashback,
his dad blows his brains out, kills himself, the dad kills himself while holding Cuck,
baby Cuck, and the baby begins playing with the wound in the head, playing with the brains.
That's the difference between these two movies, one of them was like, oh this guy was kind
of like punched, punched so hard 20 years ago, now he laughs, the other one was, I played
with my dad's open wound, totally ruined my Thanksgiving, but if you're a fan of extreme
cinema, watch Cuck, and I don't recommend it, that one on far longer than I thought it
was going to, but I just wanted to share my misery, I wanted to share my misery with you
guys, let's go ahead and move on to our first topic, Amazon, let's hop in the Carbinder
Coptor, we're headed to the Amazon jungle, the, what do they call it, the scuba gear of
the planet or something like that, the lungs of the planet, the lungs of the planet, a
bunch of oxygen comes from, comes from the Amazon, comes from trees and stuff like that,
whatever, trees are burning down, trees are burning down since the beginning of time,
I get it that these trees, this was a particularly bad forest fire, I got these notes written
down, last year there was like 10,000 forest fires, this year there was 30,000, but that
includes like just one tree burning, which I get it is still bad, but Jair Bolsonaro,
Jair Bolsonaro, he is the president of Brazil or its prime minister or something like that,
I think he's president, I don't know, I don't pay attention to anything outside the United
States, I don't know if you guys haven't caught on to that, I specifically read an article
about this guy and I don't know what political office he holds, USA, USA, now America is
the lung of the planet and the heart, the spleen probably, America is also probably the spleen
of the planet, maybe pinkries, anyways so Jair Bolsonaro believes that the forest fires,
most people believe the forest fires are man made, that ranchers were setting stuff on fire
to make room for cattle, but Jair Bolsonaro says no, that's not it, I know who's responsible
for the forest fires, it's Leonardo DiCaprio, people are like what?
And he goes okay okay that's ridiculous, that's ridiculous, and the reporters are like oh
okay that makes sense, I thought our president was just saying that Leonardo DiCaprio was
setting fires, the president goes no, no, I'm not saying he's out there personally setting
fires but he is supporting, he's giving money to the people who set those fires, people
are like what is going on, so this is the thing, apparently there's a bunch of volunteer
firefighters down in the Amazon, brain water everywhere, putting fires out as you do, but
these firefighters have been accused of setting fires, so they're fire lighters, the motive
is this, the World Wildlife Fund, the WWF is raising tons of money based on the Amazon
fires, oh no we gotta stop the fires, you know panda bears are losing their homes, they
actually happened in Australia, I guess there was a huge fire in Australia and they're like
well wait not panda bears, koala bears, panda bears in China, they said, I guess there was
a big fire in Australia and people were like oh you can guess the koala bears don't have
homes no more, gonna be extinct, no more littlest koala, what was that show on, there was that
trippy show on Nickelodeon about the koala and it would like go to other dimensions,
I think it was the littlest koala, it was these two koalas, it was like anime on Nickelodeon
in the early 90s and it had all this dream time aborigine stuff, nothing to do with
the story, totally going off topic here, but anyways so the koala bears are gonna have
a hard time finding, that's not part of the story either, but they're gonna have a hard
time finding a home, back to the story, Amazon Ray Force totally on fire, so he's saying
that the World Wildlife Federation, WWF is setting fires, having amateur, not amateur,
yeah amateur, volunteer is the word, totally different, well I guess you can be an amateur
and a volunteer but just because you're a volunteer doesn't mean you're an amateur,
he believes that the WWF is setting fires in Brazil, taking photos of said fires and
using them to get money and supposedly Leonardo DiCaprio donated $500,000 to the WWF to fight
these fires and they've arrested those four volunteer firefighters, now they've been released
but they're still gonna be tried for setting these fires, now here's the weird, obviously
here's the, there's a lot of things to unpack here, here's the weird thing about this, so
he says these guys, we don't know obviously if the people really set those fires, that
will be for the trial to be held, the media says you are such a corrupt president that
you are trying to hide your corruption from us by saying those people set fires, which
to me is a weird defense because you're saying, okay let's say I was a super corrupt president
and people are investigating me, I, there's a hundred other things I could say rather
than Leonardo DiCaprio is setting fires in the Amazon, which was close to his original
statement because Leonardo DiCaprio supposedly gave $500,000 to the WWF and they're saying
you're using this to distract, now there's a, if you were a president you could say the
drug problem's too high or kids with their fidget spinners, right, am I right, like there's
a lot of other stuff, it's a weird conspiracy theory to make up if you want to divert attention
from yourself, you wouldn't say I saw Bigfoot, you wouldn't say a ridiculous conspiracy theory,
so listen it's probably not true but I also wouldn't put it past somebody to do that,
to set fires and then take pictures of it and then use it to get donations, now Leonardo
DiCaprio has come forward and this is an all other weird part of the story, Leonardo DiCaprio
comes forward and says, I didn't give him any money, like I appreciate, I'm paraphrasing
obviously, I appreciate what the WWF does but I have not donated any money to them,
I've donated money to other charities that are fighting the Amazon Rainforest but not
the WWF specifically, which was another weird thing, he wasn't saying this isn't true, which
to be fair Leonardo DiCaprio has better things to do than defend the WWF from a ridiculous
conspiracy theory but it's also telling, again as a conspiracy theorist you could go well
that's weird, he didn't say well that's not true and I'm gonna write a check to them today,
he says I never gave him any money so the fact that I'm being brought into this conspiracy
theory is ridiculous to begin with, I have nothing to do with them, they do good work
but I didn't have anything to do with them, if I was Leonardo DiCaprio, first I was president,
now I'm Leonardo DiCaprio, first off I know how to pronounce my name, for some reason
I keep saying Leonardo, that's how you pronounce it, right, Leo, Leonardo DiCaprio, I don't
know, I feel like I've been mispronouncing it, Leonardo, it's not Leonardo, Leonardo,
Leonardo, Leonardo, whatever, it doesn't matter, Mr. DiCaprio, if I was Mr. DiCaprio I would
say that's ridiculous, no, they didn't start these fires, the end, and also I didn't donate
the money but you sir, the fact that he didn't deny it is odd and so just a weird conspiracy
theory, now, hey everybody welcome back, see you didn't take a break, I did, I had to take
what is going to be turned a heater break, had to turn the heater on and get this apartment
a little warmer, the snow is here, the snow is here, I would do anything for an Amazonian
forest fire right now, I guess technically I could just set a forest on fire, it doesn't
have to be Amazonian but it's freezing, let's go ahead and move on to our last story of the
night, we're gonna leave behind the beautiful warm fields of Amazon, I guess they're fields
now because all the trees have burned down, oh it feels so warm there, I'm setting fires,
Leonardo DiCaprio I see him, he's like handing me some gas, he's like here you go, but this
is not fossil fuel gas, this is environmentally sound gas so it's just air, I'm just spraying
air everywhere, anyways thanks Leo for nothing, I leave, we leave, I leave, you stay there,
you're hanging out with Leonardo DiCaprio, I'm like uh huh, because you can pronounce
his name correctly, he wants to hang out with you, so while you guys are partying with Mr.
DiCaprio, I'm, and I'm flying the helicopter all lonely through the sky, aww I have sad
ending, but you chose to hang out with Mr. DiCaprio, enjoy his podcast jerks, and so
I land, get out at Dixonville, Pennsylvania, walking around all by myself, hmm I wonder
where my listeners are, you guys are in the party jet with Leonardo DiCaprio, he's like
yes, you guys have all, have do whatever you want, see those hot models over there, make
out with them, or if you're not into that, have a good conversation with them, they all
have PhDs, so some of you are making out with them, some of you are talking about economics,
Leonardo DiCaprio still can't pronounce the name correctly, his jet lands, it lands on
top of the Carbentercopter, I've officially become the cuck, ugh that movie was so depressing,
and the Carbentercopter is destroyed, you guys all get out, you're still partying, and
I'm just kinda sitting there on a rock, like thanks guys for finally showing up, thanks
for destroying my only motogenthridation air vehicle, oh wait I have the dirgeable still,
let's get on topic, listen the narration is, we've set the mood, we are in Dixonville,
Pennsylvania, and the year is 1944, there was a mining disaster, pfft rocks, mysteriously
15 men and Leonardo DiCaprio died in this mining disaster, I pushed him in front of
a boulder and I'm like take my friends will you, ahhhhhhh, so now it's just me and you,
it's me and you, stripping his plane for parts, rebuild, I guess I'm gonna just use the airplane,
and instead I'm rebuilding the Carbentercopter, mining disaster 1944, Dixonville, Pennsylvania,
15 men and one gorgeous young man died in this accident, now they bring in accident inspector
Glenn E. Barger, Glenn E. Barger, Glenn middle name E. Barger, now they bring him in and
they're like hey we need to find out what happened to this mine, we need to find out
like was it like a bomb to go off, was it Wiley Coyote around here, was it a simple cave in,
what happened, so he's like yes, I will investigate this cave in, that is my job, that is why
I'm here, and they're like but before you go on to the cave, before you start looking
around we gotta show you something, and he's like ooh is it that new Mickey Mantle baseball
card, ooh is it, I wonder when baseball cards were invented actually, I bet you they were
invented like in the late 1800s, just saw this on my head, and now I know right when
I said that, a bunch of you thought Jason baseball wasn't even around in the late 1800s,
but weren't they playing it during the Civil War, like weren't they playing baseball back
then, I wonder how much of my audience listens to this podcast just to get angry, just to
be like how can one man know so little about so much, like he can go on and on about Big
Foot, he can go on and on about UFOs, but if you ask him when baseball was invented,
or when the first baseball card was printed, he will be wildly off, I'm, you know what,
I'm gonna look it up right now, I'm gonna look it up when was baseball invented, I'm
gonna say right now Civil War, let's find out how close I am, thrilling podcasting I
know, when was baseball invented, 1846, so yes, so baseball was around pre-Civil War,
nice, I was, I was very very, now let's see when the first baseball card was, you're like
Jason this isn't even the topic that you promised us, when was the, when was the first baseball
card made, 1886, bam dude, all you doubters out there, because I get so many facts wrong,
bam, you guys thought I was gonna get humiliated on my own podcast, you're wrong, that's gonna
happen next episode, or probably this episode as well, you guys are all standing around,
you're still 1944, you guys are just waiting here, story about a mysterious cave-in, I'm
going on about baseball cards, Glenn Barger is looking at me being like dude, who is this
lunatic, I'm sorry guys, I don't remember why I got on this subject, oh yeah I made a joke
about Mickey Mantle, anyways the point being is that they do have something to show him,
and so now I'm going to be quiet for a second, I'm gonna, that's why you guys abandoned me
in the Amazon, you guys are like Leonardo DiCaprio never went off on segues and talked
about baseball cards during a monster story, I'm like I know I miss him already too, but
anyways so Glenn Barger says, yeah let me see what you got, so the, this mining company
executive in this chair set, he just like come over here, and they throw back like a
blanket, let me, okay let me build a picture, that's vague, where they at, bed, bath and
beyond, then that'd be totally normal, there's a body laying on the ground, I forgot that
key detail, covered with a blanket, and they throw the blanket off, and Glenn goes, I've
never seen a rock leave injuries like this, and the mining executive is like me, neither,
and the sheriff's deputy goes, those look more like the wounds that a wild animal might
give a man, not a stalactite, or a stalagmite, and Glenn Barger stands up and goes, you're
stalag right, so, yeah, afterwards, afterwards, they, I'm sorry, Glenn goes into this cave,
I'm quite proud of that joke by the way, came up, bit off the top of my head, Glenn goes
in the cave starts looking around, and they start finding more bodies, now there's one
or two of them, just giant rock fell from the ceiling, crushed them, just like a grape,
like putting your thumb on a grape, but there are other bodies that have, what could only
be described as claw marks, deep, not like a little raccoon claw, we're talking like
fingernails, like little katana blades, like if you took a little knife and cut a grape,
and so he's walking around, he has another inspector with him, and they're like, and
they notice that there's supposedly 15 miners that didn't come out of the cave, and they
found a couple of them now, but there's a lot of them missing, and then he hears screaming
down the tunnel, and Glenn turns, you know, I think one of the worst sounds in the world
is a man screaming, it's horrifying, I think I might have mentioned this before, it absolutely
terrifies me, and here's why, I think as a society really, you become immune to the
sound of a woman screaming, because you hear it all the time in horror movies, and also
a lot of times women will scream when they're happy, you go, hey, here's your engagement
ring, they're like, but you know, a lot of times girls will scream when they're having
fun, roller coaster, stuff like that, but also you hear it so often in horror movies,
when you hear a man scream, it's chilling, because you never, ever hear it, ever, super
terrifying, but anyways, he hears this man screaming, and sleep tight kids, the sound
of men screaming all night, he goes running and he sees his buddy, his fellow inspector,
in a cave system, like in a, in a site, they're all in a cave system, that's not, that's not
a shock to him, he's like, oh my god, we're underground, what?
So he sees like a cave off to the side, like a tunnel, I guess is the term, and he sees
what appears to be some sort of monster attacking his buddy, and then the rocks, like form up,
like old school stop motion, and seal the tunnel, so now Glenn is separated from his
buddy, so he's like, come on guys, let's move these rocks, and they start moving these rocks
away, and then a bunch of stop motion skeletons show up, and they start fighting them like
old timey Jason the Argonauts, but no, in real life, they move all the rocks away, and
his buddy is okay, but there was some sort of monster down there, and the quote was,
the thing wasn't human, and they never found the bodies of the other missing miners, and
the theory, working theory was this, that these miners were working in a cave, and they
broke into an old cave system, and one of the people who got out of the cave and survived
this incident said, this is all reported in the newspaper, we'll get into that in a second,
but one of the men says, I'm in the caves, and we were mining, picking with the picks,
you know, do do do do do do, that's like a Middle Eastern snake charming song, I was
trying to do whistle while you work, but they're moving stuff around, I wonder if miners always
get tired of dwarf jokes, back then they were probably always getting made fun of for being
dwarves, so you could assume one of them went on a crazed pickaxe killing spree, but anyways,
he goes no, that didn't happen, we're going on segways, Jason, the miner says to me,
he goes, and then he turns to the rest of you in a dress, this is what happened, we
were doing our thing in the cave, we were mining, and we broke through to an ancient
tunnel that was like parallel to us, it was next to us, and then this creature came out
of it and started attacking people and was making rocks fly around and making cave ins,
and I ran out, because I was scared, I'm super spooky, so the Glenbarger takes his report
and never releases it, ever, but then how do we know this stuff, how do we know this
stuff, what happened was in the 70s his son finds this report, he's going through his
stuff, his dad passed away, mysteriously, a giant rock fell on him, no his dad passes
away, the son, Barger Jr., Mr. Young Barger, whatever his name is, he finds this report
and then he takes it to a local journalist named Stony Brakefield, and he published this
story in News Extra, Pennsylvania's newspaper News Extra, he published it in 1974, 30 years
after the attack in Dixonville's mining system.
So this story has been going around for quite a long time online, it hasn't gotten super
viral, but it's not hard to find resources on it, a lot of people have covered it, and
one person in particular covered it, and I gotta give credit to this website, it's called
the Paranormal Pastor, Paranormal Pastor basically did all the research of the after
events, the stuff that I normally have to do, so hats off to the Paranormal Pastor for
this, my first thing is looking at the story as I go, that's dope, that's totally awesome,
monster underground, chopping people up, eating dudes, making them disappear, making Geomancy,
controlling the rocks, all that type of stuff, really cool, really cool thing, but it's probably
not true, so let's find out, the easiest thing for us to track down is the newspaper, News
Extra, Pennsylvania's New Extra, doesn't exist, newspaper never existed, so that's the easiest
place to start, the guy who runs the Paranormal Pastor did some more digging, there are mines
in Pennsylvania obviously, and there are mines in Dixonville, but there's no mines by that
name, they named it the Dixonville Mine, I think it was like Dixonville Mine 22 or something
like that, there was no disaster in the year of 1944, again, you know mine disasters are
very, very well documented because they usually turn into lawsuits, there's all sorts of paperwork
filled out, they're run by corporations that have to report it in their books, now I'm
not saying that obviously they're an illegal mining operation, they're not going to have
any paperwork or the best paperwork, but generally mines that are run by companies are very well
documented, they would have to show, oh there was an accident this year, this is how many
people we lost, this is government oversight, these are the penalties we paid, these are
the lawsuits we had to file, or settle with the families and all that stuff, so we're
losing a bunch of the information, and then actually he goes on to say Paranormal Pastor
says I searched and there is no Stony Brake Field, there is no reporter by that name,
so this story is interesting for two reasons, one it's a cool little monster story, it has
all the hallmarks, it has people in an area that normal humans don't go to, it took place
a long time ago, and you have this monster running around in the darkness gutting people,
just like a horror story, and I think that's why it spread so much on the internet, this
is what's fascinating about this, and the reason why I wanted to cover this isn't just
because it's kind of a cool spooky story, because of the implications, the implications.
What I think is interesting, we talk a lot about deep things, we talk a lot about video
footage being manipulated to look like it's real, and that has implications on two sides,
one if somebody, if I want to make it look like my political opponent eats babies, then
I can have doctor footage to show my political opponent eating babies, and on the same factor,
if I do actually eat babies, I could then say that wasn't me, that was a deep fake, and
they're like, sir we're watching you eat a baby during this press conference where you're
denying it, you're like I'm hungry, but that video, that was fake, so can people are afraid
that deep fakes are going to work both ways?
I think that the cryptid game, because we've covered a lot of stories like this where people
have totally made stuff up and when you track it back there was no newspaper of that time,
there was no op, this isn't new, we've covered a lot of stories where they were totally made
up and when you look back and they'll be like this was reported in the Atlantic as that,
and you're like what, that newspaper doesn't exist, it might exist, but you know just an
example.
I think the people who tell these stories, tell these legends going forward, are going
to start using real sources and real names, because a key component to finding out this
story was fake, definitely for me to start off was that the newspaper didn't even exist.
If the person making up the story used a real newspaper, found an article written by someone
with a byline in that newspaper, which wouldn't be hard, which wouldn't be super difficult,
that person could be dead, that person could be old, whatever, it wouldn't matter.
If I saw, whoa, there was a news extra newspaper in Pennsylvania in operation in 1944 and Stoney
Brakefield is a real journalist, that would make me start to lean more towards, hmm, this
is real.
Now, obviously the other things he would have to, the person who made the story up, would
have to make it take place in a real mine, and then in the story include the point, because
of the mysterious events that took place, there is no record of this mine disaster, the government
covered it up.
It's that suspicious, obviously, but it works better than all of those verifiable details
being made up.
Most of these stories, this is creepypasta, most of these stories are made up to entertain
the author and then to creep out teenagers and stuff.
And then it spreads and it gets into the paranormal community and people act like it's a real
thing.
And again, I don't know how much, I don't know how many of these paranormal websites
just know that this stuff is nonsense and stuff is fake and they just want clicks or
they actually believe in it, it's sometimes hard to tell, but, and really conspiracy theories
are creepypasta, that is already using real life events.
This X happened, therefore it was the government or it was the Illuminati that did this.
That's really, and then it gathers around the internet that narrative builds, that's
a creepypasta.
But we're gonna see that same method attribute itself to monsters running around in a cave.
It will be very soon that only basic common sense will keep you from being tricked about
a story involving monsters or semen, not that type, or you know like creatures from the
deep.
Only common sense.
And common sense is, even for me, a fleeting thing.
Because sometimes you get a story that's so juicy and so scary, you want to believe it
so badly that common sense goes out the window.
And if our ability to debunk these stories is overridden by a master storyteller, who
knows what we're gonna be believing in the coming years.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is gonna be our email address, you can also hit us up
at facebook.com/deadraboradeo.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast, you don't
have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one guys.
[Music]