"If you are hearing this broadcast, seek shelter immediately."
Do YOU have paranormal powers?
If you do, I get $5,000.
And you like that contest?
Then we take a look at the story of a man who claimed he had paranormal powers.
Nobody really took him seriously until football teams began disastrously losing games today
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover.
So we're gonna get started right away.
You remember the old episodes, like the first like 100 episodes?
I was like, "My day was great."
And I'd spend like four or five minutes talking about just random stuff.
Not anymore.
I put that stuff in the middle of the episode now to trick you.
First off, is that what you're already engaged in the story?
First off, let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter,
Mokushi!
Mokushi, thank you very much for supporting the show.
You are gonna be our captain, our pilot, our gunner, maybe?
If we have like a gun in this one? We don't.
And then, if you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help get the word out about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
Still sending out supporters, stickers for Patreon supporters.
And we have merch in the merch store.
That's all in the show notes below.
Like I keep hitting home.
I'm gonna be going on vacation soon.
That means more video game time for me.
Didn't you just say you don't spend time talking about random stuff?
Mokushi, let's go ahead and hop in the Jason Jalopy.
We're going for a drive.
We're going down to Hollywood.
Mokushi, we're driving through streets of LA.
We got our sunglasses on.
I got a big hat.
That's it. No other clothes.
We're driving through LA.
We're going to a place.
We're not just down there to sightsee.
We're going to the Center for Inquiry Investigations Group.
These guys have made it their mission to prove the unprovable
or unprove the impossible.
However you want to put it, they're a group of skeptics.
They consider themselves the largest
paranormal investigation group in the world.
Because they do investigate the paranormal,
but they investigate the fun out of it.
So, I mean, and I do the same thing for the most part,
but I also believe in like ghosts and aliens and all that stuff.
There's just certain narratives that I'm like,
"Eh."
And even ghost stories, a lot of times I'll shred
into pieces so they don't think they work.
But I enjoy the realm of the unknown.
And these guys might too, but these guys actually
go the extra effort to basically bring weirdos
to their location and come up with impossible tests
that really nobody can pass.
So we pull up outside the Center for Inquiry
and I get out and Mokushi's like,
"So why are we here though?
Like are we here to debunk stuff or are we here
to prove like the world's supernatural
'cause you believe that and I go, "Mokushi,
you first off, you drive.
Don't talk, just sit there and don't talk."
That's my job.
I don't know how you got on my podcast.
Secondly, the SIG is what they're known as,
the Center for Inquiry Investigations Group.
They have a cash prize of $250,000.
And $50,000.
You like, "I'll pause there."
You're like, "$200 bucks, that's exactly my rent.
$250, I can also buy an ice cream cone.
$250,000, this is an expensive ice cream cone.
$250,000, if you can prove to them,
you can exhibit some sort of paranormal power."
Now it used to just be $100,000, but no one can do it.
So they raised the price.
Now, last episode I talked about me being an empath
and I said, "I don't know if I could do it on command."
And it's funny 'cause when I said that caveat,
I was specifically thinking about this story
that I was going to do for this episode.
If I went to the SIG, which actually we're here right now,
let's test this hypothetical.
We walk inside and there's a bunch of nerds
and around they got the poster's episode.
No fun.
And then there's a ghostbuster poster
with the X through the ghost
and then there's a bigger X through the poster.
And it's go, "You can't even have ghostbusters.
Boo, all paranormal stuff."
We're like, "Let me crack my knuckles.
Okay, let me use some of my paranormal power."
And I can walk into this room and I'm an empath
and I go looking around and I point at dude
and I go, "Your marriage is in trouble."
I can tell right now your marriage is in trouble.
And he goes, "No, it's not."
And then I go, "It will be when your wife sees me."
Whoa, Mimogushi high five.
Woo, no, no one's giving me high five.
I'm just standing in this room by by myself.
Okay, so here's the thing.
If you, I might be able to go into a room.
I don't think I could go in a room and dry read people
or cold read people, I think is the word.
I couldn't do that.
But if I said, "You take me to a house
where some horrible event has happened,
I could probably more than likely, more than 50/50 chance,
I could probably at least tell you something's gone wrong."
But there's a bit of a, again, there's a gimmick to that.
First off, if the house you take me to
is all run down with like wallpaper peeling,
I'm like, "Something bad has gone on here.
It's called water damage."
If you took me to a really, really nice house,
I would go, "Hmm, they're trying to trick me.
Nothing bad ever happens in a mansion.
Rich people never do anything wrong.
That's what I would think, right?
Because I'm an idiot.
But since I'm not an idiot,
since I can out thank these people,
they're taking me to a nice house,
assuming that I would think that it was too nice
for something evil to happen.
So I'm gonna say something evil happened.
So I just walking and saying something evil happened everywhere.
You couldn't really test that, right?
I couldn't have, 'cause they do actual real tests and stuff.
They go over their stuff, how they test the stuff.
You would have to literally do a double blind steady
where you take an intern.
You take two interns into two different rooms,
violently beat one and not let me see the victim.
And then the other one, you play a game of Chinese checkers.
And then I would have to go into the room and go,
"Hmm, this room's covered in blood.
It must be the violent assault one."
It would be really hard to test this theory.
And again, I don't necessarily think
it's something supernatural.
I think it's something everyone has.
Just some people, all 100% say it's not supernatural.
I think it's something that everyone has.
Just like some people can run marathons
and some people can merely walk.
I think I can run a half marathon with my ability.
I don't think I'm super good at being an empath.
But everyone can do it.
Just some people have trained themselves more.
But anyways, I don't think you would even buy that.
But this group, you know there's something coming here.
This group, they're offering $250,000
if you can prove that you have paranormal abilities.
There's gonna be all the links in the show notes.
You can actually fill it out yourself.
If you go and prove you have paranormal activities,
I get a finder's fee.
I get 5,000 bucks.
So I encourage everyone who actually has paranormal abilities.
Don't troll them, right?
We talked about that last episode.
Don't troll them.
But if you do have a authentic,
if one of my listeners happens to actually be
one of the new gods,
feel free to put me down on the recommended,
you recommend Dead Rabbit Radio,
recommended you let me get some of that money,
that 5,000 bucks.
You still get the full $250,000, but it's not easy.
It's not easy.
What they do is they have two sets of tests.
They have an informal test,
which is still incredibly rigorous.
And then they have a formal test
under strict scientific conditions.
So I was looking through them.
I might look through more of them,
but the ones I looked through were already pretty intriguing.
They had one guy, he said,
that he could tell what was in a box.
He was like a remote viewer.
And it takes months from the time you make the claim
to the time they can get you out to LA,
or sometimes they'll do it on Zoom.
If they really have to,
this one guy was in like Moldova.
They're like, "Oh, well, we know this is fake.
"We're not gonna fly him out, right?"
But anyways, they said they did it on webcam
and he couldn't do it.
But this guy said he could take an envelope.
He could look at it, tell you what the picture was
in the envelope.
And I mean, again, for the informal test,
they had double blind,
like they had one guy stuff the envelopes
in a totally secure room.
Once all four envelopes were stuffed,
he slid them under a door.
So the person administering the test
doesn't even know what's in the envelope.
So they look a sh,
that's the thing when I do tarot readings,
which I haven't done in a long time.
I'd look at your face or your body language.
And when I would say something,
if you reacted however slight,
I would know I was on the right track.
If he didn't react,
I would say something else.
I'd be like, "So you're having issues with your dad?"
No, your brother.
(gasps)
Yeah.
As I've seen your brother stand behind you
with an ax mid swing,
I'm like, "Look out!
"Should've come here an hour earlier
"before your brother picked up that ax from Home Depot."
That's how you do it, right?
So you have to have the double blind steady
because if the guy started getting them right wrong,
the tester could be like smirk and being like,
"Good thing we didn't play this too, not from Moldova."
So that's just the informal test.
That's just the informal test where they do this stuff.
Now, and no one's been able to pass it so far,
that's why they raised it up to $250,000.
But let's take a look at,
I'm gonna go into detail with this one test they did
'cause it leads us into our next story.
And it's actually really recent.
They're still doing this.
They said about six to 10 people come out a year
to test this, to be tested.
And to this day, nobody's ever been successfully.
I wonder if anyone's moved on to the formal stage.
I'm gonna do some more research on this,
but 'cause there's a ton of these studies
and it was interesting.
You feel free to look through them yourself.
June 25th, 2020, so very, very recently,
this man had been contacting back and forth.
He goes by the initials TR.
I don't know if that was actually a designation they gave him,
but we'll just call him Tom for short,
which is actually longer than TR, but you understand.
Tom, less syllables,
Tom had been contacting this group
and saying that he had the ability to
(imitates static)
make static electricity come out of his hands.
That's all he did was the sound effect over the phone
and they're like, "Oh, he's in.
"Here's $250,000."
He can make static electricity shoot out of his hands.
He could create lightning in the sky.
And he could teleport three feet.
Why only three feet?
What does that have to do with lightning?
I don't know.
Generally superheroes have a,
well, it's not like he's a superhero.
He's no Phoenix Jones,
but it's not like he's actually saying he's a mutant,
but he has the ability to shoot lightning
out of his fingertips
and call down lightning and teleport three feet.
So he comes out to LA and they have photographs
and they have video.
I really wish I could have seen the video for this,
but I couldn't find it,
but I did look at these photographs.
So they, the first test,
out of those three, what are you gonna test first, right?
Okay, he can shoot static electricity out of his hands,
which is basically any four-year-old with socks on.
He can rain down lightning from the sky
or maybe just make it go from cloud to cloud.
And then he can teleport.
Which one of those do you wanna test the first, right?
The teleport one, right?
There's 100%.
That's the one that is, if he teleported,
you wouldn't be like,
"Well, you couldn't call down lightning,
so no money for you."
Like that's the deal, right?
If someone shocked you,
it'd be like, "Ah, give me $250,000."
No, but if someone teleported,
but then they're like, "Here, make it rain."
He's like, "I lied about that one,
I can only teleport."
So that was the first one they test.
So we have this thing.
They set up these chairs in about like a 12-foot row
and covered it with a blue tarp to create a barrier.
And they wanted him to teleport somewhere in this location.
It's so funny to see a bunch of adults
out in the middle of LA.
They're all geared up for the coronavirus.
They all have masks on.
But a bunch of adults,
a bunch of adults have shown up
because another adult told them he could teleport.
And they're documenting all this stuff, right?
It's just hilarious.
So anyways, this guy shows up
and he goes, "I can teleport."
And they go, "Okay, here's his barrier."
Now he's set, 'cause they've been talking for months.
He goes, "I told you guys I can't teleport through stuff.
So I can't appear on one side of this barrier,
but I can teleport around it.
Like I can go from one end and teleport to the end."
At this point, the people were probably like,
"Just do it!
Just teleport.
I don't care if you're teleporting two feet in the air
and you call it a jump.
Like I just wanna see movement."
So we get this, this from this report they wrote.
"Upon being introduced to the TARP barrier,
TR," or Tom is recalling them,
"Tom said that he can't go through things
and reminded us that he must be moving to teleport.
He soon after showed us what he meant
and walked around the barrier
in a sort of herky-jerky motion.
He asked if we saw the teleportation
and we replied that we did not.
We only saw someone walking.
We offered to show him the just shot video of him
and he declined to view it."
So apparently, I just imagined him kind of like walking
like Samara from the ring,
but even more creepy because you're there in person, right?
He walks and then he goes, "Do you see it?
Do you see I teleported?
I have to move to teleport.
I moved from one location to another
and they're like, "No, we didn't see it."
Did you really teleport?
Yeah!
Do you wanna watch the video?
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
Yeah!
Do you wanna watch the video?
No, I'm good.
This is weird, right?
And then, that's like the definition of weird.
A bunch of adults out in a parking lot
trying to prove whether or not one of them can teleport.
I don't know what he thought.
Like when he moved, did he think?
He was obviously walking, right?
He obviously knew he was moving.
He obviously knew he had some sort of motion in his body.
So why he thought other--
Did he honestly think he teleported?
Did he think he could fool them?
But who know?
I don't know.
Anyways, they move on to the next test,
which, like at that point,
now they're like, "Oh, at least we don't--
we can put away this giant $250,000 check."
He goes, "I'm gonna call Lightning down from the sky."
Now they actually scheduled this meeting.
They had to watch weather reports
to make sure there's gonna be no storms.
I mean, these guys are pretty thorough.
He's like, "I'm gonna call down Lightning now,
but I gotta put in my music."
So he puts in his earbuds
and he raises his hands to the sky
and he's listening to music
and he closes his eyes.
And there's a photo of a dude just staring up
at the sky looking for Lightning.
It's like--
It's like noon.
It's the sunniest LA day.
There's just a photograph of one of the researchers
looking up in the sky.
And there's no Lightning.
There's no Lightning.
Now that obviously--
You could chalk that up to chance.
It could be weird.
Would be really weird.
And then at the end of it,
at the end of that, he said,
"He saw electricity shooting out of his hands,
but nobody else did."
And they checked the camera just to be careful,
just to make sure it wasn't moving at the speed of light.
The camera didn't pick up any electricity either.
As entertaining as I found this whole segment,
there was one thing that I thought
probably could have gone with that.
At the end, this guy obviously
doesn't have any superpowers
and believes that he does.
At the end of this research report,
they make kind of a comment about him being in rehab
and they ask him why he's in rehab
and he says he's in rehab for cocaine.
They ask him, "Is he taking any schizophrenia medication?"
And he says, "No."
That was--
I personally felt that was uncalled for.
Like maybe--
And then I go, "Did they mention that earlier in the report?"
And I did a word search for--
If they had said at the beginning,
he just came here from rehab.
He's out for an hour to test his powers.
Then that would be a fine way to conclude it.
But as a researcher,
or as someone who's just reading the article,
I get it, his powers don't work.
You didn't really have to go,
"Oh, he's in rehab too for cocaine addiction."
Like, I think it's--
That might be--
That obviously might be
causing some of these issues with him.
But it just felt to me like they were kind of kicking him
when he was down.
On yesterday's episode, I talked about being
how I could be way trodlier than I actually am
and how we should strive to just be nicer to people
on kind of an existential level.
And this kind of thing is what I'm talking about, right?
Like, you're kicking him--
He obviously doesn't have superpowers.
He obviously proved that this guy
has some issue you don't have to add at the ending.
"Oh, yeah, and he's just out of rehab."
"Coco, Coco!"
Yeah, I was having a good laugh.
I mean, actually, even though
we should be nicer to each other,
I was having a good laugh at this dude.
But there's a point, right, guys?
There's a point.
Like, I think it's okay to say this is story's fake.
Can I do that all the time?
This story's fake and that, and that, and that, and that.
That was a long way of saying,
"Give me some of that sweet, sweet $5,000."
If you go and do this test and pass,
you'd make a $5,000 donation of a pay--
No, no, no, you don't have to donate enough, then they'll pay me.
They'll pay me.
And I wanted to use this story as a springboard
because this other story had been sitting on for a while, actually.
"Mokushi, let's hop in the carbonar copter.
We're saying goodbye to the skeptics.
Lightning storms come in."
He's like, "Pfft, we see the dude's eyes start glowing."
"Get out of here!"
The skeptic scientists are hanging on to the landing gear.
We're kicking him off.
"You deserve your fate!"
"No!"
And before he hits the ground, the lightning strikes him.
[Lightning strikes]
Half of L.A.'s getting destroyed.
As the helicopter is leaving this destructive scene,
Tom has been unleashed.
That's actually not far from the story I'm about to tell you.
"Mokushi, let's hightail it out.
We're headed to Florida."
[Lightning strikes]
We look back to the city of L.A.'s a massive crater.
Have you seen the trailer for that new movie, "Grainland"?
Starring...
Leonidas and the Phantom?
What's his name?
Chris O'Dowd?
Craig Robinson?
What's that dude's name?
He's the dude.
Gerard Butler.
The movie looks great.
I'm going to put that in the show notes.
That looks amazing.
I love movies like that.
"Grainland."
Did a rapper recommend watching the trailer for "Grainland"?
We're headed out to Florida.
It's 1979.
And Florida is suffering a horrible drought.
Now, there is a newspaper known as the National Enquirer.
Now, newspaper is probably...
National Enquirer is interesting because it's actually a tabloid newspaper.
But it tells the truth more often than the Weekly World News.
The National Enquirer is more on a level of like the sun,
where it's a nationally recognized paper that does break stories.
But they're super sensationalists.
They will make up stuff and they've been sued in the past.
Weekly World News is a 100% fictional newspaper.
National Enquirer has covered stuff like Roswell before Roswell was a big story.
They've covered a lot of French stuff.
We've talked about National Enquirer a couple times on...
I don't use them as a main source, obviously,
but they are a less reputable newspaper than every other newspaper,
but more reputable than, say, the Weekly World News.
But you have real people working for these things,
and they're always looking for some sensational story.
In 1979, Florida's hit with a drought.
National Enquirer, the publishing headquarters, is in Florida.
And you had an editor named Wayne Grover,
who knew of a man who could control the weather.
So he calls up, can't really call him a friend,
an acquaintance, an ally, someone you'd want on your sign,
calls up Ted Owens and says, "Hey, Ted, yeah, yeah, it's Wayne.
Hey, can you do something about this drought?"
Kind of looking at his buddies all, "Yeah, yeah, in the office, yeah, I'm talking to Ted, yeah, yeah."
"Yeah, yeah, this drought in Florida, man, it's so hot, can you take care of it?"
"Yeah, yeah, okay, okay, cool, cool."
Hangs up, he gives a thumb up to him.
"Yeah, let's see what Ted can do this time."
"Yeah, he says he can control the weather."
Ten days later, massive storm hits Florida.
Now, you're going, Jason, storms always hit Florida.
But Wayne had a reason to call Ted.
Let's go back to February 10th, 1920.
That's when Ted Owens was born.
He claimed that both of his grandparents had psychic powers,
but that's not where this ended.
That would just be the end of the episode.
Believed by the age of four, he could levitate.
He said an imaginary friend taught him to read,
and he later learned how to hypnotize people.
In the 1940s, he began serving in the US Navy.
And that's when he really began to believe he had powers.
He believed he was psychokinetic, which would be an equivalent of telekinesis.
You basically can move stuff, create stuff with your mind.
Specifically, he believed that he could cause lightning storms.
So he could control the weather, violent weather.
Even though his grandparents were psychic,
he believed that he was actually chosen by aliens.
That aliens wanted to see what a human body can do.
Here's a quote from him.
"I'm an experiment with them, being the aliens.
I'm an experiment with them, to find out just how much PK power
a human being can absorb and stand.
It took them literally ages to find a human being, myself,
with whom they could communicate back and forth."
What's super interesting is if this story happened anywhere close to the internet age,
things would be completely different.
This story is absolutely fascinating.
It starts and ends right before people can actually document this stuff.
It is fairly well documented, but if this happened nowadays,
he starts saying that he can cause hurricanes.
That's really his bread and butter, right?
One of the most destructive natural events on the planet.
He begins sending letters to the US government saying,
"There's going to be a hurricane. It's going to hit here."
Now, he wasn't just sending them to some flunky of the government.
He was doing that, but he was also letting other people know.
Wayne Grover, for example, became a confidant of his later on.
So he's sending out these letters to the US government,
but obviously they're just thinking he's a crackpot.
He has this weird, quick fall-off.
He didn't seem to be the most stable person to begin with.
I mean, he's levitating at H4, right?
That can't be good for your psyche.
That must give you some sort of...
If it's true, obviously, that would make him feel so far separated from normal people.
How could you even stand being around them?
But he does have a family.
In 1969, he quits his job.
He's really not doing much, but he believes that he should be paid for his powers.
That people should pay him because he's so powerful.
He has this weird money-making scheme where he starts to send letters to football teams
and say, "If you don't pay me X amount of money, your team's going to lose."
People are like, "What? No, we're not going to do that, obviously. We're not going to do that."
And then the game would come, Sunday would come,
disastrous loss for the team.
Now, there's an easy way and a hard way to do predictions.
The easiest way is to write a riddle,
and then afterwards, anything that even comes close to the riddle go,
"Predicted that."
That's not what Ted Owens was doing.
He would send letters out to everybody,
send them out to news agencies, to football coaches,
friends of his, Wayne Grover, who ends up becoming a close confidant of his,
would get letters and say, "Buffalo bills are going to suck today."
And everyone goes, "They always suck."
And he goes, "No, no, especially suck today." And they would watch the game with bated breath
and they would just lose.
Fumbles, mistakes, stuff that they should know better.
They'd lose.
But the teams weren't paying him money.
Is it a fluke? What's going on here?
But he would predict it, send it out to multiple people,
and then say, "See, I told you, you need to pay me money or your sports team's going to fail."
What does it have to do with lightning?
Well, trust me, that was basically on an off day when he was messing with football games.
At one point, he thinks the city of Cleveland is dissing him,
that they weren't giving him the respect he deserves,
which, I mean, that's how any normal person feels in any city, right?
But we're not Ted Owens. He sends out letters.
Cleveland disrespected Ted Owens.
Cleveland is going to pay.
I will cause devastation. I will cause a heat wave to strike the city.
People are going to go mad. They're going to hear voices.
Lightning storms, plane crashes, blackouts across the city.
Nobody disrespects Ted Owens.
That summer, lightning storms killed three people in the city.
Citywide blackout, week-long heat wave,
and oddly enough, people were calling up City Hall at all hours.
"Hello? Hello? City Hall?"
"You gotta get it out of my head. What's going on?"
"I can hear them. I can hear God in my head, and you gotta get the voices out.
Gotta get 'em out."
Some people said they were getting messages in their head being from space,
or getting intercepting secret transmissions from spies.
That was May 30th, 1972,
when he made the claim that he was going to strike out the city of Cleveland.
And then that summer, we had all of that.
January 30th, 1976, Ted Owens said he would end the California drought.
He began sending these letters out. "I will end the drought."
"Could use a little extra money to take care of it, but to show in good faith,
I won't go into this drought."
February 5th, not even a week later, the first snowstorm in 100 years hit San Francisco.
Lightning storms. People are killed.
And this time UFOs are sighted.
There's an increase in UFO sightings around San Francisco.
This is where Wayne Grover and a couple other people enter the scene.
Because National Enquirer is picking up on all this stuff.
In 1979, National Enquirer sends out Wayne Grover and Don Horine
to meet up with Ted Owens, because Ted Owens says he can make a UFO appear like that.
You can just see one with him.
"It'd be great. We'll come out with our photographer.
We're going to stand here in this alleyway.
This UFO is going to appear. It's going to be awesome."
Now, Ted Owens is doing whatever he does.
And at a certain point, Wayne and Don are kind of looking at each other and like,
"This isn't working."
It's like those guys at SIG.
Like, "This isn't working."
So they end up saying, "We don't see a UFO."
Now, Ted goes, "No, no, no. It was right there. I could totally see the UFO."
"Didn't you see me teleport?"
And they're like, "Ted Owens felt that he was disrespected. It was a waste of his time."
This was supposed to be finally some big exposure for him.
Honestly, National Enquirer probably offered him some money,
because they've done stuff like that in the past.
But there's no UFO.
So they leave. The story's over with.
Ted feels double-crossed. He actually curses Don Horin.
"You're going to lose your job. You're going to lose your wife.
And I'm going to bring another drought to Florida."
And all three things happen.
At this point, this is where Wayne Grover,
because Wayne Grover had talked to him before, before the UFO incident as well,
but this is where things really kind of start to take a turn for not just Ted,
but Wayne, because Wayne is now thinking this guy might actually be legit.
And he begins steady phone conversations and mail correspondence with Ted Owens.
And he says, "This is what would happen. I would get a phone call from Ted,
saying something was going very specific, not just like,
'Oh, there's going to be an uprising somewhere in the world.
There'd be like, 'There's going to be a hurricane. It's going to hit here.'
Then I would receive a letter from Ted saying,
'This is where the hurricane's going to hit.'
And then I'd either get a phone call or newspaper clippings,
or both, showing that he was right.
And Wayne Grover started off thinking this was all kind of funny.
In the end, he said it was about 80% accuracy.
That this guy was putting this information forth.
At one point, there was a hurricane headed towards Florida,
and Wayne was talking to Ted, almost jokingly, and was like,
'Yeah, you know, we probably can't afford to get hit by another hurricane.'
Ted goes, 'I'll take care of it. I'll take care of the cane.'
That's what he called him.
He dissipated before it made landfall.
There was another time he said,
'Yeah, there's another hurricane coming. I'll take care of it. I'll take care of it.'
And it went and it hit South Carolina instead and caused massive damage.
Now, obviously, hurricanes are always hitting Florida,
and sometimes they dissipate and things like that.
I actually have a theory about Ted Owens, but let's finish out this story.
He feels like he's powerful, obviously, right?
If you believe that you can create hurricanes to move hurricanes out of the way,
you should be paid for it.
But he was more well-known in the sports pages than he was for anything else.
Sports writers would talk about this guy,
because he would send them articles, he would send them letters saying,
'Philadelphia Eagles are going to have a bad game this Sunday unless the coach pays me X amount of dollars.'
People would want to take it seriously and they would lose.
He was reported about way more in the sports pages than he was covered in national news or anything like that.
And he couldn't deal with that.
He's a superhuman.
I'm sure it's funny. I'm sure some of the teams actually paid him off.
I'm sure that people never admitted to it, but I'm sure a couple of teams actually paid him off.
And he told Wayne, he goes, 'I can't make a team win. I can make a team lose.'
So if a team came to him and said, 'Hey, can we win this week?'
He couldn't make, he couldn't have a good outcome.
He couldn't make an average team better or a better team have good luck.
He could only make a team worse.
In the end, though, he ended up homeless and he's in New York City.
He's still in contact with Wayne Grover at this point and he's completely bitter.
Obviously, I don't think there were many happy homeless people.
He's completely bitter.
And he, to the end, believed the government needed to pay him,
but he also began to confide in Wayne that he felt his powers were diminishing.
He was losing the ability to control the things he used to control.
Wayne Grover said in the end, in 1987, he gets a phone call from Ted Owens and says,
'A UFO's coming to pick me up. Me and my family are in New York City.
A UFO's coming to pick us all up. I want to tell you something, Ted.'
We have this quote from Wayne Grover.
It says, 'The predictions of that last conversation changed my life
and caused me to wonder where science leaves off and the unknown begins.'
His family did not disappear on a UFO. Neither did he.
He ended up dying that year of cirrhosis of the liver.
Interesting story. You see what I mean?
Like, if this was happening nowadays, when he's sending out letters to these newspapers
in the 60s and the 70s and stuff like that and you'd have editors throwing them in the trash
or passing them around as jokes,
did you imagine if he had access to YouTube or any internet forum?
I mean, it would be a totally different ballgame, right?
Now, it's definitely possible that this guy was making random guesses.
80% is outside the chance of randomness, but we're taking Wayne Grover's word for that thing.
He's saying, 'I definitely was getting a lot of hits from this guy.'
But yeah, if that had happened today where everything could be documented,
he could pull out his phone and go, 'I got a prediction for you.'
The Buffalo Bill still suck.
Just a million views. Actually, that'd be his least viewed video.
They're like, 'Yeah, yeah, I know.'
But imagine that pulling out YouTube, going on Snapchat.
A real-life 2028 man, right?
But one who could also control lightning.
I have a theory about this guy.
It's very interesting because there's very--
There's a lot of resources on this guy and they basically all corroborate each other.
There's a book called The PK Man which kind of combines all this stuff.
There's three possibilities.
One who's just very lucky.
But someone who dies homeless with cirrhosis of the liver,
I don't think you can define as lucky.
He just had good guessing abilities too.
He did have the ability to call down lightning to stop storms.
He claimed that he actually killed 100 people who were in an airplane once through lightning.
I wasn't able to corroborate that.
I only found that in one source, so I didn't include that in the main narrative.
So he would claim a bunch of stuff. We don't know if that's true.
But he said that he can call down lightning, he can create and diminish storms and all that stuff.
He can make football teams win and lose. These are his powers.
What other power or what other ability would give you all of those things?
Time traveler.
Every single one of those events would have been documented, right?
Hurricane reports, massive storms, electrical disturbances in the city,
teams winning and losing, every single thing.
You could even add UFO sightings to that.
I have a list of nearly every UFO sighting in the world.
I check it out all the time. Time traveler.
Someone who came back with the knowledge of the world before him.
That would actually be a more reasonable answer than someone who would have the ability to do these things.
Because that's why he said, "I can't make one team better, but I can make a team lose. He just knows which team loses."
And it wouldn't be every game.
It would be games with losses that were so odd that they would stick out.
And the ones that he got wrong would just be ones he forgot.
So I think a time traveler makes more sense, but more interesting than that is what if he's an unwilling time traveler?
What if he didn't travel back in time as an adult?
But traveled back in time as a child, lived an adult life in a future, traveled back in time and relived the life and remembered the things.
And even weirder, what if it's backwards reincarnation?
I know now I'm just kind of throwing stuff out there, but...
Someone who lived in the future and they reincarnated in the past. A true glitch in the system.
Wasn't able to predict what movies were going to be big box office hits.
Wasn't interested in that in the future.
Was interested in sports? Interested in hurricanes?
Interested in weird events?
And whether they ended up here as a time traveler and simply made up a story of their past,
or something even weirder happened, reincarnating backwards or time traveling back and being reborn,
none of it's provable, obviously.
But it would be interesting to see what the SIG, that skeptic group, could test with Ted Owens.
He could either come out there and go, "I'm going to cause lightning in five days." And then a massive storm hits and they can go, "Ugh."
Or he could just arrange for the test to take place on a Tuesday.
And sit there and go, "A freak storm is hitting Talladega right now."
They go and they check the news.
What? Because he knew that was coming.
The whole time I was reading the story I was thinking, time traveling, he knows these events, he can't control them, he's predicting them.
And it would be even more interesting if he doesn't know he's predicting them.
He feels a tingle in his skin.
He gets a hint of a memory, a vision, some might call it.
But it's really just him remembering, sitting down and watching a game and going, "Those damn bills!"
Can't believe they lost again.
Like they always do.
I don't know why I bet money on them.
Ted Owens, the PK man as he's known, is all but forgotten nowadays. I had no idea who this guy was.
I never heard this story before. Some of you guys may be familiar with him, but I hadn't heard of it.
It's fairly well documented.
Of course, one of the documentarians is working for the National Enquirer, which throws a lot of stuff in a suspect, but not everything.
Did Ted Owens have special powers that would have earned him $250,000 today?
Or was he just able to predict the future, which would also earn him $250,000?
His biggest problem wasn't that he was a man born with special powers, and the world didn't understand him.
His biggest problem was he was a man born with special powers in the wrong time period.
He was born today. Not only would he have $250,000, he would have a massive following of fans, of worshippers, falling at his feet, waiting for his next prediction.
On YouTube, on TikTok, on Instagram, on Twitter.
If Ted Owens was a time traveler, he ended up coming back to the wrong time.
[Music]
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]
(upbeat music)