Is there a house in Michigan that is haunted because of the work of a serial killer?
And then we take a trip on a UFO with a young boy, Roger S.
He woke up one night to find aliens standing around his bed,
and he stumbled into one of the greatest conspiracies today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having an awesome day leading into an awesome weekend.
I've actually had a really good week.
I've actually had a really, really good week.
If you listen to the first episode, I was a little distraught because of the whole job situation,
but everything's been going great.
It's been awesome.
And I want to thank you guys for being such awesome listeners.
Really, really appreciate it. You guys rock.
And I also want to say this too.
I want to give a shout out to three listeners, in particular, WiggleWoggle22,
HerbRoasted, and H.Sucker.
All three of them left five-star reviews on podcast apps.
It could have been iTunes, could have been Podcast Addict, Spotify.
I'm not for sure, but all three of them left.
Not only did they leave five-star reviews, but they left pretty detailed reasons
why they thought the show deserved five-stars.
So I really, really appreciate that, guys.
That helps get the word out too.
Any way that you can support the show is always appreciated.
And I appreciate you guys so much.
You guys rock.
Let's go ahead and move on to our first story here.
So let's go ahead and hop in the Jason Jalopy.
We're going to drive to Detroit, Michigan.
That was supposed to be the eight-mile song, but it wasn't.
We're driving to Detroit, Michigan, right?
And we're going, specifically, we're going to the Brush Park Historic District.
So load up.
Let's go to stop at the gas station.
You can get a bunch of Fago.
Yeah, Glu-Glu-Glu-Glu-Glu-Glu.
So we got our sugar rush in.
Mm-mm-mm.
So I don't think I've, I think I've had Fago once, one time.
I imagine it tastes like Shasta, but a Fago famed drink of the insane clown posse, famed drink.
I think you can only get it in Detroit, Michigan.
I'm pretty sure it's just Ford factory runoff water that they slap a label on.
And depending on the color of the water, that's the quote-unquote flavor.
But anyways, prove me wrong.
Send me a bunch of free Fago.
It's Detroit, Michigan.
We're in Brush Park Historic District.
We're specifically going to the Hot Mansion.
Now, I'm sure I'm mispronouncing that.
Not the word mansion, but "Hot H-A-U."
How often do I spell stuff out on this show?
H-A-U-G-H-T.
The hot, I don't want you to think it's Nelly's house.
It's not the Hot Mansion.
It's the Hot Mansion.
Anyways, it's just this building on an empty lot.
And we're just standing there.
We're looking up at this.
And he goes, "So, who wants to go in first?"
And you volunteer because you're the bravest of all of us and you go in first.
And in about 20 minutes, you haven't come back out yet.
We're just drinking Fago.
We'll start painting our faces.
We're juggalos now.
And you still haven't come out.
So we're like, "Well, that's the end of that segment.
Now let's go on to the next one."
No, eventually, though, we are going to have to go on a look for you.
In particular, we're walking where shiny flashlights around.
Spooky place.
Now, this place became famous recently because of an urban explorer.
And he wrote a book and it was like a photo essay type book.
And in this book, this house is featured.
The book is called "13, An American Horror Story."
And it's all about like these ancient decrepit buildings and their sinister past and experiences
that this urban explorer, he goes by the name "Seph Lawless."
It's illegal a lot of times to do urban exploring.
So the fact that he's using a pseudonym makes sense.
But anyways, Seph Lawless has photographed.
Guys, don't do the comments just yet.
The Seph Lawless is photographing these locations.
He wrote this book and he's kind of popularized this one.
So we're walking around.
So we've seen this place in Seph's Lawless beautiful photography.
We're walking around and it looks great.
But the problem is we find you.
We find you cowering in the corner.
Get up, man.
Come on.
He's like, "No, no, no.
I was just pretending to cower.
I was just pretending to wet my pants.
I wanted to, it was a social experiment.
We're like, "Yeah, yeah, we still love you."
So this place was a gentleman's club for, it was a whorehouse basically back in the 1920s.
Probably a better way to put it.
But it was a little bit higher than a whorehouse because it was for the wealthy and the elite.
So you want to just go down there and it wasn't just like Betty, who was the girl there.
It was like Esmerelda, who, it's still Betty.
She changed her name, put some more makeup.
But that was this place.
What happened was in 1941, this is according to the Courier Mail.
It's a newspaper, obviously.
1941.
The place was shut down because there was more.
People kind of turned a blind eye to it because one,
it serviced the elite, serviced in more than one way, the elite of the city.
And two people were kind of like, "Oh, you know, it's the Roaring Twenties and then the Roaring Thirtys.
But by the forties, people go, "Las, shut it down."
All this new anti-prostitution laws got passed.
Law enforcement really put an elbow on the place that got shut down.
So it was just an empty building sitting there of a glorious past where you could go and pay money and have sex with beautiful women.
Now it was just a place where bums showed up to have sex with each other.
In the 1960s, though, a phone call was made to the police.
"Hey, guys, I was just down here being a bomb, being a homeless person.
And there's something down here. It smells really, really bad.
Apparently Rick Sanchez was a homeless person in Detroit, Michigan."
The cops go down there and as they're getting close to the place, they can smell it.
Uh-oh.
So they walk in, they're walking around and get their flashlights ready.
You smell that? Yeah, yeah, I smell it. I smelled it out there.
I mean, why are you even asking me that, bro?
Of course I smelled it.
They go down and they follow the smell like straight-up fruit loop in it down to the basement.
And there's just bodies everywhere.
Like, do quick, quick cut flashes of all these individual bodies.
[imitates gunshot]
Straight CSI style. And then we're gonna do a cut to police scene tape.
I wonder when police scene tape was invented.
I don't think they had it in 1941.
Oh wait, when does this happen?
This happened in the 1960s, so I don't think they had it in the 1960s.
'Cause you would need... I wonder how they used old-timey police tape.
The Papyrus, did they use that back in Egyptian days?
They're like, "Okay, guys, cordon off this area."
I guess originally you probably just used string.
But I wonder if it said police on it.
Anyways, they cordon off the area somehow.
They just stand... they just have a cop standing every few inches.
Cordon off the area, bringing homicide investigators.
A ton of bodies down there.
Now, to this day we don't know exactly how many bodies were in this basement.
It was enough to make the place stink from outside the building.
But each of the bodies had what seemed to be a perfect circle carved in the torso.
So some people have thought that this is some sort of cult.
Maybe the elite came back to continue to use the building.
Now that they couldn't like, you know, bang people there,
they're just going to use it for other elite activities.
Even sacrifices.
Some people believe it was a serial killer who that was his place to dump the bodies.
And it wasn't until they just got...
The homeless people just were living there and just like, "Ah, what are you going to do?"
Like, there's two or three bodies in the basement.
But I've lived in worse place.
And again, it's Detroit, Michigan.
So two or three bodies in your basement, you're like, "Yeah, it's normal."
But by the time the human body started to stack up and homeless people,
I mean, imagine waking up to that smell.
So some people think it's a cult.
Some people think it's a serial killer.
Now, what's funny is there is an other urban explorer who goes by the name Nailhead.
And he's actually nailed this one on the head.
He's actually figured out this thing.
Seth Lawless made it up.
It never happened.
Now, this, like I said, this was featured in his book, "13 An American Horror Story."
And this house and 12 other locations were published all over the internet.
Look at this spooky photos and read about these terrifying backstories of these locations.
And I found out about this on an Italian website called illparanormale.com.
And they said, "This is the true story about this mansion that has all these bodies in it that's haunted today."
And here's a photograph of it.
And I go, "Oh, that's interesting."
And then I start researching it.
And I'm finding these other things.
13 ghost locations that are super spooky.
Courier Mail did actually run an article on it.
Headlined 13 Real-Life Haunted Houses in the Horror Stories that go with them.
Nailhead, this other urban explorer, followed this story up.
Whole stories made up.
Seth Lawless is an urban explorer.
He exists.
He does take these photographs, but he made up the backstory to sell the book.
Nailhead was just using the photograph and having a rough idea, Detroit, Michigan,
seeing where the photograph is at, seeing where these photographs are at,
was able to locate the building in real life.
It was a border house.
And this Nailhead goes through all of these public documents.
He's like, "I'm really going to disprove this one.
This is absolutely ridiculous because I know for a fact that he's making this stuff up."
He begins going through public records and he goes, "Listen, I'll be honest with you guys.
It was a border house.
People died there, but people tend to die at home."
And he begins listing all of the elderly people who've died there.
There wasn't, they weren't rotting so bad that the hobos were leaving.
There were no hobos.
It did become a derelict building, but as of 2016, they're rebuilding it.
The people who bought the property are like, "Guys, no, it's not haunted.
That story's totally made up."
Seth Lawless early on before this gets out that he's caught doing this,
has this quote.
He calls his war creative nonfiction.
So he's saying it's true, but it's creative.
Here's a quote from him.
"It's taking real life stories and making them appear to be fiction.
The goal is to make the reader become so enthralled by the details and the fantasy
that they forget the story is real."
Unquote.
Now, Huffington Post did a "Here's 13 Spooky Things" and think about it.
It's a puff piece.
It really is a "Here's 13 Photographs."
They are beautiful photographs, but here's 13 photographs.
That'll make your skin crawl.
Ooh, probably came out around Halloween.
Maybe sometimes it came around the release of his book,
but if he was smart, he'd release the book around Halloween.
A puff piece article.
"18 Things You Can Do With Cheez-Its."
Stuff like that.
They issued a retraction on this puff piece.
People aren't going to write it and say,
"You can't do those 18 Things With Cheez-Its.
They just let the article stand.
It's garbage article for clicks to get money."
Whatever.
They issued a retraction.
They said, "Listen, a lot of our readers have reached out to us
to let us know this is fake.
However, we want to leave the article up for historical purposes."
And I think, one, they're getting--
They did put the retraction at the very top of the articles, like, bam.
As art, the photos are beautiful.
Now, the backstory is totally, again, totally made up.
We know for a fact that the hot mansion one is fake,
but we do know that the hot mansion is fake.
That story is totally made up.
And it's most likely the other ones are as well,
especially since Huffington Post was like,
"Hey, so many of our readers have written in."
And that was the end of that.
So, it's really disingenuous because part of being in the paranormal community is trust, right?
Like, that's part of it, is that when we read these sources, we trust that they're accurate,
but this guy is just manufacturing this stuff wholesale.
And it really goes to show that a lot of it probably is as well.
This guy just happened to get caught.
So, Nailhead, thanks for exposing that.
I mean, and as an urban explorer and as a photographer,
Seth Lawless is-- I'm sure he's pretty good at what he does,
but as a author of creative nonfiction,
he's just muddy in the waters for everyone else.
And let's go ahead and move on.
Let's use it as a transition for our next story.
Because our next story, while not knowably false,
it's recently come to light.
I could-- the only reference I can find to this was back from November of 2019.
So, super recent story.
It's fascinating, but it'll be interesting to find out
if we get any additional information regarding this.
But let's go ahead.
We're hot back in the Jason Jalopy.
We've gotten you a brand new pair of clothes.
You're like, "Thanks, Jason.
I bought you some straight up Dickies pants.
We're wiping off our Juggalo face paint,
buying one more 2L of Fago for each of us.
I get the orange flavor."
And we're driving off bumping some ICP to Orlando, Florida.
Now, most of this information I'm getting is from--
because I want to give credit to this guy who wrote this awesome article.
His name is Marcus Loth--
Loth? I just really can't pronounce names.
Marcus Loth, he writes for ufounsight.com.
I've got a ton of stuff from him.
They seem to be a pretty reputable website.
But again, this story, because we're only just hearing about it
and it took place so long ago, it does raise a little red flags.
But I find it very, very fascinating.
So we're going to take off our skeptic hat for a bit.
We're going to take our baseball cap and turn it backwards.
Even though we've left Detroit, we still got Detroit inside our hearts.
And we get to Orlando, Florida.
It's April 29th, 1989.
It's 1130 p.m.
There's a little boy, little 10-year-old boy laying in bed.
He goes by the name Roger S.
It's an interesting pseudonym to use because Roger S.
is actually hard to find on the internet
because he keeps wanting to pull up Rogers.
Rogers.
So a detail to make it more difficult to verify this story
or just a pseudonym that accidentally makes it difficult to track stuff down.
Who knows?
But Roger S.
10-years-old little boy, he's sleeping.
Wakes up in the dark of his room.
But he's not alone.
Not alone.
Standing around him in the darkness, he sees four aliens.
And by all description, they fit the classical gray pattern.
Little arms, tiny little bodies, short, about four, four and a half feet.
But he describes her head as being heart-shaped.
So it's not the typical giant oval, but basically like a heart.
So right there, there's kind of an interesting detail,
something that kind of sets it apart from other alien stars.
But everything else, no nose, slit mouth, big eyes,
but the head had a lump in the little valley and then another lump.
It wasn't the straight old big old egg head of the gray aliens.
They're standing around him.
And their mouths, actually, this was another detail.
They wore slits, but they were gold mouths.
So the pale skin, gold mouth.
So where they doing makeup before they are like,
"Oh, we got to get ready for this abduction.
We're going to look so beautiful."
"Sally, don't!"
Beauty school dropouts playing over there.
I wonder if they listen to music in UFOs, dude.
Because think about it, like when you're in a battleship,
I've never been in a battleship at sea.
But you know, I've seen like under siege,
that documentary that came out a long time ago.
As you're walking along in a battleship, right?
I'm sure like you walk by the cook.
He's like bumping some guns and roses, right?
Please correct me if I'm wrong.
I can't have never been on a battleship.
But you think like if for an interstellar journey,
or if you're just time traveling or whatever,
coming from other dimensions, however you have those get here.
You don't need to listen to music.
I actually have a theory that aliens don't have music.
They don't listen to me.
They don't know what music is.
I think music may be a completely human thing.
You look at all the alien encounters ever.
Ever.
There's very rarely, is there any mention of art or drawing
or anything like that or music?
So that's kind of creepy to think you can have an entire race.
No music.
None.
Because music is such a part of the human experience.
Just to the point where we've created an entire industries
that you can press a button and listen to any music you want at any time.
It's like water for humans.
It's available everywhere.
To imagine a species that that's not important to is very weird.
But anyway, so while we're considering those implications,
this 10 year old boy is getting abducted.
We're standing in the bedroom.
I'm like, but no, I mean, have you ever heard of an alien hitting the bongos?
The kid's like, help me.
Help me.
These aliens, they throw him on a hover bed and it starts to kind of hover out of his house.
Now, I don't know how the layout of his house is.
I don't know if it's like hovering down the stairs and then going through the foyer.
But eventually he's in this hover bed and he can't move.
Because what's the point of having to hover bed if you just kind of get up and hop off of it?
And the hover beds leaving his house and he sees a saucer in his backyard.
He blacks out.
He's inside the ship now and these aliens are standing around him and he can talk to him telepathically.
The aliens are doing that.
He's able to talk back back and forth.
One of the aliens ask, what are you?
Thanks about it for a second.
He goes, a human boy.
Pretty basic, pretty basic way you would explain it.
You want to say that to another human.
But when you're talking to an alien, that would be how you would describe yourself.
Aliens are bringing him on this craft and then he's on this hover bed and he sees a row of panels.
All these different visual images that are going to be feeding him information here.
And on one of them, he sees his friend Nancy.
Assumably she's asleep as well at her house.
But in one of these panels, he sees her in the hospital.
And so he asks, where's my friend Nancy?
Why is she in the hospital?
And the aliens are just kind of going about their business, but they're communicating with him and they go,
she's on another ship.
She's on another ship right now.
And then we have this interesting quote.
She will not be reborn because she has been born too many times.
Long alien fingers just hitting buttons on a control panel.
Ten year old boy is just sitting there in this UFO trying to digest everything.
One, he's been abducted by aliens.
That's kind of bizarre.
Two, his friend who should be sleeping in her house is in a hospital somewhere.
And now he's been hit with this idea that not only is there reincarnation, but there's a limit to it.
And aliens have some hand or knowledge in reincarnation.
The alien ship is flying around in the cosmos at this point.
And the aliens take him on a tour of the ship.
He's walking through and he's kind of doing this whole like walking through looking in doors and stuff like that.
He walks past the room.
These aliens are leading past the room.
He sees what he describes as a 30 year old man just kind of sitting on a table looking at Roger.
And aliens kind of looking, doing steady in the 30 year old man.
He moves to the next room.
He goes to this one room.
The aliens take off his pajamas and they give him a red suit that Roger puts on and he says,
when I put it on, it clung to his skin.
So it didn't matter what size he wore, it was the perfect size for him.
And he said it was red and it had what appeared to be hieroglyphics.
Now he's walking around in his cool jumpsuit.
That's an interesting detail too, because a lot of times when aliens wear clothes,
they always talk about how form fitting it is.
Very rarely have we come across alien stories where they're wearing baggy clothes.
He gets taken to another room.
There's another panel there and he's showing this specifically on this panel is him sleeping in bed.
What?
Just like pre-recorded?
Did you guys plan this?
What is going on?
And he's watching himself sleep in bed and he sees his dad actually open the bedroom door
and go in and kind of look, check on him and then go back to sleep.
And that's when it dawns on Roger.
This is happening now.
He's watching video footage of right now.
So now he's really, he's like, "Well, where am I?
Like, am I having an out-of-body experience?"
Which is something that a child wouldn't be able to process.
I don't think anyone would be able to process any of this information, but am I still there and this is,
I'm having an out-of-body experience?
Is that a clone?
Is that a doppelganger?
Little Roger's sitting in bed and what if the dad walked up and touched it and it,
that would actually be creepy that dad walks up and he like touches it.
Two minutes of doppelganger and it's not alive and the dad's like, "Oh no, my son's passed away."
And then the aliens look at him and look at Roger and be like,
"Well, that was unfortunate. We can't take you back home now because how would we explain you coming back to life?
I don't know."
Or maybe, who knows what it was?
Who knows what it was?
But yeah, that if their plan was discovered halfway through, it's not like the aliens could show up with the real Roger
and say, "Oh, here you go."
Like, it would be too late.
I don't know. That was kind of a grim thought experiment.
He also, then they show him on this panel, video of himself skiing down a mountain in the future.
He sees himself as an, this is a trippy one.
And again, we really have to wonder like, what is behind the story?
But he sees himself as an older man, not super old, but you know, older than ten, skiing down a mountain.
He's taken into another room and there are heart-shaped head aliens with gold lips.
But these ones are orange.
They have an orangish tint during your way to that Fego, I bet.
And he is told that these ones are the female of the species.
Little orangies, little females.
And they begin to ask him questions about how humans procreate and he's like, "Bfff, dude, don't ask me.
I'm ten years old. I have no idea.
You abducted the wrong person.
I couldn't even begin.
I don't even know what procreate is."
And he's like, "Yeah, that's fair enough."
He then goes into a room which seems to be kind of common in some of these stories.
It's a room full of animals.
A zoo, basically.
And we always hear the same description.
There's a mixture of real-life animals, so bears, badgers, boars, butterflies, baboons, banana slugs,
and so forth.
But also animals that he couldn't identify.
Does that mean that the animals are alien?
Does that mean the animals are from Earth that he's just not familiar with?
We don't know.
I guess the implication is they're alien.
And again, since we're already on and if somebody on Earth said, "I saw an animal the other day.
I've never seen it before. I think it's an alien animal."
You would be like, "No, dude, you're an idiot. It's a real animal.
Let's go look at it."
But if you're already on a UFO and you're going to expect to see animals you've never seen before,
but I've come across this a lot recently.
People talking about these space zoos aboard UFOs, which would make sense because they're abducting people anyways.
And again, that goes to show why our cows getting...
I believe cows are getting mutilated, but I don't think they're UFOs.
If anything, it's a human colt, some weird colt thing.
But it doesn't make sense for a UFO to abduct a cow, suck all their blood up, and then throw them back onto the Earth.
Why not just incinerate them?
They can cut the cosmos in half with their vehicles.
They don't have a heat ray.
They don't have a crematory.
But then they also are keeping all these other animals.
It doesn't make sense.
Cattle mutilations on a UFO perspective doesn't make sense.
But then we come to the most interesting room, which honestly for this story is a bit of a high bar.
We've got space zoos.
We got seen into the future.
We got the idea of out-of-body experience versus photocopies of humans being left so abductions can go on undetected.
Did the father...
That's kind of interesting thing too.
I'm not a parent myself, but did the father wake up in the middle of the night because he just felt something was off?
Does he always check on his son?
Or did something prompt him that night to kind of wake up and feel a little uneasy?
Something in the pit of his stomach that made him go in and check on his son and go, "Oh, everything's okay."
When his son was really possibly millions of miles away.
So it's a pretty weird story.
We got reincarnation.
We got hieroglyphics, spaces.
But for the creme de la creme, for the coup de gras, whatever French term you want, the aliens really saved the best for last.
So we got all this stuff going on.
The aliens take him to one final room and he sees a bunch of other humans in there.
So we've already seen the 130 year old man sitting on the table, but now we have a bunch of humans sitting in this room.
And there's a bunch of like hover beds as well.
But the humans aren't on the hover beds.
The humans are wearing what Roger could identify as NASA uniforms.
And on the hover beds are unconscious aliens.
And the humans are running experiments on him and taking notes.
Roger is then dropped off at home now being shown the greatest conspiracy possible involving UFOs.
He's dropped off at home.
We specifically get this quote from UFO Insight.
The next thing he knew, he was alone in his room, which in normal terms means he woke up.
Like I said, the earliest we found the story was November 2019.
And I keep seeing the same phrase.
It says Roger S.
This is the story of Roger S.
As told by James Greenin.
But I can't find a James Greenin in UFOology.
I can't find...
I found a bunch of James Greenins, but I couldn't find a particular James Greenin who's attached to this story in any sort of way.
So who knows why this story is just getting exposed now?
Who's James Greenin is?
Roger S. wants to keep his identity secret.
I understand.
I mean, it does make the story harder to verify, but I do understand that.
So there's a little bit of suspicions.
There could be a ton of reasons why this is like this.
And but I think we'll assume for the sake of the story that it's true.
The narrative is true because I'd rather address some of the stuff there.
The idea of the aliens having access to the future.
The idea that the aliens have access to the knowledge of life and death.
That makes them feel more supernatural than alien.
But the idea that you have these aliens being tied to these abilities I've seen in the future past lives makes you wonder if there's not a more supernatural element than we previously thought.
To me, though, the more interesting thing is the humans.
Not only are humans working with aliens, but that humans are experimenting on aliens on an alien starship with the alien's knowledge.
I guess there's always been the suggestion that humans have worked on dead aliens or captured aliens.
And this has always been kind of the X-Files type theory that we found out aliens existed after the crash of Roswell.
The government or members of the shadow government or deep state as it's known today made alliances with the grays or the reptilians or both to have an exchange.
You give us technology to help win the Cold War or to take over the world.
And we will give you humans that you can abduct.
We will not investigate it at all.
It's a quid pro quo situation.
We want technology.
You want humans to experiment on.
That's always been kind of the main.
I don't know if that's as popular as it used to be, but in the 80s and 90s, when I was really into researching UFO abductions and stuff like that,
there was always kind of the underlying conspiracy.
The US government and governments around the world allow people to get abducted in exchange for technology.
I think it's interesting to think that there may be another layer on that, that humans are not just finding dead alien bodies where they can and working on them.
But the aliens themselves may be kidnapping their own alien people to be experimented on by humans.
Does that make sense?
Like, is it possible that there is an alien planet where there was some young, heart shaped alien headed kid playing bloke arc?
And then he does his homework, does his space work, lives his life, says goodbye to his friend,
walks in bloke arc and eats his noodles because they have that everywhere.
And then goes to bed and then he wakes up and there's four six foot tall humans standing around his bed in uniforms with a weird emblem on it.
And the next thing he knows, he's being pulled around the ship.
You see some of his fellow aliens there, but he's mostly being worked on by these tall, pale creatures with small heads and beady little eyes.
I find that idea fascinating.
That they may not just be abducting us, we may be abducting them.
And both are working together for whatever means, whatever the end result is, both are working together.
And we're just the experiments.
We're all just the pawns in this game of the powerful of the alien planet and the powerful of Earth.
And if that's true, it's kind of interesting.
It's kind of an interesting thing because maybe it's not us versus the elite and their alien allies.
Maybe it's us and a planet full of alien us's workers and dreamers and lovers, just of a different species from a different planet
that are also being preyed upon by their corrupt government who made a deal with another corrupt government thousands of light years away.
Because if that's the case, then we have allies.
We have friends.
Someday will we not be fighting an alien race, but be allied with an alien race to overthrow both of our systems of tyranny.
Who knows?
But it's an interesting spin on the idea of the alien brotherhood.
We're not going to join some galactic federation and become just a cog in the machine.
We're going to team up with other oppressed peoples across the galaxy and overthrow those governments that thought we were just there as specimens.
An interesting theory that may simply be based on the dream of a 10-year-old boy.
But it could be the start of a beautiful friendship.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
Twitter is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm so glad you listened to it today.
Have a great weekend, guys.
[Music]