A terrifying encounter with part of a ghost.
A spectral spirit warns a young woman of an upcoming tragedy.
And then we are going to travel to the deserts of the Southwest United States.
It may seem like an odd choice, but if you want to see Bigfoot, that's really where you
need to go today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover today, so we're not going to be chit-chatting too much here.
Actually, we're not going to be chit-chatting at all.
We're done with the intro.
Let's go ahead and jump into the first story.
Now, the first story is really short, but it's super creepy.
And there's a hotel that is listed as being haunted, and it only has one sighting.
But the sighting is so creepy that that's all you need.
We're going to Arizona.
Aren't we just in Arizona?
Oh yeah, the big skeleton dude and the phantasma Colorado, the camel one.
In Arizona, there's a hotel called the Lost Trail Hotel.
In 1976, the year I was born, actually.
Pretty awesome.
I'm a little baby during this story.
I'm just like a newborn baby.
I'm like, "Ummmmmm."
The whole story, I just want you to imagine me crying and pooping my pants, or my diaper.
So anyways, that aside, we're in the Lost Trail Hotel.
The year is 1976.
Hey wait, that was the year I was born.
I was just joking.
Okay, so 1976, there's a couple sleeping at the Lost Trail Hotel, and they hear a "Ahhhh!"
Just a scream.
That hurt my throat.
They heard this screaming in the hallway, and they're like, "What the hell is that?"
So they hop out of bed, they open the door, and when they look down the hallway, they
see a severed woman's head just floating, floating in the middle of the hallway.
Long black hair, bright red lips, eyes full of pain and fear, and an open mouth.
"Ahhhh!"
And they're watching, they're just looking at this dumbfounded, and the head slowly begins
to fade away, and as it's fading away, "Ahhhh!"
That is terrifying.
That is the only ghost, again, ghost walking around in the middle, you know, walking around
in the middle of the night, that doesn't scare me.
A severed human head screaming in pain just floating there, even if it's laying on the
ground.
It could be sitting in front of the television on the couch screaming in pain.
It's so terrifying, because then you start thinking, they don't know where the head came
from, they don't know who it was or anything like that.
What happened to this person?
What is happening to this person now?
Are they stuck in some sort of hellish landscape where they're just a screaming head for eternity?
Is that a comic book or the name of a band or something like that?
But it's just horrifying, and it doesn't specifically, there's two ways you can picture it.
You can picture it as a, if someone was wearing like a green screen suit and everything was
chroma keyed out so you just see like a head floating there, or most likely there was like
guts hanging out from the bottom of this head.
But whoever this was, whatever this is for eternity is just a screaming head.
I bet you that it's some horrible soul trapped in the hell dimension.
And Satan's like, dude, you know what?
You just give me, dude, just give me five minutes of peace.
It's been screaming for like 80 years down there, and he's like, oh my God, I'm going
to lose my mind.
So he's just like, that's it.
Here you go, throws it up into earth.
And it's like, oh, and Satan's like, oh my God, five minutes of peace.
And then he hears it start and rematerialize, and he's like, I hate my job.
It sucks.
You know how hard it is to run a marketing firm when there's a screaming head next to
you?
Anyway, so I thought that story was worth covering.
I find it absolutely terrifying.
The next story we're going to talk about is an interesting one, and it actually is going
to lead into a story we do tomorrow.
But it's a complete story.
I don't like doing two parters, but it's just kind of a lead in.
We're in Southern California, and there is a house known as the Harlow House.
And it's known that because Jean Harlow used to live there with her husband, Paul Byrne.
Some of you are already like, oh, I know what this story is.
So Jean Harlow lived there with Paul Byrne.
And you know, they had a weird relationship where they loved each other, but he was also
super abusive.
He was small and there was rumors that he was impotent.
And Jean Harlow was like this bombshell movie star.
Apparently he felt inadequate, but it was this very, very stormy relationship.
He beat her a lot.
He ended up eventually from punching her so much he caused her kidneys to fail.
That's what eventually killed her.
But before she died, he ended up shooting himself.
And she was totally like heartbroken.
She tried killing herself and all this stuff.
He killed himself in his house.
Now we're going to fast forward a few years where a new homeowner bought the house.
And you know, this is down in Southern California.
It's basically around Hollywood, very, very posh area.
New guy buys the house and he has a young friend.
They used to date, but they're not dating anymore, this young woman.
She's like, dude was out of town and the new owner was out of town and she's like, hey,
can I spend the night there?
You know?
And the dude's like, yeah, yeah, you know, I'm in New York for the weekend.
Go ahead, stay there.
So she goes into the house and she's sleeping.
And in the middle of the night, she's woken up.
She doesn't know why, but she just like wakes up at the start and she sees in her bedroom
a short ghost and she recognizes him immediately.
She recognizes it as the ghost of Paul Byrne because she also works in Hollywood and he
was a big agent and she knew that this was previously his house and he's now running
around in the bedroom, just frantically like bumping into stuff, opening stuff, just like
running around her bed.
She's flipping out.
She jumps out of bed, dodges him, steps over him, goes out of the bedroom and she's on
the second story.
I guess I should have mentioned that earlier.
She's on the second story and you have to go down these stairs to get to the bottom,
which is how does normally work?
But at the bottom of the stairs, she sees a horrible sight.
She sees a body tied to the bottom banister and she can't tell if it's her or the home
owner in New York.
She knows it's one of them.
In her mind, she's looking at it and she knows it's one of them and she's thinking, "I have
to be dreaming."
Like, that might be me and I'm here, but she has an emotional connection to that body.
And it is a body because it's not just someone tied to a banister.
It's someone tied to a banister.
Their throat is slit wide open.
They're just drenched in blood.
But she has to walk down the stairs because little dude is still banging into stuff in
the bedroom.
She's terrified.
She walks down the stairs, past the body, just slumped over and she still can't see
its face or doesn't want to see its face.
But she still knows it's either her or the home owner.
She's like, "I need a drink."
But she hadn't really been in the house before.
She couldn't find the bar.
This is a true story, by the way.
She has something in her head tell her, look by the bookcase.
She goes to the bookcase and there was a hidden bar, like a little private bar behind the
bookcase.
It moved over like straight James Bond style.
And she makes herself a drink.
Now, as she starts to make herself drinks, she still hears the noise upstairs of whatever
the little ghost dude bumping into stuff and she can still sense that body still on that
banister.
She's like, "I'm straight up dreaming.
I'm just going to drink until I pass out."
As she's drinking, she's looking around and she sees this gaudy wallpaper and she starts
peeling at it.
And this is like by the bar, she starts peeling at it.
And she's just kind of like trying to keep her mind thinking of anything else other than
the whore that's going on around her.
She eventually drinks herself to sleep.
She wakes up the next morning and there's no body tied to the banister.
The house is quiet.
And she's like, "Well, it just, I don't know what happened."
And she's like, "I must have just been dreaming.
Like I must have been sleepwalking or something."
And then, but she wasn't dreaming because when the homeowner came back, he was like,
"Hey, who was in my bar?
Who was peeling at this wallpaper?"
And she's like, "I got to tell you this story.
I got to tell you the story of what happened."
Now she, this woman told this, she was really into the paranormal.
And she started telling the story around town.
There's multiple witnesses that she told this story to.
When the homeowner came back and he's like, "Yo, what happened?"
She told him about the dream.
Now the homeowner was Jay Sebring and her name was Sharon Tate.
And three years later, they were both murdered a mile away by the Manson family.
And the story has always gone like this.
Was that a premonition of her own violent death?
When she would tell the story, she would say, "I don't know who the body was at the bottom
of the stairs.
I felt like it was either me or Jay."
She would tell the story around town.
There's multiple accounts of the story being told.
And three years later, they were lashed together as the Manson family were killing them.
They were tied together.
Very, very interesting story.
The idea is that Paul, he beat his wife, but he also loved her.
He just had these horrible issues.
The theory is that Paul was a loving person, but he just had inadequacy issues and he took
him out on his wife.
And he was trying to warn Sharon Tate of the danger that was coming.
That's why he woke her up that night.
But who knows?
The first thing is like, did she make up the story?
Did she somehow make up a story that kind of foretold her own death?
Did it really happen?
And she actually told it to people?
Or did people just make it up on their own?
When I said it was a true story, it is a story that is circulated through Hollywood.
People have told the story.
I personally believe it.
I think that that's possible to have a premonition like that.
That's a quite horrifying one.
But yeah.
I think the most interesting part is that she couldn't identify the body, but she had
a feeling it was either her or Jay Sebring.
And it was more of just an essence, an emotional essence of a dead body rather than seeing Jay
Sebring like, "ugh."
I think that would have been less creepy rather than just seeing almost like a soul dead.
And she knew it was a soul belonging to her or her ex-boyfriend, the person she had a
close emotional connection to.
Very, very creepy story.
And that ties into a story we're going to do tomorrow as well.
We're going to do a little paranormal story about the Manson family.
Very, very interesting one that I've been looking into for quite a while.
But let's go ahead and move on to our main story today.
Now, I said in the intro, generally Bigfoot is known to be a forest creature.
You have like the Yeti up in Canada and you have the, no sorry, you have the Yeti in like
the Himalayas and you have the Windigo, which is more of like a ghost type of thing.
You can, a human can become a Windigo.
It's more like a curse, but that's like in Canada.
So Bigfoot's are generally known in California, Oregon, Washington.
And then you have like Swamp Bigfoot type creatures down south and then you have some
other Bigfoot type creatures in Montana.
But it's funny because some of the biggest Bigfoot sightings by hundreds of people at
a single time have been in the desert.
So it makes you think like if Bigfoot exists, are there different subspecies that are acclimated
to different climates?
Oh, I bet you guys are impressed.
I said that word correctly.
And I used it correctly as well.
In the 1950s in Fontana, California, they built this huge raceway.
It's just all flat land.
You can drive as fast as you want.
There's no cops.
Not like there's cops in NASCAR.
They're like Tony Stewart would have won the race if he didn't get pulled over on the
third lap.
Anyways, they built this huge raceway out there.
Now people would go to see the race.
That's not true.
They'd go to see Cars Crash.
I used to be a big NASCAR fan, but I just don't have time to watch sports anymore.
They'd go to watch the race.
So it was basically just like this big, flat raceway.
I think, yeah, well, yeah, I would have been flat.
They don't have hills and like loop-de-loops.
It's not a Hot Wheels track.
But anyways, so the people would be out there to watch the races and they would see Bigfoot.
Bigfoot just walk on by.
Now it would be off in the distance.
It wouldn't be like at the concession stand.
One popcorn please.
They're like, sir, how are you going to pay for this?
It pays for them for like goat pelts.
They'd seem like walking in the distance, but you would have 50, 100 people sitting
there watching a...
And then just in the distance, you just see Bigfoot walk by.
And it was so common in the area they nicknamed it the Speedway Monster, which is a badass
name.
That's way better than Bigfoot.
Speedway Monster.
I'm sure there should be at least 10 bands named that at least.
There should be a governor named that, Governor Speedway Monster.
So anyways, you'd see the Bigfoot guy just walk in the distance and it happened fairly
regularly.
Now, of course you're going to say how come no one took a picture of it.
I don't know.
That's a good question.
In the same area in 1952, these stories all interestingly involved very aggressive Bigfoot.
They're not just kind of like walking lazily through the woods all blurry.
That's a joke.
That actually stole that joke from a comedian.
I don't remember his name.
He's a really funny comedian.
But anyway, so they don't normally just walk through the woods and stuff like that.
These ones are quite aggressive.
So in 1956, this boy's walking home.
This is creepy.
These are all actually all these stories are creepy.
These are creepier than the normal Bigfoot stories.
And that's why I picked them because I don't just like talking about stuff that's just
kind of lame.
The boy's walking home just has like his little fishing pole on.
It's 1956.
So he has his fishing pole on his back, a little tackle box.
All of a sudden, huge hairy arms reach out of the bushes and grab onto him and try to
pull him into the foliage.
And the boy gets away and runs home and goes, "Mom, mom!
Giant hairy man tried to pull me into the bushes!"
And the mom's like, "That's weird.
Your uncle Jimmy's at work."
But that story is creepy because the idea of a creature, like what was it going to do
to the kid?
Eat him?
Like sell him into like Bigfoot slavery?
We don't know.
What's interesting, what I kind of think about that is how did this boy get away from a Bigfoot?
They're these massive creatures.
And how does a Bigfoot hide in a bush?
I mean, if maybe it was like an eight foot hedge, he might have a chance.
That would actually explain why the Bigfoot wasn't able to pull the kid in because the
kid kept like hitting the thick branches of the bush.
Bigfoot's like, "Can't get him.
Angle him right."
And the boy's like, "Get away.
Get away."
And he runs away.
"Uncle Jimmy, mommy told you to stop that!"
So anyways, now, oh, and that same year, these are all reported in local newspaper.
Same year, a girl was sitting in her car in the middle of nowhere.
Yeah, right.
I think she was probably doing something else, but she's apparently innocently sitting in
her car in the middle of nowhere.
This creature smashed through her driver's side window and tried to pull her out and
she gassed it and took off.
The creature's like shaking its hand in the air, "Get you next time!"
Now, again, I mean, maybe these big feet have less upper body strength, I don't know.
But I think it probably should have really just like ripped your arm off of its socket.
I'm glad it didn't.
I'm just saying that.
Those stories can kind of be taken with a grain of salt.
The next story we have in that area in 1975, Boy Scouts just hanging out, doing Boy Scout
stuff, cooking marshmallows in the middle of the night telling ghost stories.
Bigfoot just walks through the middle of their camp and just trashes the place.
You can imagine all these kids are like, "Isn't this fun?
We're hanging around the middle of nowhere and we got all this chocolate and these marshmallows."
I mean, just leave ways to the camp.
Didn't kill any of the Boy Scouts.
But I mean, that's just being a dick, dude.
Like you could have went around their camp.
Their camp wasn't three miles long.
It was basically big enough to hold 12 young boys and you had to walk through the middle
of it, tore everything up.
But the boys ran back to town and said, "Hey, our camp got destroyed by a speedway monster."
And the cops like that.
It's such a badass name.
He's like writing it down on the police report.
He trials like a little car with like flames coming off of it.
We're still in the Southwest.
Now we're at the Borrego Badlands.
Now this is a place that when it's very inhospitable, there's a bunch of like deep underground caves.
There's a lot of canyons and crevices and things like that.
And when Spanish missionaries came to the area, the natives in the area were like, "Hey,
welcome.
Like, you know, let's talk.
Let's chat.
We can do this stuff."
Don't go to the river.
The Spanish missionaries are like, "Why can't we go near the river?"
And he's like, "Because there's a bunch of big feet down there and they'll totally mess
you up.
We don't even go there.
They're hairy devils is what we call them."
And the Spanish dudes are like, "Okay, yeah, here."
They're like, "We won't go down there."
And they didn't.
They didn't.
They very wisely were like, "These people have been here for a while.
They probably know something we don't."
In 1876, though, as more Europeans started to pour into the area, gold, Russian, all that
stuff, they did start going to the river.
They're like, "Hey, you know, let's go get a drink of water."
And the Native Americans like, "Single tear coming down their face."
They're like, "No, don't do that."
Prospectors are like, "Whatever.
I'm going down the river."
Of course, people started disappearing.
First sighting was in 1876, dudes walking to the river.
And it's weird, actually.
Maybe these guys do have something.
He sees a creature, an inhuman creature with the face of a human, but a big hairy body
staring at him from some bushes.
It was Uncle Jimmy's ancestor in the bushes, and the creature's like, "No, I'm Bigfoot."
Dude runs away.
Okay, he didn't talk, obviously.
So as civilization began to grow in that area, people started disappearing.
People started dying, and their bodies being found horribly mutilated.
And the Europeans, at this point, they would have been the Americans.
They had heard the legends of the hairy devils, but they didn't believe them.
But since people started dying or disappearing, the legends, people are like, "We better,
like, there's something about this."
People have said they've seen them hiding in the bushes.
People have said, "Help me, help me, and die.
We can't find them."
So it was interesting, too, because one of these, and around this time, these two, this
was in the local newspaper, these two men came across a giant creature who was just
sitting on a rock.
And they said, you know, a typical description, he had the face of a human, but the body
of an ape.
And they looked at him, and they didn't know what to think of it.
And they begin to address him.
First they try to talk to him in English, then they try talking to him in Spanish, and then
they try talking to him in the native tongue in the area.
Very learned prospectors.
And the creature stands up and starts walking towards them, and at that point, they're like,
"Okay, first contact is over."
They pull their guns out, and he runs away.
But because they're having these issues, and so they're, of course, report, "Hey, we saw
one of these things, they're real, they're these giant creatures."
People begin trying to hunt them and kill them, because they're putting two and two together.
We moved in, we were warned to stay away from the river, we were warned about hairy devils,
we're seeing them, and people are getting murdered.
So people go to start trying to shoot these things.
In 1888, these two guys, they're like, "Let's go kill it."
Or all of them, we don't care, we're gonna go out there.
Right up, I'm Rambo, you're the Terminator, and the other guy says, "What do those words
even mean?"
And the dude's like, "I don't know.
Anyways, just go with it.
Let's load up on bullets."
And then he turns, and it goes, "I'll be back."
And everyone in the saloon is totally silent.
They're like, "We don't get the reference.
It's 1888."
He's like, "Whatever."
He walks out.
So they both walk out.
Rambo and the Terminator walk out.
And they come across one of these things, and they gave an interesting description.
And they said, "Same thing, face and body like an ape."
But they go, "The way that it climbed was pure ape."
They said, "I mean, just it moved up there, watching it climb up a canyon, completely
unhindered.
Like, it grabbing on rocks, moving up as fast as a monkey can climb up a tree.
They were completely flabbergasted."
And so they shot it.
They opened fire on the thing.
They shot it.
They killed it.
The body weighed 400 pounds.
They dragged it back to town.
One steals the body.
So that story, you can say, "Well, that probably didn't happen."
Or somebody could have stolen the body.
Now there's always been that conspiracy that the Smithsonian Institute is hunting, or like,
trying to find giant mummies and close up the vaults and stuff like that.
And we'll cover that on a later episode.
But there's always been this story that there's a part of the scientific community that actually
goes out, goes, "Oh, Bigfoot sighting?
Yeah, let me see what you got."
And then they destroy the evidence for whatever reason.
We'll cover that on a later episode.
The last big sighting we have is in 1964, so it's been a while.
They may have been sighted on and off, but this is the last one that I saw.
A father and son were walking around in the area, and all of a sudden rocks started falling
on them.
And they're like, "That's weird.
This wasn't on the weather report."
And there was a bigfoot, a hairy devil, just throwing rocks at them, and they ran away.
So, I mean, maybe after the last one got shot, they're like, "Hey, maybe we're just not mutilating
people.
They're just going to keep hunting us down."
They're just going to keep on hunting us down.
They're going to keep on hunting us down.
There's a 1970s, it's Edwards Air Force Base.
Now you may see them during the day as well, but when you're looking over the desert with
Night Vision goggles, it's really going to pop up.
It's really going to show.
There was reports that the creatures would walk up to the base.
There were reports that the creatures would walk through the base and oddly enough, and
they couldn't figure out how they were doing this, underneath Edwards Air Force Base they
had maintenance tunnels.
There were sightings of the Bigfoot creature in the maintenance tunnel.
Now seeing a Bigfoot across a field would be terrifying.
Seeing a Bigfoot in a bush would be horrifying, but I don't think anything that would be a
creepier encounter than being in a building with a Bigfoot.
Because there's nowhere to go.
You're in a long tunnel with a creature who's tried is three times yours.
He will catch you.
But the Bigfoot would just walk away.
When the enlisted men would report this to their commanding officer, the story goes.
Now this could all be fake, this could all just be rumors, but the story goes is that
these enlisted men would talk to their officers and say, "I'm seeing these weird things through
these goggles."
And I'm pretty sure that guy over there who's still pissing himself just saw one in the
tunnels under the base.
And the story goes, the officers would say, "Yeah, don't ever shoot him, don't ever harass
him.
This conversation is classified."
And that's the end of it.
I don't want to hear about it again.
And the story goes that these creatures are actually picked up on the security monitors.
Because they're around the base.
They're on the perimeter of the base.
They're under in the maintenance tunnels where of course they're going to have cameras.
And seeing it walking through the middle of the base, they're all being picked up on cameras.
All the footage is taken, shipped off somewhere, classified.
Now, it just becomes something's classified.
Once someone leaves the military and it's been like 15 years, they may tell the story
and stuff like that.
They can still get in trouble for it.
But it doesn't necessarily mean the story's never going to get out there.
Is that story true?
I don't know.
Now if that story is true, if there are military videotapes of bigfoot creatures moving around
their bases, that would be the best evidence that bigfoot ever existed.
Because you'd have it come from a place where they're not, it's not like from a 7-Eleven
where some teenagers like messing with the video cameras and telling his friend to like
walk around in a monkey suit outside.
These are military security cameras.
They're not going to run them through a video editing program.
But if we have a group that comes in and goes, "Hey, nice bigfoot body.
Hey, nice bigfoot hair.
Oh, you got those prints.
Let's take them to the lab and see what it is."
And then they just send back dog hair and say, "It's just dog hair."
If that group exists within the US government, is that where those tapes are being sent?
Or somewhere to keep the truth of a separate species from the rest of humanity?
Okay.
Thanks.
Bye.
(upbeat music)