Move over Pluto, there's a new punk planet in the solar system. And we've all
heard about people going missing, but what about people just appearing today on
Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, my name is Jason Carpenter. Thanks for coming back to Dead Rabbit Radio.
The fastest growing podcast in Hood River County. Last time we were the fastest
growing podcast in this town of Hood, city of Hood River. Now we're the fastest
growing podcast in the county. We're growing exponentially. I don't really know
what that word means, but it means like... Anyways, anyways. So thanks for coming
back to the show. We got a lot of cool stuff to talk about. Venus is back on the
podcast. Venus made a previous appearance when I said that up until the age of 14
or 15. I thought Venus was covered in lush jungles and prehistoric creatures
and couldn't figure out why everyone was so hyped up to go to Mars. I'm like, "Why
don't we just go to Venus? We know there's trees there. We know there's..." And no one
ever corrected me. That was an earlier episode, but that and that was also an
earlier episode of my childhood. But they are back in the news and then we're
gonna talk a little bit about appearing people. I've always thought that was
interesting. But first off, I want to talk about... Yesterday we talked about day
dreams. Today I want to talk about day dreams. Bigger brother, dreams. You know, as
much as I find daydreaming fascinating, and I've realized listening back to
podcasts, I say the word "fascinating" all the time. I have to come up with a
better word, but that was me taking off my glasses. Okay, so as much as I... like the
idea of daydreams, like you can instantly go into your head and picture a
perfect world down to the smallest detail and you can direct the action. You
can do whatever. You know, yesterday I talked about daydreaming and about
winning the talent show. Honestly, the most common daydream is the diehard
daydream, which is funny because do those daydreams really exist before that
movie? You're like, "Oh, I'm trapped in this single location. I'm trapped at
Sunrise Mall. I'm trapped at a school. I'm trapped, you know, downtown and it's
been cordoned off and it's me against terrorists." That's a very common daydream.
I thought it was funny once a girl was telling me that one day she was
sitting at a coffee shop and she daydreamed. Someone was talking
loudly on their phone or something like that and she daydreamed that she put
his head through the gated, like the spokes of a gate, a metal gate. Like she
kicked the crap out of him and then slammed him in between that. And it's
funny because if I remember the story correctly, no one was actually talking
on their phone. She was just sitting there and she was daydreaming. If someone
was talking on their phone very loudly, I would beat them up and throw them
through a gate. And I think that was the first time I'd ever heard a girl talk
like that, but I definitely had daydreamed like that. I think that kind of
titters the line between daydream and fantasy. But yeah, to sit there and be
like, "What would I do if the bank got robbed right now and you daydream out the
whole scenario?" And of course, obviously, it's completely ridiculous. I was like, "Oh
yeah, I'm in." Like I would stab the terrace in the neck and then take his
gun and I'd lead people through the building. And at the time, I mean, I was
350 pounds. I don't think I could run up a flight of stairs, let alone do a role
and then pop up into a firing position and fire an AK-47, which I've only
fired a few times in my life as is. So yeah, but the daydream, obviously, I'm
like, "Yes, I will jump up and climb up to the top of the elevator and I couldn't
do that at my healthiest." I couldn't do that at my healthiest. So, but in the daydream
world, you can do whatever you want. The interesting thing, though, is going back
to dreams is the idea that... And I don't know if it's just me. Again, I think anything
that we think is just us, millions of other people do it. I've learned that, but
when I dream, I don't... I'm in it, but it's not... It's not me physically, it's how I
see myself. I think that's fairly typical. Going back to the being over weight
thing, sometimes I would have dream... Very rarely would I have dreams where I was
my actual weight. Like I said, I used to be 350. I'm down to 275 now. When I was
350, I wouldn't have... My dreams, I would be in the body of someone who was like 240,
220, you know, like thinner, considerably thinner. And every so often, I'd have a
dream where I was fat in that dream. And it was because of that dream had to do
with people like making fun of me for being fat or me having some health issue
from being fat. But any dreamer, I was like running around writing dinosaurs,
punching, you know, Denzel Washington in the mouth, whatever. That... I was skinny.
You know, it's interesting too, the Denzel Washington... I have this theory.
It's called the Denzel Washington. That just popped in my head. The theory didn't.
The theory didn't, but it's related to dreams too. So I used to hang out with
this girl, the time name Monique, back in Sacramento. She's a really good friend of
mine. We worked at Best Buy Together. And she was black. She was a black girl. And I'm
white if you haven't figured that already. And so we're sitting there one day and
I remember we were out eating dinner or something like that. And I said, I looked
at her and I go, I, in my dreams, I never dream about black people. And she starts
to laugh and then she kind of freezes and she goes, I never dream about white
people. And what I mean by that, that yes, I remember specifically back then that
I had had dreams where I had interacted with famous black people like Denzel
Washington or Will Smith. You would, you know, people that you had seen on
television, you would, you would, they would be in the dream. But as far as, like,
in a dream I went to a coffee shop or I'm walking down the street, everyone was
white. And in Monique's dreams, everyone was black unless she was having a
dream and Tom Cruise was in the dream or Katie Holmes or whatever. And what's
interesting about that is this was, we lived, we both lived in Sacramento,
California, which was very diverse city. You interacted with people of all
different ethnic groups constantly, constantly. The workplace is full of
different ethnic groups. Everyone, I mean, just, there were no, like, white areas and
black areas and stuff like that. Everyone was constantly intermingling. So what
was, and of course we were friends and we interacted with each other, what is the
mechanism that makes it so the background characters in the dreams were all of the
same ethnic group that we were from? If it was a specialized person in that dream,
if it was a famous person in that dream, that person was their, their race that
they are. But if I got on a bus in my dream, it's full of white people. As I've
gotten older, maybe that there's been a couple instances where that hasn't been
the case. And I remember waking up and going, "Oh, that was weird." But for the most
part, everyone in my dreams, I'd say 99.9% of the time, unless it's a famous
person, everyone in my dreams is the same race as I am. And that was the same
thing for Monique. And I've talked to other people in the interim and they've
said, "Oh yeah, no, that, like at first your first thing is you laugh and then you
kind of get uncomfortable. But then when you think about it, go, "You're right. I don't
really have dreams about people of other ethnicities. It's, it's really weird." And
again, I'm talking about like the background characters that make up the
world. Where was I going? Oh, oh, this was my point. The Den, the, not the Denzel
thing. Denzel thing is just because I, he was, I dreamt about him or something like
that. I didn't punch him in the mouth. Anyways, I'm getting off the point. People,
this was the kind of what I wanted to get to and it's taking me like eight
minutes to do this. When, so when I've dreamt and I'm overweight in real life,
but then I'm skinny in my dreams or I'm more fit in my dreams, here's my question.
Do people who wear glasses, I very rarely wear glasses, but people who have to
wake up and put their glasses on and wear them all day long, when they dream,
are they wearing, are they wearing glasses? In their dreams, do they not have
glasses on and their vision is perfect? Or do they wear glasses in their dreams
because they're so used to wearing glasses simply to see my weight has no
impact on how I take in the world, take in the world at all, but vision is super
important. Would a, because I know blind people's dream and colors or something,
that's again off the point again. Do people who wear glasses all the time
dream, are they wearing glasses in their dreams? I think if I was like, I don't
know, like if I had, if I dreamt that my vision was perfect and then I woke up and
I'm like, everything's blurry, there would kind of be disheartening all the time and
then you got to put your glasses on. I'm curious about it. Or is the same, or is it
the same thing? Do they only think of dreams? Do they only wear glasses in
dreams that require glasses? I don't know, that took way too long for me to get to
the point, but you know, sometimes it's the journey and not the destination. Is
that the same? I don't know. So let's talk about the biggest punk of the solar
system now, and it's Venus, and this is why. So Pluto got, the whole thing about
Pluto not being a planet is the dumbest thing ever. If you look at the stories
about it, it was like, there was a scientific convention and a bunch of
scientists went to lunch and the nerds who stayed after, because they didn't
want to go with the jock scientists, they held a vote and they said Pluto's not a
planet anymore. Any astronomer worth their salt thinks that's the stupidest
thing, but the pop culture gets hold of it and they go Pluto's not a planet,
Pluto's not a planet. It is a planet, but anyways, even if it wasn't a planet, Venus
is still a total little punk right now. So I found this out. So Venus has a weird
rotation, the planet itself, the spin, spinning around, and scientists are always
like, why does that, like the length of a day on Venus they can't really agree on,
because it varies. They couldn't figure it out. And here's why. So there's a bunch
of big old mountains on Venus, mountains and volcanoes and stuff, and that's crazy
to think like that planet is belching up fire. But anyways, it's like, first off, a
single revolution takes 243 Earth days, which that is lame. Like, it should, that's
way too long to spin around. That's, they need to get to react together, Venus. But
anyways, so the planet, the reason why it spins weird, it sometimes will spin
faster, sometimes it'll spin slower, because there's these giant mountains, and
the wind hits the mountains, and it like pushes the, the planet in one direction,
and then sometimes the wind comes from the other direction and pushes it in the
other direction. How big of a, how big of a lame, I'm just gonna say it, how big of a
planet do you have to be to have the wind move you, to have the wind actually
affect your rotation? That's ridiculous. I, if I was a planet, wind barely doesn't
even move me. Like, if I'm walking on the street and like a 60 mile an hour wind
hits me, I'm like, uh, okay, maybe not 60, but 50, 30, whatever. I'm walking on the
street and I'm like, uh, but I'm not like flying backwards. We're talking about a
planet that is so big and the wind moves it. That's ridiculous. Even if it's not,
it's not necessarily like moving it across the universe, but it's enough
force to slow you down. That is lame. If we want to talk about planetoids and
things that aren't planets, I think Venus qualifies for that, unless there's
dinosaurs and jungles on it, and then I will take back everything that I said
about it in the past five minutes. I do have a question though. I thought about
this before. Could you have, and this is, there's some things you just can't Google,
because I typed this into Google before and it nothing, I couldn't get anything.
Google is actually, it's kind of lame, but I typed in, "Could you have a mountain so
big it goes into space?" And I didn't, couldn't find anything. Here's my question.
Could there be planets where there's a mountain so big, because you know, like
Mount St. Everest, is that Mount St. Everest or just Mount Everest? It's so
big that you climb up it and you start to need oxygen tanks, because the
atmosphere gets thin. Can you have a mountain that's so big it actually pierces
the atmosphere so you could walk up the mountain and float into space and just
float away? Is that possible, or does the height of the mountain determine the
height of the atmosphere? Like, will the atmosphere always like be bigger than the
mountain, because it's like circling the globe and the mountains part of the globe?
Could you imagine though, if there was a mountain that was so tall, you could
literally walk up and float it into space? Like, we wouldn't need our space
program would be so advanced. We could literally have people up there just like
throwing stuff, like climbing close to the top, and then they're like chained onto
the planet so they don't fly away. And they could just be like, have a fire
brigade chain, where like one guy at the bottom is like throwing up a box, and then
you keep throwing up the box, and then you throw it up there. Or I guess what would
be easier is just the truck. You can just drive a truck up there, that's probably
easier than fire brigade and stuff, but imagine, that'd be awesome. If we had a
mountain that tall, you could just like jump. That becomes like people are like,
"Mom, I'm run mom, dad, I hate you, I'm running away from home," and you like run up
the mountain and just jump into space. That'd be cool. I don't know if it's
possible though, because Google has let me down. What was the other story that I...
There was actually a lot of stories I wanted to talk about today, but I've
realized that I can't really control what I rant about in the beginning, and then
I go off on a side tangent. So I tried to keep it down to about two stories. What
was the second one? Was it aliens? Oh no no no no, I have an alien story, we'll see
that for tomorrow. This one's really cool. This one's about people who appear. And
there's two parts to this story. The first one is the story. So in 1954, in a
Tokyo airport, in an airport in Tokyo, the Tokyo airport, there was a passenger
who gets off the plane, 1954, he gets off the plane and they show their passports
because it's an international flight, and the passport is for a country called
Torrid, T-A-U-R-E-D. And the traveler looked European. He definitely wasn't
Japanese. And the Japanese official was like, "This passport is fake. There's no
country called Torrid." And the passenger was like, "No, there is. Yeah, I'm from
there." And the him and the immigration official, you know, a little
polite at first, but they're just going back and forth. And they can't...
They can't convince each other. The man's trying to convince them that
Torrid, he's from a place called Torrid, and the immigration's official is like,
"No, that's impossible." Now, what was weird is they look at the passport, it had
been stamped before. So like, he had traveled to different countries, and
they said, "You know, why don't you show us on a map where your country is?" They
tell you to come aside. And now they're like, because they think, you know, is this
guy some sort of like criminal or something like that? They take him aside,
and they pull out a map, and they go, "Where is Torrid?" And he looks on the map,
and it's not on the map. And at this point, the man starts to get frustrated,
and he goes, "It's between Spain and France. There's a country here called
Torrid, and it's been there for like a thousand years. It's an old, old country."
Now this guy, he spoke multiple languages, and he could speak Japanese well. He was
fluent in that, and he could fluently speak French as well, and he's like, "That's
where that is." And yeah, they couldn't figure it out. So at this point, the
Japanese official said, "We need to take, you know, like, this is gonna take a
little more time than we think, so we're gonna put you up in a hotel, and we'll
convene again tomorrow." And so they put him in a hotel, and again, they don't,
didn't know what this guy's motives were, so they posted two guards outside of his
hotel, and they said, "You know, have a good night's sleep. We'll meet you tomorrow."
And there was like no, there was like a ledge, a window with no ledge, and it was
high up. And so, the next morning, they go in there, and he's gone. The guy's
completely gone. There's no proof that he was ever there. So I heard about that
story, the man from Tourette, years ago, maybe like 20 years ago, and it's been
one of my favorite stories. The idea of people appearing into our world, or
appearing into our reality from somewhere else. I think we always hear about
people disappearing, and it's always like, "Oh my god, what happened? It's totally
scary." And I'm not talking about like people getting kidnapped. That's just
tragic. Talking about like weird disappearances, like disappearances that
could be chalked up to some sort of paranormal event, which are still
tragic. But you know what I mean? Like a dad abducting his daughter, that's not
necessarily paranormal. Just just terrifying. So, but this story always
interests me, because it's the other side of that story. People just appearing in
our reality. Imagine in this man's reality, he gets on a plane, and then he
goes to sleep in his reality, and wakes up in ours, and when he's on the plane, he
doesn't notice anything's different. The two realities are so closely linked. The
plane lands in Japan, which is where he wanted to go, which where he planned to
go, and he got off the plane like he always has, and nothing seems out
ordinary. The two realities are so close to each other. Maybe he spots an ad for a
product he's never heard of, but you know, nothing's really clicking for him. And
so he goes, and he shows his passport, and then that's when people go, "That
country doesn't exist." You know, that's, "You're not, that doesn't exist." And then I
imagine when he's in the hotel room, kind of the same thing happens. He goes back
to the reality where he was supposed to be, and is in a hotel room in that Japan,
and comes out, and they're like, "Oh, hey, you know, you're, yeah, you are from
Torred. We know Torred. We know where that's at." Interesting. Now, there's two,
like I said, there's two parts of that story. So, I had heard that story, and I'm
gonna post this link up, because it's fascinating. The great thing about
conspiracy theories and paranormal stuff, and I talked about this a little bit
when I was talking about that rapper who got shot, how conspiracies grow, how you
take a single thread of information and have it grow. I was doing some research
on the man from Torred today, because I wanted to talk about it. This whole story
that I just told you comes from a single line that we know of, from a book
called The Directory of Possibilities. It was edited by Colin Wilson, Colin
Wilson's is one of my favorite authors of all time. He's a nonfiction author, and
he has put together several collections of true... He wrote a book called The
History of Crime, and it is the best nonfiction true crime book you
will ever read. It is literally The History of Crime. We learn about the very
first time fingerprints were used. They go all the way back to the oldest types
of crime, and most of it's centered in England, like in Europe, and the
Americas. But it's amazing. The book has to be like 600 pages. Please, please, if
you're interested in true crime, pick up The History of Crime, I believe it is.
But you look at Colin Wilson, all of his stuff is good. However, he edited a
book back in 1981, 27 years after the 1954 event, and in a part of this book
there, this line, it had a section on appearing people, and it said this line,
"And in 1954, a passport check in Japan is alleged to have produced the man with
papers issued by the nation of Toret." That was it. That was the only line in that
book playing into that. And then back in 1999, again this is what I find
fascinating, this is kind of... and none of this has been cited. These are kind of
the evolution of these stories. In 1999, there was another book called Strange
but True, the Mysterious and Bizarre People. Let me read this real quick.
This is an excerpt from that book that was 18 years later. "There have been many
reports of visitors from other planets dropping in on Earth. In 1954, the
Japanese authorities detained a man trying to enter the country with the
passport that revealed he was from an unheard country named Toret. A thorough,
thorough check was made by custom officials to see if there was any such
place, any such a place anywhere on Earth by the Dura Blank. The stranger refused
to throw light on the whereabouts of mysterious nations of Toret and quickly
left Japan." So the story that I told you originally was a story that I had
always heard, and this is that evolution of that story. Now I'm not saying it
didn't happen, because this is one of those mysteries that I did... I hope it
happened. But from that single line in that Colin Wilson edited book, and then 18
years later a little bit more, and you're starting to see how that story grows.
You're starting to see how that paranormal story grows. And I think that is
another level of fascinating information on the story. The initial story I find
very fascinating and intrigues my mind, but the fact that we can watch this story
grow, we can kind of go back and read about this. And kudos to the person who
put this article together. I like I said I'll post the link, but it's a great...
and this guy sources it and every... or woman I don't know. But yeah, so check out
this link, and I'm gonna spend some more time on this website and look around. But
you know, I think one thing about the man of Toret is cool is that what if
that's what happens to people who go missing in the woods? They go missing in
the woods in our reality, but then they just go to another reality where
everything's normal, or it would be creepy if they go to a reality where
something is totally abnormal, and they're stuck there too. I always wonder
what happens to people who just go missing in the woods. I think everybody
does, but yeah, it's like, is it like a wolf eating them, or is it something
creepier? I don't know. I don't like the woods. We've been over that a hundred
times. I would much rather get zapped away on an airplane and end up in another
country. Another... I guess everyone gets zapped up in an airplane. It goes to another
country, but you know what I mean? Like go to another reality, then be shifted into
another reality in the forest. This forest should be anyways. So that's gonna be
our episode for tonight. I hope you had fun. A research that man from Toret story.
Again, I think that's a fascinating thing. There's other stories out there about
people appearing, which again, it's... some of you don't hear it very often. You hear
the disappearing, you hear the missing 411s, but appearing people, I think, isn't
just another spin on that. And that's what I like to talk about. I like to talk
about stuff we really haven't heard of before, so... We're gonna go ahead and
call it a night. I am Jason Carpenter. Oh, so yes. Let's go over this again.
DeadRabbit.com is the website. You can check out all the show notes there. The
email address is deadrabbitradio@gmail.com. We have the YouTube channel. You
can hit us up at @deadrabbitradio. Check that out. And then Twitter is @jasonocarpenter.
That is my Twitter handle. We're gonna... tomorrow we are going to do ghosts. I've
noticed this podcast has been kind of ghost light. I want to do a lot of... not
a lot, but I want to do more ghost stuff. I was like, "Oh, we're talking about science
and stuff like that. Boners." I think we talked about that in a previous episode.
But I want to talk about some ghosts. So tomorrow I'm gonna give you some ghost
news. I found some good ghost stories. We're gonna go through that. So hopefully
you tune in for that tomorrow. I am Jason Carpenter. This is DeadRabbit Radio and
I'm just gonna come up with a sign off right now. Let's see. I am Jason Carpenter.
This is DeadRabbit Radio and you have just entered the rabbit hole. I'm Jason
Carpenter. This is DeadRabbit Radio and... dude, is there any rabbit-based puns?
Don't get bit by a dog with rabies or you'll get rabid. I could work with that.
I might be able to... I could work with that. I don't know. There's something there.
Have a great day guys. I will see you back tomorrow.
[Music]