A failed revolution forces a man to sit in the hot seat, a female demon that haunts
the jungles of Central America and South America comes equipped with a one-of-a-kind superpower,
and then we take a look at the political belief known as posadism.
How far left do you have to be for even Castro to denounce you?
Well, saying that you want a nuclear war is a good start today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
It's nice and rainy out here.
I kinda like the rain as long as I'm in sight.
But that's it.
That's all the intro I got, because we got a lot of stuff to cover today.
Now the first story I'm gonna talk about is a little grim, but I have this thing that
it's seen, I really am starting to think that most of history has been retconned.
Not like in it, I mean I can think the Battle of the Bulge happened and stuff like that.
And I think there were key events that happened throughout humanity, but sometimes the stuff
that is reported is so ridiculous that you really have to sit back and go "that didn't
happen".
Now there are some events that actually we know 100% happen, but for this first story
though, I just find absolutely ridiculous.
So let's hop on the carboner copter.
First we gotta make a stop off at the Bermuda Triangle because we're going back in time,
so *makes a noise* and now we're also magically transported over Transylvania.
Bermuda, Romania, but back then it had the more badass name Transylvania.
And we get there just as things are starting to heat up pun intended.
In 1514, to make a long story short, because I don't want to get into the history of everything,
but there was a papal order, there was an order from the Pope to stop the Ottomans from
just wrecking all this stuff throughout Eastern Europe.
And they appointed this dude, I'm assuming I'm pronouncing this wrong, because if I'm
pronouncing this right, this guy does not have a badass name.
His name is Georgie Doza.
Georgie Doza.
So anyways, easy Doza.
Oh, okay, I'm sorry about that.
Georgie is appointed to raise this army, and he does raise an army, but he doesn't know
how to control them, and eventually he has this huge army, and they go "let's fight for
our rights, let's take back the land that was ours."
And all the gentry are like "oh this isn't good."
They're like "control your army, control your army."
He's like "I'm trying to, there's like thousands of these guys, what am I supposed to do?"
Maybe if you gave me some of that sweet sweet vampire power you have in Transylvania, and
they're like "silence!"
And so anyways, this army that was meant to stop the Ottoman Empire, to stop the Turks,
was just like rampaging, and this went on for a while, and they were basically killing
a bunch of noblemen, and the knights were having to show up and beat up the peasants.
And the whole time Georgie just cannot control this whole mob.
It's a mob.
So anyways, eventually the quote unquote rebellion that wasn't even, that's not even why he started,
it was crushed, and they tell Georgie, they go "you want to be king, you want to take
stuff over, we'll make you king."
And he's like "I never want it, what do you, I never wanted to be king.
I was given this order to do this, and it just didn't work out."
But anyways, so this is what, that's all, I believe all of that happened.
I don't believe that his name is Georgie.
I think it was probably a little more badass than that.
But anyways, this is what I don't believe.
So this is how they kill Georgie.
Now I know back in time they were pretty brutal with their tortures, but let me explain it
to you and then explain why I don't think it's real.
They take Georgie, and they take a throne, and they make it red hot.
And then they put him in it, and they're like "you want to be king, right?
Get in this throne!" and he's like "Ahhhhhh!"
And then they make a crown, you know a crown that you put on your head, because I know
I have trouble pronouncing that word.
They make that red hot, and they go "here's your crown, your highness!"
And he's like "Ahhhhhh!"
And then they go "you know what a king really needs?
He needs a scepter.
Go fetch me that hot red scepter please."
They just have a line around.
The guy's like "yeah sure, it puts on big mittens.
Hands it to Georgie.
Ahhhhhh!"
Now he's holding a red hot scepter, sitting in a red hot throne, wearing a red hot crown.
Now this is all supposedly historical.
And you're like "well that's awful Jason, that's terrible."
But then, according to historians, they then were starving nine dudes, they were prisoners
of war that Georgie knew, one of them was his brother, and they bring the nine dudes
in and they go "Georgie, here's your court.
Look at all these people here to serve the new king."
And then they chop his brother up, and Georgie's like "Noooooo!"
And then the remaining eight guys who are starved to death, they are then told to eat
Georgie.
So they eat him.
They begin taking bites out of him.
And those that refused got chopped up so the other dudes were like "well I'm either getting
chopped up or I'm taking a bite out of this guy so they all walked up and ate some of them
and they were allowed to leave."
And Georgie died.
That was the end of that.
I don't believe that story for a second.
And here's why.
Let's say that someone has a spear on you and says "go sit in that hot seat, go sit in
that red hot seat, what are you gonna do?"
You'd be like "no, spear me then dude."
And they would have to like fight you and maybe they were like poking you in the butt and
you're like "ahhh" and they finally throw you on the throne and you're immediately gonna
get up.
If someone and here's the other thing, so I don't believe that.
If you are standing around, if you are surrounded by guards, because obviously they would have
to guard you otherwise you would keep jumping up.
There's a bunch of guards around you and they hand you a red hot scepter.
What's the first thing you're gonna do?
Drop it, most likely, but if you have any forethought you're gonna begin wielding that
like a mace and attacking people with a red hot scepter.
It's already melted to your hand, you can't do anything to it.
It's like someone took a G.I.
Joe figure and put it in a microwave.
It's just one form of mold now, your hand in the scepter.
Maybe swinging it around and you could argue well Jason maybe they strapped him down to
the throne and then made it red hot.
What strap can you name that won't melt under red hot heat other than a chain and again even
if they chained me to a chair and then handed me a red hot scepter, I'm getting somebody.
The guy who hands it to me is getting hit in the head with it and then getting eaten while
you're sitting in a red hot chair.
Have you ever tried to eat a hamburger out of a frying pan while it's still cooking?
You would melt.
I mean this story is so ridiculous.
But apparently this happened.
I think they probably took a guy and they got a chair, there was red hot and they threw
it threw him on it and he jumped up and he got like third degree burns and then they just
stick stuck him to death with spears and then they made the rest up.
Not saying that the storyings today are like hey Barry wouldn't this be cool if we'd say
that this guy got melted and eaten at the same time.
But I think it was probably propaganda back then and they were like and then we put a
red hot crown on his head and all the revolutionaries were like I don't want to do that.
That sounds like a terrible thing.
But I think if you ever tried to recreate that and I don't recommend doing it because
again you're going to get hit in the head with a red hot scepter but I think what's
bizarre is that when I read about it no one was like but that's impossible that probably
didn't happen.
A couple different sources are like yeah this happened and I'm like it didn't.
I can understand getting impaled because you could have a couple guys hold you down and
a stick stuck up your butt.
The amount of people it would take to hold a man down in a red hot chair, those dudes
are getting burnt and there's a big struggle and they're handing you a weapon that is red
hot it's just a bad idea all around.
So we're going to go ahead and we're going to leave Romania or hop back in the Carbenter
copter.
We have our heat shields on so we're not filling the heat and again I don't think that ever
happened so we don't even need the heat shields we just see a man getting stuck with spears
as we fly away.
And we have to go forward in time now.
We're going 100 years in the future.
That story took place in 1500.
We're hopping back in the Carbenter copter.
Now we're going to the 16th century which actually be the 1700.
So we're going a couple years in the future.
I'm new to this whole time travel device on my helicopter.
We're going to Columbia.
And our helicopter is in stealth mode and it's a good thing because what we see going
on beneath us is not a situation we want to be involved in.
It was a dark moonless night and a slave ship became overrun by their cargo.
The slaves, not like sugar, the slaves broke out and attacked the shipmen of the boat.
Through them overboard, stabbed them, one guy tried heating up an iron throne, the whole
boat caught on fire, but eventually 25 of these slaves bail out on little rowboats or
dinghies or whatever they're called and get off the ship and they land in Columbia.
Now these slaves believe that they are totally free now.
But their freedom doesn't last long because they end up running into a group of natives
and very quickly the two groups become hostile towards each other to the point that a battle
breaks out between the slaves and the natives.
And this battle is so bloody you have muskets, pfft, reload, reload, reload.
You have knives, ceremonial daggers coming out of sheaths and just digging in the flesh.
It blood everywhere, the screams of the dying, the moans of death.
It is music to the devil's ears and while he is underneath the planet, he hears these
noises above and it just gets the blood boiling.
He has to see this magnificent battle so the devil crawls out of the earth, sees these
two groups fighting each other and realizes he needs a piece of this.
He then runs into the battle and slaughters both sides.
Claws, teeth, tail, swipe, swipe, you get the point.
The devil just destroys them all.
Oh and then horn, stick!
Sticks the last dude with the horn.
He had to use all of his weapons.
But while he's up there, he's like finally cleaning the blood.
Oh no, he would love the blood.
He's rubbing more blood on him, he's rolling around in it like a pig in a slop pit.
And he sees a beautiful woman somewhere.
This is a legend, I'm not making this up, somebody did.
As he's rolling around in the blood, he sees the most beautiful woman he's ever seen.
And he sees her, they lock eyes and instantly fall in love with each other.
Now this is not the start of one of the most bizarre romantic comedies you've ever seen.
It's the start of the story of a creature known as "La Tunda".
You see the devil and this chick bang all the time and she has a ton of kids and one of
them is named La Tunda.
Now because she is the devil's child, she cannot have children herself.
But she wants them more than anything.
She wants kids and she wants servants.
So the legend goes like this.
That legend went like that.
And in Colombia and parts of Latin America and South America, they believe that La Tunda
is this creature, this child of the devil, that if a kid sees her, it appears as a mother,
it appears as an aunt, it appears as someone who cares about them.
So if the child's mother was horrible and she had no sisters, the child would see nothing.
It would just see a predator and visible type shape coming towards them.
But anyways, if they had a loving mother, it would appear as their mother.
And to adult men, which was her secondary target, it would just be the most beautiful
woman they've ever seen.
If you're an adult man and it's your mom, you might have some issues.
But anyway, so unless your mom is the most beautiful person you've ever seen now that
I think about it, anyways, she captures you.
Now we did an episode recently on South American cryptids that become women and I think there
was one in Southeast Asia as well.
And we're talking about all that stuff.
This one I found when I was researching a different topic and this one's absolutely bizarre because
even though it fits the criteria of it lives in the wilderness, it's a shapeshifter, it
can be the most beautiful woman in the ever, the other ones would either kill you or drive
you mad.
This one, this one's absolutely nuts.
Whoever made this up was stoned out of their mind.
Absolutely.
So Latunda, she wants kids and she wants slaves.
She wants men to entertain her and she wants kids to raise because she can't have any herself.
So what she does is she lures you in by being someone who's cared for you if you were a
child or the most beautiful woman in the world.
But first off, huge handicap here.
She is an expert shapeshifter except for one thing.
Her leg looks like a whisk.
Her leg looks like a giant wooden spoon.
Which basically is the same as saying you don't have camouflage at all.
If you could morph into any shape but your left arm looked like a blender, technically
you can't morph into any shape.
But apparently she always stands behind bushes so you don't realize that her leg looks like
a whisk.
Like an egg beater basically.
It's like this old fashioned wooden egg beater they use.
But anyways, so she always has to hide behind a bush which again, she can't chase you and
that's really not being an expert shapeshifter.
Secondly, once she has you under her control, we'll get to that in a second, but once she
has you under her control, she feeds you shrimp to keep you under her control.
When has the mind control abilities of shrimp ever been extolled in any legend ever?
I've never heard someone once say, you know, if she's not really, you know, giving you
what you want, try shrimp.
Like that is not a phrase that any human has ever uttered ever.
She uses shrimp to keep you under control.
But you ask Jason, we know how she kidnaps you by imitating someone you love.
And we know how she keeps you under her control by feeding a shrimp.
But how does she get us under her control in the first time?
This is the best superpower ever.
You go back to this chicks house, she's the most beautiful woman you've ever seen.
No, no, no, even better.
You're a little kid and your mom is like, hey, come under the jungle, come in the jungle.
And you notice she has an odd limp but it's constantly obscured by jungle foliage.
So you're not really like, you know, like, that's weird.
Kind of looks like an egg beater, but you go off in the jungle with this woman.
She then gets you back to her layer and farts in your face.
And her farts, I'm not making this up.
Her farts smell so bad, it breaks your mind and you immediately become her slave.
How bad smelling does a fart have to be to destroy your consciousness?
How bad can that be?
But apparently it works for her.
You're back at some chicks house, she's the hottest chick you've ever seen.
You're a little concerned that the chicks house is in a cave in the middle of the jungle
and she's wearing knee high boots.
But you're there with her, she's super sexy, she bends over in your face and then you're
her slave forever.
As long as she keeps feeding you shrimp.
A lot of people believe that and there may still be people who believe in this creature.
But that is flat out ridiculous.
There's a part in the bible where this missionary is like getting picked on by these teens and
he prays to God and a bunch of bears come out of the forest and maul the teens to death.
That story is more believable than a farting ghost to feed you shrimp.
But somebody came up with it.
This is my scenario.
A jock somehow tricked his way into becoming a shaman of a village and he was just pulling
pranks the whole time.
Basically Van Wilder is the medicine man who came up with this story.
A farting ghost.
With farts that smell so bad it destroys your mind.
I can't imagine a smell that bad but I want to see this cryptid on supernatural.
They do a lot of one off monster of the week episodes.
I want to see Sam and Dean fight this thing.
I want to see Dean falling in love with this hot chick and Sam warning him don't fall for
it you already banged that werewolf we got in a lot of trouble with that.
He ends up going back to this girl's flat.
It's face farted on and then they both just shoot her in the brain because that's pretty
much how every episode ends and then they spend the last 10 minutes talking about how much
they love each other.
I want to see La Tundah on an episode of supernatural.
Make it happen.
I'm Eric Kripke I know you listen to the show.
Oh wait you don't work for that show anymore.
Still make it happen.
But we're done with farts we're done with the juvenile humor.
If I edited out a lot of fart noises and there's only like one or two in that consider yourself
lucky but we're done with that.
We're done with that part.
Now we are going we're actually staying in the region because our next story actually
takes place in Latin America South America things like that.
So we don't even have to use any fuel on the carbonicopter we're just going to wait here
for probably about 150 200 years.
We go into our cryogenic chambers and we sleep the restful sleep until it's the year 1962.
Imagine you're a college student which actually a lot of you are but imagine you're a college
student in 1962 and you're curious about the world you're looking at different political
beliefs and things like that you kind of want to broaden your scope.
I actually had a lot of run-ins with who are those lunatics who follow Lyndon LaRouche.
I had a buy oh man I got a hundred stories about those actually no I have four.
I have four stories about dealing with Lyndon LaRouche people at my college.
These guys are nuts.
But anyways but again you just kind of want to broaden your horizon you want to look into
different political beliefs.
So a friend invites you to go to a seminar he says there's just new political party they
broke off from the Trotsky's.
They are socialists to a degree that they see the future of humanity.
And you're like well you know Trotsky's okay but I'll go check it out.
I'll go check it out just to see what they have.
You go into a large auditorium not a lot of people in there maybe like 30 or 40 but everyone
in there you can tell the energy level is high.
They cannot wait to hear what their speaker is about to say and to be honest you get a
bit of a cult feeling something seems off but you put those feelings inside and say
you know what I'm going to keep an open mind.
A speaker comes to the stage gets his papers ready and begins speaking.
We are preparing ourselves for a stage in which before the atomic war we shall struggle for
power.
During the atomic war we shall struggle for power and we shall be in power.
After destruction commences the masses are going to emerge in all countries.
In a short time and a few hours capitalism cannot defend itself in an atomic war except
by putting itself in caves and attempting to destroy all that it can.
The masses in contrast are going to come out will have to come out because it is the only
way to survive.
The apparatus of capitalism police army will not be able to resist.
It will be necessary to organize the workers power immediately.
Nuclear war equals revolutionary war.
It will damage humanity but it will not.
It cannot destroy the level of consciousness reached by it.
Humanity will pass quickly through a nuclear war into a new human society.
Socialism.
That's not just a guy breathing heavily in your ear the crowd goes wild at this speech.
And you quickly say goodbye to your friend and you sneak out of that auditorium and you
basically run home.
What you've just heard is a speech from Jay Posadas.
Jay Posadas is the founder of a belief known as Posadism.
Now this story was recommended to me on YouTube from Adi Naton.
Adi Naton.
And I appreciate it.
Thank you for the recommendation.
Posadism was a political group in the 1960s.
It's still around today.
And they were so nutty that Castro himself kicked him out of Cuba.
After the Cuban revolution Jay Posadas said "Wait, why do the Americans still have a
Guantanamo Bay?
Let's mar-" and which I've always thought was weird too.
I never knew Guantanamo Bay existed and I mean it was common knowledge but I didn't
know it existed until after 9/11.
But the fact that we had all these problems with Russia and Cuba and all that stuff but
we had a military base on the island I always thought was weird.
But Posadas said was basically saying Castro's not doing enough because there's still US
troops on the island and Castro's like "Listen, it's not worth it."
And Posadas actually started to get groups of people from the cities to march on the
base and Castro's like "Listen, no, this is the deal we have set up" and he kicked Posadas
out of Cuba.
He was too much of a revolutionary for Castro.
He ends up going to South America and Latin America and he starts all these little cells.
Originally he was part of Trotsky groups but he didn't feel they were going far enough.
So he started forming this new political belief named after himself called Posadism.
His beliefs were that nuclear war was not only inevitable but good.
The Soviet Union and China should strike first.
The only way to defeat capitalism is through a global thermonuclear war.
Now his followers thought that was great but his followers were never given the chance
to rebut him.
All the meetings were, he would go to the town hall meetings and if he wasn't there
personally all the meetings were a group of people sitting around listening to tape recordings
of his speeches.
His political newspapers were mostly transcripts of his speeches.
And people would just sit around and talk about what they learned.
There was no leader but him.
So it was basically a cult.
A doomsday cult really.
He wanted nuclear war and had these visions of nuclear war and within hours of the nukes
falling all the workers would rise up and kill all the cops and stuff like that.
Fairly short-sighted because while that may happen in the short term, even if you win
the world is in nuclear ruins.
So he gained a lot of followers from that but he lost a lot of connections in the political
world.
Other groups didn't want to deal with him because he was too nutty.
That was only the beginning so you had groups already severing ties with this group but
in Latin America and South America it was fairly popular.
I mean in compare, I mean it's fairly popular compared to other offshoot communist socialist
groups.
He wasn't like top of the pops.
It wasn't this huge thing.
But it had a good amount of membership.
But anyway so the nuclear thing they kept preaching and they really do, they're not around as
much today but that's still part of their belief system that nuclear war is revolutionary
war.
It is the final step.
But around 1968, Posadas has another vision.
He realizes that they actually have an ally that is an untapped resource.
They actually have now looked around the globe and said if we can get these people to take
our side we will win.
There will be no defeating us.
They didn't really look around the world.
They looked up.
In 1968, Jay Posadas wrote a pamphlet called Flying Saucers, The Process of Matter and
Energy, Science, the Revolutionary and Working Class Struggle and the Socialist Future of
Mankind.
It made four points.
One, UFOs are evidence of the existence of extraterrestrial civilizations too.
Since advances in society come from advances in technology, extraterrestrials must come
from a more advanced society than Earth, like socialism.
He had this belief that the reason why science wasn't as advanced as it should be is because
capitalism used science to kill, socialism would use science to heal.
He envisioned this world where everyone could talk to any animal.
People could reproduce like amoebas asexually, but I just love to imagine a person splitting
in two and then having two of them come around.
He believed that women should give birth in space.
He believed in this idea called "Russian Cosmicism" that once we left the planet we would be these
immortal people with no worries.
And he believed that the aliens had already reached this level and the only way they could
have reached this level is because they were already socialists.
He believed the reason why aliens, this was point three, the reason why aliens aren't
interacting with us is because we are a primitive, i.e. capitalist society and as long as we
were a capitalist society, worldwide, there were obviously huge communists and socialist
strongholds.
But worldwide you had this huge thing of capitalism in the Europe and in Western Europe and America,
as long as we're there the aliens weren't going to interact with us because we were
seen as primitive.
So four, and this was kind of the main point, posatists had to contact the aliens to get
them to align with the socialists and destroy capitalism on the planet.
Now what's funny is this, the nuclear war thing always struck a lot of other socialists
as kind of weird, but they said "Yeah, I get where you're coming from."
Like yes, if there was a huge nuclear war or a limited nuclear war or whatever it would
destroy capitalism because capitalism needs material goods to sell and buy.
You need groups of people to buy and sell those items, you need labor to make the items
to sell and to buy and all that stuff.
So yes, yes, you are right that if a nuclear war happened it would impact capitalism more
than it would impact communism or socialism.
Yes, you're correct.
However, it would involve the deaths of hundreds of millions of people and tons of land that
wouldn't be able to be used, it would be a tragedy on a global scale, literally.
It would be absolutely terrible.
So yes, I see your point but I don't think that's the path, I think we can do these other
things.
When he came out with this UFO thing, everybody laughed at him.
To the point that like immediately they were classified as a UFO cult, they became a huge
joke in political circles.
Other people, other socialists started referring to them not as Posadist or Fourth International,
they just started calling the members extraterrestrials.
Whenever they referred to this dude, Jay Posadist or anyone in his group, they would call him
"Hey look at the ETs over there."
Completely destroyed their credibility, 100%.
Posadist then realized that he'd probably overstepped his bounds.
He ended up getting exiled from South America at this point, he's in Europe now, where
he eventually died in 1981.
But they started talking less and less about weirds.
And the weird thing too is that when they're reading this article they said, "You would
be reading the Fourth International Posadist newspaper and it would have an article about
like a worker strike in Britain and then next to it it would say, "When man talks to dolphins,
world will be better."
It was like all intermixed with like real events and then this super fringe science
stuff.
And his followers still believed in it, but it rapidly started having drop off because
people did not want to be connected with a UFO cult.
They wanted to be socialists and they kind of believed this guy, but once they were basically
getting mocked from their own side, you started to have membership drop off.
To this day they're remembered as a wacky UFO doomsday offshoot, far far left of socialism.
And up until around 2011 they were still producing material, their website's down now, but they
stopped talking about UFOs.
It was just completely damaged their brand.
Nobody wanted to join, they were big laughing stock, so they really backed away from that.
But they still talked about, "Yeah, nuclear war is good."
Because that again, I can, that idea is logically, it's stupid, but you can see the logic in
it.
What's interesting about this conspiracy theory?
Like you have a guy, he has a ton of members, he has all these groups around the world.
He had some in Europe too, but it was mostly located in South America, Central America.
You have all of this power and he ends up making the mistake of talking about aliens
in 1968 and becomes a big joke.
And it's funny because nowadays you have cults, religious stuff, we'll talk about UFOs, it's
a little more accepted now.
But in 1968 that was his big misstep.
But the thing is.
He broke off from the Trotsky groups to start this sect, to start this political belief
system.
It's just as likely that he could have kept those views hidden, not have argued, towed
the party line, moved up through the ranks, get to the top or near the top and begin to
whisper those beliefs into somebody's ear.
That's how you play the long game.
You may be a weirdo in real life, you may have some bizarre political beliefs, but by
starting your cult or your offshoot group you're actually handicapping yourself.
It's much more beneficial to these fringe beliefs, to work their way up through the system
legitimately.
And some people do.
And what happens is over the years and over the decades as they move up these groups, their
own fringe theories start to get dulled and they start to become a little more mainstream,
a little more palatable, you get older, you have more experience, you're talking to people
with different ideas and you go maybe the nuclear war thing is not a great idea.
But to a hardcore believer, you're holding onto those beliefs the whole time you're
working your way up that ladder.
How many people are out there who believe the only way to win their ideological war
is through nuclear war?
You could have someone out there who believes that the path to the future means the nuking
of a religious city, that the path to a glorious new future is biological weapon use across
vast continents.
You may have people out there like Posadas who believe that only a full-blown nuclear
war can lead to the perfect world for the humans that are left.
Jay Posadas died in 1981, but people with that type of mentality still live.
And how many of them do you think are whispering in the general's ear on a daily basis?
How many of them are generals themselves?
How many of them are just waiting for the day to make their dream our reality?
[Music]
(upbeat music)