*Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh* *Sigh
city devastated by the coronavirus, a city full of the lost, a city full of the dead,
a city named your hometown, and then we travel to New York City, where a world famous trial
is currently being held. And amidst all of the documentation, all the legal wrangling,
all of the evidence is the word I was looking for. In the middle of all that comes a disgusting detail
that no one expected. Nobody except one man, Hans Wormhat, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a lot of
stuff to cover man. I just spent 18 minutes talking about the coronavirus and was like,
"Ah, this is boring." So I'm gonna try to cut it down. It might still be 18 minutes long,
but we're gonna make it exciting this time. We're gonna put some sound effects in there,
and we'll have some visuals that only I will see. This is a podcast, so whoa dude, look at that to
wasteland. Let's hop on board the Carpenter copter. We're gonna fly to Wuhan, China. Wuhan! Wuhan!
Helicopter lands. Okay, we're all getting on our... I had my hazmat suit on already. You're like, "Hey Jason,
what's this story about? Oh, I've been asleep for the past couple weeks. You're getting off the
helicopter. Everyone else is snickering at you. At your impending demise. Why are you guys all
wearing those hazmat suits?" You're just walking around. We're like, "Hey dude, here. Bat soup?"
You're like, "Yo, I've always wanted to try this. I'm a huge fan of Batman."
And anyways, as you start to wither in front of us, this is actually perfect because now that you
have the coronavirus, which is what we'll be talking about, now we can get access into all
these hospitals that we're gonna be also looking into. So you're like, "Uh, Jason, you're kind of a
jerk for me." And we're like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah. Go to sleep. Go to sleep. I'm getting you in a chokehold
to speed up the process." We rush you into a hospital. "Hey doctors, get out of the way. Get out of the
way. No, we want you. You doctor. Come here. Come here." So I'm Jason Garbender, host of Dead
Rabbit Radio. These are all my fans and this dude poking you with a stick, this dude was eating some
bat soup and the doctor's like, "That's not good." We all rush you into the ER. Actually, the whole
hospital at this point is the ER because even though I'm not gonna go over specifics, I should
go over some of the general stuff, the city of Wuhan in China, it's in the middle of the country,
is completely quarantined at this point. Now, I know a friend of mine has a friend in Wuhan and
it's not good over there, as you would expect a quarantine of 11 million people. Nothing can get
in or out. The military brings in supplies all the time, but can the military really supply 11
million people? They're gonna have to start airdropping stuff in, but anyways, they quarantine the
city because the coronavirus, they don't really know what it is. They're still trying to figure out
how it's spread. What they believe now is spread through drop, water droplets,
sneezing, coughing. If you're a dog and you're shaking your body and water's going everywhere,
it's probably not good. Beethoven movies are banned over there now. Everyone's like, "No."
And then poop, poop as well. So it's in the liquid of your poop, which is fine by me because my poop
is rock hard now. It's super dry. I don't know what's going on. It's like trying to push a link
and log through a hot dog bun. It's definitely doing some damage down there, but so I don't have to,
you don't have to worry about it. If you touch my poop, you're not gonna get it. And so the doctors
like that, you really should go to this other ward and find out why your poop's so hard. It's like,
"No, I don't. I'm waddling through the hospital now." So that's kind of the basics of the coronavirus.
Now, obviously with something like this, I should say this too, as of the recording of this, 18 to
20,000 people have become infected. Three to 400 people have died, and the majority, like 99% of
that or 95% of that is in China. Tragic? Yes. Basic illness, similar to the flu? Yes. It could get
bad. It could get, it looks like it's kind of tapering off, and you could say, "Well, it's tapering
off because they've isolated these cities. What's going on in these cities?" This is where we get
into all the conspiracy theories, because you knew this was coming, right? You knew there were
going to be conspiracy theories popping up about this. So there is video footage coming out of Wuhan,
okay? So we're here, and we're going to be walking around. We see a guy holding a video camera over
a ledge, and we're like, "Oh, dude, let's go see what he's doing." And at the bottom of like this,
this is a video that's floating around at like the, on the first floor of some hospital, there's
a bunch of people who are sick with this coronavirus, but they're not just coughing, they're not just like,
"I'll look at all mucusy and stuff." They don't all just, they're not all green, like the Musenex man
just covered in goo. They're twitching. Their arms and legs are flailing wildly as nurses walk around.
Creepy, right? There's footage of a man walking around in a hospital. That's not unique. There's
a lot of men walking around in hospitals, but this one, there's a man walking around with a camcorder
in a hospital in Wuhan, China, and there's a bunch of doctors going, "This guy's dead. We couldn't save
him. This virus is killing all these people." Oh no, look at this guy. He's dead right here,
in front of a secretly recorded camera. This guy's dead. Why am I talking so loud? But he's dead.
And then that same guy videotapes a truck full of body bags. There, and then there's some photos
that Sheen Anagans. Sheen Anagans is actually a Patreon supporter, so if you appreciate the show,
you can support the Patreon. If you can't afford the Patreon, just help get the word out about the
show. Yes, we're going to plug that during the story of hospitals and death. Sheen Anagans sent
me some tweets over the vacation and said, "Hey, I'm a little concerned about this whole coronavirus
thing, and I'm wondering if you're going to do a story on paraphrasing, obviously, but I wonder
if you're going to do anything on it." Now, these tweets, one of them was from a Twitter account
called Trends in China, and it was like, "Hey, look at the city. The government of Wuhan is building
a hospital for a thousand people, so they're trying to build a pop-up hospital real quick.
That's one of the reasons why the death toll seems to be so high in China. It's overwhelming
their medical services. Not that the disease is particularly deadly, but it's overwhelming
their medical services, so they're going to build this hospital." And then another Twitter user goes,
"Yeah, right. They're building a hospital? I don't think so. Here's a photo of a trench full of
garbage bags. You see, they're not building a hospital. Building a makeshift morgue."
Now, I responded to Sheen Anagans. I know I think I've told you guys this before. I used to work
in a crematory. Those aren't body bags. It was a trench full of garbage bags. We can't tell if
they're six feet or two feet. There's no scale to them to trench of garbage bags. You go, Jason,
why would a construction company throw all their garbage in a trench? I would respond,
"Any construction company in China would." And I'd also argue that any construction company that
could get away with it would. They're not going to haul it out to the dumpster. Just bury it.
Now, I don't think it's a--if it was a trench, first off, it's a--it's maybe a foot or two deep,
this trench. But I--when I was looking at the photos and I'm like, "Those aren't body bags.
That's not how you build a mass grave. I know how they're dealing with the bodies in China right
now and that's not how they're doing it." This is something--this is a piece of advice I want to
give all you guys. When? This is tricky, too. This is tricky, but this will help you guys a lot from
getting fooled, hoodwinked, however you want to put it, or scared, rarely would probably be a better
word. When you see someone post something, if this person posted the absolute opposite thing,
what I believe them. See, you had trends in China saying, "Here's photos of a ditch bean duck." Now,
somebody, the other Twitter user, went by the name "Dirty Monkey." So, "Dirty Monkey, a random person,
found another photo of a trench full of garbage bags and said, 'No, it's body bags.'" And because we
are conspiracy theorists and because we researched this stuff, we can be prone to believe the most
outlandish theory. So, when we see someone, whether or not they have any clout or investigative skill
or access to information--because you don't have to be a journalist to get information out or to be
knowledgeable on something--but who is "Dirty Monkey"? Who in the world is "Dirty Monkey"? I'm going to
assume one, they're not a Chinese national, just because the name isn't in Chinese, that could be
racist, but I'm assuming they're not a Chinese national. I'm going to assume that they found the
photos third hand, which means they didn't take the photographs because they seem to be taken at
the same time that the photographs of the other construction going on by--that were referenced
in the Trends of China article. So, based on that, I could say, he probably didn't take the photos,
he probably didn't publish the photos, he found the photos after they had been taken and published
by somebody else, and said, "This looks suspicious," and posted out there and then other people see it
and go, "Oh my god, it's a trench full of bodies." If "Dirty Monkey" had responded to that Trends
in China article and said, "Yeah, good job, China. They're really on top of this. Would you, as a
conspiracy theorist, go, 'I trust Dirty Monkey'?" We want the--we don't want the human devastation, but
we already feel like there's stuff hidden from us, so when a Dirty Monkey man shows up and says,
"I got a little bit of that sweet, sweet, like conspiratorial news, conspiracy theorists have
a tendency--" and ghost hunters and Bigfoot people, all the--all--everyone on this journey,
have a tendency to ignore our better judgment. If someone named Dirty Monkey--the guy jumps out
round corner, whereas the shirt says, "Dirty Monkey"--has a burger and said, "I made this for you.
You wouldn't eat it." But if that guy jumped out around a corner with a Manila envelope and says,
"I have the documents that prove that the Wuhan virus is killing millions and hands it to you,"
you may go, "Urgh, that's believable," because you already have a tendency to believe that.
The videotape of the people twitching, we don't have any source of where the videotape come from.
It's undated. It's creepy. But was it in Thailand in 1999? Was it in Wuhan yesterday? We don't know.
The video of the guy walking around the hospital is the newest video I saw on the doctors being
like, "Oh, no, this guy's dead in the body bags." That video, the guy was arrested and then he was
let go, because, you know, China loves to do that, too. China loves arresting people for exposing
their deepest, darkest secrets. And then letting him go, we all know that, like, political dissidents
just don't disappear in the Chinese legal system. They let him go so he could give another quote to
the news article, being like, "Oh, no, what will happen to me next?" When in China, there is no
next. You just kind of disappear. Also, how many cops are chasing people down in Wuhan at this point?
The city is... The reality is the city is under quarantine. That's real. But apparently this
guy took this video. And then what was the... Oh, I already explained the garbage-back things.
And there's a lot of videos of people walking up street and falling down on their face, which would
be hilarious with some Benny Hill music to it, but for right now, it's just people going, "Oh,
and they're saying, look at this guy dying." Almost every single video that you are seeing about that
came from the same source, The Daily Star. Now, The Daily Star is a website that I've talked a lot
about on this show over the course of 381 episodes. Daily Star is one of the most fanciful websites
out there. And there are so many times where I'm like, "Giant Pyramid floating over
the Great Lakes," and click on it, and it's Daily Star. It's like, "Oh, my God." They make stuff up
wholesale, and you're like, "So, Jason, did they stage a bunch of people twitching on the ground?"
No. I don't know when the date of that video was, but I will say this. It's really easy to get a video
of a bunch of people who don't speak your language, stand them around, talking about stuff, and then
put subtitles on it. And you could say, "Maybe no one else is covering this because Daily Star is the
only one with the balls big enough to expose the Wuhan virus." That's true. Maybe CNN and MSNBC
and Fox News and all them don't want to cover this, and Daily Star and The Guardian and The Independent
and no other media outlet in the entire planet will cover this, except for the one that we know
constantly fakes their news. You're right. You're right. This may be the one time they're actually
right, but boy, he cried wolf. So I discount all that stuff. People are dying. People do get sick,
but when the government, and you're like, "Jason, if it wasn't that bad, why would the government
are trying to lock this stuff down?" So, but let's get back into the conspiracy theory stuff.
Let's get back because there's another huge conspiracy theory about this that may be true.
Wouldn't surprise me if it was. So, but we have to also dig through the fake stuff.
In the city of Wuhan, there is a laboratory. So now we're leaving behind the hospital. We're
leaving you, the dear listener, at the hospital. No, you're better now. You've, you, because people
recover from this. People are like, "You get up. You're like, 'Oh, man, I'm kind of stiff, kind of
hungry. You guys got any bats I can eat?'" Because I guess that joke doesn't make sense if you don't
know. They believe it came from bats. They believe it came from people eating bats soup. But you're
like, "Oh, man, I'm so hungry. Are you looking at us? You're seeing us? We look like Batman."
We're like, "No, no, you're not going to eat us. Maybe we'll pick up some like bat-flavored
gummies on the way home." But let's go. Let's go. So we're pushing you in a wheelchair. We are headed
to the Wuhan Institute of Viralology. And we get there, and it's in the city of Wuhan. And now
they had actually been working on a way to figure out why bats don't get so affected by the diseases
they carry. Why is it that a bat can have Ebola, but it doesn't poop blood out of its butthole all
day long? Now, a couple months ago, last year, the Wuhan Institute of Viralogy was putting out like a
now hiring thing, saying, "We're looking for people who specialize in bat-related diseases. How is it?
We want to figure out how bats have such great immune systems, because maybe that'll help us.
Plus, in the little asterisks, plus we want to fly around." And they were trying to figure this stuff
out. Now, people go, "Hmm." And there's a whole thing going around about the Wuhan Institute of
Viralogy. Their logo is similar to the logo of the Umbrella Corporation, which is the villains of
the Resident Evil series. There is a company in China that has a logo similar to the Resident Evil
logo. It is not the Wuhan Institute of Viralogy. And again, do I think it's possible that this virus
came from the laboratory? Yeah, sure, it's possible. It's absolutely possible. Absolutely possible.
And that it escaped on accident. It wouldn't make much sense as a bio weapon, because it doesn't
seem to actually have that high of a kill rate. So we're back in the city center. We're getting
ready to board the carbon helicopter to leave behind the city of Wuhan. And you go, "Well, Jason,
okay, so do you think it's a biological weapon?" And I go, "It's pa- I don't know if it's a biological
weapon. It doesn't seem to have that high of a kill rate." But it's definitely possible that
they were working on something and it got out. That's possible. That type of stuff has happened,
or at least been considered to have happened. People think that Lyme disease was a biological
weapon that got out of a laboratory. That's an old, old conspiracy theory. But it's possible you
create something. The fact that you can have the disease and not show any symptoms and still pass
it along to people seems oddly specific, because that's what they were trying to investigate,
why bats could carry a disease and deliver it, but not show symptoms of it. So that's a little
interesting. That's a bit of an interesting side note. So it's possible that it's, you know,
China's very, very packed in. People were eating bats. The bats could have had the disease and
they got the disease and now it's jumped from human to human because it's mutated slightly.
It's possible that the facility was working on it and it got out. Let's go ahead, because I'm
not going to split this up into two episodes. I know this is running long, but there is no way.
I've teased you guys too long about this next story. And I do have to say this. On yesterday's
episode, I said, "I have no idea why this guy's name is now Hans Warmhat." And I feel stupid,
because someone on YouTube pointed it out to me. Corey Dennis. Corey Dennis said, "Uh, his name is
Hans Warmhat." Or he didn't say that. He said, "The name Hans Warmhat is from, it's always
Sunday in Philadelphia." And I was like, "Ah, you're right. You're right." But like I said,
the fool. Does that walk over to turn on the light because it suddenly got dark? The corona infected
cloud is now passing over my hometown. It's here. It's too late for me.
It's too late for me, but I'll finish this podcast anyways. Hans Warmhat. So originally,
he went, his channel was called Conspiracies by Hans. Now it's Hans Warmhat. And now my
videos always start off with a little introduction and then the most notable thing. Hey, everyone,
welcome back to another episode. Other videos go, "Hey, everyone, thanks for jumping in." Like
another podcaster or whatever PewDiePie. It's PewDiePie. All that stuff. Hans Warmhat has this.
Hans Warmhat. That might be the best sound bite. It lets you know what you're in for. It lets you
know that you're in for the most dead panned, insane information ever. I've never had anyone just
walk up to me and say, "Hans Warmhat." That's so bizarre. And I love it. Hans Warmhat. I love it so
much. So let's dig into a little bit of Hans Warmhat here. Now, Hans Warmhat talked about on the
show before. He's notable for two conspiracy theories. He has a ton of them. We're actually,
I've been digging back into them. We got some really interesting Hans stuff coming up. Did you know?
Did you know that Nickelodeon, the channel Nickelodeon, is satanic? Did you know that?
And here's why. This is, I can't believe I didn't figure this out. So he stated in an earlier video,
we touched on this before, that the color orange is satanic. That's why NASA loves the color.
NASA famously loves the color orange, right? What color is all the Nickelodeon stuff? Yep,
orange. But that's not it, man. There's lots of that are orange, dude. Vescovals and oranges,
and tangerines, and sherbet ice cream. Lots of satanic stuff. So why specifically is Nickelodeon
satanic? Nickelodeon. Nickelodeon. Nick, you hearing it? You hearing it yet? Nickelodeon. Now, I'm
gonna, you Nick. You Nick. So a man whose testicles have been removed. You Nickelodeon. You Nickelodeon.
You seeing it plays in, he has a whole video on that, by the way. Just him saying those two words
over and over again. His two most famous and bizarre conspiracy theories, one, monkeys don't exist.
Someone actually asked him, what animals do exist? And he said, the list is too exhaustive
of animals that don't exist. It'd be easier for me to name animals that do exist. He didn't do
that either. But platypuses are CGI. Sloths are fake, because they're different colors.
Monkeys aren't real. Like every monkey you've ever seen is either a man in a suit, a kid in a suit,
a puppet. And his other big conspiracy theory, other than that animals are just figments of our
imagination, is that all men are, except for a few exceptions, all men are women and all women
are men. So he's a man, and he's a man because his arms are long. Men have long arms and women
have short arms. Men are always fit. If you're overweight, like I am, you're a woman. And you're
like, Jason, you're not a woman. You're not a woman. I go, I know I'm not. And you are whatever
you are. But Hans and many people believe this conspiracy theory, by the way, that at birth,
someone looked at a little baby Jason and said, "It's a beautiful baby girl, but we're going to
pretend it's a boy." And everyone's like, "Wah." So the whole medical community's in on it, and NASA.
So anyways, he believes that all men are women, and all women are men, and it's this huge fraud
that's put on by the scientific community, and NASA, and the St. Worshippers, and Clarissa explains
it all, but she's not explaining it to us. She's part of the secret. So, foolish. I made fun of it
on my episode, "Monkeys Don't Exist," where I talked about Hans. I think it's a hilarious
conspiracy theory. It was something that only someone who exists in a small town could ever
believe, that him and the other people in the town are the true genders, and then everyone else
outside of those places are mixed up hermaphrodites, at best, at worst, totes of the satanic elite.
So imagine my shock. Imagine I'm reading the news the other day. Now, before I go into this,
because this is all true, but before I go into this, I want to be very, very clear,
to me, this does not back up his claims in any way, shape, or form. But to him, I can't wait for his
next video. If he doesn't put a video out about this, shame on you, Hans Wormhat. Shame on you,
because this would be the equivalent of NASA accidentally printing a picture of a flat earth.
I mean, this is big news for people who believe in this transvestigation, because mostly it's
centered on Hollywood. Vin Diesel is a woman, and they're all women. I mean, it gets really tiring
after a while. Every video about this is just like, "Hey, look at these men." Nope, they're women.
That's every single video in this transvestigation series. But this happened. Harvey Weinstein's.
Harvey Weinstein is currently, I gotta take my glasses off for this, because I'm going to keep
rubbing my forehead while I'm talking about this. Harvey Weinstein is currently on trial for rape.
All these women are coming forward saying he did this to me, he did that to me.
And his defense is saying, "Well, you did get a movie role, so, you know, tough luck." That's
kind of how this trial's going. And it's all pretty much standard stuff. Harvey Weinstein's
sitting there one day. Now, there's a lot of things that can suck about going to trial. One,
is that you can lose and something really bad can happen to you. Two, people can describe what your
genitals look like, and it's part of the public record, and you have two choices. You can either
defend it and say, "That's not true," and then show them to people consensually. That'd be a
totally different trial. Either way, he's like, "That's not true," pulls his pants down. Or you can
just go, "Yeah, that is true," and run with it, right? So this woman, Jessica Mann, she was
testifying against Harvey Weinstein. She said that he had raped her. The prosecutor's asking
her questions, and she makes the bombshell revelation, which if any other, if Kobe Bryant
hadn't recently died of the coronavirus, wasn't creeping across the globe. This might have been
the biggest news story ever. Apparently, Harvey Weinstein has no balls. His testicles are completely
gone. There's nothing down there. So you go, "Jason, a lot of people don't have balls." Well,
half the population doesn't have balls, but there are men who don't have testicles, right?
Yeah, yeah. You get blown off in war. They get chopped off. Some guy has a fetish, you know.
Guy who's trying to play a game of marbles didn't have any, but he had two. He always keeps with
him and cut his sack open, he's playing marbles. So that's definitely possible. But here's this
quote, this woman leaves this quote. Jessica Mann, here's the quote, "The first time I saw him naked,"
this is a reference to Harvey Weinstein, "the first time I saw him naked, I thought he was deformed
or intersex." So right there, she's basically saying he didn't have, he didn't appear to have
any testicles, and I was barely aware that he had a penis at all. I thought actually when I looked at
him, he could have been a hermaphrodite. So right there already you're on trial for sexual assault,
and you're thinking, "Oh, this is just the beginning of a very, very bad sentence." Now,
someone could say, "Yeah, he was lame, and he had a really tiny dick," and you're like, "Oh, man,
and again, what are you going to do?" You're going to be like, "No, I don't," and then pull your pants
down and everyone's like, "Yeah, it's kind of small," or you just roll with it. But she's saying,
"I thought he was deformed. It didn't look like there was anything down there." But then it gets
worse. The rest of this quote, "The first time I saw him naked, I thought he was deformed or
intersex." I didn't know, this is insulting, I didn't know if he was a burn victim, but it wouldn't
make sense. So now you're being compared to looking like someone who's had 30 degree burns.
She continues the quote with, "He does not have testicles, and it appears like he has a vagina.
He does have a penis." And apparently, when she was making these comments, Harvey Weinstein just
put his head in his hands and just kind of sat there. Because again, how are you going to defend
that? And the fact, a reporter asked him later and says, "Hey, how accurate was that description?"
He's like, "It was perfect." And again, kind of, "He might not have testicles. He may look like a
burn victim that's all busted up down there and everything like that." Which, fine. I mean, listen,
if you got it flaunted, I mean, like maybe you're into that thing and your dick's all gross and stuff
like that. Now, I would hope not, but I'm sure there's someone out there who's into that. The thing
is, is that there's a difference between not having testicles and having a gross penis. And
another thing, and people, you being a man and people thinking that you have a vagina and you
don't want them to think that. Like, if you were trans, like, that's okay. But if you're not,
and people are like, "Oh, that's a vagina." Like, that would be embarrassing, right? But this isn't
just about being embarrassing. This is 100% what Hans and company have been talking about. Again,
I'm not saying I believe in this conspiracy theory. I think it's absolutely insane. But
this is, I'm actually surprised the videos haven't already started on this. I did type in Harvey
Weinstein Transvestigation. And did you know, did you know that according to these lunatics,
every accuser of Harvey Weinstein is actually a man, Rose McGowan, Asia Argento, Jessica Mann,
it's in her name, she's also a man. These are all men. Harvey Weinstein has only been targeting men
throughout this whole ordeal. #men2 maybe is what it should be called. But it's not,
Transvestigation is trying to enlighten us. But the fact of the matter is the only video as of
right now about this is, you know, I just realized something. Hmm, if Hans and company does not
cover this Harvey Weinstein story, the fact that a major Hollywood mogul has been outed as not
at least not appearing to be fully male, not having testicles, having what appears to be a burned
up vagina and a penis, if they don't cover this story, is it possible that Hans Wormhat and his
ilk are actually controlled opposition? Hmm, is it possible that they show us ridiculous photos of
absolutely jaw-droppingly gorgeous women and say, "That's a man. That's a man." But when actually
given, state-recorded, legally documented proof in the court record of a woman saying,
"This man has a vagina that looks like Freddy Krueger goes down on it." That wasn't actually the
quote, but a burned up vagina was more like the quote. If they don't cover this, does that mean
that they're all controlled opposition? Does that mean that they're part of the cover-up as well?
Is it possible that Dead Rabbit Radio is on the forefront of exposing the burned vagina agenda
of the elite satanic Hollywood? Hopefully not. Hopefully this is not what Dead Rabbit Radio is
remembered for. No, not that. Not gonna be that. I totally don't believe that all men are women
and all women are men. But when I read this article, I basically stopped following the Harvey Weinstein
trial and I thought, "Damn you, Hans Wormhat. Damn you. If you take a win for this, if you don't,
you're part of the conspiracy. And if you do, I really think I need to have him on the show.
I really think I need to interview this guy. Maybe we can team up. I'm not a huge fan of
Weinstein. He's not a huge fan of facts and science. This might be the beginning of a beautiful
relationship. I can feel his strong manly arms wrapped around me. We're standing on a cliff
overlooking Hollywood, the city below us. He's holding me. I'm all bundled up. I'm all nestled
against his shoulder blade and he's petting my hair. He goes, "You see out there my young beautiful
girlfriend, Jay Cena. Jay Cena, you see all that town is full of beautiful dudes, but they think
they're women. And we will show them the..." He's not a very eloquent speaker, by the way.
"Hans Wormhat." He looks out and he points and he goes, "You see those city lights, Jay Cena.
Now that you've accepted your true role as a woman, this is getting really creepy. This
is getting really creepy. But you see that out there, the beautiful brunette bride. That's the
city of sin. They all believe that they're the correct sex, but they're not. And Harvey Weinstein
has given us core documents. He pulls the core documents out of his pocket, waves them in his
hand, provided to us ironically by a person named Jessica Mann. Part of the conspiracy as well,
I guess. And then he pulls out of his pocket a vial of coronavirus and he's like, "This, this is your
whatever." He's not a well spoken person. Throws the jar into the city of LA. We hear it break,
even though we're miles up. I guess that's not... The mountains aren't that high up. We hear it
break and then we start seeing people coughing in the city of LA. And I look at him and I'm like,
"Oh Hans, you big, you big, you big strong man with your tiny little thin arms. Hold me." And he goes,
"Did you know I will never let you go?" He's holding me tight. And then he turns to the camera and goes,
"DeadRapRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address." I'm like, "Oh, our email address? We're
finally... DeadRapRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRapRadio. Twitter is @DeadRapRadio. DeadRapRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it
today. I'm sure you're not though. Have a great one guys.
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]