An invisible city, populated by shape shifters.
And a story so weird, you're just gonna have to take my word for it. Today on Dead Rava Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rava Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. I have a busy weekend coming up.
I hope your weekends are equally busy and fun. So I'm recording this episode a little bit early,
but it'll be released in the normal schedule. It's cold. It's like 11 o'clock at night here.
My window's open. It's actually time for me to start running a heater. That's neither here nor
there because I want to go ahead and get started with this episode because again, it's going to be
a weird one. So I mentioned earlier that I had finished watching Twin Peaks Season 3 and that
kind of ties into our first story. So let me go over that just super quickly. I'm going to recommend
it for people who are a fan of anything 40 and or weird. Now the first two seasons are a bit different
than the third season. The first two seasons is a long kind of drawn out soap opera that has these
creepy elements and they first it starts off, you think it's a murder mystery and then it involves
stuff like demons and UFOs and portals to other dimensions and it really started to kind of freak
people out. As a kid, I was always afraid of Twin Peaks, but I was also obsessed with it. It's really
the the forerunner of all the shows like X-Files and Buffy the Vampire Slayer, The Killing. A lot
of these shows wouldn't exist without Twin Peaks. It broke a lot of ground. Now when Twin Peaks Season
3 was coming out, there was always the question of was it going to be the small town slice of life
with a little dash of dimensional stuff or was it going to be balls to the wall weirdness?
And it was balls to the wall weirdness. And the show's genius, the last episode ends of the second
season with Agent Dale Cooper, FBI Agent Dale Cooper being trapped in another dimension and being told
in 25 years he can leave and Season 3, I believe, starts, was filmed 25 years later. I don't know
how they planned that. It could have been 20 years later, but it was close enough. And Season 3 is
all about other dimensions, doppelgangers, demons, an invasion force like this interdimensional alien
coming down. I'm not spoiling any of it really because there's tons of more stuff, maybe a little
bit of spoiling, but it was amazing. It was absolutely amazing. And it actually had one of
the things that creeps me out the most. And that is, and David Lynch is really good at this,
making the normal horrifying. So there's a scene where, so there's two special Agent Dale Coopers.
One is a doppelganger who is being piloted by a demon knowing as, knowing as killer Bob. And the
other one is actually special Agent Dale Cooper. And there's a scene where the evil version,
Mr. C, is what he's known as. He goes to a gas station in the middle of nowhere. And he walks
up the stairs of like, he walks up the stairs of the gas station to the roof and he flickers and
he disappears. And he ends up in this pocket dimension that's like an old hotel, which is,
that's creepy to me because you drive past these places constantly. And I'm always afraid of those
portals, those like the man from Torah type of things, where you just kind of walk in the wrong
spot and you disappear from our reality. I don't necessarily think it's super likely, but I think
it's possible, definitely. And so the show is full of stuff like that. At one point, a couple other
FBI agents go to an abandoned lot. And then a couple sheriffs go to this meadow in the middle
of the forest. And there's just these vortexes of activity. If you go to the right place or wrong
place at a certain time, you will get thrust into these horrifying events. And that really plays a
huge part in season three. Then when he's leaving the gas station, when he comes back down the stairs
and he flickers back into our reality, we learn the gas station doesn't even exist. It's just a
grove of trees. So imagine you're a civilian in this situation. You're just driving down the road
to get to your house. You're driving through the wilderness. And you're just passing grove of trees.
And you don't know that in that grove of trees, sometimes if you're there the right time,
there will be a gas station. And if you walk up the stairs to the roof of that gas station,
you will be thrust into this pocket dimension. I find that absolutely terrifying because it is the
mundane turned into the terrifying. And that is where we're going to start our episode. And again,
if I haven't made it clear enough, watch it. It's a great show. It's incredibly well done.
And especially season three, I've wondered if you could hop into season three without having
seen the first two seasons. I definitely recommend all of them. But if you just wanted to get like
the super weirdness, you might be able to jump right in episode three. I mean, season three,
I watched all three seasons and there's still stuff that doesn't make sense to me. So,
but anyway, so we're going to talk about, I'm going to probably mispronounce it, but
Beringin City. So Beringin City is basically a real life little gas station. Now what I mean by
real life is that people say it exists. This is a city in the Philippines. And it's just in this
mass of wilderness. And if you go at night, if you're in the right mental state, or you're attractive,
you'll see the city. Now fishermen will be out fishing out in the Philippines and they'll look
over and they'll just see a huge towers with lights on. It's been compared to Hong Kong,
but it's not modern skyscraper. There are these huge, huge spires, these huge ancient buildings
that have been built up. And you look over and you're fishing at night and you see this lighted
city. Bus drivers have been driving at night, driving through the area, and then they lose time.
And the next thing we know, they're in the middle of the forest or jungle, right where the city should
be. When people go missing, when people, they say visitors come to the Philippines, come to that
area, they go missing, the locals go out. They went to Beringin City. They got them. Sometimes
they'll find bodies of people who have gone missing. And what's interesting about that is the locals
go, that's not a body. That's a tree stump disguised as a body. His soul is in Beringin. So what is
Beringin City? It's populated, again, in legend, it's populated by the Ing Kanto. What the Ing Kanto
are is they are a race of shapeshifters. Now they can take any form that they want, but oddly
enough, when they take human form, they're missing that little groove underneath their nose. You know
how people have fetal alcohol syndrome, just kind of have a flat lip, something akin to that.
They dress in all black and all their food is black. Interesting little side note. And they're
considered neutral to evil, depending on the situation. They're considered, a lot of times
they're considered demons in the area, but it's been told that if you are picked to go to Beringin
City, you will be taken care of. You will mate with them and you will live this life of luxury
in this amazing rich city. So a lot of times poor kids go missing and again people go,
the kid must have went to Beringin City because look where he's at now. He's in a slum and now
he's off someplace better. It's fascinating to me and this legend's persisted for centuries,
really, that there is this city that people swear exists and to the point where when they find
something that contradicts it, like if they go, well that guy must have gone to Beringin City and
then they find his body a few days later, died of exposure or animal attack or whatever, they go,
no, that's not really his body, that's a tree stump. It's magically, I don't know how they explain
the autopsy. They're doing an autopsy to a bunch of butterflies come out. There's like a snail on
them, I don't know, but it's just interesting. That's how pervasive this legend is. They say that
in the neighboring cities around where Beringin City should be, and again, excuse me, I apologize
if I'm mispronouncing it, I probably am, but in the neighboring cities there's portals. There'll be
like a branch or an odd shaped rock or a particular inlet to a river and they go, don't go over there.
Why not? Well, that's a portal that'll take you right to the city. That terrifies me, you know,
because it's one of those things, like when you hear about missing people in national parks or you
just hear like people just straight up vanish, of course your first thing is, oh, they probably fell
or an animal got him or the guy came after something like that, but there's always that 0.01%
that they're like, this guy just literally vanished. He disappeared off the face of the earth,
and I think, what if there are these portals out there? And when we look at old legends like
the legends of the Fae, when we look at modern day UFO abductions too, there are just these places
where you go and you're taken away. The Philippines is far, far removed obviously from Scotland and
Ireland, but it has the same myth and that is you can get tricked into entering to their realm.
And like I said, they're neutral to evil. You can join them. You very rarely get to leave. People
have seen the city and gotten to the outskirts. I think a couple people have said that they
went into the city. That's how we have more detailed events. But for the most part, once you're in,
you're in, you're not getting out and they use you to make. They look for like strapping young men
and gorgeous women. They take them in to mate with them. Imagine, put aside all of your
reservations about this idea if you have any to begin with. Imagine the impact if that was ever
proven. Like imagine if one day Google Earth is running a satellite over the Philippines,
or one night, and it picks up a spattering of light. And we send, they send in a like a team
of explorers and they actually come out and they say, yeah, this city actually exists. You can only
see it at a certain point in time and we only got so far and we encountered these creatures.
What that would be far more devastating to the human psyche than UFOs exist. Like if UFOs came
down, people would go like, yeah, I kind of figured that. Like it's creepy knowing that we're no longer
the most advanced species in the galaxy. But imagine if it became proven that on this planet
there is, there are portals to other worlds full of magical creatures. Like that you, that would
shake everything up. I mean, how it would shake everything up. It would shake up everything from
like travel exploration. It would shake up police because then they'd be like, well, the guy could
have been kidnapped or he could have fallen into a portal and went to Zha Zha land. Like it would
completely change, change the way we looked at our own planet. We would have, you'd have travel guides
saying, don't go to this place at a certain time of night because you will never come back.
And then people, people would just say, you know what, honey, I'm out of here. Wait, no, no, come
back. We have five kids war goes into a portal. I mean, you know what I mean? Like, and to me,
see again, that's, that's terrifying. Ghosts are scary, but it kind of a little comforting because
you know there's life after death. Aliens, I think are exciting if they're like, like, you know,
running bombing raids and we're like rising up as a single species to take them down.
But what if it's like, yeah, don't go out of your house today. There's a roaming portal in your
neighborhood. Please stay inside. If you start to see any of your silverware like get sucked into a
vortex, immediately call authorities. There is a portal in your house. Like that's way more
terrifying because it's primal. It's this phenomenon that's just kind of happening. And again, people
would go missing and you'd be like, well, maybe maybe they're in the portal. Don't go near those
rocks. Don't go near. Damn it. Lost another one. Time to have another kid. I think that's far more
terrifying. It would be one thing that I definitely wouldn't go looking for. There's a scene again in
Twin Peaks Season 3 where a guy stands on a rock and gets electrocuted for like two minutes and
just blows up. I don't want to go to that rock. I don't want to accidentally be like, hey, honey,
where do you want to have a picnic? Oh, how about that rock? Again, that's, that's scary to me.
This city full of these shape shifting creatures, stories of like the fairies, like taking people
away into their realm. They walk, like dance in a circle or like, you know, they always say,
never eat anything a fairy gives you because you'll never, you'll be sucked into their realm.
How do I know? It's not some hot chick at a rave wearing fairy wings. I don't know. Spooky.
Barrage in city. You guys might be brave enough to check it out, but not me. It's, oh, it's the
reverse of Dublin, Wisconsin or Ong's hat. It's not a city that disappeared. It's a city that appears.
Cities disappearing and dying are normal, but cities appearing and disappearing, then appearing
again and disappearing. That's the definition of paranormal, of supernatural. It's something that
doesn't belong in our reality. This next story is weird. And I'm not able to find the resources
that I had on it, but not because of any sort of cover up. I kind of knew that was going to be
the case when I started looking forward again, because it was hard to find in the first place.
Now I got to tell you a little bit about myself. I used to be 10 toes into the conspiracy world.
I used to believe everything. You getting me now as a skeptic is a sharp turn from where I was
10, 10 years ago, maybe even less than that, maybe like six, seven years ago. I used to believe all
of it. I used to be a 9/11 truther. I used to believe in the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the
behind it. It was an inside job. I was 100% a 9/11 truther. Absolutely believed in things. I didn't
believe in the laser beams blowing up the buildings or the hologram planes, but I did believe in the
explosions inside. I believed mostly that the George Bush let it happen. He knew that the planes
were coming and he didn't do anything. So he could enact his great Christian plan to purge the Middle
East of everyone who's not Jewish or Christian. Absolutely. I turned away from that because I
kept, I was investigating it on 9/12, like a lot of people. And I was a big fan of info wars back in
the day. It was the first time I'd ever seen anything like that. You're getting this immediate
information. Felt for a hook line and sinker. And I investigated for years and years and years,
and always the linchpin was building seven, building seven. And then I started seeing videos from the
other side of building seven, the building that had no structural damage whatsoever. There's videos
that show the other side of building seven, huge gash, huge gash in it from falling debris from
the towers. And then the video where they show building seven falling like a controlled demolition.
You may not know this. That's an edited video. They always show you the same video where it just
pancakes down. There's videos out there that show the whole sequence of events. There's a
small structure on top of building seven. And that collapses first, and then it starts collapsing.
So that structure on top fell down, and that just the structural, it was the building already had a
huge gash in it. And once that structure fell down, that was the straw that broke the camel's back,
it collapsed. Whenever you see 9/11 Truth or Videos, they cut out the scene where the first
structure falls down. And I've talked about this on another episode. I know the government lies to
me. That's just what governments do. It's how they function. It's not good or bad, but that's how
they function. I didn't expect the conspiracy theorists to lie to me, but once I realized that
they were cherry picking their facts as well, I was like, well, they're not believable either.
If they were saying everything hinges on building seven, and that was fake, then I went back with a
more critical eye and looked at all this other footage and started to look at, yes, jet fuel
doesn't melt still beams, but it weakens it. And all of this, all of these other facts, you know,
before that I was like popular science, they don't know what they're talking about. No building has
ever been brought down by fire. I am far more skeptical now than I was then. I attribute that
to a couple different things. One is just looking into the facts more, having a more critical eye
when I look at anything. This is going to sound funny. And this is a huge plug. My favorite podcast
of all time, Parapod is a podcast with two British comedians. One believes everything, the other one
is a skeptic, and it was interesting to see stuff that I believed in being with a skeptic,
kind of pissing it away in such a funny, entertaining way. It also made me go, maybe I'm
mistaken on some of these beliefs that I have. I'm not a proponent of someone who says you can
never change your mind because my mind has been changed by facts. My mind has been,
I've moved back and forth on the political scale. I've moved back and forth on all sorts of issues
because the facts change or I get a new set of facts, or I've just grown as a person and don't
feel the same way. So I wanted to do that introduction because like I said, I was totally deep into
conspiracy theories. When back in 2010, I used to spend all my time researching this stuff,
back in 2010, I came across the website that was titled something to the point of the plan
to take over America. It was from a Norwegian group, some sort of paramilitary group based out of
Norway, and they had a map of the United States and you could click on each individual state and
some states were broken up into zones and it would tell you what the plan was, how they were going
to conquer these areas. And I lived in California at the time and California was like 30% nuked,
rest of the survivors rounded up into camps. And then I'm checking like Nevada and I'm checking
Utah and they're like Utah, massive exposure to radiation, no survivors. And it was a very detailed
map. And I'm reading this and I'm like, holy shit, I just stumbled across this thing. I don't even
remember where I found it. I just like I said, used to spend all my time doing this stuff.
And I started to share it. I started to share it with people. I'll back then I spent a lot of time
on the website, GodlikeProductions, GLP, GodlikeProductions.com. It's a conspiracy website. They're
complete nuts. And it was so funny to watch the follow up part after 2012, because again,
like I said, I was pulling out of that I went back there about the week two and the week after 2012
just to watch everyone freak out. But I shared it with some people on there. And I tried checking
my Godlike Productions history, but I had changed accounts and there was nothing there. See if I
could find the original link. The reason why the story is interesting. I remember this stuff very
clearly. Around 2010, there was a comet you may remember, Elenin. Elenin was a comet that at the
time in the conspiracy community, people were like, this is going to hit the planet. This is going to
cause massive destruction. And it's going to the New World Order is planning. I believed all that
stuff. All that stuff. Anyways, I still believe that there are private groups that want to enforce,
put their rule on people at large, but I don't believe in like a single group now.
But anyway, so the New World Order was planning all this and they're going to outlive the destruction
and then anyone who was alive, they're going to take their slaves. Elenin was coming in and I was
freaking out. I thought, oh my God, this comet's going to hit. It's going to destroy everything.
And what was interesting was the plan to take over America, that website, a key component of it was
Comet Elenin. So it was even feeding more into my paranoia. You would click on states and it would say
this state will be wiped out due to the tidal waves by Comet Elenin. This state will be devastated
by shock waves when Comet Elenin hits. Like it was all built into that. And so what the website
was putting forward was after the comet, Elenin, hit us, this private army was going to then,
their first thing was they were going to attack and then invade America. They saw that as the
biggest threat. They saw that that after the comet hits, we would either rebuild the old world order
or we could take out America and rebuild the New World Order. And I checked, I was looking at all
these states and I was like, oh my God, like where's safe to go? Like obviously I couldn't, I didn't
have, I couldn't go anywhere. But I was freaking out. I was actually talking to friends about it. I
was like, what state do you live in? I mean, it was ridiculous. Like I was that level of doom guy.
The interesting thing about it was that in the early summer, maybe around May or June of 2011,
a message popped up. And I know you're thinking Jason, how do you remember all these details,
but you can't even find the site? And fair enough, I'm not, I'm not making it up, but you have to
take my word for it. If you don't take my word for it, that's fine. If you think I'm just making
it up, that's totally fine. I'm not, but I would understand if you said, ah, he's just riffin'.
Fair enough. It was around May or June of 2011 and the site got updated. And it said,
warning, warning, Comet Ellenan is breaking up. May have been taken out by alien spacecraft.
We will revisit the new plan in July. I was like, what? It's weird. So it was like they had to,
they still wanted to go on with the plan, but the Comet was now breaking up. They had
realized there was a structural integrity issue and the Comet wasn't going to impact the way
they wanted it to or the way they thought they were going to. So Comet Ellenan is breaking up
possible extraterrestrial intervention. We will come back to this plan in July and figure out what
we're going to do. I was like, I'm paranoid still. July rolls around and July 22nd in Norway was one
of the worst mass shootings. I personally think it's one of the worst mass shootings ever.
And that was when that scumbag, Anders Brevik,
went to a summer camp and it was shot a bunch of kids. And I remember reading in the newspaper
how kids were like, it was on an island. First he dropped it, he set off a couple bombs in the
capital also. Then he went to this island and he was shooting up this summer camp and kids jumped
into the water and were trying to swim away and he shot him. Scumbag. And do you know because of the
prison system over there, he's sitting in an apartment better than mine?
He's in there for life, but
anyways, Andrew Brevik shot 77 people. And the site, like I said, was a Norwegian.
It was based in Norway, but it was all in English. And the shooting was also in Norway. So
maybe like a couple days after that happened, the site got updated. I checked it regularly.
It was terrified. And the website got updated and it said, listen, this was all a troll.
This was all a joke. We have nothing to do with the shooting that happened in Norway.
Our hearts are broken over it. This was all just a joke. We are going to just shut it down.
None of this was serious. Our hearts and prayers go out to the people involved.
So I thought, that's interesting. Like, okay, well, I mean, I guess I'm not paranoid anymore.
It was all a troll. The plan to take over America and the fact that the comet was going to hit and
the reason why they were going to, it was very, very detailed. But again, you know, trolls can do
that. Trolls can be very detailed. And so eventually the website, I just kind of was like, oh, it's
a troll. I kind of stopped going there. A couple months later, same year 2011, August, September,
comet Ellen and broke up in deep space.
It fragmented. It fell apart. Just like the website said.
I've never been able to figure out how they guessed that.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
You can, our Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter.
I swear that story is true. I know I talked about doing short horror stories, but that one's true.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen
to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great day, guys.