A cell phone left behind in a taxi cabin Fiji shocks the nation.
Then we travel to Mexico to see if there's any truth to the rumors that a satanic homeless
person is letting the world he will no longer get dumped on.
Then we travel to Los Angeles to take a look at the story of Philip Taylor Kramer.
First he was a bassist for the band Iron Butterfly, then he began working on missile systems
for the US government, but in the end he mysteriously disappeared.
Is it possible that it was suicide?
Or was someone truly out to get him today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We have a ton of stuff to cover, no joke, you heard about all the stuff in the intro.
Let's see if we actually get to the stories I presented.
First off, let's give a shout out to today's supporter, it's another person who supported
my 2019 Thanksgiving livestream.
Sorry it took so long to give a round of applause for SK.
Everyone give a round of applause for SK, he's slithering in like a snake holding a
K holding a K with him.
SK you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the show financially, that's fine too.
Just helps spread the word about the show.
Really really really helps out a lot.
So SK we're going to give you a little reptilian hands, you're going to evolve some arms and
legs I'm hoping for this episode otherwise it will be tricky.
I'm going to toss you an ore, you can catch it in your little snake mouth until your arms
grow.
It's a tiny ore, it's a tiny souvenir ore.
I'm going to toss you an ore to the Dead Rabbit Robot, we are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed to the island nation of Fiji.
That's us rowing, very very dynamic sound effect.
The year is 2016 and specifically we're in the town of Sava in Fiji.
Beep beep, cars are driving down the road, taxi cabs, there's like a bus, couple people
on bicycles, a normal day in the city of Sava.
And some guy gets into this taxi cab and he sits down and he goes "Ow my butt!"
He gets up and he realizes someone had left their phone in this taxi cab.
He asks the taxi cab driver "Hey is this your phone?"
He's like "No I have my phone in the front of the cab.
Why would I have my phone in the back of the cab?"
"Oh chill out bro."
I was just asking, I found this cell phone, do you have any idea who's it is?
The taxi cab driver thinks about it and he goes "Well I did have these other fares but
you know people come and go, it's a taxi, you just hop into a taxi, you get out.
Hopefully when you get out you take everything with you."
But here's this cell phone.
Now the man who finds this cell phone, like we all would, if it's an unlocked phone I've
done this, I know you guys have done it, I've found several phones in my life.
So start scrolling through stuff.
And this phone had a video.
How are you not going to watch a video on a mysterious phone that you've found?
That story, that intro, seems to be in dispute.
I actually am getting this story from the 40 in map, we've talked about this several
times on the show, it's an interactive map of weird events.
Some of them have turned out not to be verifiable, this one is, but that intro I just told you,
I can't verify that part's true.
But the second part is 100% true, because it's available on YouTube.
Whether or not the video came from this cell phone that was found in the back of the taxi
cab or that's some sort of a bizarre creepypasta, the fact of the matter is there is cell phone
footage from Fiji taken out in the middle of the ocean.
There's wreckage of a boat, there's debris just kind of floating there, the boat itself
is overturned, and there's people hanging onto it.
But what's weird is that the person who's taking the video isn't part of the debris,
they're not holding their phone up and they're like maybe I'll get a signal, but until then,
selfie as they're floating, there's a boat floating next to the debris filming all this
stuff.
And they're not making a move to rescue these people, they're letting these four people
cling to this debris in the middle of the ocean.
This goes on for about 5 minutes.
5 minutes of just videotaping people clinging to life.
And then you hear someone say behind the camera "Buka!
Buka!"
Which means fire.
Now it's not like they're watching a fire envelop the debris, someone is telling the
people on the safe boat to open fire.
"Dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat dat
that