I got invited to join the Illuminati.
A couple questions I have about ghosts and demons interacting with humans.
And I honestly don't know how the show will go on after this episode.
This might be the dumbest conspiracy I've ever heard.
World War II never happened.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
I wish you guys could see the smile on my face every time I start one of these episodes.
I'm always super excited.
The last story though man.
I really had to steal myself to do this one.
I came home.
Relaxed.
Watched a couple YouTube videos.
I really like Mr. Gigi.
Took a shower.
Drank a large glass of Diet Cola.
And was like, "Okay, now it's time to talk about this stuff."
Because it might honestly be the dumbest conspiracy theory I've ever heard of.
And I was actually denying that anyone in the world would ever think about it.
Or believe in it.
But we'll get to that in a bit.
I want to talk about our first story.
So a couple, probably about a month ago on YouTube.
Now this comment went into, when people leave comments on YouTube, if you provide a link
generally or an email address, it goes into my spam folder.
And then I have to approve it to go to the actual comment page.
So a couple people have dropped stories and said, "Hey, have you thought about covering
this?"
And they'll include like a Wikipedia link.
That usually starts off in the spam folder.
Have to send it over.
About a month ago, I got this, someone commented on one of my videos regarding the Illuminati.
An invitation for myself to join the Illuminati.
And technically, anyone who reads the YouTube comments.
Let's take a look at this.
Welcome to the Great Brotherhood.
This is what the comment says.
Do you want to be a member of the Illuminati as a brotherhood that will make you rich and
famous in the world and have power to control people in the high place in the world wide?
I think you're already picking up English is not this person's first language.
Possibly not even their second language.
Are you a businessman or woman?
They should know whether or not I'm a man or a woman based on the show.
If the Illuminati's inviting me to join them, they should have basic information.
Are you a businessman or woman artist, political musician?
I should say politician, but political musician, student, do you want to be rich, famous, powerful
in life?
Illuminati Brotherhood cult today and get instant rich sum of $2 million in a week
and a free home anywhere you choose to live in this world.
Not the next world, but just this one.
That sounds nice.
$2 million within a week.
I could use that.
Benefits given to new members of the Illuminati.
So this is what they're trying to pitch me on to make me join the Illuminati.
One, a cash reward of $5,000 US.
You just gave me $2 million, dude.
And now I get another $500,000.
You should have just said I'll get $250,000.
Plus it takes more than a week to get the $500,000.
Number two, a new sleek dream car.
Car is in all caps.
Valued at $300,000 US.
I could just buy my own with the $2.5 million you've already given me.
Plus why is there a cap on the amount for the car?
Don't quite get that.
That's the, you're the Illuminati.
There should be no spending limit.
Three, a dream house bought in the country of your choice.
Oh, that's nice again.
I mean, I'd pick America.
I don't really want to go anywhere else.
Four, one month holiday fully paid to your dream tourist destination.
Why one month?
I'm a member of the Illuminati.
Can you imagine like your 29 days in and they're like, the hotel's like,
"Listen, you only paid up till tomorrow.
I'm in the Illuminati.
We control this planet."
Five, one year golf membership package.
Now golf rumors jokes aside, I don't like golf.
They should say one year.
I don't know why I'm trying to tell the Illuminati how to recruit,
but it should be like season tickets to your favorite sport
or unlimited movie pass or something like that.
Six, a VIP treatment in all airports around the world.
Big whoop.
I mean, technically I should be taking private planes
since I'm in the Illuminati now.
But I guess now I just get to go to the little like free bar
up in the like sections, off section.
Who care?
Oh, VIP treatment in any airport in the world.
Seven, a total lifestyle change.
I think that's kind of built into becoming a member of the Illuminati
and getting $2.5 million and a $300,000 car and all that stuff.
I don't know why that has its own bullet point, but it does.
Eight, access to the Bohemian Grove account every month as a member.
Now, I don't know what the Bohemian Grove account is.
I know what the Bohemian Grove is.
It's really only active once.
I think every year it could be every four years or somewhere in between.
Other than that, it's just a state park.
It's not actually like a state park that you can go and visit.
But yeah, I would just be walking around talking to owls and stuff.
If no one else was there, what's the point of going to the Bohemian Grove?
And if I have access to the Bohemian Grove account, I'm taking everyone's money.
Because I have access to it.
What do I care?
Nine, one month booked appointment with top five world leaders
and top five celebrities in the world.
Now, here's my thing.
Do I get to...
It says one month booked appointment.
Does that mean the appointment is booked within a month of me joining?
Or does that mean I literally get to spend 30 days with these people?
And they can't go anywhere.
I'm like, dude, we're having this appointment.
It is one month long.
Nothing will get done.
Let's see.
Top five world leaders.
Who?
I don't...
I can't even...
Who would I hang out with?
What world leaders would I want to hang out with for a month?
Donald Trump would pick on me.
He'd probably be like, hey, chubby.
And then he'd be like, I'm just joking.
I imagine that would go on for a month.
Hey, you're walking real slow there.
Maybe you should lose some weight.
Nah, I'm just messing with you.
I'm just messing with you.
At 30 days of that.
What other top world leaders would I want to hang out with?
I'm trying to think of someone who could teach me something.
Like, is Arnold Schwarzenegger our world leader?
He could get me in a shape.
We could spend a month with Donald Trump hazing me for my weight in the morning,
working out with Arnold Schwarzenegger in the afternoon.
So then by the 30th day, I can be like, peace out, Donald.
Not so big anymore, am I?
Who else is a world leader?
Obviously, we're getting really loose with these guys.
I can't think of any world leader I would want to be trapped with.
Even those two I don't think I'd want to spend a month with.
Is there anyone else?
I'm trying to imagine the planet Earth.
The Pope.
Nah.
He'd be preaching to me all the time.
Oh, geez.
See, now here we are.
OK, top five celebrities, though.
I can name those.
George Lucas.
I'd love to pick his brain and find out what should have happened in the next episodes
of Star Wars.
Ice Cube.
I'd hang out with him.
He wouldn't put up with me, but I'd hang out with him.
I got to name the other ones real quick here.
I got three more celebrities.
The Illuminati wants their answer.
I will pick Zack Snyder, because I really like the guy.
And I think he gets a bum rap.
And I feel really bad for him.
He's not like pity-wise, but I'm sure he loves movies.
And every time you watch a YouTube channel about movies or read anything about movies,
pop culture, they always talk trash about him.
So I'd hang out with him and lift his spirits up.
And we can talk about Don and the Dead, because that's one of my favorite movies.
Oh, geez.
Two more celebrities.
Come on, let's go.
You guys have already shut the podcast off.
But the Illuminati needs me to answer this question.
Who's my favorite actor?
Or musician?
Oh, man.
The Illuminati really is putting pressure on me.
I don't know.
Robocop and Darth Vader.
They counted celebrities, right?
I would hang out with them.
It's the Illuminati.
I want Robocop and Darth Vader to show up.
And then it says, it finishes it off.
If you are interested of joining-- a bad grammar.
If you are interested of joining us in the Great Brotherhood of Illuminati, contact Mr.
Roland or WhatsApp him.
And then there's a WhatsApp number here, plus 234-814-258-7627 or email.
This is the best email I've ever seen in my life.
IlluminatiPower666Brotherhood@gmail.com.
So the Illuminati uses Gmail apparently.
Now, of course, when I saw this, I was like, what?
And I looked at it.
I did a search for Mr. Roland.
He posts-- it's a bot.
Anything that is posted about the Illuminati, this pops up.
I saw it on a bunch of blogs.
And I saw it in a other YouTube video related things.
Weird thing is, is the amount changes.
So I get a cash reward of $500,000.
Some people only get a cash reward of $300,000.
And others, I start off with two millions in a week.
Some other people got offered five million in a week.
I give you the WhatsApp number and email address.
I'm going to actually approve the message so it will appear.
I wouldn't-- it's obviously a scam.
I know what's going to happen is that they're
going to say, well, if you want this money,
give us your bank account.
And we'll transfer it in there and blah, blah, blah.
Or we'll send you a cashier's check
and you have to deposit and all that stuff.
But it's a bot.
Anytime someone posts something about the Illuminati
on the internet, this pops up.
IlluminatiPower666Brotherhood@gmail.com.
Just sounds ridiculous.
First off, why would you put 666 in there?
If you want to trick me into joining you,
that's a red flag that things are going to go south.
Not interested.
However, $2 million in a week does sound nice.
And if you can get me meetings with the real Robocop--
I don't know Peter Weller, actual Robocop and Darth Vader--
we might have a deal.
But they can't kill me.
It can't be like a genie thing where I go to meet them
and Darth Vader cuts my head off.
It has to be legit.
Like, I meet Darth Vader.
We shake hands.
I warn him.
I'm like, dude, things are not going to go well for you.
I want to meet Darth Vader at the beginning of A New Hope.
So I can be like, hey, this is what's going to happen.
You're going to become a good guy eventually.
So just become a good guy now and kill the emperor.
And then you can prevent all of the sequels.
You can set up a legit government with your son
and your daughter.
Yes, you have a daughter.
And then you will set up a peaceful government now.
And we won't have to worry about Princess Leia flying
through space.
And he'll be like, what?
And I'll be like, peace.
And I'll just come back to our reality.
If you can do that for me, we have a deal.
So now for our second story--
our second segment, really.
I want to talk to you about some questions I
have regarding ghosts and demons.
Now, yesterday or a couple days ago when I did the episode
about the Conjuring 2, I referenced
that I had written a review for the Conjuring 1
on my website, Video Vandals.
The link will be in below.
But I was reading my review.
And it had some questions I had about the movie and ghosts
in general.
And as I was reading it, I thought,
these are actually really good questions.
And I think this will make a good segment on the show.
Because a lot of times when we think of ghosts,
we don't really think logically.
Or we don't extend it to the realm of logic.
And I believe in ghosts--
I've said this before-- I believe in ghosts and demons
and stuff like that.
I don't believe they're as powerful as people think they
are.
I think that if they exist, they're
some sort of quasi-paranormal, multidimensional type
of thing.
I don't think that they are as powerful as a lot of people
think they are.
And here's my questions for that.
Just ghosts and demons in general.
Just a couple questions.
Just asking questions like people like to say.
So if a demon can possess a doll and run around the house,
if a demon can possess objects, which is generally like--
they're like, this music box is haunted.
And it wakes me up at night.
Or this doll is haunted--
Robert the doll is haunted or Annabelle is haunted.
It's possessed by the ghost of this person.
And they're just running around and scaring you.
Why can't a ghost or a demon possess a predator drone
and just fly around and blow up churches?
I mean, why is it they just--
they use their supernatural powers
to enter an inanimate object, make it animate,
and then hide around the corner or little footprints
that you hear late at night?
Why don't they step the game up?
These demons and some of these ghosts
are like, get out of my house.
Type of like, grabbing you by the throat.
You know, the ghost hunters are in the house
with their infrared cams.
They're like, something just grabbed me.
Why don't they just make the electrical cables
wrap around the dude's neck?
Because it can.
Why is it just you scary stuff and not deadly stuff?
If your goal as a ghost or a demon, again,
is to get people to not move into a house or to leave a house.
So you'll see stuff like, written on the mirror, get out.
Or they'll be walking around to haunted asylum
and you hear a voice being like, leave now.
They're like, I caught it on my EVP.
I totally heard that.
Oh, no, something's choking me.
If they don't want people there, if they don't
want to be disturbed, which is a common theme, especially
in haunted house movies, that was what
was happening in The Conjuring and The Conjuring 2.
Why don't they just possess a home inspector
to show up and be like, yeah, this house has a really bad case
of black mold.
No one can live here.
Yep, the wiring is faulty.
This place is a fire hazard.
No one can live here.
Why not?
Because they can possess people, right?
Why don't they do that?
Are Muslim, atheist, Jewish, ghosts of other religions?
Are they affected by crucifix or by prayers?
Latin Catholic prayers.
Can a Jewish ghost haunt a non-culture kitchen?
I think those are relevant questions.
If you believed your entire life, if you were a Muslim,
and that was the faith you abscribed to, and then you die,
do you use your ghost to go, oh, no, no, no.
Now I'm this other religion that's affected by crosses.
Or would a ghost of a Muslim dude be like,
you're like, get out by the name of the Lord Jesus Christ
and they're just like, whatever, dude.
They're like, eating halal food.
You're like, oh, no, where did all my chicken go?
So I mean, again, that's something
that I think people who believe in ghosts
kind of have to address.
I think the idea is that there's one true religion,
and if you're a ghost, then you are bound
to that true religion or whatever.
But if you believed all your life, if you were Buddhist
and you found out you were a ghost and you're like,
oh, I guess reincarnation isn't true,
and then someone comes, some priest comes,
and he starts screaming at you in Latin,
are you just gonna be like,
I can't even understand what you're saying.
I'm trying to meditate.
Why do ghosts always wear clothes?
Most people die in their underwear or naked.
But when we look at ghosts of like Elizabethan times,
they're in like the full garb women are in the corsets
and the bustier or the bustier, whatever.
They're in like the full gear and they have the,
can you imagine wearing that stuff?
I'm an actor, I do stuff in local theater.
The costumes are so heavy and it's hot as hell.
I do a lot of Shakespearean stuff.
If I had to spend eternity dressed like Lord Capulet,
I would go insane.
That wouldn't make me an evil ghost.
If Marie Antoinette died in her knickers,
wouldn't her ghost be like topless in knickers?
Why aren't there more ghosts like wearing like
stained tank tops or like Frankie says, relax shirts.
And they're like, oh man, I died in this?
That's okay.
Frankie says, relax is a great band.
And then five years later, they're like,
oh, you die wearing a matchbox 20 shirt
and you're like just stuck forever.
Okay, so here's another point.
Does anyone else think it's a coincidence
that 90% of the things attributed to ghosts
like door slamming shut, things falling, cold spots,
et cetera, can also be caused by that mysterious force
known as wind?
Why is it always stuff that can happen naturally
under the right set of circumstances?
There's so funny.
So in Conjuring 2, you know,
Conjuring 2 was supposedly based on a real case.
And there was a photo of a girl levitating
in the middle of the room.
It is a very, very famous photo
among paranormal investigators.
Look at this picture of this girl.
She is floating in the middle of this room.
She has very, very, very clearly just jumped off the bed.
There is no way she did not just jump.
And the photo was taken while she was in midair.
It is the most ridiculous piece of evidence
that I've seen regarding ghosts.
And that's saying a lot.
'Cause I've seen stuff that was out and out like CGI fraud.
But this has been, look at her.
She's levitating.
No, she's jumping in the air.
If I take a picture every other second
of a girl jumping rope, is that proof
that she is possessed?
'Cause her feet are off the ground?
It's insane.
I mean, and there are a lot of other questions
about ghosts like, why do you go?
So the way we see is through light going into our eyeballs
and it refracting so we can see what's out there.
Ghosts don't have eyeballs.
So how can they see anything?
Technically, they don't have eardrums either.
I mean, so they can't hear you.
Ouija boards, they don't make any sense
because can I talk to a ghost who doesn't know English?
Can I talk to a ghost who knows English
but it's old-timey English?
And they say like thou a lot.
It's always like it'll spell out, don't go there,
not like thou shalt not moveeth from thou place.
What if you were talking to a Korean ghost?
Would the Ouija board move to like Korean?
Would you need to get a board with Korean characters on it?
And when you become a ghost,
you automatically become a master linguist.
Can you speak any language?
How do they not fall through floors?
They walk through walls, how do they not?
And you know, here's my biggest question actually.
I was thinking about this today.
Everyone has a cell phone camera on them now
and we pretty much get the same amount of ghost photos
that we've gotten over the past 20 years.
Now you'll see proof of ghosts
and this is orbs, it's pieces of dust.
We should, if ghosts were 100% real,
I'm not saying that all ghosts are fake,
but if ghosts were 100% real
and they were as numerous as we thought they were,
everyone should have a photo of them.
Also, sometimes there's ghost animals,
but how come when I'm walking to work,
I don't see a bunch of ghost squirrels?
How come the world isn't populated
by billions of life forms of ghosts,
like plant ghosts and slug ghosts and squirrel ghosts
and puppy ghosts and just there should be ghosts everywhere.
People who are like, I'm a medium and I'm sensitive to ghosts.
They should be like that dude in Better Call Saul
that can't leave their house.
They'd be like, every time I walk out of the house,
a million ghost J-birds like crash into me
'cause you would see every ghost possible all the time.
You can tell I'm stalling for time
because I really don't wanna talk about this last story
and that's not fair.
I do wanna talk about the last story,
but it's the dumbest conspiracy I've ever heard
and I just did an episode on mountains or tree stumps.
So that should tell you how I feel about this.
Now, it was so ridiculous to me
that on my YouTube video for TGA Grace Basing,
someone said, hey, you should take a look
at this new iceberg and I said,
no, that new iceberg's full of fake stuff.
There's something on there that says,
World War II was full of crisis actors.
So what a crisis actor is,
it's somebody who plays a part during a preparedness drill.
So if they're like, okay, so we're going to run a simulation
at an earthquake struck San Francisco,
we wanna see how our preparedness is.
They'll get people to be like, oh, my arm,
oh no, my kid's buried underneath that stuff.
Ah, the crisis actors has also used a lot of time
when they talk about Sandy Hook was fake
or the Boston Marathon bombing was fake.
They're like, oh, they just had crisis actors.
They just had people out there that pretended
that their limbs were blowing off.
That guy didn't have a leg when he showed up to the marathon.
And then he had a fake leg that fell off
and then he laid on the ground
and goes, ah, my bloody stump.
People actually believe that conspiracy theory.
That the victims of the Boston bombing
during the Boston Marathon,
they didn't have limbs when they showed up.
So anyways, that's what a brief overview of crisis actors.
Now, World War II, it was full of crisis actors.
I was like, that's ridiculous.
And then SN, a YouTube user known as SN said,
you know what, I hate to play devil's advocate,
but this is actually a legit conspiracy theory.
He goes, the YouTube video is taken down,
but click this link.
And that's when I discovered that people will believe
or not believe truly anything.
I thought that I had reached the levels
of what was possible in conspiracy theory
until I found this.
And what's interesting is this whole conspiracy theory
is hinged, we have, it's almost like fossilized remains.
It's almost like digging through the dirt
and finding a tusk, two ribs and a hoof
and having to try to build a mastodon.
'Cause this conspiracy theory,
it has no mainstream appeal, obviously.
What we have is a YouTube video from a YouTube channel.
The video has been deleted
and the YouTube channel has been deleted
for violating community guidelines.
We don't have the name of the person
who put up the YouTube channel.
All we have is a Reddit thread
where people who watched the video,
talked about the video and copied and pasted comments
from the video.
And we have a merchandise store,
but I'll get to that in a second.
So, World War II never happened.
A lot of the arguments you'll find with this one
is the same arguments you find
with a lot of conspiracy theories.
Footages faked, pictures can be photoshopped.
Eyewitness accounts can be faked as well.
This theory, and it's not, I wanna be clear,
it's not if World War II never happened.
This is what the world would be like,
like Harry Turdled of.
It didn't happen at all.
These are the branches of this conspiracy theory
from what I've gathered
from the limited amount of resources
I've been able to pull up on this.
One, some people believe that it happened,
in a sense, where we did send everyone sent over
their young men to fight in this war,
and they all were in on it.
There was no actual war taking place.
So they all came over to the war zones
and they were told, "You're gonna go back
"and tell people these great war stories.
"We want people to believe
"that this big, huge war took place.
"You guys will get medals.
"You guys will be heroes."
And it's to keep the status quo.
The Illuminati, Satanic, banking, merchant system.
We're just gonna pretend that we fought it,
and then you go home.
That's one part of the conspiracy.
Second part of the conspiracy, or the second option,
is that the war happened in a sense where
they shipped all of the young men from America
over to Europe, and then all of the young German men
and the Swedish men and stuff like that,
and then bloom up, killed them all on purpose.
And then called it a war.
So the war itself didn't happen.
It was the genocide of, and here we go,
young white men.
That was the point of the war.
So here's an actual comment that was on the YouTube page.
That was saved onto Reddit.
"The purpose of wars, at least since the American Revolution,
"and in earlier centuries," that doesn't make sense.
If it's since the American Revolution, but whatever.
"At least since the American Revolution,
"and in earlier centuries, was to kill off large numbers
"of young, healthy, and brave white males,
"which ostensibly prevented most of them
"from passing on their genes to the next generation."
You know, we fought in Japan, too.
Vietnam, Korea, Middle East, Native Americans.
America doesn't only fight white people.
We fought in Mexico.
So that one's not really washed,
and none of this washes, none of this washes,
but that's the theories that they're just like,
the purpose of the war was to just
kill a bunch of white people.
That's the reason why the war happened in the first place.
But then, we're also told,
those who spread the lie of World War II was real.
Please provide proof.
I mean, I get that the boy in the striped pajamas
and saving Private Ryan are not documentaries,
but there are documentaries,
thousands and thousands of hours of documentaries
and books and eyewitness accounts,
and bombs that didn't go off
that are still buried all over Europe.
That's the proof.
Do they just think cities vaporized on their own?
I mean, their argument is the cities didn't get vaporized.
Photos of Dresden were photoshopped.
They didn't happen.
Battle of Britain, it never happened.
Really, the World War II,
people who believe that World War II never happened
is no different than most conspiracy theories that say,
that photo is fake or I'm just asking questions,
which is a very common thing a conspiracy theorist will say.
When you start to push back,
you know, they'll say with whatever pet conspiracy theory
they have, flat earth or the moon landing was fake,
they'll say a couple of things and you'll push back
and they'll go, hey man, I'm just asking questions.
And this is the end result of that.
When you say, you know what,
I don't think planes crashed in the World Trade Center,
I think they were holograms
and I don't think we landed on the moon.
I think all the photos were fake.
What's really to say that World War II never happened
is not that big of a logical step.
If you already believe that those things
that we have documented with film were fake
and you're like, no, there was a sound stage,
then why couldn't you fake World War II?
Why couldn't all the newsreels be fake?
Can you go, well, it's the amount of people involved.
Maybe you had people shooting blanks at each other.
I'm old enough that in my lifetime,
I've met people who were,
and I'm sure a lot of my listeners too,
but I've met people who fought in World War II.
I knew a woman who went to my old church,
she was German and when the Soviets came in,
they had to dress the men, the German men as women
because they were just shooting any man in the street.
And I knew her, she went to my church
and she was probably like 60.
So did she make that story up?
Did she say that was she like, yes,
I get my crisis actor money still,
I'm still perpetuating the lie.
Just to let you know too,
US Revolution was faked.
Britain just set that up.
They're like, hey, let's pretend we're having a war.
Civil war was fake as well,
according to these guys, civil war didn't happen.
It's just a lie you've been told
by the history military complex.
Never happened.
What's interesting is I wonder if they think
Vietnam happened or the Gulf War.
Like at what point do these wars actually start taking place?
Do any of them take place?
The one thing I can give them,
the one thing I can give them
is when we look at the book 1984,
how all the wars are completely fictional.
And one day you're aligned with one country
and the next day you're aligned with a different country
and you have to change your whole history
and they just kind of launch bombs at each other
and every so often there's a small version of casualties.
But the war that they talk about
with the raging war machines,
they don't actually happen in the book 1984.
They could be inspired by that.
But the thing with 1984 was that the news media
was so controlled that you would see the fake photos
in the news of these troops like fighting each other
and we've never had that level of global control
over our media.
And I don't wanna hear that,
oh no, the Illuminati controls Beyonce and Katy Perry.
No, the level of control where you could actually
manipulate everybody's version of events at one time
and nobody disputes it is not even a claim
that's been made by the most diehard
Illuminati conspiracy theorists.
'Cause if that was true, if they had that level of control,
you wouldn't be able to write about it on the internet.
I wouldn't be able to read out that Illuminati email.
So that's again, I could see them being inspired by 1984
and thinking the war was entirely fake.
It was just sold to us for propaganda purposes
to make us feel like we're the best
and maybe in Germany they think they won the war.
I don't, oh my God, I don't know.
I wish I could talk to this guy
'cause he put up a bunch of YouTube videos,
the channel that got taken down
and the other videos they referenced
where the Civil War never happened,
the American Revolution never happened.
I looked all over for more information on this.
I couldn't find anything 'cause when you type in,
did World War II happen,
a lot of it is like alternate reality stuff,
like what if it didn't happen and so on and so forth.
I'll keep looking around.
I did find out though,
that the guy who had the YouTube channel
has a merch store that you can buy merchandise.
If the merch store is called You Got Hoaxed,
not like We Got Hoaxed that it's a fake conspiracy theory,
but like no, you believe the lies.
You can buy T-shirts, mugs, magnets, bumper stickers
and even a jigsaw puzzle.
Jigsaw puzzle, it's completely white.
All of the items are the same.
They just have text on them,
but you can buy a 30 piece jigsaw puzzle
and yes, I will buy this puzzle.
So 30 piece jigsaw puzzle in black lettering
against the white background,
the worst jigsaw puzzle image I can think of is just words.
This is what it says on the jigsaw puzzle.
No one died and no one got hurt.
Sandy hoax, Boston hoax, Aurora hoax,
Chris Dorner hoax, LAX hoax, Navy Yard hoax,
7-7 hoax, Kenya Mall hoax, 9-11 hoax, et cetera.
Period, full stop, end communication.
So this is the guy we're dealing with.
Everything's a hoax, everything's a lie.
Every shooting, every bombing, 'cause it's et cetera,
all of it, it's a lie.
Period, full stop, end communication.
There is no other debate to this.
These things are hoaxes.
And when you believe that, if you can go Sandy Hook was fake,
Aurora shooting was fake, 9-11 was fake, 7-7 was fake,
LAX shooting was fake, Navy Yard shooting was fake,
Chris Dorner, the guy who went around
and shot a bunch of cops, fake, Boston bombing, fake.
When you can just go fake, fake, fake, fake,
why not just say World War II was fake?
Because at a certain point you go,
you do have to ask, well, what do you believe in?
What horrible incidents do you think
that has happened in world history that you believe in?
If you already believe that everything's a hoax,
and all these tragedies are crisis actors,
and all evidence presented to you is fate,
why stop there, why not say World War II was a hoax?
And if you thought that was ridiculous,
on Monday, we're gonna talk about people
who believe nuclear bombs.
Nuclear bombs don't exist, they don't exist.
(laughs)
I just wanna talk about ghosts.
It's October, I don't mind doing the conspiracy stuff
but for October I just wanted to talk about ghosts,
and this stuff just falls in my lap.
Nuclear bombs don't.
(laughs)
I just wanna say I love doing this podcast, guys,
and I do have a lot of fun doing it.
Like these two stories, World War II doesn't happen,
and nuclear bombs don't exist.
It's one of those things that I just look at so logically,
and I'm like, do I really need to cover this?
Is this something that really needs to be covered?
But because we deal with these wacky conspiracy theories
that no one's heard of, I did wanna cover 'em.
So I hope you enjoyed the setup,
World War II did not happen.
If you ever hear anyone say that it happened,
pull out your jigsaw puzzle, just tap it slightly
and go hoax, and then on Monday, when I go in depth
of why many, many people don't believe
that nuclear bombs exist and why, you'll remember,
you're gonna have to pull out that jigsaw puzzle
if anyone says, hey dude, did you hear North Korea?
My nuke would be like, mm-mm, nuclear bombs don't exist.
(sighs)
I just wanted to talk about ghosts.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up on facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is gonna be @JasonOCarvener.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Hey, have a great one, have a great weekend, guys,
and I'll see you Monday.
(upbeat music)