Single ladies of the world, Shed a tear.
The world's most eligible bachelor ghost has gotten married.
And then we travel to Afghanistan to take a supernatural look at the current conflict
raging over there.
Is it possible that a bunch of witches on Reddit may be able to defeat the Taliban today on
Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garminer.
I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys had an excellent weekend.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're going to slide right into this.
First off, let's give a shout out to one of our legacy patreons coming into Dead Rabbit
Command right now.
Give it up for Young Ghidorah.
Everyone give a round of applause to Young Ghidorah walking into Dead Rabbit Command.
Long time supporter of the show.
Really really appreciated.
Young Ghidorah, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys cancel by the Patreon, I totally get it.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That really really helps out a lot.
Tell your friends, tell your family, tell your enemies.
Tell them "ooh I'll hate it so much.
If you listen to Dead Rabbit Radio that'll really get my goat."
Young Ghidorah, I'm going to go ahead and tashi the oars to the Dead Rabbit Robo.
We're going to take a nice leisurely sea journey.
Sea bound journey.
All the way out to a location I did not write down in my notes.
So we're just going to swirl around in a boat for a bit.
We're going to go through a magical whirlpool and we're there.
Because this is one of those stories that the location doesn't really matter because
we're talking about love.
Right?
Love doesn't have any geographical boundaries.
Love doesn't have an address.
So we're there.
We're at the address where this woman lives which I clearly could have written down what
country this story took place in.
But that's lame.
The reason why we're here, we're going to talk about this woman named Kathleen Roberts.
She's a woman who is just going about life.
Right?
Just like the rest of us just trying to figure out where we belong.
Our addresses are trying to figure out what country we live in.
But she real...
See some of us never get to figure out who we are.
It's tragic, right?
Some people just live their entire life going, "What could have been?
Who am I?
Where do I live?"
Kathleen Roberts knows who she is though.
She is the reincarnation of Marilyn Monroe.
And she...
You want proof?
Okay.
You skeptic?
There is a TikTok video.
There's a bunch of TikTok videos of this woman dancing to a Marilyn Monroe song.
Now I ask you.
I ask you, listener.
Could you dance to a Marilyn Monroe?
Is there a Marilyn Monroe song?
Is she known for her music?
I guess she was in musicals?
And I'm going to tell you this too.
I don't want you guys to click off right away.
You guys have to finish listening to this episode.
She has her own podcast.
Kathleen Roberts, aka Marilyn Monroe, has her own podcast.
Actually, you should click off mine.
Why would you want to listen to this big schlub talking a haunted closet about Marilyn
Monroe?
You can listen to Marilyn Monroe herself.
And Marilyn Monroe is currently married.
She's the reincarnation of Marilyn Monroe.
But she's married to a ghost.
There's just so many layers to this story.
This is just...
So Kathleen Roberts, aka Marilyn Monroe, is married to a ghost.
The probably the most famous ghost of all time.
You're like, "Jesus?"
I'm like, "No, not Jesus."
And technically he's not a ghost.
But Michael Jackson.
Okay, maybe the second most famous ghost.
Maybe the 10th most famous ghost.
I'm sure there's more famous ghosts out there.
But the most famous ghost of our lifetime would be Michael Jackson.
You're like, "You're shaking your head?"
He's like, "No, he's not."
Listen, man.
If you were reincarnation of Marilyn Monroe, that would be the best you could do.
That would be the best you could do.
Who's better than Michael Jackson?
So Marilyn Monroe is married to Michael Jackson.
And you want proof?
You want proof that any of this stuff is real?
Why got proof?
Are you skeptic?
Why even listening to this podcast if you're just gonna go, "What?"
No, this is just nonsense.
Jason's just reading off the ramblings of a mad woman.
There's video proof of this.
She gets...
So what happens is Michael Jackson possesses her.
So they got married because Michael Jackson put this story in.
We haven't even gotten to help us.
This is still just scratching the surface.
So Michael Jackson married this woman and he possesses her as well.
So sometimes she's Marilyn Monroe...
Well, she's always Marilyn Monroe because she's a reincarnation.
But sometimes she talks in Marilyn Monroe's voice and sometimes she dances like Marilyn
Monroe.
But sometimes Michael Jackson possesses her and she can sing.
There is a video clip of her and I really wish I could play it for you.
There's no sort of copyright laws and probably like anti-bullying laws and things like that.
But there is a clip of this woman.
She's singing...
Sorry, sorry.
There's a clip of Michael Jackson singing through this woman all of me by John Legend.
And here's the thing.
I have this weird hang up.
Don't do the whole song.
Like obviously you're John Legend and you're performing it.
Don't just do 30 seconds.
But if you want to show me what a good singer you are or if you want to show me that same
Michael Jackson as possessed your body, you don't have to go all the way to the bridge.
You don't have to do the fade out of the end.
Just give me a good couple bars.
30 seconds, I'm good.
She sings this whole song.
Maybe she didn't sing the whole song.
I couldn't listen anymore but I listened for about two or three minutes.
She sings all of me by John Legend.
I'm sorry.
Michael Jackson sings all of me by John Legend through her body.
That's proof guys.
I kind of feel bad that...
I'm a big Michael Jackson fan so I kind of feel bad that I'm shooting him down this much
because there's proof of this.
So they got married.
And who?
Okay so if Marilyn Monroe and Michael Jackson were getting married, who would officiate the
wedding?
This woman probably is suffering from something so I shouldn't be so giddy but when I was
reading the story I kept going this can't get any better and yet it did and yet it constantly
got better.
Who would officiate the wedding between Michael Jackson and Marilyn Monroe?
What's the most famous ghost you could see doing?
You're like Jesus.
I'm like no Jesus isn't a ghost for one.
And two, who's the most famous minister that would...
So now you guys got it.
Who's the famous minister who would...
You're like Jesus I have no idea where you're going with this.
Who's the most famous minister who would marry Michael Jackson and Marilyn Monroe?
As she was getting out of the bathtub one day, Kathleen Roberts was getting out of the
bathtub one day.
Michael Jackson showed up as a ghost.
They'd been dating for a while.
He's not a creepy stalker or anything.
Because Kathleen Roberts had to get out of the bathtub one day.
Michael Jackson showed up and Michael Jackson brought into this woman's bathroom Reverend
Martin Luther King Jr.
And he is the minister who officiated the wedding.
She goes listen Michael Jackson is normally just in possession of my body and like he's
like hanging out in there.
It's like that movie identity.
Spoiler alert for a 20 year old movie.
It's a brilliant film but it's like that movie identity where there's like multiple people
living inside of this woman.
So one of his favorite things to do.
Marilyn Monroe's been getting along swimmingly with Kathleen Roberts.
They're the same person.
They're not she's not possessed by Marilyn Monroe.
I don't know why someone would make such a bizarre claim.
That's not true.
But Michael Jackson is possessing her and she goes Michael Jackson loves to make me eat
cookies.
Sorry I eat a bunch of cookies now.
And he likes to so he's not always there.
Sometimes he's like floating around but sometimes he's in her two distinct times whenever she
eats cookies she's possessed by Michael Jackson.
And when she goes to the bathroom Michael Jackson likes to be inside of her while she's
using the restroom.
I said earlier I'm a big Michael Jackson fan and I know that he's had a lot of scandals
which I don't believe that he's guilty of.
I would not be a big Michael Jackson fan and be like oh yeah but no he's totally guilty
you know I think that was a lot of trumped up stuff and he went through multiple trials.
But anyways I almost did a whole episode on it once and I didn't.
So I'm not gonna do it now but anyways I think he's innocent.
I wouldn't be a big fan of his if I thought he was guilty but if he does if he forget
the old stuff because I don't think he's guilty of that.
If he is currently guilty of making a woman eat cookies and then making her poop and being
like yeah this is what I wanted.
This is what I came back from the dead for to eat cookies and then poop him out.
Bro you got some serious issues.
I mean the other allegations were rough and I did believe him for a time.
Like when they first I was not such a big Michael Jackson fan.
That first trial I was like oh no dude that sucks I can't believe that he did that but
then as time has gone on I don't believe it.
But that aside if you do like possessing women and making them poop I might have to start
burning my Michael Jackson albums again.
She also says that when he possesses her she can't touch herself because he'll be in her
body and be like oh Michael those cookies are so delicious she's rubbing her belly and
Michael doesn't like being touched by her.
So while she's trying to interact with Michael Jackson in her body this should be the clue
right.
If everything else wasn't a lead up to this woman might have some underlying issue she
says that if Michael Jackson is in her body and she touches herself she sees visions of
dead corpses.
She just sees rotting bodies in front of her.
Now you go that must mean that you need to go to a doctor.
You're having hallucinations not only are you having hallucinations you're not hallucinating
say like a smell you're not hallucinating a cartoon bird landing on your shoulder you're
hallucinating an unending sea of decaying human bodies you might want to go get checked
up.
What happens is that's Michael Jackson in her brain saying I don't want to be touched
I don't want to be touched by you so I'm going to show you the most horrific things a human
can see.
I'm going to show you corpses I'm going to show you rotting human flesh.
So little heavy handed there Michael Jackson and really the question you're asking the
question you're asking isn't why didn't Martin Luther King show up to my wedding no the question
is why her and she has a good answer for this she says it's disgusting the answer is disgusting
but it makes sense in her mind and in the minds of millions of other people the reason
why Michael this is when I knew the story was fake this is why I totally believed everything
else I was like whoa she is dancing like Marilyn Monroe but when she said this I go it's fake
she goes the reason why he's attracted to me was because of her quote childlike of course
you couldn't have a Michael Jackson story that bringing this up I'm not bringing it up
she is but quote there this is the reason why he's attracted to her her quote childlike
personality and small hands and feet unquote she's not a hobbit she's a normal sized human
she didn't have particularly small hands I've watched multiple tiktoks of her but yeah so
I did get a sense of the dimensions of her body so these articles are recently published
in the Daily Star which is a trash website it's not even a step above the national choir
it is the national inquirer I got the story though from the New York I normally don't
read the Daily Star as entertaining as it is because there's so much fake stuff in it
I've researched stuff and it turned out to be not true shocker of shocks the New York
Post which I read every day ran an article on this woman and they linked it back to the
Daily Star and she does to be fair Daily Star didn't make this up they're just reporting
this as if this was real and so I went through all of her tiktoks and I was watching her
I'm sorry Michael Jackson performed all of me by John Legend and she has her own podcast
if you guys are like to listen to that but she's actually come out because these New
York Posts article was fairly recent and she's come out since August 18th and she goes oh
no no no no no no no no those articles are old like that or that news is old the articles
are new but they're they're picking that up from old tiktoks and old podcasts me and
Michael Jackson have gotten a divorce they've actually been divorced for a year now she
said they got divorced we don't know where he's floating around he could be standing
right behind you right now and if he was at vc we're jealous Marilyn Monroe is now dating
what might be the best band name ever Marilyn Monroe is of course right the star just can't
end with her not being I'm gonna be single I'm gonna be single until the ghost of Genghis
Khan rides into town now she is currently dating an Astroly projected Johnny Depp if
someone doesn't have a band called Astroly projected Johnny Depp by the end of the week
I don't even know why I'm doing this so Kathleen Roberts aka Marilyn Monroe we wish you the
best whatever that may be I'm not gonna make any assumptions that she does have some sort
of mental illness I will say this though if you continue to have visions of dead corpses
then you might want to go see someone because then it shows that it wasn't Michael Jackson
doing it you're just hallucinating unending fields of the dead in the damned so that is
worth going to a doctor to have a checkup on young Ghidorah I'm gonna go ahead and toss
you the keys to the carbonicopter we are leaving behind wherever we were at people are like
please I want to know where this story took place because I'm afraid it might be in my
hometown I'm afraid I may know this woman young Ghidorah take us up up and away in
the carbonicopter we are headed on out to Afghanistan and as we're headed out there
I want to do really quick dead rabbit recommends this one's a bit unusual for dead rabbit recommends
I recommend a lot of movies pretty much all movies this one's a book it's a children's
book though it's basically for ages four to nine but I read it and I thoroughly enjoyed
it it's called Mr. Waffles this book is dope I'm not gonna go super in a detail to avoid
the plot but it's perfect it's the story of an alien invasion happening in the middle
of the afternoon and the only person there to stop it is a house cat or depending on
your point of view some alien explorers are just coming towards earth but they're tiny
and they come across the path of a malicious black cat there's a little bit of English
in it but the most of it is these aliens talking to ants and you kind of the kid can kind of
make of their own it's really interesting because when I first read in it I thought one of this
be hard for like a kid to like learn language but Sabine who who showed me the book she
goes no it actually it's for the kids imagination like what are they saying this time what are
they say and from the expressions on the aliens faces and what they're doing you can actually
make up your own dialogue it's really cool it's really really cool I recommend checking
it out if you guys I know a lot of you guys have kids it might be a great book to read
to them and to read with them because there's a lot of imagination has aliens and it's a
really cool adventure and if you got to get a gift for someone if you don't have kids but
you got nieces or nephews or friends that have kids or things like that or you just want
to buy copies of this book and throw them out into the neighborhood don't do do not do
that but Mr. Waffles that rather recommends Mr. Waffles it's a really unique book and
it's unlike an award-winning book it's it's kind of old I think it's like from 2013 but
very highly recommended overall not just me but I do recommend Mr. Waffles that'll be
in the show notes young Adore land this Carverner copter we're not going into Kabul it's a
Taliban controlled really the whole country right now is Taliban controlled but there
are uprisings there are freedom fighters see now Taliban's in control now they're the
government now they got to worry about streets and electrical grids and pollution and stuff
like that it's always easier to be the freedom fighter it really is you have no responsibility
other than don't die which is pretty big responsibility but you're not worried about
transportation you're not worried about are there potholes in the road when you're a
freedom fighter you're starting to see there is this resistance movement growing up in
cities on the outskirts or you know farther off from the capital in Afghanistan so we're
starting to see that but we're out here where Afghanistan we're sitting on a mountain we're
looking down and we're thinking man you know this country has just been in war for so long
so it's invaded it then they went through like a four or five year civil war and the
Taliban took control and then the United States invaded it and what could we possibly hope
for for this nation and that's when we hear a turn and there stands Michael Jackson Michael
Jackson's there he's like hey guys and he sits down and he realized that Jason didn't do
any Michael Jackson's so he's sitting there with all this mountain and we're looking
over Afghanistan and then we hear and we all turn and we look and there's this witch standing
there and we go whoa we know she's a witch not because she has the pointy hat and like
the bumpy nose and the broom she does have all that stuff she totally looks like a stereotypical
witch but we also just feel the energy coming off of her we kind of shirk back Michael Jackson
so scared he possesses you Michael Jackson so scared he's now in your body he don't
touch yourself and so this witch is standing there and she's looking over she goes foolish
models while you sit on this mountain debating your human affairs we have already taken action
and she snaps her fingers electricity shooting everywhere the Taliban run power grid is gone
awry of course she's just but electrocuted and a bunch of people but that's not what
she did she's looking and we see the landscape in front of us all these Taliban soldiers
they're running with their guns our guns they're running with us made guns and body armor but
they're running towards us and she just waves her hand and they just turn to butterflies
and she goes you see you want to solve things with violence us witches are different we
want to use magic I want to give a shout out to listener why do countries exist they've
they've recommended a bunch of stuff on this show longtime listener of the show thank you
very much they recommended this to me the other day really appreciate it super bizarre
and I gotta say this I'm really torn on it because a lot of this comes from a subreddit
called be which the Taliban which is I gotta be frank that you're seeing memes come off
of this already when you've tracked the memes down to the user and you look at their username
their trolls like there's a real popular meme going around right now saying do not face
Allah alone while astral projecting and it tells this story about this woman who's trying
to astraly project to weaken Allah so the Taliban will be weaker and she's floating around
and Allah shows up and just totally owns her right just totally defeats her and she's like
I had to come back to earth and she goes I man it was so he was like way stronger than
I thought he was gonna be like totally messed me up I didn't expect him to be that strong
throwing galaxies at me so I stopped meditating and had to light some candles and had it heal
my soul you'll see that pasta pop around a bit do not face Allah alone when astral projecting
and basically saying if we are able to weaken Allah then we can weaken the Taliban it's dumb
and it's fake it's fake that was actually posted by a troll and I know it was posted
by a troll because I was looking through their post history and someone called the mountains
how dare you try to take down God they responded quote I'll have you know I graduated top of
my class in the coven and I've been involved in numerous secret astral raids on al-Qaeda
and I have over 300 confirmed banishings to the shadow realm if you don't recognize that
right off the bat that is that is a pasta that's been going around that always gets modified
it was originally a special forces guy and so yeah when we're talking about this banish
the Taliban subreddit a lot of it is trolling stuff but it's hard to tell if it started
off that way because it started off on the original witchcraft subreddit there was a
user named Cogito ergo someone their initial post on the witchcraft subreddit was can we
cause a mass hexing of the Taliban forces you want to do something you want to help
people out so I can understand if you thought you were a witch thought you had magical powers
that can we do this and I honestly believe and it could be wrong on this but I honestly
believe that that initial post was sincere and that was it and then people started talking
about it but it was mostly people fighting with each other sure the Taliban is bad but
if you hex them hex is only going to come back on you even more other people say yeah
hexing is bad but the Taliban deserves and it breaks into this weird fight that goes
on and on and on and it seemed to be mostly people who actually believe in witchcraft
believe in magic so I do believe the initial thing was sincere but then Cogito ergo someone
starts their own subreddit called be witch the Taliban which immediately got taken over
by trolls and that's when we see this person come in and leave this thing about actually
projecting to fight Allah it's definitely meant to be inflammatory there's much stuff
and then we saw another subreddit pop up from that called be witch Taliban they left out
the the and they left out all the people who want to join them it seems to be dead at this
point and then in some bizarre I don't know if this was something set up to show how ridiculous
the whole thing was or there's now one called be witch the KKK and that has the same post
someone took the same post from be witch the Taliban and just changed the words so they
said oh I actually projected to fight God so I could weaken the KKK and blah blah blah
so I don't know if they're trying to make a point what the point may be but whatever
it is that one is trolley as well so the be witch the Taliban may have started out sincere
it was overtaken by trolls very shortly be witch the KKK is trolley to begin with so
this story here I'd say probably if you look at these forums I'd say you probably have
70 to 80% of these people are trolls trolls are larkers and they know they're larkers
and they're all trolling each other trolls like oh I can't believe that person actually
took me seriously and the person who quote unquote took them seriously was like oh my
god I can't believe they took that comment seriously and it's just like this back and
forth thing and everyone thinks they're fooling other people but the people they're fooling
also are fooling on each other and then there's probably a good 20% who actually believe this
stuff not saying that they believe in magic overall but they believe that this is a movement
and they're not getting the irony they're not clicking on the user names to see what else
they've posted that's usually the first thing I do when I come across the ghost story that's
too good to be true I click on their name and if they've posted four or five ghost stories
that are too good to be true it's a bad sign doesn't mean they're lying but it does make
it a little suspicious this is my issue with this story though I mean it could have easily
just been a story I covered in the beginning and said this crazy thing's happening on Reddit
these witches think they can fight the Taliban but it's mostly trolls let's move on to our
next story I think this is dangerous stuff I am always joking around with witches and
saying how lame they are and how their magic isn't real and stuff like that but at the
same time I'm gonna stand by that stuff but at the same time I do believe in magic I do
believe that magic exists and I've never really talked to you guys about stuff I used to do
in college regarding that and maybe maybe I never will there's some of my stories are
just so bizarre that you go that's just insane and I go you're right it is Michael Jackson
was hanging out with me in college it was so bizarre I saw so many corpses with that
man but I do believe that magic exists I don't believe it's as readily available as most
people think it is I don't think you can buy a couple books and go on Reddit and start
hexing people so their shoelaces fall off I think it's a combination of a learn skill
which really this goes down to anything it's always a combination between learn skill and
just natural ability but that's the individual that's the individual spellcaster what happens
when people do take this seriously you're seeing all this horrible stuff going on over
in Afghanistan you want to do something people start taking this seriously and it's not just
one or two people but this movement will grow the footage coming out of Afghanistan is
only going to get worse it's really only going to get worse over the months and the years
must you know a miracle happens but you see this movement grow and you have people forget
about the troll origin of it it actually gets outweighed by the earnest by the sincere and
these people who believe that they're magic users if you get enough of them together can
they accomplish something a single magic user single well trained practitioner of magic would
be better than a hundred students but what about ten thousand students what about five
hundred thousand students they're all really inept at it and they can barely do anything
but if they're all focused on the same goal could they enact change if they you have five
hundred thousand people meditating for an hour a day two hours a day whatever meditating
to hex the Taliban could it work and you go Jason maybe that would be a good thing though
wouldn't it their gun stop working their vehicles are breaking down good old American engineering
helicopters are falling out of the sky that would be great if they could do a mass hex
spell against the Taliban you would think so and I would think so too but I want to
end it off with the thoughts of a Reddit user named dolly throw away 99 and they warned about
this the last time you guys tried casting a mass hex against president Trump remember
that which is against Trump that went on for four years we got the coronavirus you got
rid of Trump you hexed them but your collective energy hexed all of us sure the Taliban maybe
hex they may fall out of power they may be pushed out of the land but every true magic
user knows you pay a price for every spell you cast will the world be ready when that
price tag comes due.
you
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]