A hero risks his life to save an innocent bystander.
What would you do if you were driving through the woods and you spotted a bizarre man walking
across the street?
And then we traveled to Columbia to take a look at the bizarre story of a series of
murders that took place there.
Is it possible that a man was trying to harvest the blood of young people?
Or was everyone simply wrong?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvenor, I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so let's go ahead and get started on this.
First off, let's give a shout out to one of our legacy patreons coming into Dead Rabbit
Command right now.
Everyone give them a salute and clap.
It's David Lazaridis, everyone give a round of applause to David, longtime Patreon supporter.
David, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it.
Just spread the word about the show.
Leave reviews about it.
Talk to your friends, talk to your family, talk about it online.
I want to see more of that.
That is also how you can help the show.
David, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the, let's see, I'm going to go ahead and
toss you a steam shovel, but let's hop in the Carpenter Caboose.
We're going to take a little train journey.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed out to Cole Pepper, Virginia.
Chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga
chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga
chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga ch
chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugga chugg
the dog is like me too all of a sudden Harvey jumps into the lake and starts paddling out into the water and Ralph's like well that's kind of weird I mean it is really hot out it's hot enough to make me pant Harvey jumps in the water and starts swimming and he sees something about 200 feet off the shore you see something kind of bobbing in the water you guys might have already read this story you guys already know the twist I don't know if it's a twist but I wanted to share it anyways it was pretty big news anyways Harvey is swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming out to the water and he's swimming
*