What fights on four legs in the morning, two legs in the afternoon, and three legs at night?
And then we take a look at the story of Martin Guerrero, a man who stole some grain and then ran out of town to avoid
prosecution. And then he came back.
Or did he? Today on Dead Reverie.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Reverie.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too.
That introduction sounded so lackluster. Or did he? It's a really interesting story though.
I thought it was really, really interesting. Otherwise, I want to cover it. We actually have a
lot of stuff to cover today. Firstly, October 31st, the River City Saloon here in Hood River.
My boy, my boy's band, Sundivers, having their album release party. I've talked about it a couple
times. I've talked about their band a couple times on the show. So if you are in the area,
October 31st, River City Saloon, I think it starts at 10 p.m. Sundiver official album release party.
After all this time, they got their album out and their music is great. I will be there and maybe
you'll see me. I'm sure you will. The question will be, will you know who I am in the audience?
You will, because it'll be the most awesome person in the audience.
So October 31st, River City Saloon. That's a little plug for you guys. Let's go ahead and get started
with the episode. So we're going to take a trip around America. America, the most fight-ness
country ever. We're just punching people all the time. A country does something we don't like. We
just walk up. We punch the country in the stomach. Take that, Germany. And it falls over. We're like,
USA. America beats people up. And unfortunately, sometimes we beat ourselves up. Not in a
emotional way when we step on the scale and we're like, "Oh man, I can't believe I ate all those
burritos." Sometimes we beat up fellow Americans. And it's a tragedy. St. Louis, Missouri. It's
December 2016, right? And you have this 10-year-old boy walking through a daycare center. He's probably
just picking up his little brother or something like that. Bored. I don't know. I don't know why
he was there. That's not the point of the story. It's not a mystery as to why a 10-year-old boy
is at a daycare center. But he hears something in another room. Smash. And he's like, "What is
going on in there?" He's like, "It sounds like someone's trying to clear their throat constantly.
I don't know what that sound effect is." 10-year-old opens up the door and sees two little preschoolers,
right? Boxing. Boxing. In the most adorable fashion ever. They're wearing giant, oversized,
incredible Hulk hands. If you've ever had those when you punch hard enough, it goes, "Hulk smash!"
or "Pshh!" Sounds like windows breaking. But these two preschoolers have both have a pair of
these incredible Hulk hands and they're throwing punches. Now, that's adorable. But there's two
daycare workers watching them and directing the fight. So it's not like these kids are just kind
of goofing off. There's two adults being like, "No, get them! Get them! Get them!" And the kid's like,
"Whip and sweat off his brow with his giant hand. Stoo-k-stoo! Boom, boom, boom!" Just punch,
punch in each other, right? And according to the complaint, according to the news articles,
there's video footage of this. There's surveillance footage of two adults. One of them is jumping
up and down because she's really excited. It's two young women. One of them is jumping up and
down because she's really excited about how the fight's turning out. And then the other set of
footage is from the 10-year-old boy. He pulled out his cell phone. So we have two different angles
on this. We see these two preschoolers just boxing with these gloves on. And the only person to
interrupt the fight, at some point in the video, another preschool kid walks up and starts separating
the... "Oh, come on guys, you've had enough. Yeah, yeah, both Hulk smash, Hulk smash. Come on guys,
just break it up. It's over." So it took another preschooler to come and break the fight up.
Now this footage ended up getting uploaded and reported to the police. I like how the article
I was reading made a fact to say that one of the boys... this fight took place on one of the boys'
birthday and he got a black eye. And that's sad, but that's a little... I mean, who really cares at
that point? First off, how do you get a black eye from a giant Hulk hand? I guess when you're a preschooler,
everything kind of bruises you up. But two, like, I don't really care about... I don't think that
kid's going to be like 18 years old. I'd be like, "Do you have any regrets?" And he's like, "Yeah,
we shouldn't get that black eye when I was four." Like, I don't understand why that sentence is even
in the... It doesn't make it any more or less tragic. What does make it tragic was these girls
were fired and arrested and then all charges were dropped. So they're suffering nothing. They're
not suffering any penalties for this. Prosecutors said there was lack of evidence, even though there
was two sources of the recording showing this. So that is our first fight. That's our first little
fight club. And really, I guess I kind of botched the intro on this. These are all fight clubs. These
are all fight club stories that have been initiated in America. And you're like, "That's a weird topic
for dead rapper, Eddie." I know, but I find it hilarious. So let's go ahead and we are leaving
behind the kids of the daycare center. They're like, "Oh, please, it's my birthday. Don't want to get
a present." You're like, "Yeah, here's an ice pack here. You're gonna have this." He's like, "Yay,
that's what I always wanted since this afternoon when I got a black eye." We're leaving... That was
in St. Louis, Missouri. I don't know if I said that. Anyways, we're leaving there. We're leaving the
place that I just mentioned. We're going to Hartford, Connecticut. And this one... What was...
What were we in the first one? Oh, we were... There's 10-Year-Old Boy was our narrator. And this
one, the narrator will be a intrepid high school journalist. And he's like walking through the
halls of the school all alone. He's like, "There must be a story around here somewhere. There better
be. Otherwise, I'm going to fail my journalism class." So as he's thinking about maybe just
making a story up, he hears us. And he's like, "That's weird. Is there like some
black and gospel church group in there practicing? And they're clapping and they're not singing?
I just heard the clapping part of their song. I'm going to go check it out."
So he looks in the door and what he sees is two dudes just slapping each other really,
really hard. That's the other guy getting slapped. It's not the same guy getting hit twice.
I'll do two different sound effects. And he sees substitute teacher Ryan Avery Fish
standing there watching this all go down. Now, that is what we legally know. There's a lot.
Everything else I'm going to say is going to be alleged, right? So allegedly, this is what happened.
Ryan Albert... No, not Ryan Albert. Albert Fish is a brutal cannibal serial killer. Ryan Avery Fish
was a substitute teacher. That part's not alleged. And there are these kids... It's also... Okay, so this
is... Okay, this is where it gets dicey because different versions. Anyways, I'm going to tell
Aversion and it's all alleged. So the kids wanted to have a slap fight and Ryan wanted to be a cool
teacher who was like friends with the kids. So he like mediated it or like moderated it or
refted it, I guess would be a better term. And they were slapping each other and he'd be like,
"Oh yeah, man. It's a good slap, bro. Good slap." And then one guy got slapped so hard he started
to throw up, which makes me think that guy is also one of the preschoolers from the first story.
Because you have to get slapped pretty hard to throw up. I don't even know that's possible.
I've walked out of violent car crashes and full-on fights, full-on getting punched in the head
multiple times and never throwing up. So unless this guy was like made of ego, I can't imagine
any human so frail surviving to high school that can get slapped and then vomit from it. But anyways,
the teacher said, "Take a break, man. Take a break." And then once the kid like stopped
vomiting in the corner, he's like, "Okay, go back in there." So they're slapping each other. So it
wasn't a full-on fight. It wasn't... The least the preschoolers were like fist to fist. Like,
yes, they had gloves on, but the gloves were incredible. Whole cans. And you know how strong
he is. These high schoolers were just slapping each other. There were, I think, six of them
between the ages of 14 and 16. So this gets videotaped as well. I tried finding the videotape,
because I wanted to see it. I couldn't find it, but I'm sure it's out there. And honestly,
I didn't try super hard. I mean, I just was looking for it. He ends up getting reported to
the principal at the school. And Ryan's response was, "Ah, boys will be boys. This is what people..."
Which is, yes, but when you're in a position of watching them, you can't really use that.
So the school fires him, but they never report any of this. And then eventually, the authorities did
find out about this. And then, like, the principal and stuff was sued as well.
This is one of the stories. This all happened back in 2017. And then it was all discovered in 2018.
And I kind of mentioned this yesterday. After a story, like, pops, you can almost never find
follow-up on it nowadays. So I don't know if this guy's doing jail. I don't know if he got, like,
a ticket. There's no follow-up. We just know that these people got fired and arrested.
Most importantly, did these kids, did that kid ever stop throwing up? Or is he to this very day
throwing up? You go to Hartford, Connecticut, and you're, like, at Target, and you're like,
"Hey, do you know where the soap is?" And the guy turns around. He's wearing, like, a Target uniform.
He's like, "Yeah, it's over." And then you realize he has, like, a red mark on his face. And you're,
like, "The legends are true. He's still throwing up." Let's go ahead and move on to our last
fight club here before I run out of time to talk about Martin Carrera again. Let's go to our last
fight club. There's not a lot of information on this, but I think it might be the best fight club
ever. Who are in Winston-Salem, North Carolina. It's 2019. And these three women, this is currently
ongoing trial, case Marilyn McKay, Tonakia, or Tonisha Tyson, and Tonisha Jordan, are being tried
for running a fight club. This one to be fair, fight club might be a bit of a stretch.
But for organizing fights, or for encouraging fights between people with dementia at an
assisted care living center, which before you go, Jason, Jason, really? Listen, listen, hear me out.
Here we go. So, a fight club at an assisted living home. The idea itself is kind of funny.
It would be better suited for a plot of movie. They're actually, though, facing criminal trials,
criminal charges for, like, assaulting an elderly person or disabled people, or both.
I think at a certain point, he becomes so elderly, they're just like, "Ah, that guy's disabled."
You're like, "What? No, look, I can lift all these whites." They're like, "Yeah, you're just disabled
now. Go lay down." And they're like, "But I'm super strong." So, I don't know. Anyways, the point is
fight clubs through all age groups. If I had to fight any of those age groups, I would probably be
the dementia boxer. Because I would just have to, like, part of boxing is out thinking your
opponent. And if your opponent forgets everything five seconds after it happens, you got it.
Like, being the little kid hit with the whole cans, that's cool, but that one dude got a black eye.
And then the slap fighting, that sounded kind of dumb, actually, because if you slap a dude,
he starts throwing up. I'd feel bad. But if I'm boxing some elderly person, I'm like, "Duck
and weave, duck." Think about it this way. Think about it this way. If you were in a movie where
you were boxing little kids, that is just, that's just like kindergarten cop three, right? They
actually should make that. They should make kindergarten cop three where they have to break up
a child fighting ring. The slap fighting and throwing up those kids are made of tissue paper,
and I would just tear through them. But think about a movie based on a dude who is in a old folks
home. He has dementia. The people he's fighting have dementia. Think about all of the training
montages you would be able to have in that movie. Because every scene would be like a guy getting
beat up and he's like, "I gotta learn a special move. I gotta learn a crane kick type move to beat
this guy." And then you do this whole musical montage where he learns to move. And then the
fight comes up. He totally forgets to move and gets beat up. He's like, "I gotta learn a move.
The whole movie would be musical montages." So there's that. You could have the love interest
be like the sexy nerd. You can't have a love interest in the other two versions because that's
gross. But in the dementia one, you can have like the sexy nurse be the love interest. And you're like
the old weathered boxer and you like meet the sexy nurse. And you're like, "Oh, I wonder if she'll
go out with me." And she's like, "Dude, we've been dating for six weeks. You're just training."
"What? I wonder if she likes me." She's like, "Dude, I just had your baby." He's like,
"Going at it." That would be a movie I would watch. That would be a movie I'd live. Boxing. I'd
have dementia. I'd be boxing people with dementia. And then the end of the movie, it turns out it
was all just the delusion. But then it turns into double twist ending. It wasn't just the delusion.
It all happened. You just forgot it happened and then remembered it as a delusion. But then you
forgot that delusions exist. And then it's just the last 20 minutes is just a white screen while the
audience contemplates what went on. And then the final second is a punch hitting you. And it turns
that it was all real. And you were just getting punched a lot during the last 20 minutes of the
movie to the point where you saw white and threw up. But let's go ahead and leave our fighting
days behind us. We are going now to France. Birthplace of the Franck. Birthplace of French rolls.
I don't think those existed anywhere. They just had rolls and they weren't as delicious.
Birthplace of French girls. Lots of great stuff comes from French. What's the other thing?
French kissing? So anyways, before that, everyone just rubbed their lips together. The years 1527
were in France. And we're going to meet a guy named Martin Guerrero. Now this guy wasn't getting
in boxing matches when he was a teenager. He might have been. But he was, this sucks, getting married.
He's 14 years old and he gets married. That is hellish. That's awful. I can't imagine being
married now. And I've had a lot of really cool experiences. I can't imagine being married when
I was 14 and not having none of that stuff. So anyways, this kid's married when he's 14 years
old. But it's kind of soft in the blow. He marries a rich chick. So there you go. I could be married
since I was 14 to somebody who was rich. I'll do that. But anyways, he's married some rich
chick named Bertrand. It's like, just when you think things are on the up, she has a bad name.
Martin marries Bertrand at the age of 14. They have a son in 1540s. Everything's going pretty
good. His dad's kind of well off. Her dad's very rich. They have a little baby. In the year 1548,
he gets accused of stealing grain from his dad. So yes, she is rich, but we're in like provincial
France. So rich means you have less cooties than your neighbors. Like yes, she had money, but he
still had to steal grain from people for whatever reason. So Martin is like, oh man, I really need
him. I really want some bread. I want to make some French rolls, but I don't have enough grain.
So he goes and he steals grain from his dad. Now, if I stole grain from my dad, my dad would be like,
where did I get all these grain from? And Jason, why'd you steal it? I think most people, if they
stole grain, they'd be like, yeah, I'm sorry, dude, I just really want to make bread. And the other
people would be like, I didn't even know I had grain to steal. But back then, that was a big,
big deal. Martin runs away. He's so petrified that his dad is mad that he leaves town for eight years.
Eight years over grain. Martin comes back to town and everyone's like, oh, where were you? And he's
like, when join the army, I did some stuff. And I didn't want to face my dad over the whole grain
incident. And people are like, that's fair. Your father was quite the lunatic. And he thought he
talked about you at his grave. He said how badly he wanted to bash your head. And he's like, oh,
dad, because at this point, father's passed away. And his father did leave him an inheritance. So,
you know, let bygones be bygones, let grain be grain. And he comes back, he gets his inheritance
from his father's estate. And he has a son with Bertrands. And they have a son and the daughter.
Now, his uncle also gets part of the father's inheritance because he was gone. So the dad was
like, I don't know if I'm going to give him all this stuff. Like I'm going to give some of it to
the uncle, because I don't know if I'll ever see Martin again. But anyways, Martin does come back
and the inheritance is split between Martin and the uncle. And Martin sues the uncle because he
wants all the inheritance. Now, during this time of disappearance, the uncle, his name was Uncle
Pierre, married Bertrands mom, who is now a widow. So basically, his uncle is now his father-in-law
as well. And the uncle is sitting there and now he's being sued by his nephew slash son-in-law.
And he's going, I don't think this is Martin. Like, something's off about this. And people are like,
well, it's Martin. He's like, listen, I don't think it's the real Martin Guerrero. I think it's
somebody else. I think it's an imposter. Now, people go, he did come back into town after a long
absence. But his wife recognized him, his daughter recognized him, his sisters, he has four sisters,
they're like Martin, they absolutely recognize them. People in town go, that's Martin. And even you,
Uncle Pierre, you recognize him. And he's like, yes, yes, I did recognize him when he came back
into town. But I don't think that's really Martin Guerrero. So he starts pushing for an
investigation into this guy. The townspeople are like, you just don't want to be sued. And he's
like, you're right, I don't want to be sued. But I don't think that's Martin. I don't think that's him.
Now, Uncle Pierre starts going on this investigation, right? And he ends up running into this soldier
who's like walking through town at some point. It's not like he was just like, I'm going to figure
out the truth. And at that point, a soldier walked by like, as he was doing legwork, he talked to
the soldier. And he goes, Hey, you're in the army, you know Martin Guerrero. And the soldier was like,
yeah, yeah, actually, I do know Martin Guerrero. He's from around here, right? Uncle Pierre is like,
yeah, yeah, he's from this town. Soldiers like, Oh, is he, how's he doing? How's his leg doing?
Okay. And Pierre is like, what? Because yeah, he got his leg chopped off. He doesn't have a leg.
No, he doesn't. He's missing a leg. Like that should be the first thing. Hey, Pierre, how are you
doing? What happened to your leg? That'd be the first thing you noticed. Uncle Pierre is like, no,
not this version of him at least. And the soldier goes, Listen, man, before you get like two
suspicious, I'm not entirely for sure that we're talking about the same dude. And I could be wrong
about Martin getting his leg cut off. Like it was a big army. There's a lot of stuff going on. But
from what I remember, Martin Guerrero had his leg chopped off during the war. And then soldier
goes about his business. Now, at this point, the uncle is super suspicious. He goes, that's 100%
not the right Martin. He gets his boys. The uncle gets a bunch of rounds up a bunch of dudes,
they get baseball bats, they break into Martin's house and begin beating him with bats, being like,
confess, you're not the real guy, or we're going to beat you to death. And he's like, I just like
sleeping. They're like, keep hitting them in the leg. They're like, do you feel that? He's like,
Yeah, it's bone and flesh. They're like, aha, they're hitting his leg to hear if it sounds like
wouldn't hitting on wood instead, his bones are just breaking. He's like, No, the wife runs in and
says, Hey, guys, knock it off. Like, why are you attacking my husband? It's not your husband. This
huge fight breaks out. But they stopped beating him with bats. So that's a plus 1559 people in the
village say Martin is not the real guy. He's accused of identity theft. And he also burned
down a barn or something like that. So he gets arrested for arson slash identity theft. The
wife goes to trial and says this 100% is my husband. All of this stuff is being stoked up by
my uncle who doesn't want to lose his part of the money. That's all this is. The charges get totally
dropped. The next year, the uncle and his wife Bertrand's mom both sit down Bertrand and said,
Listen, he is not your husband. He's not your husband at all. At this point, it had been four
years since he'd come back to town. They had a kid. And they're still saying this isn't your
husband. This is not your original husband. He is not your og husband. They go, you have to
leave him. And you have to make sure he gets convicted and not being your husband. So he
doesn't get my part of inheritance. And they lean on her so much. She finally says Bertrand finally
says, fine, I will testify in court that he is not my husband. And this will all be over with
because only she can charge him with this particular crime. Like the people charged him
with identity theft and arson. But that case was dismissed. Now there was a like a deception
type thing or adultery type crime that only the wife could accuse him of. So she does. And they
hold this massive trial and the town is basically split into you have people who go, that's Martin.
I grew up with him. I knew him. That's him. And then other people go, and I don't think so.
There was no definite proof that he wasn't. So it was kind of like this. No, I don't think that's
him. The other people are like, I'm 100% for sure. This is Martin. At one point in the
trial, like the judge or the lawyers talked to Bertrand and they asked her about an intimate
event that happened prior to 1548, prior to him leaving in the first place. And she tells this
story, whatever, we don't know exactly what it was. And then they asked Martin the same thing. And
he told the same story. So they go, it has to be the same guy. Like how could he have known this
event that happened before he left in the first place if it wasn't the same guy? They bring out
150 witnesses, people on both sides coming forward to either say it is the real Martin or I don't
think it is. His own four sisters again come up onto the stand and say, it's him. It's him. It's
him. And then Martin on the stand says, if he says to his wife, if you will swear right now that I'm
not your husband, I will happily go to the gallows and get my head chopped off. If you will swear
that you know for a fact I am not Martin, they can execute me right now. And she was dead silent
because she didn't know or she was being pressured by the uncle. But whatever the case is, the trial
ends. He's found guilty and sentenced to be beheaded. And he's like, great. That gambit didn't work
out. He appeals it though. And he takes it to basically the Supreme Court of France or a higher
court in France, right? So they're leaving behind this little provincial town and they go to this
beautiful, like French play, I don't know, it could have been a shack in the middle of the woods.
The Blair Witch could have been the presiding judge, I don't know. But I imagine they leave
behind this village and they go to like a place with actual like brick buildings and mortar and
stuff like that. So they're there now. And he appeals it and he wins. And not only does he
win the appeal, but then Bertrand and Pierre are arrested for perjury and false accusation.
And so now the tables have completely turned. And he argues, listen, my wife is being manipulated
for greed. I don't think she was actually trying to say anything bad about me. I think she was
being manipulated by her stepfather, my uncle. I don't think she had anything to do with it.
But the court is like, listen, they sat here, they told us these stories, they almost got you
executed. We now have to have a trial for perjury for them. While all this is going on, this new
trial is being set up. A man walks into town. Wooden leg hitting the pavement.
Walks up to a crowd, I'm assuming a group of people. And he's like, hey, excuse me, excuse me,
people. I heard there's a trial being held here for my wife and my uncle and like someone saying
they're me, but I'm not, I'm me. I'm Martin Guerrero. And I was just kind of hanging out in
the countryside doing my own thing. But what's this about? And basically the entire crowd turns
around at once. All of his sisters, the uncle, Bertrand, his wife, everyone who sees him immediately
goes, now that's Martin. That is Martin Guerrero. 100%. That's what happened to your leg. And he's
like, oh yeah, I was wondering, you're going to ask me about that? Got chopped off, it got shot,
or stabbed or something, and they had to operate and they cut the leg up. Now at this point, you have
the new, the Martin Guerrero that we've been following this whole story, tried to like sneak
a leak. Like he's dressing up, he's on top of a kid in a trench coat trying to sneak out of the
crowd. He gets arrested. He was the imposter the entire time. And so they charge him with adultery?
And fraud. They build the gallows outside of Martin and Bertrand's house back in the little village
and they hang them. Now I get justice, but I don't want justice in my front yard.
Martin goes off, he did run away because he was embarrassed about stealing the grain. He joined
the military, got shot, leg got amputated. He ends up joining a monastery and they go, we don't
really know why he went to a monastery, but he went to a monastery for a, for about eight, ten years.
And then he was coming back to the region anyways and he started hearing about this trial in this
other town. He was headed back to his hometown. He heard about this trial in this big city that
actually had buildings and stuff. He walked over there, which it's a good thing he did because
Bertrand and the uncle were about to be charged with all sorts of stuff. And this guy shows up,
bangs your wife while you're in, while you're in the military, you're in monastery, you're missing
a leg. Some guy shows up, bangs your wife, all that stuff. I get it, you want justice. I don't
want it in my front yard. I don't want to be like, ah, it's time to have some lemonade. Oh wait,
forgot the rotting corpse in my front yard. I'm going to go hang out in the back. And it took him
a long time to forgive his wife because he said she should have known better. She should have known
better. Who was this guy? We do know. His name was Arne de Till. He was a scoundrel. They kept referring
him to us as a scoundrel afterward. Well, I guess being another dude's wife and insisting you're
him would make you a scoundrel. Anyways, he's a scoundrel from another nearby town. He was in
the military. He learned about Martin from a couple of friends and he learned enough details
about him that he figured I can pull this off. I can sneak into his town. It's been eight years.
I can chalk up a lot of stuff to just eight years passing. Now there had to have been a passing
resemblance. I don't think he was like four feet taller than the dude. But I mean, if he had a
mustache, people are like, you didn't have a mustache when you left. He's like, I know,
but I can grow those. That's something I can do. That's something I can do. So anyways,
he does get found guilty for this. And look at it from his point of view. At a certain point,
he had to really start to believe that he was Martin Guerrero. Obviously, he wasn't going crazy.
He's like, I am myself. But he had to start to believe this is actually going to work.
And he woke up every morning playing with his newborn son, talking to his wife.
And as he's sitting out on his porch drinking his lemonade, he's just looking at this field
that he owns. And he's like, everything, my scam is going perfect. This everything is going exactly
the way I want it. But what he doesn't realize is just a few years, just a few feet from where he's
sitting, they're going to build a gallows outside of that house. And every morning that he woke up
and looked out at his property, his ill gotten property, the stuff he came to possess because
of a lie. Pretty soon, that would be the last thing he would see as that trap door gave way
and the rope snapped his neck. Arna DeTill would look over the land of Martin Guerrero
and wish one more time that he truly was the man he was pretending to be.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabberadio. Twitter is @deadrabberadio. Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you
listened to it today. Have a great one guys!