A man is sued for slander.
His crime?
Watching a once in a lifetime paranormal event and telling the world about it.
And then we travel to the Fresno Valley in California to take a look at a bizarre cryptid
that's been described as half wolf, half ape, and is it possible that by studying this
monster we can finally figure out why we can never prove cryptids exist?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too, I hope you guys have some cool plans for the
weekend.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First I'll take a look at this awesome fan art that I got from Chime Chilly.
Chime Chilly, longtime listener of the show, longtime supporter of the show.
Drew this, it is very ICP reminiscent, it reminds me of one of the jester boxes or joker boxes
or whatever from them.
I do not know if Chime Chilly is a juggalo, but I really do love this artwork, it's quite
trippy, very very enjoyable.
Thanks for sending it over Chime.
And then walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now, let's give it up to one of our
thanksgiving contributors.
Give a big round of applause to Turtle Bandit.
Wooo!
Walking in super slow.
Come on in Turtle Bandit, you can make it.
Turtle, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Tell your friends, tell your family, tell everyone about it.
That also helps the show grow and I really really appreciate it.
So as we're framing up this picture, so crazy looking, I'm looking at it on my desktop right
now, those eyes are trippy.
As we're putting that up on the wall, Turtle Bandit, I'm gonna toss you the keys to the
Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are flying all the way out to Wentworth, England.
The year is 1687.
And there's a man known as Captain Barnaby.
He is just coming home from vacation.
And he gets back to Wentworth, England and his wife is waiting for him and she goes,
"Oh Captain!"
She calls him Captain too, she works on his boat.
"Oh my loving husband, what have you been doing this whole time?
You didn't tell me you were going on vacation.
You left me here alone?"
No, they start meeting with each other.
Now he had been gone for a couple months.
This was in 1687.
So when you go on vacation, you really go on vacation, he had left behind Wentworth,
England and was vacaying with a couple of his buddies on an island known as Strombole
over near Sicily.
And they're catching up on news, right?
He's just talking about all the great stuff he did on his vacation and she's like, "Well,
actually he had to do chores and stuff."
And she tells him, "Hey listen, you know our neighbor, Mr. Booty, while you were gone,
he went for a cab..."
While you were gone all these months, Mr. Booty died.
And Captain Barnaby sits and looks at his wife and says, "I know.
I knew he died before you told me."
This is a really bizarre story.
What it is, it's where we have a paranormal event actually have real world legal consequences
and I love these kinds of stories.
We'll get to the meat of the matter right now.
What happened was on May 15th, 1687 on the island of Strombole, which is a volcanic island
near Sicily, this is a vacation spot.
A bunch of people are chilling here, boats are always dropping off people, picking up
people and part of this vacation crew during this time was a couple captains, Captain Barnaby,
who's the star of our story, Captain Bristow, Captain Brewer and then a friend of theirs,
he's just a merchant, he can't boss anyone around, Mr. Vaughn, I guess he can boss his
employees around.
And they're all on this island, they're hunting rabbits, there are other people having fun
on this island, there's a bunch of furries trying to save the rabbits, they're like,
"No, no, don't you that one, I'm in love with it."
All this stuff is going on.
But on May 15th, 1687 at 3.44pm, a bizarre event happens that at least 30 witnesses saw.
And we know that because this is a court case, very, very interesting, that's why we have
exact date, exact time.
As a bunch of people are getting ready to disembark from their boats, the three captains and Mr.
Ball are leaving the island.
And they have a bunch of people gathered at this pier.
Someone points out, "Look, look at that, look at that!"
And everyone turns and they see two dudes running, it is said that they ran faster than normal
human could run, they obviously could tell something supernatural was happening, it
wasn't just a friendly little jog, these two guys are running around the island.
One is being pursued, again, you can obviously look at the first guy and he has a panicked
look on his face, he's terrified.
And before anyone can do anything, I smell like they could catch up to these guys either.
Captain Barnaby is looking at this along with 29 other people and he goes, "What, what,
that guy in the front, I know him, I know that dude who's being chased.
That's my neighbor, that's my neighbor back in England, Mr. Booty.
What's he doing, how did he learn how to run so fast, why is he on this island, what in
the world is going on?"
But before any of these questions can be answered, in front of all these witnesses, a
portal to hell appears on the island.
Mr. Booty who is being pursued by what they can only assume is the devil at this point,
Mr. Booty runs into the portal, he's chased into hell by this devil, but he looks like
a normal guy, they don't describe him, I don't know if he's wearing like trousers and a little
bowler hat, they didn't say he was wearing like red pajamas with a trident, they just
assumed this guy's the devil because he just jumps into hell as well.
The portal closes and everyone's kind of dumbstruck.
Captain Barnaby turns around and addresses the crowd and says, "Hey, that was really
weird, I didn't just hallucinate that, my neighbor, Mr. Booty, just ran into hell and
that must have been the devil chasing him."
People are like, "Oh, I didn't make the connection, that was the devil."
Everyone should make a note of this in your journal.
If you have a diary, if you're going to write in your Dear Diary book tonight, make a note
of this.
Note the date, because I think we saw something that's a once in a lifetime event, hopefully,
you don't want to see other people get chased into hell.
So they do.
Back then, people who worked on boats were taking journals, I don't know why, I guess
if you get lost, you're like, "Let's go back a couple pages, pass the slumber party, and
the list of our crushes, and then that's the directions we should have went on.
We should have turned left at that floating turtle."
But they do, they all write this down.
Now this is taking place on May 15th, 1687.
This is Captain Barnaby's vacation, he doesn't get home until October.
Because this is 1687, boats are super slow.
Captain Barnaby returns to his home in Wentworth, England and his wife's waiting there.
She didn't get a vacation.
And they're talking and she goes, "Hey, I wanted to tell you something too, a bunch
of stuff happened when you were gone, but it was old timey Victorian stuff, super boring.
However, Mr. Booty died while you were gone."
Captain Barnaby goes, "Oh yeah, I knew that.
I knew that."
And wife's like, "How could you possibly know that he died?"
You know, again, there's no wifi, there's not even phones.
He goes, "Well, this might sound a little weird, but luckily 29 other people witnessed
this.
When we were on that volcanic island, Stromboli, we saw Mr. Booty get chased into hell by the
devil himself."
So she starts going around town being like, "Hey, your husband might have a lot of money,
but my husband saw into hell."
And they're like, "What?
That's a horrible thing to brag about."
And she begins telling everyone in town that my husband and a bunch of other people saw
Mr. Booty run into hell.
And really the key isn't that my husband has some sort of infernal site, it's that Mr.
Booty was a bad person.
You see, the Booties and the Barnabies weren't the best of neighbors.
They didn't really like each other, right?
Mrs. Barnaby goes around town and starts telling everyone, "Mr. Booty's in hell.
My husband saw it.
This proof.
Mr. Booty was a bad neighbor.
He actually got chased into hell by the devil himself."
That's how bad he was.
He didn't even send out some demon after him.
Well, of course, this gets back to Mrs. Booty and she doesn't like this, right?
She doesn't like the fact that people are saying her husband went into, not only went
into hell, but there's proof, right?
It's not like you go like you were a bad neighbor, they probably went to hell.
They're saying, "I physically saw him travel through a portal into eternal damnation."
It's true, he went into hell.
So Mrs. Booty sues Captain Barnaby for slander.
This actually went to court.
We actually have a little outline of the court proceeding.
And this is so interesting.
She's suing for slander because her argument is they're saying my husband went to hell.
That's slander against his good name, my good name.
The great name of Booty shall not be besmirched.
We actually have a record of the judge's ruling in this case.
The judge looked at all the evidence, which included all of these journals, which included
witnesses coming to the court and saying, "Yeah, I know it sounds super weird, but on this
date at this time, a portal to hell opened up and Mr. Booty ran into it chased by the
devil himself."
The official ruling was, "It's not slander because it's true."
The judge ruled in favor of Captain Barnaby, and this is what he said regarding this quote,
"Lord have mercy upon me and grant I may never see what you have seen.
One, two, or three may be mistaken, but thirty never can be mistaken."
So it was all of the eyewitnesses that made him go, "This must be true.
This story must have actually happened because why would thirty people?
Sure, you have four people who are friends, right?
The four of them said, "Oh, I saw Mr. Booty running to hell."
They probably would have lost.
They probably would have seemed like a slanderous statement, but you had people working on the
boats, you had people on vacation, you don't know any of these people involved.
They're also seeing a fiery portal appear and this dude run into it.
It's interesting because we know now about mass hallucinations, we know now about mass
hysteria.
I don't think that you could make that argument nowadays because thirty people can be mistaken.
You can have a mass UFO sighting and it's really just a cloud or one of those weird
things, that optical illusion where it looks like a city is floating in the sky and it
has to do with a bunch of science stuff.
I don't remember exactly how it works, but there can be mass hallucinations, we understand
that.
But it's really, really interesting when the world of the paranormal does collide with
the legal world, a world that is based on keeping records and being impartial, well
as impartial as it can be.
Because the guys like Lord have mercy, obviously the judge also believes in the religious precepts
of hell and there's a heaven and a god and stuff like that.
But I think that's a fair ruling.
I mean, if there's thirty witnesses and twenty six of them are not connected to the guys
who might just want to say bad things about this guy, is it slander?
No, they're saying we actually saw this.
We actually saw a guy get chased into hell, which opens up a whole other can.
I mean we focus so much on the legal part of this, it's easy to forget that a portal
to hell opened up on earth and the devil chased a man into it.
What did Mr. Booty do that was so wrong that the devil's like "Ugh, okay, what's on my
schedule for today?"
Reign and eternal torment, try to corrupt the souls of man, oh I have a 344 appointment
with a Mr. Booty, I gotta get up there and take care of that one myself.
Who knows, like you have the legal proceeding side of it and then you just have the weird
paranormal event.
And Matt, I mean I gotta say, like Mr. Booty has to be a little proud, right?
That he got the devil off of his throne to chase him in there.
But I think that he's probably being tortured and hell, I don't think he's like "Oh, I'm
a superstar down here, it's bad."
But yeah, what an interesting story and to lose that court case as well.
So then, she basically, so then I mean it was proven in the court of law, her husband
ran into hell.
She tried to get the rumors dismissed, all she did was get them written into English
law and then hundreds of years later we could talk about it and still laugh at the last
name of Booty.
Turtle Bandit, let's go ahead and talk to the keys of the carbonic hopter, we're gonna
leave behind this courtroom in England with their powdered wigs and their grieving widows.
We are headed all the way out to Fresno Valley, California.
We're in Fresno Valley, California and we're camping one night.
We're cooking hot dogs over the fire, watching shooting stars travel across the sky.
Oh, it's time to turn in I say, as you realize they only brought one tent and one sleeping
bag and as we are cuddled up in the sleeping bag, we hear outside the tent, "Oooooh, heeheeheeheehee."
Like what, that's weird.
"Oooooh, heeheeheeheehee."
And I go, "Hmm, hold me closer as I tell you this story."
That sounds, the first part sounds like a traditional wolf sound.
"Ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
That's exactly what you think it is, well maybe not, maybe you think it's an ape body
with a wolf head, but you'd be wrong, you'd be wrong.
It is the opposite, it's a wolf body with an ape head.
And apparently these creatures run all around the Fresno Valley area.
And you go, "Jason, I've lived in Fresno Valley my entire life, I've never seen a wolf
head."
First off, why are you listening to my show?
You denier, you science denier.
Secondly, I've never heard of these guys either.
Now I don't live in the Fresno Valley, but I've never heard of these guys either, so
I won't fault you, I won't make you stop listening to my show if you've never heard
them and that's one thing I love about the show, is finding out about all these new
cryptids.
I found out about this one from Dead Robber Radio's favorite super soldier, Kevin Whiskey.
We talked about him on Monday's episode, where we were covering a wolf, a dog, what
was it?
It was a dog in Watts California that had the face of a woman and it could talk and
it had a pimp.
Great story.
If you missed Monday's episode, check it out, I'll put it in the show notes.
But there was another version of the lady-faced dog of Watts California that Kevin Whiskey
said that it didn't have the face of a woman, it had the face of an ape.
And he goes, "It's possibly that it was a wolf ape from Fresno Valley."
And I go, "What in the world is that?
You just can't go, 'Well maybe it's this, I don't know what this is.'"
I looked it up, "This is a cryptid that's been cited a lot in the area.
This world is so fascinating and so weird and wonderful and we're never gonna run out
of stories."
Like, that's another thing I love about this show.
It's this six foot long wolf with the face of an ape.
Sometimes instead of having little wolf paws, it has human hands and feet.
You were just making stuff up.
Wait, what is this?
How does it have human hands and feet?
If it's a monkey face and a wolf body.
Science, what are you, science denier?
Why are you listening to my show?
Go deny science somewhere else.
Sometimes it has a baboon's face rather than just an ape.
See, at that point you're really just squabbling over details.
If this cryptid is chasing me and I'm like, "Oh no, it's a wolf ape."
And someone's like, "Actually that's a baboon wolf."
I'm pushing you towards the beast.
That's just really trying to get into the weeds of this thing.
And this creature is incredibly vicious.
We've come across a lot of cryptids that kind of leave you alone.
Me bigfoot just want to enjoy nature.
Pfft, lame.
This one wants to eat you.
And that's why we're in the sleeping bag together.
Hold me closer as I'm rubbing my scent on you.
I'll chase you first.
Now you smell like two delicious humans.
This wolf ape, as it's moving through the wilderness of Fresno Valley, they say a lot
of times it makes coughing sounds.
Which is gross, right?
I'd much rather it have a fearsome howl.
Truth be told, Jason, you mean that howl and that monkey noise wasn't even real?
Well, no, that wasn't a little bit of artistic license.
But if I started the story off with some gross creature coughing in the distance, you would
have denied the science and I would have had to kick you out of the show even earlier.
So it makes, I'm allowed to lie.
Basically, I'm allowed to lie.
This wolf makes this disgusting coughing sound and it's always foaming at the mouth.
So there is no furry that wants to bang this thing, right?
It's super gross.
It's constantly hacking up a lung.
It's foaming at the mouth.
And some witnesses have specified it.
They go, it's not just coughing.
You guys say it's coughing.
That's not what it sounds like.
They described it.
Apparently multiple people have described it.
This is disgusting, dude.
Multiple people has described it as the sound of a pig squealing.
I'm not even going to try to imitate these sounds because it's so nauseating sounding.
A pig squealing and at the same time, someone throwing up.
Now I'm going to do the sound.
That's not a pig.
What's a pig?
Well, I know it's a squealing pig.
Squill, squeal, squeal.
And then we have to layer this on.
We're going to put it in surround sound.
Squill, squeal, squeal.
Okay, that was...
Anyways, I will continue.
I'm not saying I know everything about cryptids, right?
I keep saying I've never heard of this.
I've never heard of them.
I'm just shocked at the stuff I haven't heard because I've researched this for so long and
I love learning new stuff.
I love finding out about stuff I didn't know.
Apparently there's a ton of sightings of these things, including a celebrity sighting.
Ansel Adams, world famous for your life that your celebrity you imagined, Brad Pitt, was
writing one of these into a movie set.
Ansel Adams, world famous photographer.
If you've ever walked into a dentist's office, you've seen one of his photos.
Ansel Adams was taking some pictures in Yosemite.
He's like, "Oh, another giant rock.
Ansel looked great on someone's office wall.
Click."
He was taking pictures in Yosemite and a pack of wolf apes laid siege to his tent.
Oh no, and he's like probably swinging his camera at them.
Get back, get back you monstrosities.
They're foaming at their mouth coming towards him.
He actually hid in his tent and they left.
Wait a second, did she say these things are super fierce?
They're laying siege to his campsite and all he does is he goes zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt
zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt zzzt z
Zip
Cryptids Wolf apes Never seen before
Man who's known for doing one thing in his life.
Maybe he's a loving father and husband, I don't know.
But Ansel Adams is known for one thing.
Taking pictures.
I think he would have at least stuck the camera out of the tent to get a blurry shot of a
tail or something.
You're not, at the very least, right?
Maybe he'd get a dynamic group shot of all four of them howling at the moon.
I don't think this story is true just because of that.
UFO sighting, someone looks up and goes, "Whoa, look it, there's UFO."
UFO sighting and Steven Spielberg is there.
I'm pretty sure he's going to get it on camera, right?
I'm pretty sure he's going to have the wherewithal to be like, "I've made a bunch of movies
about this, maybe I should record proof."
So the fact that Ansel Adams was there and didn't take a picture, I find, you're like
"Jason, that's the part you find unbelievable about that, that a guy didn't take a photo?"
Then, okay, so yeah, yeah, yeah, maybe that part didn't happen, right?
Because it does sound a little dubious.
Maybe that didn't happen.
What about this undated, unsourced story?
This is cool though.
Apparently in Fresno Valley, there was a single room schoolhouse there.
And so somewhere in this entire place, there was a single room schoolhouse and a wolf ape
walked into school and was like going, "Ahh, doing all that noises.
I don't want to do it again because it hurts my voice."
And the kids actually had to build a barrier of desks to keep the wolf ape from eating
them.
And the teacher valiantly hid in the closet while all the kids were actually trying to
keep away from this thing.
And the wolf ape was so vicious that they had to build, the kids had to build like a,
you're like, "Jason, these stories are clearly made up.
Why are you even talking about this?"
These kids had to build a staircase out of their desks and then they climbed up in the
rafters of this old timey schoolhouse and the wolf ape just kind of walked around on
the ground for a little bit.
And it was a school for photography.
These students were all learning how to use a camera.
The wolf ape leaves.
And
the
kids
were
just
going
to
do
this.
It's clearly fake.
That's why it's not more popular.
None of this stuff makes any sense.
It's funny because when we look at encounters of Bigfoot, right, a lot of times like the
early ones, as we saw someone in the woods, we smelled something in the woods, we sensed
something in the woods, the Bigfoot mythos was very, very kind of on the back burner.
It was just a bunch of outdoorsy weirdos who believed in it.
I'm talking about modern Bigfoot, right?
Until the Patterson Gimlin tape came out and then you could show someone Bigfoot moving
around.
Now whether or not that video is fake, you could still now put an image to Bigfoot.
The fact is that that image is so iconic.
If you just show an outline of that, you go with this Bigfoot, right?
That walk and the Bigfeet.
The Wolfape, I mean other than that really, there would be about as much evidence showing
that Bigfoot exists to a Wolfape existing.
Every piece of hair they send off to the lab turns out to be something else.
And sure they take plaster cast of Bigfeet in the woods and that could be Bigfoot's
feet.
But this guy either has human feet, right?
So you would just see regular human feet in the mud or Wolfpaw feet.
He's not walking around rubbing his face in the mud and you could go, "This is clearly
the face of a baboon and we're in California.
How else could this be here other than the Wolfape?"
But what I found really interesting about this story, and let's wrap it up like this,
is that here we have a possible clue as to why we never do get real concrete proof of
cryptids.
What if they protect their own?
Now we've always had this thing, like Bigfoot experts will always say that the reason why
we don't find dead Bigfoot is because they bury their dead.
Unless we want to dig up the entire Pacific Northwest, we'll never find a dead Bigfoot.
They bury their dead.
What if that is something universal to cryptids in a sense?
That when you kill a cryptid, you get killed.
They come after you.
They take you down.
Now this guy sold it to the Freak Show so technically there might be some...
Look up from the 1950s to today if any Freak Show owners have ever been badly mutilated.
But think about it, let's say that you do get concrete evidence that a cryptid exists
before you can expo...
Because that's what we're all waiting for, right?
We already believe in a lot of these things, but wouldn't it be nice to know that they
exist?
To me, actually, believing is enough.
To me, for me to believe in this Bigfoot phenomenon or this Wolfape phenomenon, for
me to believe that's enough.
I don't really have to prove it to anyone else.
But it would be a nice little cherry on top, right?
It would be a nice little fur-covered cherry on top.
If you could prove Bigfoot existed, but again, I just like the stories.
I believe in these things.
It doesn't matter if other people don't believe in them.
But what if you find hair and it's actually deer hair or you find a footprint and it's
just a human footprint?
Shaquille O'Neal was walking through the woods that day.
Nothing happens.
But if you find actual Bigfoot hair, if you shoot and kill a Wolfape, and now you have
proof that these things exist, if there's not some sort of...
Reckoning coming.
Because I believe if cryptids exist, they do not exist in the natural world that we
think of.
But the Wolfape has a birth life and death cycle like a normal creature would on Earth.
I don't believe that they're raring their young and they're teaching them how to walk.
I think cryptids by their very nature, and this includes Bigfoot, has a supernatural
element to it.
I don't believe if Bigfoot exists, I do not believe he is a biological creature through
and through like a gorilla or like an orangutan or something like that.
There's just zero evidence of that.
I will believe that Bigfoot exists, yes.
But the idea of him just being a real life creature that we've never stumbled across,
there's just no evidence for that.
Interdimensional?
Sure.
Alien, flying UFOs, we've done episodes on all of this stuff.
Humans turning into Bigfoot, we've done episodes on that too.
I believe in all that stuff, there's more evidence for that type of stuff because the
lack of evidence of Bigfoot being a biological creature that we've just never discovered
in the Pacific Northwest for the past 400 years, there's just nothing, there's nothing
that we've been able to prove.
Like you know what I mean?
The lack of evidence is so outstanding in that.
But if Bigfoot's a supernatural creature that takes a biological form, yes.
And if it's a supernatural creature that takes a biological form, can't it also commit supernatural
acts?
The wolf ape being in the same vein, this wild cryptid is not a biological creature,
but is a creature that has one foot in the real world and one foot in the supernatural
world.
So when you shoot one and display it in your church and then sell it, there is a supernatural
reckoning for that.
You're murdered, you're brutally murdered.
Now whether or not a bunch of wolf apes actually descended upon this dude's house, Ansel Adams
leading the charge, he's like "I was one of them all along, my photos were just to make
money to feed my wolf ape family."
Or it was a demonic force that ripped him apart?
I don't know.
I'm not a forensic investigator, I'm just the guy who tells you science stuff.
That could be why we never get proof of these things.
Because the people who find the proof die.
Or disappear.
Right?
Imagine all of these missing 411 cases, someone walking through the woods and he comes across
a box that's Bigfoot's most treasured items and he's looking through and he's like "Whoa,
this is actual proof of Bigfoot.
There's a bunch of selfies and there's some acorns.
I don't know what that would be proof of Bigfoot, but maybe, maybe they will be."
And there's this whole tuft of hair, baby's first Bigfoot hair.
You have all this proof and you're like "I can prove that Bigfoot exists."
And then you turn around and Bigfoot's standing there with his arms crossed and he's like
"Uh-uh-uh."
I mean technically it's as bad for leaving his treasured possessions out behind his mulberry
bush.
But what if the reason why we can't find proof of cryptids is because cryptids kill
the people who find proof.
If it's fake proof, if it's not the real thing, you survive.
If it's real proof, you disappear, you die, brutally murdered, no one knows what happens
to you, any combination of those.
And so all we keep getting is the fake evidence.
It'd be the same thing if you had a mafia and you had 9 out of 10 people going "Oh,
that's not the mafia, that guy, he just likes waving guns around and he eats Italian food
a lot."
And then you have one guy that goes "No, actually I'm pretty sure that guy's the mafia."
He did on Valentine's Day drive by and shoot a bunch of people.
That dude who has the proof of the mafia who's saying that stuff, he's going to be gone.
They're going to take care of him in the most stereotypical way ever.
Seamant shoes, most likely.
And then you just have the 9 people left going "Ah, nah, he's a good guy."
That could be a clue.
The people who are looking for a bigfoot aren't finding him and they remain alive and they
keep saying "Well, I didn't find them today, but I'll keep looking."
But the people who do find him don't get to tell us that story.
Or they present us with evidence and then they quickly go missing afterwards.
That may be a clue because the thing is, is we've been searching for these cryptids for
so long.
And not just cryptids, it's just proof of supernatural stuff in general.
Either there is no evidence at all, these things don't exist at all, or they exist and
they're very, very hard to prove, or they exist and there is an active force keeping
us from proving they exist.
I'm not talking about skeptics in the scientific community, I'm talking about a supernatural
force that to maintain the natural order will strike down anyone who knows too much.
So before you go on your next ghost hunt, or go hang out on the wood with your buddies
with one tent and one sleeping bang, looking for a bigfoot, looking for a wolf ape, or
whatever local cryptid like the goat man or the villains of Hunchyville, be very careful
because you might actually find proof that these things exist.
But will you live long enough to tell the rest of the world what you've found?
the truth.
(upbeat music)