Did a homeless man get help from a Good Samaritan or is he a singular victim of the Mandela
Effect?
And then we travel to a recording studio where a young man feverishly writes out lyrics to
his newest album.
But these lyrics aren't coming from a creative mind.
They're coming from the Book of the Dead, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a ton of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now, everyone give it up for one of
our Christmas livestream contributors, Kamau Kokai Taylor.
Woohoo, yeah, come on in, come on in.
Kamau, Kamau, I don't even know if these people still listen to this show, right?
They donated money back in December.
But Kamau, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or the livestream, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about this show that helps out so much.
Kamau, let's go ahead and toss you the bunny bicycle.
We'll hop on the handlebars as you pedal us all the way out too.
Colorado Springs, Colorado.
I gotta come up with a better special effect than that.
People are like, what?
Is my dog panting near my leg?
Kamau's pedaling us all the way out to Colorado Springs, Colorado.
This is a really recent paranormal conspiracy story.
This all started back in June of 2022.
This guy posted this story online.
He went by the name Revolutionary25485.
I don't have his actual real name.
We're gonna call him Cody.
That'll be his name for this story.
And Cody is currently a homeless dude living in his car.
And he's like, you know, it kind of sucks not having a house and all that stuff.
But luckily the weather's warm enough.
I can just sit in my car, kick back.
I don't know if he has a job.
Well, okay, let's put it this way.
I did go through his posting history.
He's up to something, but we don't know what this guy's situation is.
All we know is that he's homeless and he lives in his car.
And he says this, he cannot explain what happened.
And I can't either.
This is absolutely fascinating.
He said that his car has heavy oxidation on the car headlights.
And the passenger quarter panel, which is that piece of like fiberglass or metal or whatever
it's made out of that goes from the headlight all the way to the passenger door.
It's like this big pan.
I had a look at it up.
If you guys were like Jason, we know what a quarter panel is.
I was like, huh?
I don't look it up.
That big piece of plastic or fiberglass, whatever it's made out of steel that goes from the
passenger side door to the headlight on the passenger side was covered in a good layer
of dirt, dirty car, dirty headlights.
I don't know what the state of the rest of the car was.
I don't know just that part was muddy.
I don't know what the state of the rest of the car was, but that these are the parts
that are important to the story.
And he's aware of this, right?
We're all pretty familiar with the bumps and scrapes and scratches of our cars.
Well one day he's walking to his car because even though he's homeless and living in his
car, I'm sure he's like getting out to get food.
I don't think he's cooking rotisserie chicken on the back seat.
At one point back in June, he's walking around his car and he notices that the passenger side
quarter panel is cleaned off completely.
And not only is it cleaned off completely, it's brand new.
Just the quarter panel.
And then he looks and he looks at his headlight and his driver side headlight, heavy oxidation
on it, passenger side headlight, brand new headlight.
That whole area was replaced.
And he has no idea what's happened to this.
So what's interesting is when you look at the comments of people trying to help him,
it makes it very clear very quickly that nobody knows what could have caused this.
Some people said, "Well, maybe you were cooking a rotisserie chicken in your car."
They actually said, "Maybe you were breathing in too much carbon monoxide because you left
your car on all the time."
Because nobody knows where this guy's at.
I had to figure out that he was in Colorado Springs.
But he just said, "No, the place I'm at is really warm right now, so no, and gas is $5
a gallon, so no, I'm not running my car all the time."
So because people are all thinking, "Maybe it's carbon monoxide because the Post-it notes
guy, that's a story about a guy who was slowly having carbon monoxide poisoning.
He was leaving weird Post-it notes around his own house and he thought his house was
haunted because he'd find stuff out of place, but it was really him."
Bear with me with a story.
It's something that people talk about all the time on ghost forums now.
And it was weird.
My daughter began levitating around the room and vomiting.
And people were like, "Well, check out this theory about carbon monoxide.
Yeah, yeah, I don't think all ghost accounts could be for carbon monoxide."
And then the idea of that in relation to this means this guy was up in fumes for so long.
He went to the pet boys, bought a new quarter panel, bought a new headlight, didn't remember
doing either, installed them, didn't remember doing either, and then discovered them one
day.
So, I mean, I guess you can hallucinate that much.
You're at pet boys, you're all meh, thrown up everywhere.
They're like, "Ohh, sir, we'll help you.
Just please stop hovering around."
You have that theory, right?
Which, okay, fine, that's probably the best rational theory you can come up with.
And a bunch of people said this was just insane.
They said, "Well, dude, maybe someone hit you with their car and felt really bad about
it, but figured they don't want to get the insurance agents."
This is a couple people who actually said this.
This is so stupid.
They said, "Maybe when you weren't in your car," because he's not in it 24/7, "Maybe
when you weren't in the car," there was a car accident.
So, he crashed into your car.
And instead of leaving a note saying, "Sorry, I crashed into your car, here's my insurance
information," instead of getting the insurance companies involved, instead of just doing
a hit and run, which I think is what most people did, they replaced your front quarter
panel and your head of light.
They did it when you weren't there.
Straight up, they hit a car and they're like, "Oh, no, listen, I get the insurance involved.
Luckily, I have this guy's exact car parts in the backseat of my car."
And he's like, "I don't think it's been very more polite than I would have been."
I was like, "You guys are all idiots."
He goes, "I don't really think so.
I don't know when they would have been able to replace everything.
I do live in my car.
Even though I'm not in the car all the time, you think I would have just walked by when
I saw two or three guys reinstalling parts of my car."
So he has no idea what could have caused this.
And he does mention the Mandela effect as far as being part of this.
Now, obviously, when we talk about these stories, it could be totally made up.
They could, God, I would hate it if it's the start of some ARG that I got tricked into.
But yeah, that's the story we have.
What could have caused this?
It definitely seems...
It's one of those paranormal stories that is so mundane.
I love it.
It's so mundane.
It's not like...
And then he saw the three pet boys there, ghosts are floating around.
They're like, "We're sorry, you're homeless.
Homeless.
Homeless."
They fade away.
It's like, I mean, like, actually, we would have been pretty brazen out of thinking about
it.
I do like extreme ghost stories as well.
But it has to be one of the two.
It has to be so insane that you can't believe it.
Or so mundane, you think, "Why would someone lie about this?"
This is just one of those little mysteries.
Like, who replaced his front quarter panel and his headlights?
Brand new headlight, right?
Brand new front quarter panel.
So who knows?
He brings up the Mandela effect.
I mean, at a certain point, what would your options be?
Mandela effect, quantum death, right?
He died in one reality and shifted into another reality.
That's exactly the same.
He's still homeless, but this time he has a new quarter panel and a new headlight.
I mean, what could it be?
I mean, I'm like, when we look at the lore, I can't think of anything else outside of
those two, right?
Cern firing up.
We all went to the headlight universe this time instead of some big change.
It's a little change like that.
So I wanted to find out more about this guy.
I always like to do this when I'm able to.
I was looking through his posting history.
He's only posted about two things, technically three, but two or three things.
The first one being his car.
He posted about this a couple of times.
And then you can look at all this in the show notes.
And then he posted on two other subreddits where he was trying to get laid.
So I mean, I guess he has priorities in order, right?
He's living on the streets.
He's living in his car.
The universe may be slowly repairing his vehicle.
And then he's trying to have oral sex with some girl who goes by the name unlucky hedgehog.
Dude, don't roll the dice on that one.
Do not roll the dice on that one.
That's how I found out he was in Colorado Springs because he was commenting on subreddits
for Colorado Springs, like sexy springers or something like that, or ColoradoSpringsHookups.com,
wherever it was.
That is where our intrepid Mandela adventure is also spending his time.
So be safe, young traveler.
And then with the car part, who knows what that could possibly be?
Like what, how could you explain that?
If I had to guess a theory, I would say quantum death, right?
Where you shift into another, you die and then you shift into another universe that's
almost unrecognizable from the one that you're in.
But I don't even know if I'm a huge believer in that.
I'm intrigued by the theory, but I don't know if I'm a huge believer in that.
So who knows?
It's truly a mystery what happened to this dude's car.
And will it happen again?
I'll keep looking at his posts and they're watching.
They just all be swinging your posts from here on.
I'm like, oh man, I'm still checking.
Come out.
Let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carboner copter.
We're leaving behind Colorado Springs, Colorado.
We're going to head all the way out to a recording studio.
I found this story the other day on the X board.
There was a post about a band called the Mars Volta and a cursed album they were working
on.
And I actually have all the notes for that story as well.
I had to make a choice though.
I had to make a choice between doing a full segment on the Mars Volta cursed album.
What was it called again?
Like walking towards Goliath or Trouble in Goliath?
Bedlam in Goliath was the name of that album.
I read a bunch of articles about it and listened to a couple of their songs and wrote up a
detailed thing about their cursed album, Bedlam in Goliath.
But I've decided to tell this story instead.
This story was posted in relation to that X board post.
Someone goes, you know what?
Something like this happened to me and they wrote this down.
I had to choose between the two and I figured the Mars Volta story and who knows, maybe
we'll cover it in the future.
They're just so similar.
They're almost beat for beat and I would rather cover the one that's more obscure.
The Mars Volta one.
If you're a fan of the Mars Volta then you're probably familiar with this story.
If you're not, I'll put some links in the show notes of this episode so you can research
it.
But the story I'm about to tell you has been told basically twice ever on the internet.
The guy said I talked about this a couple of months ago and I didn't, nobody really
cared, nobody really cared, right?
Nobody really cared.
Who's this dude?
And then he told the story again on this Mars Volta thread.
So I wanted to cover this one because this one will just disappear into the ether.
The Mars Volta one is pretty well documented.
Some people say it was just a publicity stunt.
Who knows?
This one I like because it's not a publicity stunt because we don't know any of the people,
we don't know the name of the album, we don't even know where the story took place.
But let's go ahead and get this story started.
Maybe someday I'll do the Mars Volta but again it's almost beat for beat the same story because
I would imagine if both stories are true they would follow the same pattern.
Or coming into contact with any sort of cursed media would probably follow along the same
path.
Let's get this story started here.
Back in 1977 there was a book published called The Necromonon.
It was originally a fiction, just a brief overview here.
A lot of you guys may be familiar with this but originally HP Lovecraft as a narrative
device in his stories and his shared universe, the HPU, he created this book called The Necromonon
that could be used to contact the Elder Gods and had all these dark rituals that the followers
of Cthulhu and Blacky Cactoon and Yen Slaku Gun, all those dudes, right?
Probably just summoned one or two.
This is how you got ahold of them.
This is basically their cell phone, The Necromonon.
And he totally made it up.
He's very very clear, yeah, I made it up.
There's nothing to it.
There's no real Necromonon and HP Lovecraft for years would be contacted by people asking
where he got it or where they can get a copy and he'd be like, it's fake, what are you
talking about?
So of course eventually someone's going to publish a book called The Necromonon.
In 1977 there was a book called The Necromonon and generally it's referred to as Simon Necromonon
because it was written by a, well, I suppose it would be a brief overview, but again I
want to let you guys know how this book was crafted here.
So there was a guy who supposedly was named Simon who gathered up all of these spells
and these rituals and found the Journal of the Mad Arab and put all this stuff together
and published it as the Necromonon, but people were like, the Necromonon doesn't exist.
But this supposedly was the real Necromonon.
You can buy it at like a Barnes and Noble or an Amazon.
I got my copy at like a bookstore in the mall.
Like what were the, I don't even remember, Walden Books is where you could buy them anywhere
but it was supposed to be this dark book of the dead.
These spells could actually summon.
The dark ones, I don't think Walden Books had anything legit like that, right?
Well what's interesting about this is it has been called a hoax because people can, we
know the Necromonon doesn't exist.
This book doesn't exist.
HP Lovecraft made up the character of the Mad Arab, but you're saying you found a Journal
of a Fictional Character that would be like finding the Journal of R2D2, right?
It doesn't exist and they believe that Simon was a fictional character.
It was written by a guy named Peter LeVenda who was an occult history author and that
he created Simon, he created this whole thing.
Now that's the, when I read it I knew going, and I didn't read it, it was super boring,
but when I bought it and read the first couple pages, I knew that it was fictional.
A lot of people who get it, I'd say most people who buy it know that it's fictional, but nowadays
people go, here's the thing, with a lot of grim walls, these books of collections of
spells, basically they are just collections of spells, right?
And some might be real and some might be fake and this is the tradition that there's always
been.
And so there are some sources that say yes, the Mad Arab is fake and Simon is fake and
a lot of the Necromonon, the book that you buy at the bookstore is fake, however some
of the rituals are real because that is the ancient way of collecting these things.
Do you think Peter actually sat down and made up ritual after ritual after ritual or did
he just include some?
There's been accounts of plagiarism and all sorts of stuff.
But in general the book is considered a work of fiction.
So I wanted to be very clear on that because this fictional book is going to have some
real life consequences and what's really interesting is the people in this story also believe the
book's fictional for a while.
Let's take a look at the story, this guy's name, we don't know it, right?
He posted this anonymously on the X-board, we're going to call him Philip.
And he's at work and his co-worker's reading a copy of the Necromonon, I don't know where
they're working where you can just be in the break room, you're feet up on a table and
you're like oh you need to sacrifice 11 men for the dagger of Tiamet.
Oh that's why they didn't work, I only sacrificed 10.
He's reading the book, the co-worker's reading the book Necromonon and Philip showed a little
bit of an intro, hello what are you reading over there man?
And they started talking about it, co-worker goes you want it?
Which probably might, probably what I would say too because it was super boring, here
you want it?
And I was like yeah sure you know, I'll take it and he starts reading over the next couple
of days, couple of weeks.
And he goes you know he's just reading it casually, it's fictional, he knows it's fictional,
doesn't really take it seriously but it's a fun read, it kind of takes you into this
world where these things may exist.
And he said one day I was out reading it, there was a man, he walked by with his family,
he goes this guy was a total wasp man, not like a big old bug when he's like oh no I
have some of the dark ones.
Wasp is an old term, just by him using the term wasp, I bet you this guy's as old as
I am, it's white Anglo-Saxon Protestant, it was an old slang term for basically leave
it to beaver type dudes right?
Very clean cut, looks like they go to church twice a week, wasps, I don't think they use
that term anymore, I could be wrong.
But anyways he goes this real waspy looking guy walked by.
The man turns, looks at Philip and asks, Philip's reading this book, the man goes so what are
you reading?
And there's something about the book called his eye right?
And Philip goes oh the necromanon.
And that's when the man, he turned to his wife and his kid and says hey why don't you
guys keep on walking, why don't you guys just go somewhere, go somewhere else, go check
on the millions of eggs you laid honey.
And so they walk away and he turns back to Phil and goes hey that book, that's a very
powerful book that you have.
I want you to be aware of that.
If you open yourself up to that book, bad things are going to happen so just be careful.
And the man walks away.
And that actually energized Phil, that made him want to read the book any more serious
fashion because again it would be like if someone walked up to you while you were reading
the Hobbit and they go hey you're not going a long journey anytime soon, a town might burn
down.
And then they walk away.
It would be weird.
You know that it's fictional but here this guy is stopping and sending his family away
so he can have this conversation with you, very short conversation.
So Phil decides to actually start taking the book more seriously.
He decides to pretend that it's real.
He begins practicing some of the rituals.
He begins to what his friends could only describe as become obsessed with the necromanon.
And even he would use that term.
I was obsessed with it.
He finished the book and then he re-read it and then he re-read it again and he's pretending
that it's real.
Like what would happen if I actually believed any of this was real?
He got lost in the words of the necromanon.
Now there's a time jump in this story.
He says there's a good period of time where he's kind of moved away from he's no longer
wearing the cloak to work.
He's no longer burning candles in the break room.
He's kind of past the stage where he was obsessed with the necromanon.
And one of his friends casually brings up one day they go "Hey, dude, remember when you
used to read that book all the time?"
Phil's eyes turn red.
The book.
You call it simply a book.
Phil goes "Oh yeah dude, the necromanon.
Yeah, I used to read that all the time."
And the friend goes "Yeah, you were acting really weird back then."
I remember once he said you could talk to the stars.
He goes "It was weird because when he said a good enough period of time passed because
he goes when my friend said that to me it sounded super cringe."
He goes "I had totally forgotten about that.
That sounds like some cringy stuff that I would have said back then but like when he
said that I was like "Oh that's super like edge lord."
But at the same time he had forgotten that he said stuff like that but once his friend
said that he goes "Oh dude, I do not only remember telling you that, I remember believing
it.
Like I was really into the necromanon wasn't I?"
His friend's like "Yeah dude, the chow glad that you can now be aware of that.
It's kind of spooky."
And around that same time so this dude, he's a musician.
He's like plays guitar, he plays bass, plays piano and he's a vocalist.
He's kind of like all in one type of dude.
And it sounded like he was either a musician before this and he had a lot of musician friends.
I don't know if he was in a touring band or anything like that or he just played on the
weekends but he goes "Around the same time that my friend brought up this story about
me saying I could talk to the stars, he goes "An album, an idea for an album popped in
my head.
I called up a buddy of mine who owns a studio and says "Hey man, do you mind if I get some
studio time?
I got a really cool idea for an album."
And it's like "Yeah, sure, no problem right?"
And he says he has a process when he is writing songs but when he started writing these songs
the lyrics are just coming out of nowhere.
He said he was writing songs quicker than he ever did and when he would look back at
the lyrics he goes "These lyrics don't even make sense."
It's like gibberish.
He described the lyrics as both whimsical and bizarre.
And he doesn't, even though he's writing them down, he doesn't really understand what they
mean.
And then when he's going into the studio all of the songs have been written now.
He goes in the studio, he goes "The arrangements completely fell into place."
He goes "I've recorded albums before, I know how long these processes normally take and
this went incredibly fast."
Like far quicker than he could have ever imagined.
Everything was falling into place.
And then, this is another detail that he didn't really remember at the time that his friend
had to, his friend who owned the studio had to tell him like "Dude, what in the world was
going on back then?"
He said apparently that he kept insisting on having these small little details, these
small little notes and noises inserted into the music.
And the studio friend's like "Uh, okay."
And like he, they would do a take and they'd put that little noise in.
And the friend's like "You couldn't even hear it."
Like you couldn't hear what was being added in.
But Phil kept demanding to put in all these little strange, not like demonic growls or
anything like that, but just like odd notes and noises laid into the track.
And again Phil didn't remember doing this stuff.
This is something the friend mentioned after the album is completed.
He goes "You were super insistent on having these little noises put in."
And whenever I asked about him, whenever the friend of the studio owner asked about, so
wait, wait, wait, why are we putting in that noise?
And then Phil would get incredibly angry.
Okay, sorry, I just was wondering, okay.
The friend goes "You couldn't even hear that the noises and notes were in there."
And I couldn't even ask about him.
You'd flip out.
Now at this point, the album's near completion.
They have these songs that feels like "Dude, these songs are amazing."
Let's start practicing to do a live show, right?
We'll do a live show, we'll drop the album, it'll just be this big thing.
Now again, I don't think this was like a major label release.
I don't even know if this was supposed to be a commercial release.
This could have been an artistic release.
They were only going to press like a hundred albums.
We're not for sure on the details like that.
Like was he a full-time musician?
Was he a gig musician?
Was this the album of the lifetime or just one of 50 albums he's done?
We don't know all of those details, right?
But we do know that he, Phil, is now getting together some of his friends.
They're going to perform the album live.
The night of the very first practice, Phil has his guitar on, the rest of the band's
assembled.
As they're practicing these songs, Phil screams out loud in pain.
Everyone's totally freaking out.
He screams out loud in pain and he drops his guitar and his guitar breaks when it hits
the ground.
And everyone's like, "What in the world happened?"
And he turns around, he goes, "Something just scratched me.
Something just scratched the hell out of my back."
And he turned around and he pulled his shirt up.
And sure enough, he has these huge scratches all over his back.
Now obviously, we're doing a live show yet, this wasn't a fan running up on stage scratching
him.
Totally freaked everyone out.
Most of all, Phil, right?
There's no one in there who could possibly scratch his back.
They get weirded out by it.
He gets weirded out by it.
And they call quits the rehearsal.
And also, he broke his guitar.
He goes, "I did not have the money for a new guitar."
That makes me think he's more of like a gig musician, right?
Because I know a lot of gig musicians and that happens.
They got to wait a while.
He goes, "I couldn't get a new guitar and I also got scratched by some paranormal force."
So we're not going to be doing a live show anytime soon.
And the very next day, Phil gets a phone call from his friend at the studio.
And in a very embarrassed tone, because the friend is a professional, right?
The friend goes, "Hey, I don't know how to put this, but the album's gone."
Phil's like, "What are you talking about?"
He goes, "They're gone.
I'm looking at the hard drives.
The files are gone.
Everything we recorded is completely gone."
And Phil feels a wave of depression kind of hit him, right?
This is something he'd been working.
He was like his...again, he wasn't claiming this to be his masterpiece, so that was going
to be the album that defined him.
But he was still something he worked on for a long period of time, right?
And although he was having fun hanging out with his friends, stuff like that, it's hard
work.
And he felt really deflated.
And at that point, he goes, "You know what?
I don't have the energy in it to rerecord all that stuff."
Whatever.
And the friend's like, "You sure?"
He's like, "Yeah, yeah.
We're just going to drop it.
We're not going to finish that album."
He goes, "Around the same time, you know, I gave up on the album."
He goes, "At the same time, I moved."
And he said, "When we moved, my copy of the Necromonon went missing as well."
And he goes, "At that point, I'd really lost interest in it."
Like, there was a time where I wasn't rereading it over and over again.
But I just dealt with it, right?
I just dealt with it.
And I think in the way that he has it set up, you know, he obviously doesn't think anything
of the Necromonon, or he's casually interested in it, but it's a work of fiction that got
the guy inspired him, which was not what the dude wanted to do.
He wanted to be careful.
The guy inspired him to take it seriously.
He begins to take it incredibly seriously, reading it, reading it, reading it, reading
it, and starts saying cringey things and starts having weird beliefs that people around them
are getting a little worried.
And then it does seem like he's not so obsessed with it for a while, but the mere mention
of the book again inspires him to write this album, which I think the idea is it is still
influenced by the Necromonon.
The album, all of the ability to write these whimsical lyrics, but they are super bizarre.
They didn't make sense.
The album coming together so quickly.
The insertion of these little sounds and signs.
I think the push to the story is that that is also the Necromonon working through the
album.
He never really says, well, you know, I wrote the lyrics about the Necromonon.
I was taking rituals from the Necromonon and turning them into lyrics.
But that is kind of implied, right?
And from his point of view, it seems to be that that's how he sees it, right?
The mere mention of his phase.
What's interesting in his narrative, he doesn't say I was rereading the Necromonon over and
over and over and over again up until the time I was recording it.
And I'm in the recording studio.
But I think the idea is that the recording process was influenced by the Necromonon.
He pushed himself too far, too fast in a fictional book, but turned it real.
And the story's not over yet.
I'm just doing a little analysis right now, right?
We still got a little choice dending.
But the Necromonon influenced this album, and that's why it fit together so well.
And he was doing stuff he didn't remember, right?
This is very creepy.
That's almost like a possession.
But so he moves on with his life, though.
He's like, whatever, the Necromonon inspired me to write this album where the very least
was an underlying influence.
But I lost it and I lost interest in the album and I'm gone.
He finishes his story like this, though.
This takes place a time afterwards after he moved away and after the album disappeared.
He says, quote, "That friend with the studio actually died in a pretty brutal way."
And it happened several years later when we got together again and decided to attempt
the entire album again.
Not just a coincidence, but it left me feeling pretty messed up.
It's a fascinating story, obviously, about cursed media, lost media, what was going on
with this album.
Was it truly inspired by a fictional book that elements of it may be true?
Or is it the case of this young man who actually believed it was so true that he's connected
a bunch of coincidences together?
Things happen with technology, files disappear, people die.
These are all things that happen and is it possible that a narrative has been completed
because it borders so close on the paranormal he's putting together paranormal events?
Or was it a real-life cursed album?
Was this album actually influenced by demons?
One thing I find really interesting is let's step back for a second and get kind of meta
with this whole thing of spooky albums of cursed media.
I've been thinking about this story a lot.
If you haven't noticed the audio has changed, I've been thinking about it.
This is a couple days later I'm recording this part.
Let's play this out for a second because this is kind of the way that these stories go.
Demon?
Boy meets girl.
Demon meets the demon.
Demon or demonically influenced music, media, haunted recording, haunted movie is created.
And yet this media is almost always lost or destroyed.
Demon meets a willing victim, right?
A demon influences an artist to create the art.
The artist created and then the art becomes lost.
That's how this story always plays out.
Which again makes you think that not necessarily this guy's story is made up but every other
story involving the same things are made up, right?
Well the album created by the Mars Volta that got released and is actually critically acclaimed.
But for the most part, right, and there are people who think the Mars Volta thing that
was just a marketing thing that they came up with.
But for the most part when we talk about movies like Babylon Rising or whatever it was that
was supposedly haunted, it came out and nobody watched it.
We hear these other albums that come out like this guy's, it doesn't get released.
When we look at the history of these demonically created works of art, they seem to fall to
the wayside.
So my question is this, my question is this, why?
Why?
Because if you were a demon and your goal was to create a piece of art, a haunted art,
right, cursed art, anyone involved in the process of this they're going to go mad or
die, right?
The idea is that if this piece of art got out, you know, it was deleted from the computer,
it could never be recovered and then when they talked about doing it again, the guy died,
the studio dude died.
So why?
Why would a demon put so much work into an album and then curse it so much that it never
gets created?
So that's my question.
That's my question.
Why?
You think that now that they've had this willing victim craft this piece, wouldn't it have
been in the demon's benefit to, I don't know, not kill the studio engineer or delete the
files?
Like wouldn't it have been in that demon's benefit to have that album released?
Never had it had 50 listeners or 50,000 listeners.
It's still extra souls for the demon to corrupt.
These weird sounds that are being laid underneath the audio track.
People hearing those over and over and over again that demonic influence is now coming
to them with a snappy tune laid over it.
Why isn't the stuff being widely distributed?
It's, we talk, did I don't know, I've lost it or I've lost the order of episodes.
I'm going to do an upcoming episode about the Illuminati's influence in the music business,
right?
And those get released, right?
Your Yana's new album comes out.
Charlie XCX's new album comes out, has all this satanic Illuminati-esque imagery, and
those get released.
But wouldn't it have been in the demon's best interest to get this album released?
And if so, why did they kill the engineer if that's the story, you know, if that's the
connection?
Why did they kill the engineer?
Why did they erase the files?
That's what I don't understand about this story.
Because the Mars Volta story, it's the same thing.
They're influenced by this dark person known as Goliath.
It's like three different personalities formed into one named Goliath, and he's dictating
the album.
Or this album is about what Goliath is saying through the use of the spirit board, but they
keep running into problems too.
The studio gets flooded, the files disappear off the computer.
It's all of this stuff.
The engineer at one point takes all of his notes and says, "You guys are going to unleash
something dark upon the world, and I don't want to have anything to do with it."
So they had to start the process over from scratch.
Why would the demons sabotage their own album?
And I don't really have an answer for that.
Like I said, I've been thinking about it for the past probably week.
I'm adding this on way late in the game, and I just can't come up with an answer.
Why would the demons create an album and then sabotage it?
Or is the sabotage coming from a higher power?
Is it not the demons are deleting it from the computer?
Is it God?
Because he's like, "I don't want that getting out there."
But then it opens the question, then what about all the...
This one have like little hidden audio tracks underneath a layer of music.
You have music videos with straight up satanic imagery.
Those get released.
I also don't know why God would brutally kill the studio engineer, right?
He could have just, I don't know, give him a flat tire on the way to the studio.
And he goes, "I don't want to record anymore."
Anything, right?
There's a lot of stuff in between getting them to not do the album again and brutally
murdering somebody.
So why?
It doesn't seem like it's the most...
The original ending was like dark and spooky.
Like I normally do.
It kind of was like, "So the next time you're recording a cursed album, watch out!"
One of those endings, but I thought more about it and I just don't understand the why of
this story.
I believe, I'll accept the belief that demons were a part of this recording process, that
this guy went so deep into the world of darkness.
That he started to believe that these spells were real and maybe some of them are.
And he was putting them into the lyrics.
I'll accept all that.
And I accept that the files were getting deleted and you had this string of bad luck.
I just don't understand why the demons would put so much work into an album.
And then sabotage it.
And if they didn't, who did?
But a fascinating story nonetheless.
A story that ends not on a spooky ending, but on an open question.
Why would this happen?
What would the demons have to gain by creating an album and then deleting it?
I guess the only way to know is to craft a demonic album or so.
Don't do that.
I probably shouldn't even joke about that.
I do not understand it.
But the world of the paranormal is not for me to understand all the time, right?
That's why it's paranormal.
Why doesn't it follow along the line of normal questions?
Fascinating story nonetheless.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also go to us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great week guys.
[Music]