First off, we celebrate the life and times of Alex Trebek as I tell you the story of
how I met him and his bodyguard almost beat me up.
And then we travel to a pizza hut, cause we're hungry after running away from Alex Trebek's
bodyguard.
We're going there for the pizza and maybe play a couple video games.
Little do we know this pizza hut is haunted.
And then we travel to Japan, home of Hello Kitty, everyone's favorite white cat.
But did you know that Hello Kitty may not be an adorable icon.
It may actually be a gateway to hell.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvin, and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
My back's doing better for you long time listeners.
If this is your first episode, you're like, I don't care how your back is doing.
I actually hate podcasts where people have good backs.
Let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, Cindy Pereira.
Cindy Pereira now.
I actually looked that up under a Google pronunciation thing.
I can't even say the word pronunciation.
Cindy Pereira.
So I hope that's correct.
If it's not, I apologize, send me the correct pronunciation.
Cindy, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
Cindy, I'm going to toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're going up, up and away, and back in time to the early 2000s.
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
We're listening to NSYNC.
Those are flying through the time for it.
It lasts forever.
We listened to bye, bye, bye for 400 years.
And eventually, end up in the early 2000s and we land at Sunrise Mall, we're in Citrus
Heights, California.
So we're walking around Sunrise Mall, dude.
If you weren't alive during the 2000s or you weren't old enough to remember how awesome
the 2000s were, yes, we were in a constant state of war.
It was a lot better than it is today.
Like the late 90s, early 2000s was dope.
But anyways, we're walking around, we're flexing on all the fetuses that haven't been
born yet.
Hey, what's up?
We're yelling at women's ovaries.
What's up, dude?
You can enjoy this.
And people are like, what are you doing?
What we're doing at Citrus Heights Sunrise Mall is, I remember one day I was sitting
there, I was reading the newspaper, and they had a little article, it was a little blurb,
and it said they were doing tryouts for two game shows.
Wheel of Fortune.
So basically the denies were empty that day as every elderly person in town scuttled to
the local mall.
And Jeopardy, they were doing Jeopardy tryouts.
Now I don't want to say I'm the best at Jeopardy, but I'm pretty good.
Now I knew, though, there's a difference between sitting in the break room at work and yelling
out the answers before they can answer them.
Like I'm in a relaxed environment, drinking a soda, eating a sandwich out of a vending
machine.
I know that the stakes are much higher when you're on the show, so they're not dummies.
Sometimes they'll make mistakes and things like that.
But I'm really good with sitting at home playing Jeopardy.
So when Jeopardy tryouts were coming to town, I was like, "Haha, now I can prove to everyone
that I buckle under pressure?"
I'm okay yelling it across the living room, but in person it's going to be a lot harder.
So I show up very, very early for Jeopardy tryouts.
And I'm going to backtrack the story a bit right now.
I should have told this part first, because this isn't terrible to the rest of the story.
I'm a hat guy.
I don't wear them all the time, but I do like collecting hats.
I like getting hats that do one of two things.
They're very unique hats, not like Jamerikwai furry hats, nothing like that.
Like I have an Ninja Turtle hat.
I wore that on the Halloween Patreon live stream part of my costume.
I was a Leonardo.
I have a bunch of other weird hats.
Then I also have a collection of hats specifically to rile people up.
I'm the guy, and it's funny, because some people go, "Well, they probably just think
you're a hipster because you're doing that."
And I'm like, "Oh, maybe."
A little do they know.
I'm actually trying to revoke them.
I'm not doing this ironically.
I'm the type of guy who have a couple of National Rifle Association hats, NRA hats, and I'll
wear them to events where I know people hate the NRA.
I'll go to Hop's Fest.
And I don't dress like a hillbilly or anything.
I don't have a full cosplay to go with it.
I'll dress like a normal individual.
Shoe shirts, you know what normal people wear.
And I'll just wear an NRA hat.
And I'll just walk in on the Hop's Fest or the Grape Festival or the Apple Fair or
whatever.
A place where generally people of the NRA are looked down on.
And I'll just walk around wearing a hat.
I do it specifically to make people feel uncomfortable.
And my little brother a long time ago said, he goes, "Jason, you were a troll before that
was even a thing.
Before there were all were troll like you're a real life troll.
You don't do it online.
You will straight up troll people in the most dangerous of situations.
Now, what are they going to do to me at the Hop's Fest, right?
They're going to throw beer in my face.
I'm like, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
used to be a morgue. Maybe, probably not. Morgues aren't normally built outside of strip
malls. So like, "Hey honey, I'm going to go cremate the dog and why don't you go shopping?"
Like usually morgues are on the outskirts of town. But anyway, so that is a rumor. One
review said, "I walked into the restroom once and the water turned on by itself." So that
complements the official narrative. That review also said, "That restroom is disgusting. The
restroom at that Pizza Hut is super gross." That was actually the first. And then how gross
does a restroom have to be? If you walk in, it's haunted. And the very first thing you say in
your review is, "I walked into that gross restroom once and the water turned on by itself." That's
pretty disgusting. But what I thought the most interesting comment was, was this one. This
one really sent chills at my spine. There's a guy named Jeremy. And he said in the comment
said he was actually a manager at that Pizza Hut 10 years ago. He goes, "Listen dude, we
got tons of complaints about the place." Restrooms were super disgusting. But he said the
employees would talk about hauntings and stuff like that. He goes, "The water would turn on
by itself." He goes, "One day we came in, our lobby was flooded. So we did have problems
with the water turning on by itself. We came in, the water was running." And then again,
almost as an afterthought, he talks about the scariest thing you can think of at this Pizza Hut.
Oh really, any restaurant? What's the darkest part of a restaurant? I'll give you a hint. As
we're sitting at this Pizza Hut, eating pizza, our legs are in the darkest part of a restaurant.
It's underneath the tables. And Jeremy told this story. They would see a little girl run
through the Pizza Hut and then crawl underneath one of the tables and just hide there, laughing.
She was seeing multiple times. And one customer, he goes, "One customer was standing there."
And he saw a little girl run across the floor, go down, crawl underneath the table and just
was there, laughing. And you look under the table, the girl's gone. Customers are like,
"Dude, you can keep my two medium pizzas for $12.99. I'm out. I don't need. I'm not that hungry for pizza."
That's creepy. That's Dead Rabbit Radio creepy to me. You can hear the disembodied voices.
You can kind of rationalize stuff like that. The pipes, you can rationalize stuff like that.
And even if you couldn't rationalize stuff like that, they're like, if you go in the corner
or if you go in the storage room, if you go into the walk-in freezer, you hear a baby crying
and you go, "Well, that's your job. I don't go to any of those places." You deal with it.
But to think that when you're sitting in a booth at a restaurant, having a good time talking to someone,
there is something under there. Like that's creepy. That's about as creepy as walking down the stairs
into a basement. There are those stairs where you think someone can reach out and grab your ankles
at any given time. But I actually think it's more creepy because when's the last time you walked down
to a horror movie basement versus the last time you went into a restaurant and just sat there
in the booth. And you think about all the times you see kids actually playing like that.
And it makes it even more creepy that even in death, this little girl is still running
and hiding underneath the booths. And then you think about how many times you're sitting there
in a booth talking to someone, having a good time, and you feel something brush up against your leg.
You know you do that thing where you look under the booth and you go, "Well, that wasn't their feet."
And you figure out maybe you brushed your leg up against something else or they moved their foot away.
But we've all done that, haven't we? You feel something brush up against your leg and you kind of look under the booth
and you're, "That is Dead Rabbit Radio Creepy for me." That's that, Jeremy. Thanks for that comment
because that made it extra spooky. Cindy Kahl in that Carbner copter, we are headed out to Japan.
[imitates car engine]
Helicopters leave me, I am in Glendale, Arizona. It's a long trip. Thankfully, I brought a bunch of pizza.
We're headed out to Japan. But this story's curious because it doesn't start in Japan.
I found this story on a website I talked about, I think it was yesterday, called Quatro Cantos.
It means four corners. It's a Brazilian urban legend folklore mystery site.
Now, there's translation errors. It's written in Portuguese, but then it was trans-- I had to Google translate this.
So there's a little bit of translation barrier. But really, the headline is the headline, which is "Hello Kitty."
The charming billion dollar kitten is the product of a pact with the devil?
Question mark? Very, very good question mark. I normally put exclamation points like I'll probably put as the title of this episode.
The story's pretty simple, but I wanted to cover it because I actually talked about it 100, 200 episodes ago.
I had never heard this version of it, but thought this was interesting.
We're walking around downtown Japan. It's November 1, 1974, and there's a young woman.
She works for a company called-- I didn't write it down, but we'll pretend that I know the name of the company.
So this woman's sitting there and she's drawing something. She's like, "I wish I knew who I worked for having unpaid in months.
I don't know who to call to get paycheck." She's drawing stuff.
What they did was this company made sandals, and they started putting really cute designs on the sandals, and they started selling more.
Other than those disgusting sandals, they called them Pizza Hut sandals.
They came out with a new line of sandals that looked beautiful and cute.
So they started having their artists try to figure out cute designs, and this young woman, she draws Hello Kitty.
And they put it-- her very first item was on a coin purse, and it flew off the shelves.
People were buying Hello Kitty stuff left and right.
To this point, it is a billion-dollar phenomenon.
And she created that on November 1, 1974.
But in 2008, we started to see emails travel around the world.
A lot of them were written in Spanish. This conspiracy theory started in South America.
The idea is this. In South America, there was a young couple, and their 12-year-old daughter had cancer of the mouth.
She had mouth cancer. And the parents are like, "We don't know what to do. I'll do anything it takes to cure my daughter's mouth cancer."
So no one knows for sure if it was the father or the wife, but one of them made a pact with the devil and said, "If you cure my daughter's mouth cancer, I will create an icon the world will worship. Please help my daughter."
And so the devil took that deal. He cured the daughter's mouth cancer.
And that husband or wife, the story isn't clear, designs Hello Kitty.
Now what's interesting is we know who created Hello Kitty. I didn't write it down in my notes.
But we know the date it was created. It was created in Japan. But this email purports that it was actually created by a South American couple.
And the reason why this story spread around was even though basic facts are wrong, the word "kitty" in Chinese means "demon."
It doesn't. It doesn't. There's nothing even close to that. But it's interesting because with language barriers, maybe they could work that out some way.
But anyways, according to a Spanish email, the word "kitty" means "demon" in Chinese.
And the curious case of why the kitty has no mouth is solved by this story.
When the person who was creating Hello Kitty to save their daughter, they didn't create a mouth specifically because they didn't want any reminder of their daughter's mouth cancer.
Now I don't know what they did with the daughter herself. They're like, "You've been cured. Now wear duct tape on your face forever."
But that's why Hello Kitty doesn't have a mouth. The official reason why Hello Kitty doesn't have a mouth, I was up till 2 a.m.
This was a late story that I was researching. I know so much about Hello Kitty except the company that makes her and who designed her.
But the reason why Hello Kitty doesn't have a mouth, this is really interesting. It's a psychological trick.
The company that made it said, "We want Hello Kitty to have whatever emotion you're having."
If Hello Kitty's always smiling but you're sad, that's a distance.
And we're not going to make a doll with a bunch of sad faces. It's all frowny and mad. Without the mouth, Hello Kitty is experiencing whatever emotion you're experiencing.
So if you're sad, she's sad, you're happy, she's happy. It's fascinating. A little quirk of human psychology.
But the story of Hello Kitty being a satanic icon is something I talked about a long time ago.
I actually put forth a theory, a total conspiracy theory. I have no proof of it.
I don't remember what I was talking about at the time, but I don't want to spend a whole bunch of time talking about it again.
I said, "What's an object that people around the world know and they, I wouldn't say they worship, but they know and they treasure it?"
And when you step back and just look at the silhouette of it, it looks horrific.
It's Mickey Mouse, but it doesn't look anything like a mouse. It looks like an abomination.
He's the most boring animated character possible.
I remember I had this conspiracy theory a long time ago that Walt Disney made a pact with the devil,
and that or some sort of demon and that creature is the best representation you can draw of what that demon would look like.
So the big ears are actually like eyes or certain appendages, and the nose was something, was a nose? I don't know.
But the point is, it was the same thing. It's so funny because I came up with that conspiracy theory years ago, probably right after I met Alex Trebek.
It was back in the early 2000s, I thought of that, and here we have one that Hello Kitty is that same thing.
So not only does this kind of validate my made of conspiracy theory, I wanted to talk about this too, and we're going to wrap it up like this.
We talk a lot about people making deals with the devil to be successful.
Now, I don't think you have to make a deal with the devil to become successful.
I do think it is possible. I think you can do it literally, and I think you can do it metaphorically.
But I do think you can literally, I don't know if you can sell your soul so much, but I think you can be tricked into thinking you've sold your soul
and doing horrific things to maintain your fame when it wasn't yours to sell in the first place, but if you thought you had actually sold it.
I've heard, I've read, I've read a lot about people selling their souls to the devil and things like that, and one of the things that happens to them,
you sell your soul to the devil and then you get this fame and this success and then they say you got to do this horrific thing or the gravy train ends.
They're like, I love gravy and I love trains, I can't let this end. So you do something horrific, but the key always is, well, I'll just sell my soul and I'll live my life
and then right before I die, I'll become a Christian and God will get my soul back.
But when you start to think of that, you start to have these horrific nightmares and you're given this vision that God no longer wants you.
Like people have talked about who have sold their souls or said they've sold their souls that they were becoming overwhelmed with these visions,
with these nightmares that God had abandoned them because they were doing horrific stuff. It wasn't something they had to do every single day,
but they would do something horrific and they'd think, how could God ever forgive me for that?
And the point is having to ask God for forgiveness for doing that thing, but you've done something so horrible you can't ask for forgiveness and it's this spiral-leaning thing.
There's always that story that Bob Dylan sold his soul to the devil. He's kind of made comments about that as well.
And he got in a horrible motorcycle accident, broke his neck, almost died, and since then he's been a Christian, he's been a devout Christian.
That's a story that a lot of time gets lost in the saga of Bob Dylan through his art, but there is some weird paranormal stuff going on there.
I don't think you have to sell your soul to become successful. I think it is a path.
But this story about Hello Kitty, which isn't true, but it does offer us a weird way to kind of look at art.
If an artist sells their soul to the devil for fame, right, you have Marshall Mathers trying to make it in the world of rap, and he does.
And he starts to move up in the ranks, but not fast enough. So he sells- this is just an example, this is just off the top of head of him,
and listen to a lot of Eminem lately, he sells his soul to the devil.
Would his creations, which are being bolstered by the powers of darkness, are they gateways for us to fall into the devil's clutches?
And I know that's the whole thing with like, in the 1980s they had that huge thing like heavy metal music makes you more demonic and stuff like that.
Don't listen to that Twisted Sister album, you won't respect your teachers. But that's the easy route.
Like people listen to Eminem and then they go, you know, beat their girlfriend up or something like that, or start using drugs, do this stuff.
You can make those connections, that's dark music. I personally have always liked the thing, I actually heard this on Ned's Declassified School Guide.
People who listen to dark music, people who listen to like, you know, stuff like Eminem's, you know, gangster rap stuff like that.
They kind of explain it like this. Positive plus a positive equals a positive. They're talking about electrons, but they're saying how it works in real life.
Positive plus a positive equals a positive. Positive plus a negative equals a negative.
So if you are moody and you like darker stuff and someone's trying to get you to watch Mickey Mouse cartoons and trying to get you to listen to opera or pop music or whatever,
it's a negative, it gives you a negative reaction, but somebody who, they're not bad people, but somebody who already feels kind of angry at the world and alone and stuff like that.
When they listen to Tech Nine or Eminem or Disturbed or whatever, Cannibal Corpse, that actually gives them positive feelings.
A negative plus a negative equals a positive. So it doesn't mean that they're actually going to go out and do those things,
but it actually can have a positive effect on their mental state because they want to go "I don't feel alone anymore. I didn't know there were other people out there like me who could rock as hard as Disturbed."
But you know what I mean? Again, that's the thing. Like if someone's putting out dark music and it's causing their fans to do dark things and it turns out that musician sold their soul to the devil, that all makes sense.
But what happens to the opera singer or the pop star?
Let's forget the pop star. People already say Rihanna sold her soul to the devil in her music. Her song Umbrella is about Satan possessing people.
Let's take like a world famous opera star where they're just singing other people's music. They don't write their own music, they're just like "La la la."
They're just writing "La" all over the paper. "La la la la la." They're singing other people's music.
What happens when you take music that's created by someone who didn't sell their soul to the devil and give it to an opera singer who sells their soul to the devil?
At what point does the music become perverted to become a gateway?
What happens if someone designed Hello Kitty and it was totally normal? Their daughter was fine? They didn't even have a daughter?
They didn't even have a daughter? And they sell it to a company and that company's CFO got to that position because they sold their soul to the devil.
That's pretty low. They're like "You can have my soul. I just want to be a chief financial officer of a fortune 10,000 company."
And you sell that and then at what point does the corruption begin? Or does the corruption ever begin?
Is it enough for the dark forces to simply take your soul or do they want to use these icons to steal the souls of millions?
I don't know. I mean, I basically just asked a bunch of questions, but I thought it was an interesting story.
There are a bunch of doorways that we can look down and see all these alternatives.
And if it's true, if this is true, that at any point along the production chain, if someone sold their soul to the devil, the item gets infused,
then at this point everything would be infected. Your Hello Kitty nightlight, your Marshall Mathers LP,
but it would also be your dish soap, the raw hamburger meat sitting in your freezer, your shoes.
Everything could be tainted by dark forces sprinkled throughout the production line.
That sounds a lot less like a packed with the devil and more like the seeds of a full-on demonic invasion.
[Music]
DeadRabberRadio.com is going to be our email address. You can also visit us at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
Twitter is @deadrabberradio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]
[MUSIC]