A terrifying crime shows what happens when we take conspiracy theories a little too seriously.
Then we take a look at the story of a young woman who encounters aliens,
advanced life from another galaxy, which makes us ask the question,
what if the smartest beings in the universe are wrong today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Garvin, or I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too.
This may be the fastest recorded episode of Dead Rabbit Radio ever.
It's slowly approaching 100 degrees outside. I really, really waited a long time to record this
episode. I recorded it like almost the hottest time of the day. So we're gonna have to get right
through this. First off, let's give a shout out to one of our legacy Patreon. Actually,
you know what? Today I want to give a shout out. I don't know if I ever gave her a shout out for
this. So today's shout out is going to be Audrey Mackamson. Everyone give a round of applause to
Audrey as she's walking into Dead Rabbit Command. Do a little bow. She's not a Patreon supporter,
but a long time ago I put out a bounty. You're like, Jason, you did reward her for this. We
remember this. You just didn't put it down your notes. Audrey Mackamson, or makeum some, I put
out a bounty for a Bigfoot USB. There was something called Bigfoot the track record,
a Bigfoot Encyclopedia. And it had a, we covered the story. It was about Bigfoot hanging out in
Oregon at near a place called Cock Rock, which is, which is a place where dudes go to bang each other.
But Bigfoot was there for some reason, just looking for love. Anyways, I'll put that episode in the
show notes. You're like, no, Jason, tell us that story now. In that episode I mentioned there as a
USB. It was like lost media. I didn't think I could ever find it. She found it. She sent me the link
and I purchased it. And it's really cool. So Audrey, I wanted to really thank you for that. So
you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode today. If you guys can't find an obscure
piece of lost media for me, that's fine too. Just help spread the word about the show. Really,
really helps out a lot. Also to give a shout out to the Patreons, there is currently a debate.
It's not a debate. Everyone agrees on the Patreon Discord. How much they hate me for being a fan of
the Minecraft streamer dream. Apparently there's almost enough rising. I expect to lose a lot
of Patreons this weekend because I do like dream. Audrey, oh, oh, we got, what am I talking about?
We also got this amazing fan art for Fan Art Friday. I almost forgot because I'm not looking at it on
my screen, but this was from the Patreon Discord. This was from a long time listener of the show,
Patreon supporters will. Rudy Jazz, look at this. It's a little combination. Don't, if you're driving,
if you're driving, you can look at it later. It's a combination of myself
with the Dead Rabbit radio logo. So it's, I got my hair cut, I'm all wooly, and apparently I have
the nose of a pig. I did not know that. I always assumed my nose was Romanesque and less chief
wiggum, but whatever, I don't care either way. Rudy, thank you so much for providing this artwork
for Fan Art Friday. It really is super duper awesome. Audrey, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the
keys to the Jason jet. We're actually going to leave behind Dead Rabbit, I forgot where we were
going. We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. You're going to vroom vroom us on out to
Mexico. Audrey's flying us over the beautiful blue skies of the world,
we're headed down to Mexico. Now this first story, it's a little intense. I'm not going to go into
a lot of the details with it, honestly, because I think the implication is more important than the
gruesomeness of it. On August 7th, 2021, you had a dude named Matthew Coleman of Santa Barbara.
People are already skipping, they're like, nope, there's all this news, all this news,
where's the fast forward button? On August 7th, 2021, Matthew Coleman of Santa Barbara
decides to kidnap his own two children. Kalio, three years old, it only gets worse from here,
unfortunately. Kalio is three years old and Roxy is 10 months old and takes his beautiful little
babies down to Mexico. Shortly after that, their mother, Abby Coleman, his wife, reports her
children missing. This is a pretty breaking news story. On August 7th, we're still getting drips
and drips of information, but we don't know if the relationship was on the rocks, like if he
was sending out warning signs that he may be planning to do something brutal. They're actually
lived up in Santa Barbara, so he's driving out of Mexico and she reports them missing and the
police are like, oh great. So I think there is more stuff going on. It wasn't like, oh I think
he spent a little too long on this day trip. I think she alerted them that he's been having some
mental health difficulties. Matthew Coleman is then coming across the border from Mexico back
into the United States and everyone at the border had gotten a bolo for him, right? Be on the lookout
for Matthew Coleman, so when his car comes, they stop him. Hey Matthew, he's arm and they know his
name, he's like, oh, they start questioning him. They notice that there is droplets of blood in his
car, like on a sheet of paper, and most horrifically, neither of his children are in the car. So Matthew
Coleman is arrested, he is questioned, and it turns out that he took both of his children down to this
farm in Mexico and shot them both with a spear gun. All that stuff is just horrific. All of that
stuff is just absolutely horrific. It's a terrifying local news story and it happens all too often.
The reason why I'm talking about it on Dead Rabbit Radio, even though this is a true crime
podcast, we don't cover stuff like that. We do cover more stuff like that on the TikTok. We cover
kind of these local weird creepy crime stories on the TikTok, but on the Shell Proper, I don't really
talk about that type of stuff unless it's super bizarre. This is super bizarre because his motive,
and this is why I think they probably, Abby was probably aware that there was some mental
health difficulties going on prior to this. Matthew Coleman told the investigating officer,
I believe it was an FBI officer, because you can read the affidavit on Crime Online,
I'll put the link on the show notes, it's a really great website, I visit it every day.
For my crime fix, I go to Crime Online, he tells the FBI agent, well, I had to kill him.
I had to kill him because I learned the truth. You see, I am a, what you may call a conspiracy
theorist. He's not as exact words, he wasn't talking like Heath Ledger's Joker or anything like that,
but I'm kind of puffing it up for you. I can just read the affidavit, but that's no fun and it's kind
of dark. He goes, listen, I've been learning about this stuff about the Illuminati and QAnon.
Did you know about QAnon? The FBI agent goes, yes, I do read the newspaper, I'm aware of that term.
He goes, but see, the Illuminati has opened my eyes to what's really going on in this world.
You see, my wife and mother of my children is a reptilian. She has what's known as
serpent DNA and she gave it to my children. Officer, I'm telling you this right now,
those weren't children I killed in the desert.
They were monsters. I didn't murder my children. I just saved the world.
Now, even though that was me adding a bit of dramatic flair, the lights flickering,
that is the gist. He did say QAnon and Illuminati conspiracy theories,
and he quote, was receiving visions and signs revealing that his wife possessed serpent DNA
and had passed it on to his children. And the phrase to save the world was also used in that
affidavit as well. Terrifying story. Absolutely terrifying story. And I know right now there
are already some people typing into the YouTube comments, maybe this is just a story to make
conspiracy theorists look bad. Listen, there's already enough stuff that makes conspiracy
theorists look bad. I would be hard pressed for a group to just pick out a local crime story,
no matter how horrific. And this actually isn't in the top 10 most horrific crimes that have happened
in the past month. I mean, for this family it is, and for this family it's the worst.
But you know what I mean? Like if this was some sort of conspiracy, oh they're trying to make QAnon
look bad, so they're gonna type, no, no, no. There's worse they could have chosen. There really is
worse crimes they could have chosen. I do enjoy investigating conspiracy theories,
and I love sharing them with you. And I think you guys sense that there's definitely at the very
least an interest in conspiracy theories, and for me at the very most like a joy. Like I enjoy
finding these things, and you guys are very well put together adults as well. But this guy had
most likely an underlying mental illness and found the conspiracy theories as well. It's
interesting because I think, I don't think this is going to become a huge major story, and they're
going to try to use it to push away conspiracy theory content on YouTube or anything like that.
But this is almost like the Freddy Krueger defense, which I don't think has ever been used. But if
they did, that's a cool name for it, where somebody commits a crime based on a horror movie,
and that person had been struggling with mental health issues their entire life,
and then they became a huge fan of the Freddy Krueger franchise. They bought a time machine,
went back to the 80s, they're a huge fan of Freddy Krueger, and they end up making a glove out of
knives and stabbing someone to death. Or just took a knife and stabbed someone to death.
One that's most likely happened already. But was Freddy Krueger to blame, were those horror
movies to blame for the crime, or if he had watched The Wind and the Willows too many times,
would he have dressed up like a frog and drowned people? Because the underlying mental illness
is already there, and if it's untreated, that's really the key. If you can get it treated, you're
fine. But if it's untreated, and you have the movie stimulating the thought pattern, would any
movie do that? What if he was watching action movies all the time, would he want to go on a
mass shooting rampage? So that's where I think this lies. I don't necessarily blame the conspiracy.
I will say this though, Freddy Krueger and The Wind and the Willows and The Matrix,
they don't ever imply that they're true, even though Nightmare on the Street was based on a
true story. I'll put that episode in the show notes, it's really creepy. But the movies themselves
don't apply to be true. These conspiracy theories are supposed to be true, so there might be more
of an argument that the conspiracy theories weighed more on him. Actually that's a good point,
because as I'm arguing with myself in a 90 degree closet, Freddy Krueger doesn't go now, well listen
kids, this is a true story, this is what happens if you try to take vigilante justice
against a child rapist. This is what will happen to you. We know it's fictional. And see when we
look at conspiracy theories like, there's a whole group of population that has serpent DNA in them
and they're going to pass an on. We've covered this conspiracy theory. Not only have we covered
this conspiracy theory, oddly enough we've covered multiple times people have tried and
successfully used spear guns to kill people, which is such a weird exotic weapon. We covered it when
the guys were fighting on the airliner and we covered it with the guy who killed his family
using a spear gun. But anyways, I'll put those episodes in the show notes, it's not an advertisement,
I'm not using that as an advertisement, it's a weapon of choice, but we did cover the serpent
seed conspiracy theory once, there was a minister who believed that people were passing this around,
and that's a quite foolish conspiracy theory. That's one of the ones where I'd be like, wait,
well if we can't detect it, if we can't detect that serpent DNA, like you look at a microscope,
you see a regular little sperm, and then you look and there's little microscopic
alligator-strung ethosperm, you can't detect that there's serpent DNA in there, you can't
scientifically do anything, it's quite foolish. But he was having these visions and seeing these
signs as well, he's probably flipping through the radio station and every so often the song
Man Eater would start playing and he's like, oh, Man Eater, that's like an alligator, and
he puts this stuff together and, but who knows, it's tragic and it goes to show that sometimes
when you take these conspiracy theories too seriously, plus, I don't think that can just be
your kind of believing stuff that doesn't exist if you believe in every conspiracy theory,
you take it, someone believes the earth is flat, it doesn't affect you in any way, shape, or form,
it really doesn't, so I don't care about it, I think it's dumb, but it doesn't affect me in any
way or other people. But when you take that conspiracy theory and you put an underlying
mental illness to it, that's the problem, I think that's really the problem and I think that's
the main issue here. If people want to believe that 10% of the population is reptilian, whatever,
then the only way you can become famous and rich and powerful is to either be reptilian,
or to join the reptilian core or whatever, have a little reptilian badge ask me about my
reptilian ancestry, whatever, that doesn't affect us in any way, shape, or form, and if they just go
"ah, Queen Elizabeth, she's a big old reptile, I saw her laying an egg, it's all laying an egg the
other day and Meghan Markle popped out of it, whatever, who cares, like that really doesn't
affect us." If that person is then going to do something violent, which is the extreme minority,
which most conspiracy theorists, they don't do anything like that, but there's the extreme minority,
there's a stream minority of people who love motocross, who are also using their dirt bikes
to run drugs across the country and maybe to run over their enemies faces. They have to wait till
their enemies sleep in and then like "ring, ring, ring," they got the silence around their bike.
There's a small minority of every group, but we are conspiracy theorists, or at least we enjoy
conspiracy theories and this one unfortunately, whether or not the conspiracy theory England
is an unfortunate true crime, I'm not trying to gloss over that, but I thought it would be
interesting for us to take a look at because we enjoy these topics, sometimes people take them too
far and have other mental issues and the people who really paid for this was the two children,
Kaleo and Roxy and then Abby and then everyone who loved those people. Matthew Coleman, who cares
about that? Anyways, I won't cuss on the family episode, I won't cuss on this family podcast
where I just talked about this horrible brutal crime. Awful, awful, awful, you just, you don't even
want to think about it, but Audrey, let's go ahead and toss you the keys of the Carbenter
copter. We are leaving behind Mexico, such a sad story, and we are headed on out to the Vologadot,
what a baby name this place, you're like no Jason, you're just mispronouncing it. Vologadot
region in Russia. In the Vologadot region in Russia, it's August 2nd 1982. Wow, I didn't even plan
that, that's almost 21 years ago. Jason, how hot is it in that closet? That's not even cool,
that's like 40 something years ago. Anyways, close enough, it's 1.15 pm, we're in the Vologadot
region in Russia, and there's a young woman, her name is Elle Smirnova, she's walking through this
birch forest, having a good time, I don't know, doesn't actually say what her mood was,
she could have been deeply depressed, but anyways, she's walking through the forest,
and she hears a loud booming Russian voice, come closer, do not be afraid, the equipment is switched
off, she's like is that the voice from Gumplet? Elle Smirnova needs food,
badly, she's walking through this forest and she sees a clearing, and in the clearing is a UFO,
a flying saucer, typical flying saucer, shiny metal just sitting on the ground, and she sees
like three dudes walking around, one of them looks to be a white guy, and he has dark eyebrows with
gray eyes, and then standing next to him are these two other dudes who look Japanese, and the white
dude, she said they all looked around 25, so she is trying to gauge how attractive they are, she said
the white dude starts smiling at her, and then goes Elk on seal, which apparently some alien thing,
it's not Russian, she didn't understand it, and the two Japanese dudes leave them, they go and
they walk by these stairs that are leading up into the UFO, I didn't describe the UFO, I have more
stuff about the UFO, I'm too caught up in this romantic drama we're about to get entangled in,
the UFO wasn't sitting on the ground so much as it had the little landing gear, and then it had
these stairs, like how you would picture a UFO from a 1950s movie, and the stairs going up to
the open doorway, and she said the door had these intricate designs of animals and plants on them,
this little motif on the door, because if you're going to build a UFO, if you're going to build a
vehicle that spins 90% of its time in the dark reaches of space, you want to have a nicely designed
door, you want to show off to nothing, to the nothingness that lives in the cosmos, Elk and Sue,
all of a sudden Elk starts to go, she starts getting dizzy and sleepy, and she's starting to
think, oh no, I'm being hypnotized, I'm being hypnotized by this really handsome man in the
middle of the woods, and she starts saying please don't hypnotize me, please, please don't hypnotize
me, so he stops, and then he goes, well I was going to hypnotize you, but now I guess we'll have a
conversation, he goes, my name is Oli Kan, I am Oli Kan from the planet sunny, S-U-N-N-Y,
and this is where we really, the story's interesting, but this is where you really
start to ask questions about it, I got this story from ThinkAboutItDocs.com, they got it
from a magazine called Veer Russia, number 18, I couldn't really figure out what that digest was,
it seems to be maybe some local newspaper for the town or province of Veer, T-V-E-R,
that's not how you pronounce it, why do you even go to other countries,
anyway so I don't know what that magazine is, but ThinkAboutItDocs.com has never stirred us
wrong in the past, Oli Kan tells this woman, El, that he's from the planet sunny, and then the
name is, I think he realized that that was probably a dumb name for a planet, because then he goes,
oh yeah no no sunny, that's what those people need to call it, I call it Galeos, so there's
actually two names for this planet which is weird, like I guess we have earth and then sometimes
nerds call it Terra, but sunny or Galeos, it's one of the two, it's one of the two names, so
if you're trying to fly to this planet you might get lost, that he said it's about 45 light-years away
in the Ursa Majoris constellation, now he says that they're there in this particular, they're
having this conversation, he goes, the reason why we're here in this particular location is we
want to investigate some nearby atomic weapons, and El goes, oh well there's none in this area,
there's no missile silos, we're fully aware of that, we have to fight back the evil capitalist
pigs of the United States, and Oli Kan goes, well there actually are nuclear weapons here,
he said about three kilometers away there's an underground bunker full of nuclear weapons,
she's like three kilometers away, that's where my house is, he then pulls out a beige colored
clock dial, and he begins to present holograms of her brain, she's able to see her brain and she
sees regions of it are mapped out in green and red, it's very Christmassy, and after looking at a
hologram of her brain, he doooo shuts off the device, doesn't shut off her brain, and he goes,
quote, we will talk to you, you have a good memory, you don't smoke or drink alcohol, unquote,
so if you've ever thought about it, if you're a fan of alien encounters, and you have either of those
vices, um, stop it, stop doing that stuff, stop smoking and drinking, because someday you may
mate an alien from the planet, he begins to quiz her, which we see a lot, you know, a lot of times
humans don't have time to ask questions, because these aliens are asking so many questions, he's
asking the weird stuff, like what do humans know about water, she's like, well, I mean there's two
thirds of it, we have the most in the solar system, he wanted to know about all the elements, what we
know about water, fire, sky and earth, he asked, oh, what's the meaning of the universe, she's just
sitting there, and he's like, oh wait, oh wait, we'll just sit here on this rock until we figure it
out, he starts to ask, does she believe in God, does she read the Bible, she says she was a Christian,
and she worshiped Jesus, to which Alican, the space alien, responded, Jesus, quote, was the man,
unquote, I don't know if that's the equivalent of being like, oh, he's the man, or if it was saying
that Jesus, yeah, that's the right guy, I don't know for sure, but he also said that our religious
life, like just all of our religions in general, these guidelines were necessary, but just in the
beginning, which is a kind of an interesting, interesting alien look at it, like all of the,
maybe these religious rules that our societies follow, they're created in different ways all over
the world, but these religious rules are created, but someday we move past them, I don't know,
he begins to show her maps, they're having a long conversation here, he shows her a map of the ancient
world, and then the world of how it is today, when he's showing her the map, and these are
electronic maps, he's now rolling out these paper maps, when he's showing her these maps, he shows her
these massive mineral deposits and unearthed riches in the modern world, he also said there's three
undiscovered elements on the planet earth that humans don't know about yet, they're here, here,
and here, and there's that one from behind her ear, and here you are, it's already active, she's
all melting, no there's apparently three undiscovered elements we haven't discovered yet, and this is
where we start to get into some really interesting stuff, Arlican then went on to say that in the
year 2050 there's going to be massive climate change, it's going to ravage the world, floods,
hurricanes, tornadoes, snowstorms, islands would disappear, all coastal cities would be underwater,
so if you're big, if you're big in a windsurfing, 2050 is the year to be here, he also says that
life is eternal, which I like this one, but there's also a little catch this one, life is eternal,
it just kind of flows through the universe, life the soul force simply transfers from one
form of energy into another and then to another and to another and it's endless, but not for everyone
does this happen, so that's a really interesting again a little tidbit here, we're really kind of
analyzing this because on the one hand you could go oh hell right someone who broke the religious
code someone who didn't believe in the truth their soul does not continue to travel through the
universe they go to hell, you could also go no enlightenment, you transfer forever through
the universe and then eventually you've been everywhere and you are then enlightened and you
go somewhere else or simply obliterated what what else is there you've ascended you've
experienced everything or more those are both kind of older theories or you could say NPCs,
the current relatively new couple year old conspiracy theory of there are a lot of people
out there who are non-player characters who don't have a soul they are simply moving about society
and they don't have the life force that the rest of us have, one thing I thought was interesting
and this guy's dropping knowledge to this guy's dropping bombs not literally he's not dropping
atomic bombs, he says that a lot of the UFOs we see are remote controlled which is back in 1982
remote control obviously was a thing but it's not as popular as with drones are today but he goes
most UFOs you see are not piloted by life forms most of them are remote controlled they're on the
other side of the moon there's a base on the dark side of the moon there's a base over there so
I'm not gonna he didn't give an actual statistic like nine out of ten he just says most of them
most of the UFOs you see if they crash there'd be nothing on board which wouldn't make sense the
risk is much lower to be discovered the chances of losing an entire experienced crew is zero if
they're on a base somewhere and they're flying the UFO like because drone technology has advanced
so much you would have to assume that alien drone technology would be light literal light years ahead
of us don't want to make sense to put three tiny people on a ship on a crowded little ship and shoot
them across the cosmos you could shoot them across the cosmos but then they set up a base on Mars
then they use that to interact with us sending little UFOs that he ends his conversation with
this he says that on his planet there's a population of 200 million people there's no
skyscrapers all the buildings are pretty level we'll get into that's a really important detail
in a second he says there's no starvation because they all eat albumin which I had to look that up
it's egg white that's their entire diet is egg white and he goes they make it they have this
process that they can make tons of albumin in one minute they don't eat a ton of shit they're like
step one get 10 trillion chickens no they can mass produce his albumin and they eat it that's the
only food they need I'm sure they probably make it tastier like putting spices in it and make it
shaped like a chicken and then eat it who knows maybe they do but it doesn't matter that's all they
eat doesn't matter what it looks like it's still egg white and he goes there's no starvation and he
offers L the recipe he goes how would you like to be able to make tons of albumin in a minute and
she refuses he's like that's so disgusting that's so gross even though I live in the so eat union in
1982 I would rather stand in a bread line than just eat egg white that's pretty much the end
of the conversation he does say I'll see you again every four years and they did return in 1986
1990 and 1994 it's a typical alien story we have kind of a communication of ideas you have her
kind of being shocked by the presence of these guys very typical the reason why I wanted to cover it
is not for all that so if it is interesting I always think it's interesting when aliens talk
about religion it seems like such a man-made thing but we see all these stories that make us
think it's something else but what if aliens are dumb is the point of this story because I saved
some stuff here for the end we kind of sprinkled it on throughout but the undisclosed see I still
what's I think science I think science is wrong I think you could have undiscovered elements out
there I do I think that we don't know what we don't know it's a phrase I use a lot in my personal
life we don't know what we don't know but then there's stuff that this alien says that is noably
false it's absolutely not true so let's go back to when he said that the buildings on his planet
were not skyscrapers he's talking about climate change he's talking about the elements he's talking
about life being eternal flowing through the universe he also says that we are a lopsided planet
he tells this woman in 1982 listen lady I know you're just some girl walking through the woods but
you have a serious problem you need to address people have built buildings on the wrong side of
the planet so because we have skyscrapers and they're not evenly spread out like our civilizations
are tend to be along the coastlines and along rivers we've actually unbalanced the world
the buildings are making the world wobble a little too much and it's actually gonna make the earth
if you don't lady if you don't in the middle of the woods and Russia fix this if you guys keep
building cities and the population keeps growing the planet earth is actually going to fly out of
orbit it's actually gonna get so wobbly you're like fine you're putting the last rivet in this new
building they're like hand me that rivet Tony finally that this building is done and then
all of a sudden whoa the next thing you know we're orbiting Jupiter that is not possible I don't
even think I have to explain the science of why that's not possible but I will because I actually
think it's super interesting everything on this planet is from this planet like when we build a
massive skyscraper all that stuff is from the planet we're not adding anything to the planet
or taking anything away we're just building this skyscraper and I did an episode on this a long
time ago because I was curious about this how to look it up the earth gets heavier every single year
by tons gets heavier every single year through space dust and meteorite impacts so the world gets
heavier and bigger every year it doesn't matter what we do as far as building the stuff it's
interesting because as he is so on his planet there's no uneven buildings all everything was
perfectly mapped out so their planet didn't go wobbling off into the cosmos if we keep building
along coastal lines and it's not I keep saying skyscraper it's not even really the size of the
buildings like that's part of it but just if you have too many even small buildings on one side of
the planet the planet's gonna fly out of orbit people forget how massive earth is that's the thing
with the flat earth theory they go way up and they're like I don't see the curve the earth is so
huge like even just the size of the earth can be mind-boggling sometimes what's interesting is if
coastal he talked about the climate change if the coastal cities are wiped out in 2050 that'll
actually reset the clock because all of that coastal buildings all of those uneven cities will
actually save so he's saying climate change is good so so so take that youtube take that youtube
algorithm that's gonna hear me say climate change is good and do something funky to this video
he also says that you know when he was showing the I left this part out because I wanted to add
it to the end he said when he was showing the map of the ancient world he said the pyramids were built
with the assistance of aliens in fact it wasn't just myself I'm not not 10 000 years old wasn't
just our alien race there were five different star systems worth of aliens they all came down to
build these pyramids but the pyramids exude an ionized poison so you can't go near them
if you're around the pyramids too long it'll kill both humans and aliens because they're just these
powerful that's not true that's not true now if you told somebody that in 1982 Russia it might
might I mean they weren't bumpkins that might have raised an eyebrow or three because she's
living near that radioactive bomb factory but that's not true like there are I'm not saying
there's like people living right next to the pyramids but there are people who make their job
their tour guides around the pyramids they're not mutants they're not ionized poisonous freaks
unless that's the biggest cover up of all maybe I've exposed the biggest conspiracy I just dropped
the ultimate red pill the pyramid pill so it's an issue this story is just kind of interesting
look at because the aliens fly away and she has this information he put she passes it on to the
journalist and we have this story but what if aliens are wrong aliens are interesting because
it's the one paranormal phenomenon that we assume is smarter than us like sure people look to angels
and demons for guidance when people look to demons for shortcuts people look to demons for shortcuts
because they want to get rich and famous so they don't have any of that Serban DNA in them
they weren't lucky enough to have that made-up thing put inside their body so they'll turn to
demonic forces to become rich and famous they'll look for shortcuts people talk to angels for
protection but ghosts people even when they're like talking to ghosts maybe they'll want to know
the future but no one's ever like using a Ouija board to find the answer to some equation or to
find the cure for cancer to do something like which they should now that I think about it
we we did cover the soul phone the people who are trying to build the phone
I'll put that episode in the show notes every time I say that phrase it costs me five extra
minutes at work guys I have to go full of the episode but the soul phone they were trying to
get this phone built so they could talk to the dead and to help with scientific advances but for
the most part go start the spooky people who hang out in your closets and stand in dark hallways big
foot is just a big old dummy trying to try to hook up with some dudes at cock rock in Oregon
you know I mean cryptids are just these monsters aliens are the ones we assume are smarter than
ourselves and and it's interesting because it is it does have a bit of the demonic in it that we
want them to solve our problems there's people who believe aliens are going to invade the planet but
there's a lot of alien enthusiasts who believe they're going to save the planet they're going to help
cure us they're going to bring us together in a good way we become part of the space brotherhood
it's a shortcut because we can't do it ourselves we can't do it ourselves right we can't see past
each other's differences and we can't you hold each other's hands with people that we absolutely
hate and realize that all of this stuff is so fleeting what's the point let's be together now
we can't do that we can't do that as a people we can't do that as cultures so aliens can do it
alien it's a shortcut it's a shortcut we don't want to do it ourselves but what if they're wrong
like what if they are wrong the uneven city thing just is scientifically invalid it's an
interesting story because what he's saying is false and we put a lot of faith in these aliens
to come down and save us and we covered recently like what if aliens are demonic what if they're
trying to take over the world what if it's not even that sinister what if they're just as dumb as we
are sometimes they just give bad advice what if a fleet of UFOs came down tomorrow and said this
stuff you'll find these undiscovered elements life is eternal move move your cities around or the
world's gonna go full how would people take that they clearly are smarter than us they have this
fleet of UFOs they've descended from the heavens they're clearly more technologically advanced
from us would we as a species be smart enough to go you're wrong like you may be smarter than us in
some stuff but that's not true we know who would your your planet may be wobbly it's funny i say
well we do we know the answer most people would acquiesce to the aliens they go well they must
know more than us let's start changing the way we build cities and that would be the least of my
worries right imagine if they go these aliens no way more than us they have all this advanced
technology they've shown us where these riches are we haven't found these undiscovered elements yet
but they've shown us where these riches are we've moved our cities and everything seems to be great
they also only have a population of 200 a million we're seven billion
they know more than us maybe that's the correct thing to do as well sometimes when we listen
to the so-called smartest people in the room we end up making the dumbest and deadliest decisions
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead
rabbit radio. Tiktok is @dead rabbit radio. Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal
conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day i'm glad you listen to
it today have a great weekend guys
you
(upbeat music)