A man waiting for the bus falls into a world of horror.
A man uses a bizarre tool kit to enact revenge against his killers.
And then, you guys have been waiting for it all week, I keep postponing it.
We travel to San Francisco to meet a film director who decides to lay the perfect trap
for the Zodiac Killer.
All he needs is 5 men, a walk-in freezer, and a movie starring the Zodiac Killer.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a
great day too.
I'm gonna tell you guys right now I'm a little hungover because I was watching the election
all night, you guys who are long time listeners of the show know I'm a huge political junkie.
It's like elections are like my world series/ubervol/curling championship.
Um, basically anything, anything other than an election is like an election to me.
I love politics, I love the art of campaigning and all that stuff.
It's one of the very few times that I actually drink, and last night I drank and went on
forever, it's not decided at this point.
I also ate a bunch of pizza.
Both of those things combined, you're like Jason I do that every day, why are you complaining
about this?
My body is now probably 30% marinara, probably another 20%, I had two beers, okay?
Let's be honest, I had two Budweisers and I'm all "Uhhh" and that's, I'm just a lightweight
when it comes to alcohol and apparently also when it comes to Domino's pizza.
But anyways, the only reason why I'm explaining that now is because I'll probably be a little
more surly this episode.
I'm still feeling the effects of all that stuff, I'm just like "Uhhh" that's a good
product placement for Budweiser and Domino's, right?
They're like "Uhhh" makes you feel like you're sweating out pure chemicals.
But you know what doesn't make me sweat?
Our newest Patreon supporter, you like that segue?
Our newest Patreon supporter, Ragecat!
Everyone give Ragecat a round of applause, scratching behind the ears, rub his little
belly.
You're like "Dude, I support the Patreon, I never got my belly rubbed well, maybe we'll
rub your belly at some point."
But Ragecat is going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just helps read the word about the show really, really helps out a lot.
So Ragecat, let's go ahead and touch you the keys of the Jason's Loppy.
First off, very, very short story.
We're headed out to New York City.
*meows* After I made that sound effect, I took a nap for two or three hours.
But I'm feeling a little more energetic now, so we got Ragecat driving us out to New York
City.
This first story is actually pretty short.
But I want you to put yourself in this situation.
So we are in New York City.
Like "Dude, I'd never go to New York City."
But for this story, you don't have a choice.
You're there anyways.
It's October 28th, 2020.
Very, very recent story.
You're standing there waiting for the bus and you see me and Ragecat walking down the
street towards you.
You stop a safe distance away, kind of waving to you.
You're like "What?
That's kind of weird."
And then you take a step towards us and then you disappear.
Now it's not a time warp.
It's not Mandela Effect, nothing like that.
It is the enemy to all mankind, whether we want to believe it or not.
It's the sinkhole.
You fall down into a pit.
Fifteen feet deep and on impact, break your leg.
You're like "Why am I listening to this podcast?
This is horrible."
You're in a pitch dark pit.
Previously you were standing up on the street in New York City.
You don't know which one's more dangerous, but you're in the pit.
"Oh my leg."
And not only do you have a broken leg as you were falling, you broke your arm too.
And you're screaming out in darkness.
Now there's a beam of light coming down from the hole that you made and you see people
looking down trying to figure out a way to help you.
That's when you begin to scream out for help, but you very quickly keep your mouth shut
as a giant rat crawls onto your shoulder.
And then another one scurries across your leg and then a third is sliding up under
your shirt.
You're crawling all over your skin.
They're everywhere.
You can't even cry out for help because one of them may crawl into your mouth.
This actually really happened to a guy named Leonard Shoulders the other day.
The exact same story I just told you.
Fell down, broke his arm, broke his leg.
I spared you this fate.
As he was falling through the concrete, there was a hole opened up.
It wasn't like a perfect loony-tune hole that he could go through.
It was jagged concrete.
So part of the concrete scraped away a chunk of his face.
He falls 15 feet into this hole.
It's covered in rats.
And he said that he wanted to yell out for help, but he didn't because he felt they
were going to crawl into his mouth.
These huge rats were swarming this abandoned basement that was rotting away underneath
the city street.
He was down there for 30 minutes.
He was down there for a half hour before authorities could rescue him.
I understand that from a logical sense.
It's not safe.
The firefighters aren't like "hey come over here everyone" and they run over to the
hole and then they all fall in and break their arms and legs.
I'm actually surprised that no one else fell in.
His mom was standing next to him apparently when he fell in.
But I don't know why that's an accident.
He tells not like she made the hole or did she?
But I mean like there were people standing around.
You can actually watch video.
Video will be in the show notes of this happening.
And you see everyone just kind of checking their phone.
There's a delivery man making a delivery and then "dook" like "dook" just...
First off when he falls he braces himself.
But I think that might have actually been his downside because one of his legs is like
bent up.
He's holding onto the ground and he's only able to hold himself up for like two or three
seconds if that.
And then falls 15 feet and he fell on the leg that wasn't folded against his clavicle.
So it's not a good landing.
He sat down there for a half hour.
It's just a compounded terrible story.
Falling into a hole sucks.
Falling into a hole full of rats sucks even more.
Breaking limbs.
Can't even really fight him off at that point.
What are you doing?
Shrugging him?
Take that.
Take that slight movement you rat.
And then being down there for a half hour the rats continue to scurry around.
Now they've actually shut down this part of New York.
They shut down like three buildings on this block until they get the basement fixed.
So if you're looking for a job, if you're looking for a job in the New York area, maybe
you can go down there and get a job as a professional basement fixer/rat avoider.
I wanted to cover that story for a couple different reasons.
One, it's absolutely terrifying.
Two, there's a video of it.
That's a great combination.
The other reason why I wanted to cover it, and I don't remember if I saw this on X.
I think I did.
I might have seen it on Reddit.
I just read so much stuff, but I don't remember exactly where it came from.
Someone put out this theory that what if, not all of them, I'm not gonna say all of
them, but what if an amount, well let's just throw out there, 10%, 10% of missing kids
are falling into the sewer.
And this is the person who laid this scenario out, pretty interesting.
This kind of makes sense.
It's really easy to fall into the sewer.
I mean it's not, they're kind of designed not to fall into, but people do fall into
them.
There's a lot of things in waterways and things like that.
You fall into the sewer, you're out playing in the neighborhood.
Everyone's like, "Hey look at this, there's a little Billy running down the street and
then Billy rounds the corner and he's never seen again."
It's not a super common story, but it happens enough to creep us out.
Everyone's looking for the kid, they never find him.
Suspect may get arrested and then it turns out that he was killed, which is horrible
ending obviously.
Most of the time the kids are found.
Most of the time it's a runaway situation or they're just lost statistically they're
found.
But in the horrible cases where they're not found and there's no suspect and there's
no arrest, this poster said, "What if they're falling into our water systems?"
And you go, "Well Jason, I'm sure you would find the body within at least the maintenance
schedule of a sewer."
They don't just build them and they're like, "It's the alligator's problem now boys.
Let's leave and hope everything goes fine."
There's constantly workers down there, but if it's a sewer system or a storm drain system
that has enough flow of water in it, either during the time of their disappearance or in
between the maintenance schedule, the body's gone.
The body's absolutely gone.
Case in point, there was a woman, let me pull my notes up real quick.
You can tell I'm super prepared for this one.
Now this is an extreme circumstance because this took place during a storm, but on July
6th, 2020 in Paseik, New Jersey.
This was over by the Dairy Queen on High Street in Benson Avenue.
If you want to go there, if you want to reenact this event.
A young woman named Nathalia Bruno, 24 years old.
She was a door dash driver.
She was trying to make a delivery during this massive storm and a flood hits, a flash flood
hits.
And her car gets lifted up by the water, it's floating down the street, everyone's seeing
what's going on.
And it's headed towards a giant storm drain entrance, like this tunnel that's perfectly
car sized for her car.
The water's carrying her away, she's getting pulled into the tunnel and she has to make
an executive decision really really quick.
Do I stay in the car and hope that it provides me some sort of protection?
Or do I get out and swim?
Now anyone who knows anything about physics knows that neither is optimal, neither is
a great option.
And people are standing there in their houses, in their warm and cozy houses, and they're
seeing this car go into this storm drain and they see Nathalia jump out and then the car
gets sucked into the storm drain and she gets sucked into the storm drain too.
They're immediately calling 911.
They didn't wait until that.
Once they saw the car floating, some guy's like "Oh no, my Taco Bell!
She's supposed to deliver it to me!"
Car's going into the sewer.
As the fire department is getting these phone calls to get out there, they're rushing out
to the scene.
Nathalia has already been sucked into the storm drain.
Before they even get to the location, there's a bunch of other 911 calls from a mile away
because people are sitting in their warm cozy houses and you know just enjoying the view,
enjoying the storm drain view of New Jersey.
People are looking out their windows and they see a woman shoot out of a storm drain as if
she was going down a water slide, crashes into this rapidly growing reservoir river, and
she swam in and then she crossed the land and then she just kind of collapses.
What had happened was she got, she survived.
She got sucked into the storm drain and she basically within 30 seconds ends up a mile
away.
Whoa!
Totally tubular dude!
She's all swimming.
She actually, she wasn't swimming.
She's been sucked along by water going 30 miles an hour.
It takes her from that main storm drain and deposits her in that river.
Had she at any point, she had no control over which way she was going.
At any point if the water had zigged instead of zagged, she would have ended up stuck
underwater drowning in the darkness of a sewer.
Instead, in some bizarre like dragon's layer like choose your own adventure, the lights
are flashing.
The water made every perfect choice to lead her to safety because it had all these other
inlets in there.
Her car, they show a photo of the car, was completely crushed.
There's a photo looking down a manhole at her little dot's in or whatever it was, smashed
the pieces and it was wedged into the storm drain.
I have no idea how they're going to get it out.
They're just going to have to like cut it out, cut it out piece by piece, lift it out
of the manhole and then reconstruct the car.
She did end up making the right choice.
If though the water at any point had tried to put her down one of those side areas, she
would have been dead.
It would have been a tragedy.
But instead, she had a really fun time, right?
Whee!
But imagine now this happening, people aren't viewing it, it's a kid falls into a storm
drain and is then drowned.
This is dark, this is super dark, but a kid falls into a storm drain and gets washed away
and ends up in a reservoir somewhere or deposited into a river and is never seen again.
I think I have limited my amount of morbidity on this episode, but you know what I mean?
I thought there was an interesting theory that you could have a lot, maybe 2% maybe
1%, but maybe enough that these kids that go missing, especially younger kids, maybe
they're falling into storm drains and getting washed away, they're not going to the water
reclamation plant, they're not going somewhere into the sewer where they could eventually
be found, they're being deposited in the waterways that lead off into the rivers and
the lakes and the oceans, never to be seen again.
Sorry, that's a good dark turn, you're like "woo!
Rats, that's cool, I'm not afraid of rats" and then we end up talking about that.
Ragecat call in that.
Dead Rabbit Durgible, we're leaving behind New Jersey, we're headed out to Pompano Beach,
Florida.
Dead Rabbit Durgible flying over the eastern seaboard.
This is a really weird one, I actually came across this one today, that happened about
a month ago.
It's October 18th, 2020 and we're standing outside our new job, we now work at WastePro.
We are professional garbage men, or garbage people, I guess is their call today, although
that makes them sound like some sort of cryptid.
But we are now professional garbage people.
It's October 18th, 2020, it's 2.15am, there's video footage again of this, a man walks up
to the front gate of the WastePro parking lot.
So we have a building that is where all the garbage people work.
Oscar the Grouch is the boss and super smelly, there's banana peels everywhere, and then
they have this parking lot that's full of their garbage trucks.
And a man walks up to the gate that's holding the garbage trucks and he's standing there.
This man is wearing goggles and he's dressed as trash.
He's disguised as trash.
Specifically they said he has a suit made of garbage bags, but we'll put a pin in that
because I have a theory about that.
He gets to the front gate, there's many ways to get into a sealed location.
You can cut the lock, you can pick the lock, you can have a key, you can blow it up if
you're adventurous.
This guy does something that I've never seen before.
He sets the gate on fire.
And apparently the gate was made of coal because it burns.
He sets it on fire, it's so hot.
I guess he melted the lock or something like that.
He opens the gate, flames still flickering where a lock once sat.
He begins walking into the parking lot and setting garbage trucks on fire.
They're going up in flames.
There was actually at least one explosion when he was doing this thing.
There were residents who had their windows shattered.
It's 2.15 in the morning, you're worried about gray aliens coming in your house or something
like that.
You're worried about your missing kid, he's been gone ever since that storm.
And then all of a sudden, pshh, glass comes shooting in.
Ah, what is it now?
You see a fire.
Several fires from the WastePro location.
Then he kicks in the door of the WastePro building, pulls out a bottle of liquid, sets
it on the ground and sets the building itself on fire.
At that point, this garbage shaped man gets into a black sedan.
I know it kind of ruins the mystique, right?
You were just kind of hoping.
You have like the garbage mobile or something like that.
No, it's just like a Chevy.
He goes and he gets in his black sedan, rrrrrr, drives away.
There's no word on whether or not he peeled away his tires left fire marks, but you know,
you can always hope so.
Apparently, and tad another bizarre twist, there was also a white SUV that the police
are looking for because they think it may have been a lookout.
So the police are looking for two vehicles, a black sedan, probably smells like garbage.
Probably a good tip.
What I find interesting about this story, other than every single part of it, I didn't
know you could open a gate through fire, what if, let's put on our conspiracy caps here,
let's put on our conspiracy caps here for a second, what if this man is some sort of
garbage, I'm being serious, I'm being serious, I'm not saying this is true, but this is what
I thought when I finished reading this article.
You may be thinking it as well.
What if this man is like garbage incarnate?
What if this man is a garbage vengeance spirit?
And for 10,000, no, 100,000 years from the first time that a caveman ate a banana and
looked at the peel and goes, what's this for?
And throws it on the ground.
Or a little kid unwraps a toy, a little caveman unwraps a toy, they invent wrapping paper,
they invent paper first, and he unwraps a rock and he's like, awesome, this is what
I always wanted.
And then throws the new invention wrapping paper on the ground, the garbage spirit standing
there in the shadows.
He's slowly collecting all this refuse to become sentient, and he waited all this time.
This is his first strike against humanity, setting garbage trucks on fire.
I do find it really weird, like if I was going to break into a toy store, I wouldn't
dress up as a giant teddy bear.
Although they should actually, maybe this guy is a garbage vengeance spirit, maybe he's
just ahead of the curve.
Maybe someday you'll be sitting in a bank, getting ready to deposit a check, and a giant
money bag runs in with an AK-47.
Give me all your me.
And everyone's like, what?
That's super confusing.
He's like, I'm money, give me money.
From now on I decree that every criminal should be dressed as what they are doing.
In hypodermic needles standing on street corners, pimps and prostitutes.
They just look normal.
They just look like normal pimps and prostitutes.
You're driving through a desolate area of town, you see a man dressed as a hatchet hiding
in the bushes.
So is garbage man actually a sentient spirit, or is he just a trendsetter?
We won't know until he strikes again.
I'm telling the story as I'm looking at two bags of garbage I gotta take out to my garbage.
But one thing we gotta do first, this episode may run long, I don't care.
Rage cat, fire up that carbonar copter.
We are leaving behind Florida.
We are headed out to San Francisco.
It's the year 1971, we are walking down the streets of San Francisco.
We're having a ball, we're dressed up in bell bottoms, medallions, this is totally dope.
Speaking of dope, there's a giant hypodermic needle man standing on the corner there.
But we're not there to buy drugs.
We are there to watch a movie.
The movie called The Zodiac.
Now all this information actually got from an article written by Jake Rossin.
He wrote this for MentalFloss.com.
So really appreciated Jake.
We walk into the movie theater, we see all the candy, we see old 1970s gross candy like
dots and candy corn.
I don't know if they have candy corn in the movie theater, but it's gross anyways.
Then we see an unusually large podium, like a lectern.
Like we're expecting Billy Graham to show up and start giving him a speech.
I've never been to a movie theater in 1971.
Maybe this is normal.
What's not normal is the Kawasaki motorcycle.
The guy standing behind the lectern goes, "Hey, you guys want to enter the drawing for this
Kawasaki motorcycle?"
Just write down your name, address, phone number.
We're going to put it into this giant, this massive lectern.
Kawasaki can hold a person, doesn't it?
And when we look at each other, we're like, "Yeah, I guess it's big enough to hold a
person."
He goes, "Well, it doesn't!"
There's no one hidden in this podium.
Why would you even think that?
And we're like, "You kind of brought it up."
It's also weird that now we hear the sound of someone eating dots and they're getting
stuck in his teeth.
But whatever, we don't care about personal privacy.
We fill out all of our information.
I'm filling out extra information for you.
We drop it into the podium and then we go in to see the movie The Zodiac.
Now this movie came out in 1971.
I guess I should spoil something right now.
We to this day still really don't know who the Zodiac killer is.
There's been suggestions that it was this dude or that dude or whatever.
This whole plot, I just realized there's something wrong with this segment.
Or at least the way I'm presenting it.
I think it's a fascinating story.
But this whole plot is, they're trying to catch the Zodiac killer, but we know for a fact
the Zodiac killer is never caught.
I'm trying to figure some stuff out of my head on how to...
You're like, "What?
He was never caught!"
Click off the episode.
I'm trying to figure out a way to continue the rest of the story.
I do have to say this though.
I think the Zodiac killer is one of the lamest of all the serial killers.
The only thing the Zodiac has going for him is the fact that he has that gimp suit.
Which is what it is.
Like I remember when I was a kid, I'll say this too.
I have a personal beef with the Zodiac killer.
He ruined one of my Halloween's.
I was probably like 9 or 10 years old.
So it was like 1985, 1986.
I was living in the Bay Area.
My dad was going to seminary at the time.
So it was in Marin County.
This is when I went to Strawberry Point Middle School.
This is when I was involved in the gate program.
And I made that weird sculpture.
That episode was a while back.
Check that one out.
The dragon is what that one was called.
I'll put it in the show notes.
I was going.
I was in the area as Marin County.
I didn't know who the hell the Zodiac killer was.
I was 9, right?
And he had done all of his kills back in the 60s.
So even by the time they were making this movie, he stopped killing people.
Actively killing people.
But Zodiac killer, and let me say this too if you don't know, Zodiac killer was this
quote unquote famous serial killer who killed like 6 or 7 people.
I'm not entirely for sure.
And he would leave these cryptic messages in the newspapers.
This little symbol and he's like, "I leave this code and it's like I'm the Zodiac killer.
I'm going to kill again."
You know, I'm such a bad boy.
Catch me cops.
It's just all that cringe, edgelord nonsense that you would laugh at today if someone posted
it online.
But he was posting it in this paper and they were publishing it and everyone's like, "Oh,
who's this total badass Zodiac killer?"
He'd point a gun at you.
He would make you like restrain.
He'd make the guy restrain the girl and then he would restrain the guy or whatever order
they'd both end up being restrained then he would stab him to death.
Come on.
I mean like to me, see I don't have a huge opinion of serial killers to begin with, but
that's pretty lame.
He wasn't enough of a fighter.
He wasn't enough of a scrapper to actually try to go at two people with a knife.
He was a big punk.
So he had to tie him up and then stab him and whatever.
And then he'd get an erection because these guys, their dicks don't work unless they're
committing violence.
That's one of the reasons, if your penis doesn't work or if you don't have one, I don't care.
That's totally fine.
My thing with serial killers is they are almost always a sexual dysfunction.
But yet society's like, "Oh dude, this guy's a hunter of man and he left these cryptid notes."
He couldn't get it up and so he killed people.
I don't have a high opinion of serial killers to begin with.
I definitely don't have a high opinion of serial killers.
You have to wear gimp suits because they look so neb-ish.
Like if you saw Ted Bundy coming out of the woods after you, he looks like a serial killer.
He's like this tall, handsome guy and you would think that guy's probably gonna kill him
because he's running out of the bush with a knife, but you're thinking, "I might not
be able to take that guy in a fight."
Now again, he attacked co-eds in their sleep where people trying to help him put a bicycle
on his car.
Like he was just a gross loser.
But at least with Ted Bundy or Jeffrey Dahmer, that dude had the lame.
That dude was tall, right?
So if you were like boxing with that dude, he's got a little bit of reach on you.
But again, he was drugging men.
He wasn't going toe to toe with these dudes.
None of these serial killers are leading them into the octagon and goes, "Ugh, only one
of us is gonna leave here alive because they would lose every single time."
The Zodiac Killer was such a dork that he had to hide his face behind a mask.
Now he looks like someone that Seymour Krellborn would push down the stairs.
He looks like a big old nerd.
I'm not saying you should pick on people just because of what they look like.
But if they are also serial killers and they look like dorks, it's fair game, right?
He's not like, "Oh, I feel the need to kill.
I'm gonna go join the Liberation Army of the Congo and fulfill my needs," because he'd
get blown away.
So he's just shooting people who are defenseless.
But I have a personal beef with Zodiac Killer.
When I was like 9 years old or something like that, 9 to 10 years old, Halloween was cancelled
because of this jerk.
He didn't just say his reign, his murders ended back in the 60s.
Well they did, but because they never caught him, people were always afraid.
We were getting ready for Halloween.
I was probably dressed up as Yoda or something like that.
And it was just normal Tuesday, it was June, I was dressed up as Yoda.
Halloween was coming, everyone was getting ready to go out and get our food.
And the newspaper got a letter from the Zodiac.
They got a coded message from the Zodiac saying that they were going to drive around shooting
kids on Halloween.
Now it didn't happen, it turns out to be a hoax, but I didn't get to go trick-or-treating
that year.
I think this, it wasn't like a city-wide canceling trick-or-treating, everyone was just like
be a little cautious.
They might be a serial killer, out to kill your kids.
So parents weren't letting the kids go out, people who normally did give out candy were
giving out less.
It was truly a drought.
And as I stood there on that moonless night, holding half a bag of Snickers, instead of
the full bag I normally would have, I raised my hand up into the sky and said, "Damn you
Zodiac killer!"
Probably wasn't him.
Probably was just someone having a laugh.
But anyways, I never liked the serial killer.
After that people were like, "Dude, you know that, people actually lost loved ones."
That's horrible.
Sure, but 9 year old Jason lost Snickers because someone wanted to pretend to be the Zodiac
killer.
Let me get to this, let me get to this actual story.
It's actually not super long now that I'm thinking about it, now that I kind of gave
it away.
What it is, is that Tom Hanson, he was a fast food chain franchisee guy, he had all these
fast food restaurants, but things weren't going well business wise.
And he was thinking about cashing out and moving back home.
He lived in the Midwest, at this point he's in San Francisco and he goes, "You know what,
I've always wanted to be a movie director/producer."
He had done bit parts in movies in the area.
And he figures out, it's interesting because this is both like being a vigilante and having
a gimmick for your film.
He comes up with this idea.
I'm going to make a movie about the Zodiac because the Zodiac killer was a publicity
hound.
In one of his coded letters where he's like, "You will find the eighth body near the tenth
reservoir if you look at some."
He's like, "I wonder who will play me in a movie."
So I mean, you know, again, he was just adored.
If TMZ was around back then, he would be walking down the street in a Zodiac suit, leaving
San Francisco airport and they're like, "Hey, Zodiac, Zodiac, is it true you're dating
Jennifer Aniston?"
He's like, "Get out of my way."
"Yes, it's true."
Also, will you tie yourselves up there?
Like, no.
And he's like, "Ugh."
He was a publicity hound.
He was super vain.
So Tom Hanson comes up with this idea.
He goes, "Maybe I'll make a movie about the Zodiac killer."
Having premiered in San Francisco, the Zodiac killer is going to show up.
I got two ways to catch him.
One, no serial killers love Kawasaki motorcycles, right?
So they can chase their victims down.
So he got a Kawasaki motorcycle and he said, "We're going to have people fill out these
cards.
We're going to put them in the podium."
And inside the podium, don't tell anyone this, inside the podium there was a man.
There was a man inside of this lectern with a flashlight.
Every time a card was dropped in there, he would match it against no one's samples of
the Zodiac's handwriting.
The address is written down as a bunch of glyphs.
He's like, "Hmm, these look familiar.
I'll put this in the maybe pile."
"That's not good enough, right?
Who knows?
This Zodiac already has a Kawasaki motorcycle.
Maybe he's a Harley man."
So he had people posted all around the theater and they had to steady a picture of the Zodiac's
... This guy walks in with a giant mask on.
Because they did have a sketch of what he looked like underneath the mask.
So everyone had to steady the sketch and they go, "Just keep scanning the crowd.
See if you recognize this guy."
And then they had a guy in a walk-in freezer for some reason.
I read the article multiple times.
I'm going to make heads or tails of that if they just tricked him into going in there.
Apparently there was a guy in a walk-in freezer and there was a light in the walk-in freezer.
Now the guy in the lectern, if he caught a signature that was correct, he would hit
a button and then the light would come on in the walk-in freezer and then the guy would
come out of the freezer and just go, "Surprise!"
He's like, "I don't know.
Okay, you know that there's a signature match, but the guy walks out of the freezer isn't
going to know who that is."
He just walks out and he's super cold.
He's like throwing popsicles in every single direction.
How did that help anyone?
They actually ended up foiling part of their plan because the guy in the walk-in freezer
one night, this went on for multiple nights.
The movie premiered for about a week.
The guy in the freezer runs out of oxygen, starts to pass out.
He's somehow able to signal he's running out of oxygen.
It's a poorly thought out plan.
So other people in on this plan had to go and rescue him, including the guy inside the
podium jumped out and ran.
That'd be shocking.
You're buying your candy.
You see a full-sized man jump out of a lectern going, "Oh, I'll save you!"
And run off into the freezer.
You're like, "What?"
That was more entertaining than anything going on in the movie.
When everything settles down and the guy gets back into the lectern, he finds a card
that says, "I am the Zodiac.
I was here."
Later on, investigators like private investigators, I don't know if this ever got turned over
to the police, but people who looked into the case said that wasn't a match for his
handwriting.
I find it odd that that card was deposited during this whole craziness.
So was someone actually watching this and figured out the rules and put it in there
as a joke?
Who knows?
Or was the real Zodiac killer there?
But that's not the end of the story because Tom Hanson believes that the real Zodiac killer
did show up.
Because Tom Hanson, you know, he goes, "I worked at a lot of fast food restaurants.
I owned them.
I'd been working at them for a while.
I'd been robbed a lot and I learned how to steady people's faces.
I knew exactly what the Zodiac killer looked like."
One day in the movie theater, the movie's playing, I go to use the restroom and I go
into the men's restroom and I'm peeing and a guy walks up to the urinal next to me and
it's peeing as well and he says, "That's not what blood looks like.
That's not what it looks like when you stab somebody."
Tom Hanson, his pee runs cold.
It freezes.
It's all slow motion.
And he turns and he looks at the man at the urinal next to him.
It is the Zodiac killer.
He goes, "That was the guy.
That was 100% the guy.
I know what he looks like.
I've seen many sketches in my life.
He looked like that video from AHA.
He was all animated."
So he actually convinces this guy, "Hey, yeah, you know, yeah, blood looks like that too.
Hey, you mind if we go and talk in my office?"
And the guy does.
The story does get weird here because you would think an innocent person would be like,
"Let me finish peeing and then no.
I don't want to go in an office with someone I just met in a bathroom, but this man says,
"Yeah, sure.
I'll go in the office with you."
So as they're going into the office, Tom starts giving the signal to his other conspirators
who are there to help catch this guy.
The movie's still playing.
Everyone's having a good time.
The movie about the serial killer.
They're like, "Ha, ha, ha."
They're laughing.
You can watch this movie.
It's actually, I don't know if it's available on Amazon, but you can watch it.
It'll be in the show notes as well.
I don't know if it's Laugh Ride or not.
So I do know there's some interesting twists and turns.
It's actually fairly well reviewed for like a Grindhouse movie, but they all walk into
Tom Hanson's office and Tom Hanson's sitting there, he's talking to this guy, and he said
the guy seemed extremely relaxed.
Wasn't nervous at all that he was in this room full of a bunch of people who were there
to catch a serial killer.
Now he didn't know that obviously.
He just thought Tom Hanson liked their own parties in his office.
But he said, he goes, "It was interesting because of this guy.
I was trying to be combative."
I actually said to him, because we were talking about the Zodiac Killer, we were at the movie
theater.
I said that I was the producer of the movie.
Tom Hanson said, "I had said the reason why I made the movie is that one of my relatives
was a victim of the Zodiac Killer."
So I have a personal stake in this.
And the man didn't even react to that.
He didn't get nervous, but he also didn't show sorrow.
He'd be like, "Oh, I'm sorry, bro."
It's just kind of no reaction at all.
He also noticed it was weird because the man started winning over the room almost instantly.
He said that he had served in the military.
There are other people in that room who had served in the military, and they're kind
of bonding over a military experience.
And Tom Hanson thought it was weird.
He was basically working the room.
He was turning the temperature down.
This stranger among all these people who were there to catch someone who looked just like
this guy.
Now Tom Hanson didn't really have anything to hold him.
And this was a flaw to the plan to begin with.
Even if you caught the guy, what could you really do?
You could call the police and he'd be like, "Okay, I'm just gonna walk out the door because
you can't prove I'm the Zodiac Killer.
You definitely can't hold me captive.
That's kidnapping."
So he just kind of left at a certain point.
They're talking, he's like, "Okay, I'm just gonna leave now."
And Tom Hanson is sure this is the Zodiac Killer.
He kind of walks out of the office.
And that was totally his right.
Tom Hanson doesn't...
The movie, it's not a flop, but, well, one, it didn't catch the Zodiac Killer show.
I mean, I guess it could be considered a failure, but it also didn't catch on.
It didn't make a ton of money.
It's more notorious now for the backstory to it, but like I said, you can now find it.
You can now watch it on digital.
So then he comes up with another plan.
These next couple of plans were not nearly as audacious and were actually kind of messed
up.
If this guy was the actual Zodiac Killer, then I don't care.
But if he wasn't, it's kind of mean.
It's kind of mean.
First off, you can decide which one you think is worse.
He hires private investigators, they track the man down, they get his address, and then
he tells the man, "Hey, remember that contest you entered to win that cowsocking motorcycle?"
And the guy's like, "Yeah?"
They're like, "You didn't win that."
"Aww."
"But you did win another prize."
"Oh, right, awesome."
"We're gonna give you this prize.
We're gonna send someone to your house with this prize."
He's like, "Okay, that's a weird detail that's normally how prizes are delivered."
Our suspect opens the door and there's a man holding a box and he hands the box to the
suspect.
The suspect's like, "Aw, awesome.
What?
I've always wanted a box wrapped.
Wrapped in some sort of thing.
I don't know what's in the box yet."
And then the guy goes, "Oh, oh, oh, sorry.
You didn't get the prize."
And then he takes the box away from the dude and walks away.
What?
What is that even?
That's your plan?
It was.
This is weird.
This is spooky.
He takes the box.
He gives the box to the suspect, immediately takes it back.
And then this guy, with the box now, takes it to a forensic investigator or just a guy
with some baby powder and a magnifying glass.
I don't know.
The goal was to hand it to the dude, get his fingerprints, immediately take it back,
and then match those fingerprints to known fingerprints of the Zodiac killer.
That's not a bad plan, other than the fact nobody likes getting presents taken away from
them.
Alright, that's kind of messed up.
Alright, it totally, aw, I didn't win anything.
That sucks.
I don't know if I'd wish that on anyone other than the Zodiac killer.
But here's the weird thing.
The hand in the box, he takes the box back, they take it to the lab, they check it out.
No fingerprints.
Now, the dude wasn't wearing gloves, right?
That would be a dumb plan.
He handed it to a guy with gloves.
You're like, "This time it'll succeed."
The guy obviously wasn't wearing gloves, our suspect.
Touch the box, still no fingerprints.
Now, maybe you have to touch it a little bit longer, or maybe he had his fingerprints burned
off.
I guess there's a huge thing.
Could be anything in between there as well.
But, or maybe the guy just wasn't going to take his fingerprints, he didn't hold it
long enough.
Who knows?
But there are no fingerprints on that.
So he tried that, that didn't work.
I think that's kind of miserable to give someone something and then take it back.
But then, because Tom Hanson is not one to give up, he finds out where this guy works.
So he works at Bank of America.
And he calls up Bank of America and goes, "Hey, can I get the personnel file of one of your
employees?"
And the manager goes, "No.
We don't know who you are.
I'll open an account.
I'll open one of your SuperSaver accounts."
And the manager's like, "Tell me more."
But no, the manager goes, "No, we will not give you access to this employee's files."
And then the manager asks the question, which I think he would ask.
I don't know if Tom Hanson called him up from the Kentucky Fried Chicken he was managing.
You hear a chicken grilling in the background, chickens getting chased around the kitchen.
I think he had one of the private investigators call him up.
But anyways, the private investigator calls up the bank, asks for this guy's personnel
file.
They tell him, "No, but what do you want it for?"
And they said, "We think he's the Zodiac killer."
So that guy got fired from his job.
That guy straight up got doxxed and fired from his job.
And then pretty much just disappeared.
Which would make sense if people were calling up your workplace and telling them you were
the Zodiac killer.
Most estimates are now that whoever the Zodiac killer is, he's long dead.
Some people say it was some dude's dad, like this guy's written a book saying, "My dad,
the Zodiac killer."
I was always a little confused because my dad didn't teach me anything about the planets.
He'd only talk about the constellations all the time.
And before I learned my ABCs, I learned to write in rones.
I was like, "Hmm, my dad might be a serial killer."
He has extra Snickers.
In 1986, he got extra candy from a little boy.
And then I've heard that, you know, like he, that he died back in like the 60s or 70s,
or he was arrested and thrown in prison for something else.
There's always these interesting things.
Jeffrey Dahmer, there's always been a theory that Jeffrey Dahmer may have killed that little
Adam Walsh.
There was, that was a big case when I was a little kid.
I remember that was the first year I was like, "Oh, great.
I'm not going to be able to play in where the Red Ferns grow anymore."
There was that young boy.
It's a horrible story.
Adam Walsh was kidnapped from like a local strip mall.
This is all off memory, so.
But Adam Walsh was kidnapped from a local strip mall, and then they found his head in
a swamp, or they found his body and not his head.
It was one or the other.
It's grisly either way, and then you may know the name Walsh, his dad.
I don't remember his dad's full name, but he was the one who started America's Most
Wanted.
He had started all these child protection groups after his son had died.
So it was a super high profile case, especially when I was a kid.
They made that movie, "Where's Adam?"
Like, I was six, man.
I was, I don't think I was six when the crime actually took place, but I remember being a
little kid in the 80s, and it'd be like, "ABC tonight.
Adam!
A nation in the grip of terror.
Where's Adam?
I don't know.
You tell me where he's at."
And then they'd see scenes of cops walking through a swamp tonight on ABC.
I was terrified, man.
Some spooky stuff to see as a kid.
Spooky.
And I remember, though, that was when I remember that movie, "Where's Adam?"
And I thought, "Oh, this isn't good."
Like, obviously, it scared me to feel bad for the kid.
I also remember, though, that there is a sea change coming as far as, like, what we could
do as kids.
I wasn't a dummy.
I wasn't the smartest kid on the planet.
But I wasn't a dummy either.
Like, I could sense social changes, I think, even back then.
I knew I was like, "Hmm.
I don't have a lot of memories as a kid, but for some weird reason I remember that.
I remember watching commercials for that movie and being like, "Oh, this is why we can't
go out anymore because ABC made a movie of the week."
Horrible story.
Major, it was a national crime, it was one of the first big missing kid things.
One of the first big national missing kid things.
And now there is a theory that that was Jeffrey Dahmer who did that because he lived in, he
was in the area at the time.
But I don't know where I was going with that.
I think now I'm just saying basically serial killer true crime trivia without being trivial,
just kind of weird elements in it.
I do want to end the episode with this, though.
I think it's fascinating.
We used to, I'll say it, we used to glorify serial killers.
You'd be books and movies based on these people.
How many movies about Ted Bundy?
Again, super boring serial killer.
I'm going to make a prediction.
I think they're holding off on it because on the one hand they say they don't want to
glorify it, but I think they're just waiting for the right moment.
I think we've moved past glorifying serial killers and I think we're moving closer to
glorifying mass shooters.
I think we already do that.
I think there's already parts of society that do do that.
I think you're actually going to start seeing movies and books based on mass shooters.
Now I know you have had Columbine.
You know movies based on Columbine, like Elephant.
You've had movies that are like slightly based on the events.
I think you're going to start seeing more of that.
I think the kids who grew up with that as they start to control the mechanisms of culture.
When my people were in charge, my age range was in charge.
We had Transformers movies.
We had movies, G.I. Joe movies and stuff like that.
We're still running the things.
That's why all these Marvel movies are so huge.
We're the controllers of the mechanism.
Just a generation or two ago, remember you had the Flintstones and the Adams Family movies?
You had this whole retro-bingion and they appealed to everybody, but when the generation
is in power, they go, "Hey, remember those times?"
I think we're going to get to a point where they're making live-action Ed Edd and Eddie
movies and a live-action Ren and Stimpy movie.
And the kids who grew up with Are You Afraid of the Dark and all this stuff, they're going
to want to tell more stories about these mass shooters.
The people who were watching Virginia Tech and it really affected them.
By the time it was happening, when it happened, I was older and I go, "Well, that's a tragic
thing.
It didn't affect my psyche."
Columbine did slightly because my younger brother was in high school at the time and
it was just this bizarre thing.
But I've never had a massive fascination with Columbine itself.
But I think you're going to see that.
I think you're going to start seeing more movies, more books and everything like that.
I think there's less of a mystique because they get caught right away.
They usually die right away.
But for some people, that adds to the mystique.
So we'll see.
We'll see if culture starts to move away from these Netflix movies where Zac Efron
is playing Ted Bundy and we start to see movies with Keenan and Kel shooting up a nightclub
or something like that.
Like, I think, I know that's a flippant joke, but it's actually not a joke.
I think we're moving in that direction.
I think we'll see that.
My thing I'm curious about is we've moved past serial killish in the most part, they're
kind of lame.
Now we're going to be, I believe we're moving into an era of the mass shooters being celebrated.
Dorner, that guy.
You got a whole bunch of them.
A whole bunch of hits you can unfortunately choose from.
I wonder what the net, let's prognosticate 50 years in the future.
What's the next big crime that's going to capture the imagination of humans?
What's next?
What else is coming down the pipe?
Because in the 1910s, you never would have thought you would have a bunch of serial killers
running around from the 60s to the 80s and to the early 90s.
You don't have many nowadays.
When you were in the 60s, 70s, 80s, you would never think, even though schools were getting
shot up all the time in poor neighborhoods, in black neighborhoods, school shootings were
quite common.
You would have never thought in the 80s that schools would be war zones and colleges and
nightclubs and things like that would get shot up.
So now we're here today.
What is going to be the next big crime wave that's just going to shock the nation that's
going to keep happening over and over and over again?
Who knows?
All we can guarantee is that someone will make a movie about it.
(upbeat music)