A man hunts for a monster only he believes in.
And then today is the day. I know I always say this, but the most requested topic, just wait
till I read the list of names of people who have requested this story, is from the Conspiracy
Iceberg, and it may change the way you think about history, because now we are going to tackle
the Great Mud Flood today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. I hope you are having a great day too. I'm always happy when I
start recording again, because you know I go maybe two days without recording and some days I
bulk record episodes when I have a lot of free time, but it's always nice to come back. It's always
nice to get back on the mic and I'm having a lot of fun and I hope you guys are still having a lot
of fun listening to the show as well. So this first story is actually a recommendation. I got it.
This was in my email and this was sent by Moss X. Mos X, one of the two, but I appreciate this story.
So he goes, "Hey, here's a story idea for you. Honey Island Swamp Monster. Probably never heard
of it before." And it was funny because he also said that it's... the way that I read sometimes,
especially when I'm reading emails and stuff like that, before I respond I have to read it again.
When I'm initially reading it, my eyes kind of scan it real quickly. So I see the title,
"Honey Island Swamp Monster," and then I see the word "smell." So I was like, "A monster that smells
like honey? I'm in!" But then I realized that it was just a smelling monster, but it was still
intriguing, although I would have enjoyed the sweet smelling monster. I wonder if any cryptids do
smell good out there. I wonder if there's a cryptid that smells like sweet, sweet flowers.
Ghosts do, so I don't see why cryptids wouldn't. Anyways, so we're going to Louisiana.
And a little bit out of New Orleans, a little couple miles away from New Orleans,
there is the Honey Island Swamp. Walking through the swamp.
The... we're walking through the swamp. We got those rubber pants on so we won't get wet,
but I made sure that yours were just a little too short so they immediately get fled with water
and you sink up it, and then I have a good chuckle. And while you're dealing with horrible
diseases you catch from the swamp, we also go back in time. We're going back to the year, 1974.
And in 1974, too many merged from the swamp. Harlan Ford and Billy Maze. No, sorry, Harlan Ford
and Billy Mills. They come out of the swamp with a plaster cast of a footprint and they like throw
it down on the ground and go "proof!" Now there wasn't anyone around when they did that, so then
they had to pick it up and actually go into town and then they take it into a bar and go "proof!"
People are like "proof of what?" So Harlan Ford and Billy Mills had said that they had once seen
a creature in Honey Island Swamp. They described it as seven foot tall, gray haired creature.
They estimated it would weigh about 400 pounds. Giant monster man. So, and it had yellow or red
glowing eyes and the difference in the eye color could be chalked up to either what time of day
they saw it in or how bloodshot their own eyes were when they were out hunting. Glug glug. But
anyways, they come into town with this plaster cast and people are thinking "well that kind of
sounds like a big foot Harlan" and he's like "yeah but this one's different because look at this
plaster cast and it looks like it had webbed toes." And you can see photos of these. They basically
looks like it has four toes once kind of folded in or something weird. The toes are webbed. It's
not like a primates footprint. And the thing is in 1963 these guys came out of Honey Island Swamp.
They're like "this is what we just saw. We were walking through the swamp. We saw a boar with its
throat ripped out and a giant monster and we went to shoot it and the monster ran away."
Nobody believed them. People are like "that's... you're making that up. You're making that up."
So about nine years later, more like 11 years later, they find this... they find a footprint
they go and they pour the plaster in there and bring it back. People are like here they go "here's
proof. There's proof that there is this monster running around." Nobody believes them. And it's
one of those weird things that a lot of communities really like to have like bigfoot sightings and
stuff like that because you can sell chotchkies and things like that. But this would not take off.
This would not take off. Harlan dedicated his life to finding proof of the Honey Island Swamp
monster. He was out there consistently after these two sightings and he did bring back other
plaster casts. But for whatever reason, the people in the town took it as a myth. They weren't really
embracing it. Even today you have tour guides and they say the swamp... the swamp is really like
beautiful. It's very untouched. You go there to visit. It's just a great place. It's a great
recreational place and they have boat tours. You can take boat tours through the area. I was reading
this article one guy did. He said "hey I'm gonna go on this boat tour. Check it out." He talks to
the two tour operators and they're like "there's no a Honey Island Swamp monster." And it's funny
because these people could actually make more money by saying that there was. But they're like
it doesn't exist. It absolutely doesn't exist. There are boat tours you can take where it's
called the Honey Island Swamp Monster boat tour. But it was funny in the article where the guy was
taking the boat tour. He saw that boat still docked. No one was on it. Because people just want to go
and enjoy nature. Even in that area people aren't like "this creature exists you know oh no I ran
into it when me and my uncle were out playing baseball one day and the baseball fell in the swamp."
They don't buy it. Which is odd but I might just be because the only people who have ever seen it
are the two people who first saw it and then the people who started bringing back
plaster casts. Harlan Ford was dedicated to finding the proof of this thing. So much so
that for the next six years he was constantly looking for it. Why only six years? Because he
died in 1980 without ever having any proof, conclusive proof that what he saw standing over
that bore and what was leaving those footprints was real. And it would be a footnote. No pun intended.
It would be a footnote in cryptid history about the Honey Island Swamp Monster. It would just be
a funny name for a creature that the locals don't believe. That they almost actively dismiss.
Just like when people go to towns and start asking for the Blair Witch they're like "Blair
Witch isn't real you know it's fake right?" Now like I was saying this would be a footnote in
cryptid history but the main proponent of it is dead. I don't know what had ever happened to
Billy Mays. He's a footnote within a footnote. It was he passed away there was never any proof.
People assumed it was a hoax and it might have been. But a hoax that has become cemented in the
minds of millions of girls everywhere. Monster High dolls are a line of dolls of monster girls
that are attending a school called Monster High. So you have Frankie Stein and you have like a
Dracula Chick and a Wolf Girl and Laguna Beach or whatever. They're all the daughters of famous
monsters and somehow all these famous monsters now are also attending Monster High with Honey
Swamp. The daughter of the Honey Island Swamp Monster. She's not a bigfoot she is like a sea
creature thing so she get rid of all that fur. No girl wants to be covered in fur be seven feet
tall or four hundred pounds some of them might want to be seven feet tall but she's just like a
a creature from the Black Lagoon type creature. She's 115 years and monster years according to
her bio which is how I'm going to start describing my age. And so here's her bio let's learn a little
bit about Honey Swamp since we don't know much about her father. I'm a proper southern ghoul
from the swamps of Honey Island. My mama always taught me if you work hard and follow your screams
you can be anything you want to be. Well I want to be a world famous cinema togherfer
in Hauntleywood. Now I do know how to pronounce the word cinematographer but the dashes here make
me think they're trying to emphasize ogre cinema to ogrefer because you know she's a monster.
She's also friends with Claudia Wolfe and Vipereen Gorgon if you want to complete your
collection so he did get that legacy at least. So Harlan if you're up there and you're watching down
I hope you're happy with the fact that millions of girls around the world are now playing with dolls
named after your hoax so it wasn't a waste of time. Who would have thought that when you and your
buddy one drunken evening decided to go out and start pouring plaster into footprints you made
and that hoax turned into a worldwide phenomenon if you play with monster high dolls otherwise
you still don't know about this creature but good job Harlan you created a hoax and it became a doll
and I don't honestly I don't think anyone else can claim that. A lot of hoaxes out there but not
all of them attend monster high. So let's go ahead and move on to our next story. Now I know that
a lot of times when I do these iceberg topics I go this is the most requested topic we've had
because at the time they were but there was one that was constantly gaining people saying hey
when are you going to do this story? When are you going to do this story? And it's time. The reason
why it took so long these stories are much more time intensive to research. A lot of times people
go do more iceberg conspiracy stuff and I do like Kentucky Meat Storm was iceberg conspiracy but
the stuff that I really like the deep conspiracies I really have to get into they take a while. I
enjoy researching these ones I really enjoy researching them because I'm kind of trying to unravel
a puzzle you can just take a while because they keep running into roadblocks and go now I'm back
to square one. On YouTube this was requested by Bint Fox by Red Baron. On email there was Matthew T
Jimmy M and on Twitter I had Harrison. All of these people requested mudflud.
Now you go mudflud what is mudflud?
The year is 2019. The place wherever you're at right now it may just seem like a normal day
but you remember in the back of your mind you remember when you were in school learning about
this day it was the day after humanity decided to start building out of the mud. This was the day
when humanity said the mudflud would no longer hold us back. You remember learning in school about
the great excavations of Europe how they had to dig cities out of tons of mud that came rushing
down from the mountains. You also remember hearing stories about the American frontier where the mud
just smashed into buildings burying them up to a floor deep until humanity decided to take back
the land. And you think you reflect back on that day that you learned about all those years ago in
school what an amazing feat of human engineering that we were able to clear out that much dirt
and regain control of this planet. But that 2019 that place where you are that existed an
alternate timeline because in this timeline not only did the mud stay but the powers that be
covered the entire thing up. The great mudflud is a very very interesting conspiracy theory and for
this one I'd been working on it for quite a while. I actually reached out to a friend of mine,
Mitcham. I was like I do not know what to make of this. There has to be a rational explanation.
This one I was completely stuck in and none of these are mud puns. None of this stuff like digging
out of a hole or getting stuck and stuff like that. None of these are mud puns. I remember
reaching out to my friend Mitcham and I sent him some stuff and I said I don't know what to make
of this. I do not know what to make of this. This is I go it has to be fake. It has to be.
This is what the great mudflud is. This is the theory. In the 1860s to 1870s a massive wave of mud
covered the earth and buried most of our cities up to 812 feet in mud. And you think well that's
stupid. That's obviously not true. The evidence for it is videos and photos of buildings all over
the world buried up to the first floor in mud. So you will see buildings that have a window
like you can see the top of a window sticking out of the cement. Like you can see where the ground
is and then you see on the building there is definitely the shape of where a window would have
been that's been bricked up and now the street is level to that window. You'll see pictures of
what appear to be formally first floors of buildings that are now basements,
odd doors that you have to walk downstairs to get into the front door. You'll see photos of
excavations where they were doing road work and you'll find see a building that has an again an
entire first floor with entrance doors and windows so they weren't originally basements.
They're excavating this you'll see a front door and windows underneath the ground.
And I'm looking at these things and I'm thinking okay these photos are real. There's actually a
building that I know of that has the window sticking out of the ground corner. So these
build these photos are real. These photos are not photoshopped and I'm looking at them and I'm
watching these videos and I'm thinking yes that evidence is real. Those buildings are
farther underground than they should be. A front door should not be underground. But the idea that
a mud flood covered the planet and buried all of these buildings I was thinking that's not true.
Now see here's the thing the theory there's more to the theory so not only did the mud flood come
over but it was covered up to hide. It was basically used as a hard reset on humanity because there
was a super advanced civilization that was so wonderful and at peace and they had all these
amazing pieces of technology and this free energy and these super weapons even though they were
peaceful and it was like this multicultural multi religious society that existed before 1860s
and the mud flood came. Super technology didn't help them stop that and at that time the powers
that be whoever whatever boogie man you want it to be said we're going to wipe them off the map
and we're going to say they never existed and we're going to use this mud to basically bury
everything that's proof of them and do like a hard reset on the history of the world. So I can buy
like it was so basically I'm working against two conspiracy theories. One the the civilization the
super advanced civilization that's been wiped off the map and two a history reset due to the mud
flood and then three just the the geographical features itself. Now alternate history is easy to
kind of look into but I'm looking at these photos and watching these videos and I'm thinking this
I cannot figure this out but that was the main piece I really needed to tackle and that's why
this took so long. I talked to Mitchum and I said I sent him this stuff and I go this is killing me
this is killing me. There has to be a rational explanation for this and and he actually pointed
me in the right path on the mud flood thing which is really interesting. Now what I'm about to go into
you could say I'm going to present this and you could say well that's not the case in this city
and that's not the case in this city but I think it's close enough and I have enough proof for enough
cities that it applies to most of them. There were massive rain floods in the 1860s around the world
there was this huge rainstorms storm system set of storm systems all sorts of stuff and there's
geographical and historical records of these massive rainstorms that caused flooding everywhere
almost all over the planet and when we look at these buildings that have been covered up by the
mud this episode is probably going to run a little long but this I mean I kind of got to get through
all this stuff when we look at the buildings that have been covered up in the mud they were built
pre 1860s it's not like houses that were built in the 1970s are a foot deep all of the buildings that
have this mud problem or basically the street level is where their second story would be
are all built before the 1860s this was the thing of Mitchum turned me on to he said
I do remember reading something a long time ago about Napoleon trying to clean up the cities of
France they needed brand new infrastructure in these cities and they didn't know how to do it
it might be related to that and I started looking into that and Napoleon did go about these huge
projects because they were having issues with flooding they were having issues with cholera
they were having issues stuff like that but I could never find anything that actually said so they
did x and then I found an article on wikipedia about the raising of Chicago now this was this was
really the key to unlocking the mud flood thing because once I kind of queued into this I realized
that other than the raising of Chicago this is such a mundane answer for such a bizarre conspiracy
that it's hard to find because it's such a people were like yeah why are you googling that why are
you researching that it doesn't really make sense because we're just a small town that was built
prior to 1860 we didn't really care about that 1860 this they were having problems with flooding
and all over the world we are having these huge population explosions in cities and when you
have huge population explosions in cities no longer can you just use mid 1800 sewage technology
so Chicago says you know what we need sewers that are enough to to basically hold the sewage of
millions of people but we can't dig deep enough into the earth to put all this stuff in however
we can lift all of our buildings up put in our sewer system cover that and then we don't have
to worry about floods either and there was a ton of documentation on the raising of Chicago
entire buildings entire giant buildings were lifted and some of them were even moved and then
the ground was filled in and then they were lowered back again it was this huge effort on
behalf of the city to do this but they needed to do it because they needed to get these sewage
systems up to speed so in Chattanooga uh Chattanooga Tennessee they also oh in the race in Chicago
1860s is when that happened the uh in Chattanooga Tennessee they were like we know that they did
something like this in Chicago but we don't want to do that we are having a serious trouble
with flooding and sewage so we are going to fill in the streets we're just going to fill them in
with dirt we're going to bring all this dirt in and this was the thing it was and I think this was
a component with a lot of these other cities and that's why there's not a ton of records on this
stuff it was per building it was your job as a building owner to raise your street level because
otherwise in Chattanooga they were having serious trouble with flooding they could not control the
flooding in the area so they said floods caused disease we're having cholera outbreaks it's
go there were buildings that were never dry you'd go into the first floor it was always wet and
musty because of the floods they said we have to raise the city by a couple feet by eight to 10 feet
however it's per building so as a building owner it is your responsibility to do that
and you would have to do that because if everyone on your block had their building raised and you
didn't raise your dirt level by eight feet it's going to be you're going to be soaping wet all
the rainwater is going to go in there and it happens over the course of years where people
are just filling in dirt now I typed in like or this is what I was googling like origin of the
russian sewer system origin of the parachutist system when were the sewers built in this city or
that city in that information is so fairly mundane I'm not able to pull up anything like that I just
had to find these scraps oh Chattanooga also that project took place in the 1860s so the timeline
does match up at some point in the 1860s all these countries said we're having these population
growth and we're having these huge cholera outbreaks we're having these huge disease outbreaks
we just had these massive rainstorms all over the planet we just need to make our city a little
bit higher and we could do the raising of chicago thing or we can just bring in dirt and sacrifice
the first floor of all these buildings now the mud flood community they have their answers for this
stuff I was reading one site and they're like yeah we don't think the raising of chicago actually
happened we think that was a cover-up that's an easy thing to that's an easy route to get lost down
I don't think that that's fair to say when someone says well actually here's an explanation for why
these buildings are all around the same time covered in dirt it's because we have these massive
rainstorms in the area or around the globe and it made sense other cities were doing it and then
for people to just go out there's just part of the cover-up you can't really debate that but to me
and with Mitchum's help I had found a way to answer because those mud flood pictures were
really freaking me out dude those mud flood pictures I'm thinking like what is going on
there's tons of them this conspiracy theory actually tends to be mostly on YouTube because
it's such a visual conspiracy theory if I just told you in 1860s mud came from everywhere and
buried the planet you'd be like what that's not true but after watching an hour of video footage
and photographs of these things you're thinking mud must have buried the planet until I and I never
couldn't I mean I could imagine believing that but at a certain point in the back of my head I
always knew my voice is going hoarse from doing this episode I always knew that there had to be
rational explanation for this there had to be but we're not done and I was thinking okay we got it
that's we're good on that now I have to tackle their other issue about this lost civilization
thing because if I just do the mud flood part and leave that part hanging then I've only really
looked into half of it and that's where it took me a bit longer this episode was supposed to come
out maybe two weeks ago and then I had to look into all this stuff the mysterious civilization
that they talk about that was wiped off the map I'm probably going to mispronounce it but
it's called Tataari T-A-R-T-A-R-Y and I was reading in these mud flood blog posts and they're like
yes Tataari was this multicultural any religion you wanted to milk and honey rivers advanced
technology better than us humans this massive nation and we didn't like them so we wiped them
out blah blah blah and every time I'm reading that I'm dismissing it as more more nonsense because
I'm looking into this mud stuff I'm looking at that and as I was getting ready to release this
episode a while back I typed in Tataari and I was like okay well I need to figure out more about
this just as like a footnote god damn it if I didn't find 50 maps of the world from pre 1860
that say grand Tataari on them and I was like okay episodes postponed I gotta look into this now
map after map after map these ancient maps that have from halfway into China's borders
all the way to basically Moscow they just say grand Tataari on them now this gets weird so
grand Tataari is this idea that before the 1860s again before the 1860s people in Europe
referred to anything east basically east of Moscow as Tatar it was kind of this catchall term for
what was out there for the people that were out there and it was just like this thing and then
after 1860s Russia it's all just kind of was called Russia now at first I'm thinking well that's
kind of like how Persia exists and then like the 1930s Iran says we'd prefer to be called Iran we're
not Persia anymore and everyone goes okay no we don't care we'll call you Iran because people in
the area called themselves Iranians and Iran or some variation of that they're like we don't go by
Persia anymore okay same thing orient that's a term that's fallen out of disuse so we do have
places on maps that are fallout of disuse Tataari was basically considered a wild region full of
Mongolians and a lot of Muslims it was mostly Muslim country out there and that's a thing that
the conspiracy theory dismisses they're like no no no they weren't Muslim it was this multicultural
great place that you could do anything you wanted with this advanced technology but it wasn't just
Muslims but back then it was considered basically a Muslim stronghold we have drawings of their
uniforms of their troops sometimes they're described as militia members sometimes they're
described as an acting army we have impressions of what their flags look like there was a little
article and this was on a mudflat website but they had a scan of a little article saying there was
an opera currently being performed in six languages and it was like English Russian French Tataari
I'm like what the hell is this and all this terminology for this area and for this region
of people stopped being used in the 1860s just immediately fell out of vogue and I'm thinking
as I'm reading this I'm constantly thinking of the Persian Iranian example where people who live
in Iran that area is now called Iran so you have maps for John or the orient example as well you no
longer have maps to say the orient and it's like the entire region now you have China and South
Green stuff like that so it doesn't mean that the empire of the orients were wiped off the map and
it was all hidden history and stuff like that at all it just means that maps have been redrawn but
when I look at stuff like the flag and the uniforms I'm thinking what was out there what was out there
but I don't think and I'm thinking and I'm like I don't think there was some grand empire wiped off
the map but I have to keep looking I'm thinking there was no great I just I was like it was weird
because I it was almost like cognitive dissonance like I'm thinking this can't be real the mud
fled thing I'd already put to rest I'd already found it's to me sufficient answers of why buildings
looked like that but now for me to have to look into a civilization that I've never heard of that
used to take up one one half of Europe that was gone now I'm thinking it's just like the orient
it's not an issue and then I found this and to be fair I did find it on a mud flood website but
they have the link to the actual CIA document and I checked out it as well back in 1957 there was a
CIA document written it was talking about the way that the Russians were treating the Muslims
in the area how they basically at first said you guys are all welcome here you're going to welcome
be here but how this at the point in 1957 the Soviet Union but how they were saying how they were
actually subjugating the Muslim populations of the Soviet Union altogether and this is a document
from written in 1957 from a CIA operative or researcher however you want to put it
or let us take the matter of history which along with religion language and literature
constitute the core of a people's cultural heritage here again the communists have interfered in a
shameless matter for example on 9 august 1944 the central committee of the communist party
sitting in Moscow issued a directive ordering the party's tartare provincial committee to
proceed to a scientific revision of the history of tartarsia to liquidate serious shortcomings and
mistakes of a nationalistic character committed by individual writers and historians in dealing with
tartar history in other words tartar history was to be rewritten let us be frank was to be falsified
in order to eliminate reference to great russian aggressions and to hide the facts of the real
course of tartar russian relations and this was no isolated case in every muslim area within the
ussr historians on orders of the communist party have rewritten history to distort the facts so
that the russians appear always in a good light needless to say histories which present the facts
truthfully have been withdrawn and destroyed so that the present and future generation of muslims
are forever denied the chance of learning the true facts of their nations past
i don't think that the great mud flood happened i think that there would be way too much evidence
of that all over the world and there really isn't the evidence can easily be explained away by them
having to redo the systems i think the idea that tartar or tartaria was a advanced civilization with
way cool super epic mechs and like this awesome magic and this free energy and stuff like that and
they're multicultural and blah all these buzzwords i think it's absolute trash i don't believe that
at all but the idea that there was a nation within the past hundred years that was basically wiped
off the planet and then actively suppressed to the point where the cia is talking about it in
1957 i mean it could have been an alliance of city states type of thing so it they did have
like flags and stuff like that in uniforms but it was never a great world power i'm sure there are a
lot of countries and regions that have changed names over the years like the examples that i've
previously given but something about it still that the the tartar part something about it still just
doesn't sit right with me when i read when i was reading initially sites were like sites that were
debunking it was like oh it's just this term that the western europeans made up because the place it
sounds like a scary name it reminds them of greek mythology and and hell and so it was just some
name they threw out there because it sounded spooky and they didn't know what was out there that was
the dismissive part the people who believe that it was this great civilization they stole the virtues
of this giant empire that used to exist to the point that napoleon and the czar had to team up
to destroy them but it's weird because even the debunking stuff doesn't admit what the what the
cia document does that these people did exist at some point and that the soviet union made a
concentrated effort to remove them to change their history to rewrite it the thing that trips me out
most about the grand tata re tatar empire however you want to call it is that i'm this is episode
what like 183 184 i've debunked a lot of stuff and there's a lot of iceberg conspiracy theories
where i say i don't think this is true but this is what i think the theory is let's just put on our
little imagination caps and run with it but this one not the mudflat again that part's ridiculous
but the idea that there was a nation that was wiped off the planet and out of the history books
and if i if you ask me right now dismissing the mudflat i think that's been thoroughly debunked
but if you asked me right now jason do you believe that there used to be a nation in europe
called to tar with its own culture people uniforms flags language that covered most of the continent
and was wiped off the map and out of the history books since 1860 jason do you believe that conspiracy
theory i have to honestly answer with i don't know dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be
your email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is at
jason o carpenter dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
you don't have to listen to it every day but i'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys