A railway company wanting to have a little promotion
decide to crash two trains into each other with predictable results.
And then because I never learned my lesson, we take a look at another cult.
This cult focuses not on the mind, but on the body.
How far can you push yourself to please your master today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
"I'm a walk big gal"
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. It's almost Thanksgiving and I'm
still on my quest for some Thanksgiving-based conspiracies. Found a little bit. Little bit.
We'll see. We'll see. Some of them, you know, I'm not going to give it away. And this time I
remember to record the Thanksgiving episode the day before Thanksgiving. So you can listen to it
during Thanksgiving or before Thanksgiving and you can tell your friends and family,
please tell your friends and family, that you're listening to the podcast Dead Rabbit Radio and
it's full of all this amazing information and you can regale them with your stories.
I will say this next part with the caveat, if you are a hypochondriac, skip ahead five minutes
because this is insane. I stumbled across this article. This wasn't part of the episode originally.
I was just kind of, I'm constantly reading the news, just the regular news. I'll go to weird news
sites when I'm looking for weird news, but you find a lot of bizarre stuff just, you know,
I'm on Drudge Report and I'm like, oh, Trump's doing this and this is going on in Bolivia and
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, and then I stumble across these weird articles. So last Thanksgiving,
I guess this is kind of Thanksgiving-based conspiracy. Last Thanksgiving, this guy,
this dad, was helping make the Thanksgiving feast. He had a runny nose and he actually ruined the feast
because his nose, his snot was dripping into the food. Now, I can understand that happening
once. Like, you know, it drips into the mashed potatoes and everyone's like, oh, gross, dude.
You know, you got snot in the mashed potatoes and being like, uh-oh, spaghetti. Oh, like, I can get
that happening once, but he ruined the whole meal. It's almost like a "Fairly Brothers" film. Like,
he's just moving around from dish to dish, being like, I'll stand over here by the turkey and they're
like, no, dad, no. And it's like drip, drip. So despite it not being a "Fairly Brother" movie,
it was real and his nose dripped all over the food. And you're thinking, oh, okay, that's gross,
Jason. That's not really bizarre. The nose drip wouldn't go away. He would stick tissue up his nose
to kind of block it from dripping out. It was just like this embarrassing thing he was dealing with.
He said it was very embarrassing. The doctors couldn't figure it out. He finally went to another
doctor and the doctors run and test because that's weird. Shouldn't have lasted this long. Like,
people have seasonal allergies, but their nose doesn't drip all the time. Let me run some tests.
They tested it. It was brain fluid dripping out of his nose. His nose, his, basically, they had a leak.
So they repaired his brain. They put a little flap. They took a little flap off of him somewhere,
a little flap of skin. They went in there and they just covered it up. And I'm like, okay,
that's cool. The last sentence of the article says, "Dr. Ilorta," Dr. I-- oh, sorry, Dr. Ilorretta,
I think, said to watch out if you have a runny nose on one side of your nostril. If there's a salty
taste associated with it and all that comes with an intense headache, it could be more than a runny nose.
What? What snot doesn't taste salty? Like, I haven't tasted my own snot in decades. I can't imagine
that. I'm trying to remember the last time I actually, like, got it in my mouth. But if I-- if
someone had to say, "Hey, man, what does boogers taste like?" I'd be like, "Oh, I think they're salty."
Memory serves me right from being eight. So they're basically saying if your nose is running and it
tastes like salt-- and I'm wondering how many hyperchondriacs read this article or will listen
to this podcast and then immediately start looking, testing their snot every once in a while to make
sure it's not brain fluid. Because it being like salt should just be a given. And then, you know,
the intense headaches, it was probably the biggest factor to it. But anyway, so yes, if you have a
runny nose and it tastes like salt, like all runny noses do, your brain may be leaking. Hopefully,
maybe someone's listening to this and they've had a runny nose for years and they're like,
"Oh my god, thank you." That happened to me once. I remember once-- I remember once I was talking
to someone in the break room at a job that I had. I had this story super vague, but-- and they were
explaining some sort of problem their husband had medically. And I remember going, "Oh, you know what?
It might be this. I read an article on this before. It sounds kind of similar." And she's like, "Oh,
you know." And I ran into her. She caught up to me like maybe two or three weeks later and she's
like, "Dude, you saved my husband's life." Like, he was actually having some really serious problems
in that article you just happened to read and readers died just four years earlier. Like,
that's exactly what he had. I don't remember what the illness was. Maybe this story is not
just for hyperconjurax. Maybe someone out there is suffering from brain leakage. Let's go ahead and
get started with the first story here. That didn't count. That was just kind of a throwaway story.
Not a throwaway story, but that was just kind of a starter story. Now we're going to move on to
another starter story. So this one is the story of Crush, Texas. Now Crush, Texas is a city in
Texas called Crush, or it was a city in Texas called Crush. It was a city that only existed for one day.
So in 1896, there was a guy named William George Crush. And he worked for the Missouri, Kansas,
Texas railroad. And they called it the "Katy" for short. So the Katy railroad, and he said, "You know
what? There's a couple other companies that have done this. Let's do this promotional thing. We're
going to take two trains that were in there, not in service anymore. We're going to take two locomotives,
and we're going to crash them into a... They didn't have television back then. So this was a good
idea. They're going to crash them into each other and we'll use it as promotion for a railroad."
So what it was was they said for anywhere in Texas, it only cost you two dollars to take the
train to Crush. Again, two dollars back then was the equivalent to like twenty dollars now,
but it was still a good deal. So they were able to show off their railway. It was going to be this
big promotional thing. And the Katy railroad said, "That's a great idea. Other people have done it.
It's been totally fine." They got the engines. They took six box cars and put it on each locomotive.
They chained them together so the cars wouldn't buckle. Buckle off. Go flying on. And they said,
"Okay, well, you know, we're not using these locomotives anymore. We have these big boilers
in them that power the locomotives. Is there any chance these are going to rupture?" And they're
like, "No, no, no. These are designed to be rupture proof." So I think you know where this story is
going. Because William Crush came up with the name, that's why they decided to call the town Crush.
It was... The town was basically set up where the two trains would collide. And it didn't have...
They didn't like build buildings like... They didn't build like a whorehouse and a saloon and
stuff like that. It was just people came out in big tents and it turned into a huge event. Like,
you had carnival rides. You had events, which is what I have written down in my notes. So just
fill in the blank what events are going on. There's events. And as much people showed up. And when I
say a bunch of people, 40,000 people showed up. For this one day, Crush, Texas became the second
biggest city in Texas. Now, the trains are only going 45 miles an hour. So 40,000 people are there.
Of course, there is going to be a journalist there. And they took some notes of what was going on.
Two trains... I guess no one is blowing the whistle. Because no one is on the train. But anyways,
the two trains are coming at each other. The 40,000 people are standing around. Little kids
holding balloons. People playing events. The two trains collide. And then here we go with this is
a quote from one of the eyewitness accounts, the journalist. A crash, a sound of timbers,
rent and torn, and then a shower of splinters. So the wood on the train just... That wasn't all.
There was just this back to the quote here. There was just a swift instance of silence.
And then if controlled by a single impulse, both boilers exploded simultaneously and the air was
filled with flying missiles of iron and steel, varying in size from a postage stamp to half of
a driving wheel. So yeah, the boilers that were built to withstand rupture, both ruptured at the
same time. So the two trains... And they expected there to be splinters and stuff coming off. They
expected there to be some debris. And that was one of the things that people kept wanting to get
closer and closer to the tracks. And they had to have guards there to kind of like push them away.
But they didn't factor in. They basically built two giant IEDs. And they just... When the boilers
exploded at the same time in the two different trains, it basically vaporized the trains. Huge
chunks of metal, huge chunks of iron shot up into the sky, hundreds of feet into the sky,
and then began to land. And the crowd panics. Everyone's running. 40,000 people, all trying to
get as far away from this shower as possible. This is where it gets weird. So all of that stuff,
you kind of expect it to happen. Now we're going into Topsy-Turvy land because this really beat
the odds. This is a really bizarre story. So after all of the shrapnel came down, 40,000 people,
three people killed, six people injured, which is amazing. Which is an amazing act. That's a
miracle that people weren't just impaled. As people are laying there, some are dead,
six are wounded. The remaining people there, the remaining 39,993 people, roughly. Some go to assist
the wounded. Others start picking up pieces of metal and wood as souvenirs. So they just survived
this horrible event. And now they're just like, oh, look at half a driving wheel worth of steel.
I'm going to take this home. So you had people bleeding out and other people picking up souvenirs.
The railway company was like, okay, that was report, it was big news. It's supposed to be this big
promotional event. Back then, nine people dying was like 10% of the US population. There weren't
a lot of people back then. So nine people died. They're like, oh my God, flags at half mass.
This is terrible. The railroad company, the Katie Railroad Company fired William Crush.
They fired him. They said that was a terrible idea. You got these people killed. We're going to get
sued. We're going to lose so much money over this. You're fired. And then when the newspapers started
talking about it the next day, they're like, what a horrible accident. Who could have predicted this?
And there was no blowback on the Katie Railroad. So they hired William Crush back and he worked
there for another 60 years. It's funny nowadays people get fired from Chipotle for getting caught
on video saying we're not going to serve you guys. And this dude killed three people, wounded six more,
destroyed two trains, and then got hired back the next day. And they're like, don't worry about it.
We'll pay those people out. Don't worry about it. Katie actually benefited from the publicity. More
people knew of that rail line afterwards. So it actually worked out for them. And the weirdest
part of this whole story is trains kept doing crashes after this. They're like, ah, I guess people
go to NASCAR races and airplane shows and stuff like that and people blow up. But it's just weird
that it was just kind of, it was like, the world reacted to it as it was like a tragedy. There was
a lot of news articles on it, but then they're just like, oh, let's just keep doing it. Super
bizarre. That obviously, first off, nowadays they would never do the train crash without like 100
safety protocols in place. An environmental protection agency coming out and being like,
well, you know, if this train wheel goes off this way, it's going to roll over a frog. You
can't do that. And if it had, if it had these results, then everyone would get sued and everyone
would disappear. It's just crazy. But anyway, yeah, I thought it was a weird story. So let's go
ahead and move on to our next story. Now it doesn't involve brain juice and it doesn't involve train
crashes, but it involves something so horrific. Now podcast listeners, you're going to be spared
the photos, but the photos are going to be linked in the show notes. So you can go check them out.
You're going to have to just go off my description of what these photos are for now. And then if
you want to torture yourself later, click the links below. So let's get into it. There's a group of
guys in Seattle that are into bodybuilding. Now when I say bodybuilding, I'm not talking about
spending four hours in the gym, you know, trying to achieve the perfection of the human body,
or trying to beat your strength records, or, you know, working out with your buddy and trying to
one up each other. These guys are into the morphine of the human form into basically a caricature of
what a man should look like. These guys look like cartoon characters. They look like somebody drew
them. And I'm not saying there's I could be like, that guy looks like he was drawn by Todd McFarland.
I mean, like look at the chiseled chest. Look at those amazing calves. They don't look like that.
They look like a doodle. They're just these weird, they look weird. They have thin hips,
and kind of a thin waist and like a really big cartoony chest and balls the size of a cantaloupe.
So you go, okay, well, I know you can lift weights to get like a big chest. And you can do leg thing,
get big legs. What exercises do you do to get balls the size of a cantaloupe? There aren't any.
They started off by the all allegations, but they started off by injecting themselves with saline
into the balls. So to like, like swell up. Then eventually the saline, I guess leaks or leaks
on your Thanksgiving dinner. The saline is a temporary solution. So we have this group of guys
that are into body modification to look like big, big old cartoon characters. They look like Steven
Universe's dad. That's probably the best way I can describe it. If you've ever watched that show,
I watched it one season because I was with a girl who was into it, but it was okay.
You know, it was okay. But they look like Steven Universe's dad. They look like cartoon characters.
So what happened was last year, one of these guys says, you know what, the saline's not cutting it
for me. My balls, I want them to be huge. Let's get some silicone and inject them into my balls.
Get big old, big old permanent testicles. And so he ends up going to a black market silicone
injector, a young man known as Joe Quater. So Peter Dovac was the bodybuilder guy part of this group.
And Joe Quater was the guy who did the injections. In 2017, Peter Dovac gets his testicles inflated
with silicone. So they're the size of a coconut. And some of the silicone gets into his bloodstream,
gives him an embolism, dies. The guy who injected it, Joe Quater,
he was then going to be charged with manslaughter so he killed himself. Now there's probably about
like six or seven guys in this group. So then now we're in the year 2018, on October 15th,
Tank Hafertappen. Hafertappen is part of this group. And he goes, you know what,
I gotta get them the big testicles. I don't know where he goes. He went to another black
market silicone injector, injected with silicone, has an embolism, again, same thing, goes into a coma,
dies. And all these guys are younger than me. I think they're in their 20s or their 30s.
So this group of bodybuilders and big ball people is led by a guy known as Dylan Hafertappen.
Dylan Hafertappen. Or he also goes by the name noodles and beef. Noodles and beef. So it's funny,
the story I just told you, I was talking to one of my bosses at work. And I said, did you hear
about that cult up in Seattle, you know, the bodybuilders? And she's like, no. And I was like,
yeah, they, they do steroids apparently, or they work out all the time, but they're like,
look like cartoon characters. And she's like, really? I was like, yeah. And then like,
they get their balls and large of silicone and they're a couple of them had died. She's like,
really? I go, yeah, and the guy in charge is called noodles and beef. And she goes, you're making that
up. Like that's the part of the story she had a problem with noodles and beef. And to be fair,
that is the worst nickname you could ever pick. That is the most unappetizing, you get to pick
your own nickname. That's the one thing you get to do in life. Maybe other people give you a nickname,
but generally, I guess you don't get to pick your own nickname, but the you get to pick your online
alias. Let's put it that way, you kind of get to pick your avatar. Noodles and beef is what is in the
toilet after you throw up. That is the most unappetizing three words possibly put together.
Other than brain juice, Thanksgiving, noodles and beef is completely disgusting. But that's the name
this guy goes by. He was married to Tank. That's why Tank shared the last name. And he has these,
this group of guys, Tank was one of them, Peter was one of them, and a couple other ones, they all
are just really big guys. And they're his pups. Now, those are all the facts of the story. Now
we're going to get into the allegations. Tank's mom lives in Australia, and she got a call saying
her son had died. And she was besides herself. She couldn't believe that her son was in a coma,
that she didn't know, that she's like I would have flown out there to see him. They did a program
in Australia where they profiled the mother. And she's like, look at these pictures of my son growing
up. He looks like a normal person. Here are the photos of him after he went to Seattle and was
hanging out with Dylan. He looks grotesque. Like he just looks like this cartoon character. He's
super big. What did Dylan do to my son? What was going on here? She ends up saying, Dylan,
will you please bring me my son's ashes? And Dylan's like, yeah, of course. And she had a news crew
hiding in her house, like straight to catch a predator type of stuff. Dylan pulls up with his two
business associates. They didn't look like they were his pups. They walk into the house with
the ashes. And the mom sits down. I can't imagine a mother being brought her son's ashes. I can't
imagine, and she had like her mother there and a couple other relatives. But I can't imagine the
horror and the sadness that was going through her to have her son, like she saw her son, and now
he's she's seen a container of him. And Dylan immediately realizes there's cameras around.
He's like, what are these? And the woman's like, no, don't pay attention to those. Just sit down.
Let's talk. And the mother just rips him for a straight five minutes. What did you do to my son?
You know, you could should have could have called me. My son used to look normal. You tortured
him mentally. You did all this horrible stuff. And before tank died, tank had a $200,000
inheritance. Tank's brother is autistic. And when the father died, he split the inheritance in half.
So 200,000 to take 200,000 to the autistic brother. And the idea was kind of what the deal was,
was that if one of them passed away, the $200,000 would go to the other one. That seemed to be
the deal. But before he died, tank changed his will. So Dylan got the $200,000. Now, to be fair,
I think Dylan did not know about that. I think he knew that tank had changed the will, but they
were married. But I don't necessarily think Dylan had him murdered or did anything like that for
the $200,000. I don't think that's that's a true part of the story that I don't think that's a
completely I think that's a complete allegation. I don't and even the mother wasn't necessarily
saying you had him killed or anything like that. I think that was just a coincidence. It would make
sense when you get married to change your will. But anyway, she was like, you tortured my son,
you made him feel like he was trash, all this stuff. And eventually Dylan's like, you know what,
I'm done. I'm out of here and he left. But when the mother said that Dylan had mentally tortured
her son, that he had caused him anguish, that's because tank would post stuff online about how
he was tormented by Dylan. And of course, Dylan denies everything. Dylan's like, I never, this is
not true. This isn't true. I never said this. This is what tank is saying happened when he was still
alive. So tank posted this thing called pup rules, which was a list of all of the rules
that the followers of noodles and beef must do. You want to talk about a cult if these
allegations are true, this is what you would see in some sort of cult document. Now again,
tank posted this and we don't know we can't talk to him and Dylan denies it but tank did post this
stuff. So we just have to say that, you know, this is what tank posted. Here's some of the rules.
This one, this one's about the mind. A pup will profess his love, his loyalty, and his devotion
to his master at all opportunities he can. As a pup progresses deeper into his subspace,
a pup may find his ability to create words and coherent sentences is diminished.
Whimperine and I should say now all these dudes are gay. I don't know if that was implied,
but this is they're all the Dylan was banging these dudes and maybe they were banging each other,
but this is a total fetish thing. Okay, I just figured that I was like me, I didn't address that.
Okay, so back to this. The ability to create words and coherent sentences is diminished.
Whimpering and grunting are usually considered adequate substitution. But again, Dylan's like,
no, I never never never wrote that. This is all I have nothing to do with that. I just am banging
these dudes and I'm in love with these guys and it sucks that they died. Back to this pup rules.
While a master has some responsibility in guiding his pup into his subspace,
it is the primary responsibility of the pup to guide himself forever deeper into his subspace.
The slave will strive diligently to remold the slave's body, activities, habits,
actions, and attitudes in accordance to his master's desires. A pup has no sense of value or identity
outside of that which is given to him by his master. When a pup does wrong or finds fault in
himself, he is to internalize his flaws, dwell upon them, and then take all corrective actions he
can to improve himself for his master. How many cults have we covered on this show? We had the
cult in Brazil, the colonial dignidad, we had the restoration for the Ten Commandments in Africa.
We've done a few. And this is this type of stuff, this self-flagellation is very, very common in
these groups. Colonial dignidad was the German cult that was all about order and that
guy was a chameleister, he was totally nuts, but it was all about like order and creating order in
this paradise and things like that. And then you have groups that are about bringing about the will
of God, we have groups that are about... and I'm talking about what they say they're about,
not what they're actually about, it's all about power and money, but you have these cults that
some are about bringing the Lord's work into the world, some of them are about taking on the
non-believers, some of them are about preparing for the apocalypse. This one is sex-based. This is
100% sex-based cult. They didn't have any plans of enlightenment or religious freedom or it's
us against them, they're all just banging each other. It can... cults can really happen anywhere.
Now this is where it got... so Tank wrote this or posted this and he, you know, he was saying that
this what Dylan wrote, Dylan denies it, but this is the type of stuff the mother saw and was like
my son's being tormented. And this is the part that is where it gets iffy with the silicone.
Dylan's saying they did it on their own and the allegations are that he asked them or told them
to go do it and that will be decided in a court of law and because I don't know honestly. He could
just be talking about it so much and they go, "You know what? I really love my master, I'm going to
go get this done," because they have tattoos that say property of Dylan or property of noodles and
beef, one of the two. And he goes, "I never asked them to get that. They got that on their own."
This is where we get into the body part. Master has explicit body goals for his pup regarding
their weight, their muscle mass, their measurements, and their proportions. The pup will make all
efforts possible to ensure these goals are realized and should never feel satisfied until his master
is satisfied. There is always additional room for a pup to push their physical limits. Additionally,
a pup will submit to all orders for body modifications including piercings, tattoos,
scrotal, saline inflation, as well as body growth supplements including steroids and HGH
in accordance to the wishes of the master. So according to this, it specifically says the
saline, the temporary stuff. So that will protect Dylan to a point. He goes, "Hey man, I just told
him to get saline injected into their balls instead of silicone." I think when you turn people
into fetishes, when you turn people into sex objects, now people go, "Oh Jason, you objectified
that woman because you said, 'Man, damn, look at, dude, she's hot.' Fine, whatever, I objectified her."
But this, I don't go and then ask her, "Hey baby, become a bridesmaid and put on 40 pounds."
There's objectification and then there's turning people into a literal fetish doll,
into a object just for your sexual pleasure. Now, it is interesting, as I was reading into this,
they said, "The thing with the silicone is that it looks completely disgusting." And you're like,
"Well, of course, Jason, their balls are the size of a newborn baby. It is going to look disgusting,
but it goes far than that." There was an expert, I was reading an article and they said, "You notice
when these people get these silicone injections, they're always wearing clothes over their balls."
Because this isn't, these aren't the first two people in the world who have had this done.
The one guy made a living doing black market silicone injections. This stuff happens,
people get it into their butt and they die, people get it into their scrotum, sometimes you live,
sometimes you die. But this expert was saying they look absolutely disgusting, they look distended
and veiny and all sorts of gross stuff. So when you put clothes on, if you're into this gigantic
proportion body, you can put a clothes on it, wear like a tight bikini bottom and you're like,
"Whoa, look at that giant nut sack, that's awesome." That's, I'm not saying that, that's
the voice of somebody who's saying that, but when you take the clothes off, they, it looks gross,
looks grosser than you would imagine, cantaloupe size testicles to look. Because it's just distended
and lumpy, it's just not supposed to be down there. Silicone does tend to lump up. So, you know,
it'll be interesting to see. There's other resources out there where Tank told these stories
that about him being talked down to by Dylan, but again, it's hard to tell. You know, Dylan's
denying all of it and Tank is dead, he can't answer Tony of it. We just can kind of go through
posts and texts he sent to people here and there, people have kind of pieced it together. I don't
think Dylan is liable for any criminal acts. I think he is totally protected to say,
I never told them to get this stuff done. It will be interesting to see if he's open to civil
action, because you, that takes a lower threshold of evidence and the mom may end up suing him and
saying, I have this digital footprint of these things and I'm holding you responsible. That may
happen, but when you, there's just that power dynamic, you have a very dynamic leader and then
you have these men doing anything to please their leader. And then that's fairly common
in cults and groups like that. But it'll be interesting to see if anything changes from this.
If noodles and beef says, you know what, everyone get big, but don't do the, don't do the ball stuff.
I always think it's weird when people focus on sex first and their life just begins to
revolve around that. Like it's fun and all, but when it becomes, when you're basically like
breaking yourself down and going into the subspace of a pup where it's okay to just whine and
gurgle noises and inflate your body and get giant testicles and break down your mental and physical
body to please someone else, when that's all you are, when all you are is the fetish, that's when
it's really easy to get sucked up into this stuff. And from all appearance, I forgot what
Tank's real name was honestly, but from all the parents, that wasn't Tank's not his real name,
from all appearances Tank was just like a normal kid growing up in Australia who met noodles and
beef online and then came out here and just fell in love, fell in love with noodles and beef,
fell in love with the transformation and fell in love with pushing his body so hard to please
his master that it ended up killing him. That's an easy trap to fall into. And I know the question
you guys are all wondering. Jason. Okay, a bunch of guys got their balls inflated with silicone,
really what's the difference between a guy doing a gay guy doing or a straight guy doesn't matter,
what's the difference between a guy doing that and a girl getting a boob job?
And I have the perfect answer for you.
DeadRabber Radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address, you can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio. Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter. DeadRabbit Radio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.