Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio Classics, where we listen to some
classic episodes with new intros. Now I'm gonna tell you guys this right off the bat. I have not
listened to this episode. I recorded it, you're like Jason, you recorded it. Like in a sense, yes,
my voice said it, my ears heard what I was saying, and I edited it obviously, but I have not listened
to this episode in two years. I know it because I lived through it, but it's one of those episodes
that was difficult for me to record, it was difficult for me to edit, it's not a fun episode for me to
listen to, but I think it's one of those core episodes at Dead Rabbit Radio. Now I talked about
this before when I do personal episodes, they tend to be the ones I don't listen to the most,
because not only have I experienced the events, but I've thought about the events over the years.
Long before I had the podcast, I would still, my mind would still dwell on these events,
and that's why so many of the details are so fresh and raw for me. So I'm specifically talking about
the marquee story of this one, the Solar Plexus Clown Gliders, which is an conspiracy iceberg
term, and I kind of take that and go with the thing that I think, if these things are real,
and I kind of tell this story about this thing that psychically may have, it's a really, really weird
story, it's probably one of my most personal episodes. I've talked about like,
"Oh, I was here," and then like the mummy started chasing me, or "It was a dark and spooky night,
and a shadow man crawled out of his" I've talked about stories like, apparently in Vincent Price,
now I've talked about stories of me having paranormal encounters. This one took place over
the course of years, and I watched my life spiral out of control as I was just enveloped in pain,
and physical pain, and mental pain, and that's why I don't really like listening to the episode
again. It's a period of my time where I had some great friends, had some great experiences,
but there was that fog of pain over all of it, and now you know it's funny because I'm much older
now than when this episode took place, but, and I'm in pain still, I'm doing jiu-jitsu,
my neck hurts, my shoulders hurt, like everything from my ears to my waist is in pain right now,
because it was a crazy day training today, and then I throw 20 pounds on my backpack,
and I'm walking everywhere, and all this stuff every time I turn my neck, but the pain is different
because mentally I'm in a different place. The pain is actually probably as painful
as it was back then, but one, I know this is temporary pain, and two, I'm in a different
place mentally. I'm in a different place mentally. So, which is good, which is a good thing, right?
So, I think it's an interesting episode, I think, I remember two when this episode came out,
because we're talking episode 69, so I did not have a lot of listeners back then,
not a lot of listeners at all. I remember, and over the year this episode came out about two
years ago, I've gotten the occasional email from someone saying, I think one of these attached
itself to me as well, I'm lost in a sea of dark emotions, I'm not getting letters from my chemical
romance, but basically people saying they're struggling with these things, how do you get
out of them and stuff like that, and I've kind of counseled these people, they all seem to be doing
well, but yeah, it's just a weird, it's weird for that, it's weird because it's a deeply personal
episode where I'm talking about me being in pain and me being horribly depressed, but it's all,
let's not forget this story too, it starts off with a story about the sunspot solar observatory,
remember that? Where the observatory got shut down and the helicopter showed up and the FBI
agents were swarming it and it was gone to mainstream media, like what's going on, I did an
episode on that, and then this was the follow-up episode where I go, oh they found a guy accessing
child porn, and again, I have not heard this episode in two years, so, but I believe, correct me
from wrong, but I'm pretty sure in the episode I say this could be a cover story, because that's
such a gross allegation, people really don't want to look into it, we'll see what happens,
we'll see if I can find any more information, I believe that I say that I just went back to Google
and looked into it and there's still no information who this guy was, court dates, sentencing, so it
most likely was a cover story, weird man, weird, the sunspot solar observatory is one of those
things that gets lost among all the stupid conspiracy theories about lizard people and
coronavirus turning people into bat soup and then China's burning them and then using the ashes to
create more coronavirus, this story, and I think like in this episode I'm like, oh it was probably
just this, and this is one thing, when you're even a skeptic has to go, maybe I was wrong about that,
because we should have had more information, court transcripts, things like that by now,
but it's just gone, so, or it could just be that that was the real thing and then people just
stopped paying attention to it, who knows, the whole story was weird, whole story was weird,
and it's back, the observatory's back open, you can go there, check it out, I wouldn't recommend
using their wi-fi, but other than that, it's just that's bizarre, the solar plexus clown glider
story is bizarre, this one also has the dog vivisection one, that's a weird story, a weird
historical story, and like I said before, I like telling those weird historical moments, so anyways,
I'm rambling at this point, I hope you enjoy this episode, it is a little more serious and it's a
kind of a very personal episode to me, but I hope you guys enjoy it, and if you are currently
having some sort of emotional pain or physical pain or both or just depressed, maybe this episode
will help you, because I got through it, and you can get through it too, you can get through it,
I didn't believe it and it sounds trite when you're going through that, when other people
tell you stuff like that, when I was in the middle of it and people would be like, oh,
you'll get over it, they weren't that kind of sending, but you know what I mean, like,
when you're in it, it's really hard, when you're in the valley, it's hard to see the sunset,
but when you get to the peak, the sun never sets, because now you're like in Alaska maybe,
and the sun sets every six months, I don't know, terrible analogy, but you know what's not terrible
is episode 69, Solar Plexus Clown Gliders.
The real reason why the Sunspot Solar Observatory was shut down,
United States has issues with Confederate statues, but that's nothing with what happened
in England a hundred years ago, and finally we tackle an issue that has been highly requested,
Solar Plexus Clown Gliders, and I think I might have seen one today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio, I'm your host Jason Carpenter,
I'm having a great day, I hope you're having a great day too, we're going to dispense with a
bunch of pleasantries, this episode's going to be coming out early because we have breaking news
and I want to get to the forefront of it. The Washington Post reported just a few hours ago
that the reason why the Sunspot Solar Observatory was shut down was due to someone using the servers
to not only download but distribute child pornography. The FBI has said that that is why
they've gone into the area, the reason why the places were evacuated is because the suspect was
the janitor, I haven't released his name yet because he hasn't been formally charged, but the
suspect was the janitor working there, and for the past year he's been moving a laptop from
room to room that he knows aren't really used during certain times of the year to download and
upload child pornography. When a worker, like a scientist at the Sunspot Observatory, thought it
was weird, saw the laptop in a room no one should be in and it was running, and he had seen, the
scientists had seen the laptop kind of move from room to room every once in a while, he looked at
it, and then he alerted the authorities and took the laptop. When the janitor came back looking,
so then what happened was later on the scientists saw the janitor come out of the room where the
laptop was previously and started acting a little odd saying, "Hey, was anyone in that office were
missing some cleaning supplies?" and the scientists was like, "I don't know." And then the janitor began
acting very frantically in their words and started talking about there might be a serial killer in
the area and he was afraid that terrorists might hit the observatory and that someone may end up
getting executed. So at that point, and like I had, like they had stated previously, the ARA group,
the people who ran the Sunspot Solar Observatory, made the decision to pull the people out because
of the way he was behaving. So that's why they cleared out the observatory and that's why they
cleared out the post office. The FBI came in and were doing their investigation. There are still
some unanswered questions, but I hope I have a couple answers for them. A lot of people are going,
"Why was there a Black Hawk there for child pornography investigation?" Fair enough. Personally,
I don't know how FBI rides into and out of locations. If they felt that it is a federal
facility and if they felt that the danger was high enough, they may not have wanted to take
vehicles and that was the best way of them to get up there. I mean, a Black Hawk helicopter is not
really going to help against aliens either, but there could be a logical reason for that.
There's been a lot of YouTube comments on my channel and a lot of just comments everywhere
saying, "But this wasn't the only observatory shut down." Now, it was. I stated in the original
episode that it was the only observatory shut down and then I got pushed back on that. Fair enough.
I went and I did more research. I'll provide the links below. The other observatories that were
being stated as being shut down have been down for quite a while. I think one was down for maintenance
and the other ones were websites that had been offline for like a year or a couple months. These
weren't new things. So those other observatories have been down for a while. They were, you know,
there were reports saying all these observatories or cameras were shut off. They'd been shut off
for a while. I think one, it just recently went down for maintenance. You have to remember,
there's hundreds of these observatories around the world. So the fact that only six went offline
you know, other people could do this work as well. Plus the big one in DC, which has the,
which gets the information from the SOHO that has the golf instrument on it that we've talked about
a couple times on the show. They were fully operational. So apparently that is why the FBI was
investigating child pornography. Child pornography is, is, it actually can be used to cover up
stories. There was the weapons inspector in Iraq who went against the official narrative and said
that there were no mass weapons of mass destruction in Iraq. Then they found child porn on his
computer and he fought it. And he's like, I'm not that they put that on there. FBI put that on
there to retaliate against, you know, it's an easy thing to take out a political or a really any
opponent. You fled their computer with child porn. They lose a bunch of allies. That could be the
case here. It's the perfect cover up. But I think that is the most logical explanation. I talked
about that on my episode with solar observatory. I thought it may be some sort of criminal activity.
I was thinking more towards drugs, but using someone else's server to upload and download
pornography, child pornography in particular is definitely, you know, I, I, one of the crimes
worse than cooking drugs out in the middle of nowhere. So this may be the end of it. I'm like
I said also in that episode, this conspiracy will go on forever. People will keep saying no, no, no,
it was aliens. It was this, it was that. But at a certain point, you have to look at the preponderance
of evidence. If why aren't all of the observatory shut down? Why just that one? Because we know
for sure it's just that one now. So a lot of those myths have been debunked about the other
observatories being shut down and so on and so forth. So there we go. We can still keep looking
into this. If any new information pops up, we'll cover it. But I wanted to go ahead and get that out.
That is the official reason of why the Sunspot Solar Observatory in New Mexico is shut down.
Crazy stuff. Crazy stuff. Wanted to guest it, but there we go. We're going to go ahead and move on
to our next story. Now it's funny because I'm in America. We have listeners all over the world,
and I don't know how much of the news got out from America to the rest of the world,
but we've had a big controversy the past couple of years of tearing down statues of confederate
leaders and confederate generals. I guess that's the same thing as leader, but they're tearing down
these statues because they say it's a monument to hate. It's a reminder of racism. It's a really
interesting topic politically and socially because it's a part of history. I get, I see both sides.
It's a part of history and you don't want to forget history. It really smacks of 1984 and the
Taliban blowing up the statues of the Buddhists, blowing up the statues of Buddha in Afghanistan.
It's this real thing about destroying the past, renaming streets and schools and things like that.
It's really odd. On the other hand, I get the idea that in certain parts of the country,
we have these schools and streets and statues named after people who, one, not only tried to
break America apart, but also were trying to uphold the institution of slavery.
So I get both sides and it's not a particular issue that is divided strictly among race either.
There are a lot of black people who are like, "Oh, no, I'm cool with that statue. I don't have
a problem with it. You know, I've lived in this area my entire life. My grandpa lived here. It's
whatever. It's a statue." And then you have white people going, "No, no, you have to destroy it." So
it's kind of a weird, very interesting issue. For the most part, they do get taken down.
Once people start complaining, they're just like, "Ah, take it down." That is nothing.
That is nothing compared to the Brown Dog Affair. So we're going to travel to England,
Jolly Old England, as I like to refer to it in my show notes. And what we're going to look at
is this horrific story. It's pretty sad. So back in 1902, at the University College London,
there was a laboratory and they were doing a lot of vivisection. So that's where you basically,
you cut the dog open. I think vivisection is where you cut the dog open while it's still alive.
And dissection is where you cut something open after it's dead. And there's medical reasons to
do both, obviously. But they had this little brown puppy, this little brown terrier. Skip ahead.
Skip ahead, guys, if you're sensitive to dog stuff. I'm not going to get into too much detail, but
I don't know how long this is going to run, maybe 10 minutes. Once you start hearing me talk about
demonic clowns and all that stuff, you know you're in the right place. So they had this little brown
terrier and they said, "Okay, this is for medical reasons. We're going to do this." They did a
vivisection. They took out its pancreas and then sewed it back up. And they're like testing,
doing testing, things like that. And it was still alive. Like they took the pancreas out and then
they kept it alive. Then what they did later on was they go, "Okay, you know, now it's time for the
next part of the test. We are going, now it's 1903, so it's a year later." They have a lecture hall
with all these medical students standing there. And again, I'm not going to get into the details
here, but they did another. They opened the animal backup, did some more stuff in there. It gets
real graphic, but I'm not going to talk about that. Closed it back up, gave it to another researcher,
and that researcher performed another procedure in the same room. You know, like, "Oh, here,
I'm done with it. Here you go." And the other guy did another thing. And then they go, "Okay, well,
they gave it to a third doctor and he stabbed it in the neck and killed it." Now in that audience
was two women who were actually undercover. They were anti-vivisectionists. So there was a group
of people, like we have PETA now, these people, because it was a big issue back then. A lot of
vivisectionists were going on and there were special laws. One of the laws was that you could not
perform more than two procedures on the same animal, which is interesting. And the other one was the
dog had to be properly anesthetized. You need to be given enough anesthesia. And so they reported
it. They left the lecture hall, totally grossed out, and basically reported it and wrote a book
on it and contacted law enforcement and got a lawyer and all that stuff. And they said, you know,
the doctor was like, "No, it was properly anesthetized. You don't have to worry about that." But
they did break the law on doing the two procedures. And it was this big brouhaha back in England,
because it really gave the anti-vivisectionists something to hold onto. It gave them this item.
They're able to hold this dog up and say, "This is the horrible things that are going on." So now
we're going to move ahead to 1906. And near the school, they erect, the anti-vivisectionists,
erect a huge statue of a brown dog, big metalwork statue. And it says on the plaque, "In memory
of the brown terrier dog done to death in the laboratories of university college in February
1903, after having endured vivisection extending over more than two months and having been handed
over from one vivisector to another till death came to his release. Also in memory of the 232
dogs vivisected at the same place during the year 1902, men and women of England, how long shall these
things be?" So this statue stood there as this monument of what happened. And the scientists
were like, "You guys are so superstitious. This creature doesn't have any soul. It's just a thing.
You guys are totally trying to put all of this old world thinking. We're creating health. We're
doing this so we can help people." And the anti-vivisectionists were like, "It's cruel. It's cruel.
It's cruel." And scientists were like, "It's not cruel. It's just an animal. What are you going to do?"
So this debate raged back and forth. But what happened was you have these young medical students
and their college students. So they're going to get a little rowdy. They started to
try to break the statue down with crowbars. They tried to destroy the statue to the point
where they had to start stationing 24 hours a day seven police officers at the statue to prevent
people from trying to destroy it. Because of that, because the scientists can no longer try to destroy
the statue, 1,000 scientists, 1,000 students, medical students descended upon the statue one day.
And at that point, they were met by anti-vivisectionists, by suffragettes, by trade unionists,
socialists, and other progressive factions. Riot breaks out. They're battling over this multiple
arrests. I think it took, I think I saw it was like 240 police officers had to get involved in the
melee. They just, it was this huge fight. And it went on for a couple days from what I could see.
There's an interesting quote here. It says, "The mainstream press was apparently largely
supportive of the medical students, offering up mind blowing headlines like, 'Medical students
gallant fight with women.'" So you had the media going, uh, that women are just being hysterical,
you know, because they had, it was, there's a lot of women. You had the suffragettes and the
anti-vivisectionists and things like that. And the scientists just wanted to get rid of the statue.
And this went on for so long. So all of that started in 1906. The statue went up in 1907.
The brown dog riots is what they were called, started. And then in 1910, the council, the
Battersea Council, which oversaw the park, said, "You know what? We're done with this stupid statue."
In the middle of the night, they sent four workers and 120 police officers to protect them.
They took the statue down, gave it to someone, and it disappeared. They think it was Melton.
As of today, there is a new statue. In 1982, a new statue went up in the area. So 80 years later,
70 years later, they put up a new statue with pretty much the same plaque and it's a picture of
a little dog. It's a much smaller statue where the old statue used to be, all that's left is
like an indentation in the ground. And there's a sign on the fence nearby that says, "No dogs."
And it's funny to think, like, I imagine a bunch of medical students, I know they weren't wearing
like white coats and stethoscopes, but just like these college students fighting with
suffragettes and the police like, "Oi, oi, oi, break it up, break it up. Don't make me wallop you."
And, you know, all, just all like this craziness over a dog statue. And you know what's funny too,
is now whenever I see a story about a Confederate statue being taken down, I'm just going to think
of a bunch of scientists in white coats riding over a metal dog and, you know, a bunch of like
terriers on the other side, like biting them on the ankles. It's like, you know what they need to do?
They need to make, okay, let me pitch this to you real quick. I don't want this episode to go
long, but let me pitch this to you real quick. Airbud MD. And MD stands for medical dog and he,
Airbud, after done, he's done playing sports. He got a scholarship to play football in college.
He ends up going to medical school and he finds out that the other Airbuds are in laboratories
and they're going to be vivisected and he has to save them. And it's perfect because all the kids
who grew up with Airbud, they're adults now. So it's a little edgiest little like dark retelling
of the Airbud store, you know, like they love doing that. They love taking a normal franchise
and giving it a grim dark feel. Airbud MD. And it could be at the ending, it'll be like,
everything you saw in this movie is based on historical events. If you'd like to know more,
please visit your library. And it would be, if we'd just be like peeing on scientists and like
putting poop down and they'd be like, like slipping on it and stuff. And then like,
he's rescuing the Airbuds. That would be awesome. Oh, oh, you know, and you can have a scene where
Airbud actually like ties down a scientist and he picks up a scalpel and Airbud goes,
hate to cut and run, but and then like all those guts come out, telling you million dollar,
million dollar idea, million dollar idea, Airbud MD. Let's move on to the next story. Because the
next story is from the conspiracy iceberg list. And the next story is something that people have
been talking a lot about, requesting a lot about. Most of you guys have never heard of this. And
it's a kind of an odd one. Like I said in the promo, if we accept that it's real, I might have
seen one of them. So what this is, is this is something called a solar, a solar plexus clown
glider. So a solar plexus clown glider is simply a phrase that appeared on the conspiracy iceberg
list. And because of that, we have to go through a couple of different things real quick. The most
likely explanation, people watch my videos and people mostly my videos and they go,
what, you're an idiot that's totally made up. Listen, I get that. I get that a lot of these
phrases are totally made up. I investigate them nonetheless. You know, the most obvious answer
is solar plexus clown gliders is a joke. It was posted on the iceberg list as a dead end.
It's a random collection of words. I get that. That doesn't make for an exciting episode or an
entertaining episode. Because then right there I go, that's it. Dead rabbit radio, gmail. So we
do extrapolate from that. But I fully understand that phrase is like golf rumors, the ocean at night,
things like that. Ailish travel was able to be tracked down, but there are certain phrases that
could just be made up. You know, I'll always address that as that. We will take that as a possibility
and really the most likely possibility. Solar plexus clown gliders, first explanation is it's
just a word stew. Means nothing. I've heard that it is a creepypasta from the Usenet days. So it's
basically like an old lost scary story. I've searched this episode I've done probably about
two or three weeks of research on and I've used all my internet tricks of like isolating time periods
and doing all sorts of different definitions for the words and having to break the phrase up solar
plexus clown glider, jester glider. I've done everything I could and I was setting parameters
for when I could search and I couldn't find anything from showing a creepypasta written
pre-2017, which is where the earliest phrase, the earliest use of this phrase, solar plexus
clown gliders is August 19th, 2017. So it's very, very recent. It's the earliest I could find of this.
There's a theory that it's an old hacking term. Again, couldn't find anything of it related to
that prior to 2017. Now the two theories that were the most intriguing was one that it is a phrase
that if you speak aloud or meditate on or think about for prolonged periods of time, it causes
a mental breakdown. It is basically a tool that can be used to break down a human's mind. I was
going that angle. The thing is, like I said, I spent three weeks prepping this story and I have not
had a mental breakdown or really any ill effects and I've been focusing on this story exclusively
on my free time. Looking up, looking this up hours and hours and hours into this and like I said,
trying every variation. People have said you have to think about it while you're listening to a certain
frequency, but that theory just came out yesterday, this morning, as I was on the paranormal board on
X. Never heard the thing about the frequency, so I mean that could be an out, but like I said,
I've heavily researched this and the only things I found about it being a phrase to reprogram your
mind was on the 4-chan board. So that leaves us with our last and most compelling explanation.
A solar plexus clown glider is another term for, and you're going to have, so here's where we get
onto the crazy train guys. Solar plexus clown glider is another name for a interdimensional
demon that latches onto your solar plexus like an infection. So after a ton of research on this,
and I looked, I saw those couple, saw those five theories and I looked for other ones and really
out of those, the one that I was able to find the most supporting quote unquote evidence for
is the interdimensional demon. And they're specifically known as archons. Archons? Archons?
Archons? We'll go with archons. The re, the only way that I've ever found a connection between
the creatures known as the archons and the term solar plexus clown gliders is they attach to
your solar plexus. And again guys, this is, we start stretching after that first one. The clown
and the jester are loosely tied, very loosely tied. I'm even saying this here, loosely tied to like
demons, trickster spirits, things like that. Gliders couldn't find anything. I tried everything
to figure out how these things supposedly move, what type of technology they use. I, the, so I
tried valiantly to connect all four words to this idea of these demons. And I could only really,
I could connect two of them and then the clown was kind of loose in the glider. I wasn't able to
find anything. Unless you count the way that they do move as gliding because they slide across the
floor. So apparently what these are is these are interdimensional demons that invade your solar
plexus. The solar plexus is where supposedly your chakra is that determines things like will.
Your will to do things, your personal power. And these demons supposedly, again, they travel
through these dimensions. They have cut themselves off from the divine light so they can't create.
They have no imagination. There's, they are basically in the darkness. And so they attach
themselves to living beings to experience light, to experience creation. And when they're attached
to your solar plexus specifically, they can get you anywhere. But when they're attached,
attached to your solar plexus specifically, it causes you to like overly worry and depression
and doubt and all these things. And it feeds off that fear. It brings you into their darkness while
it's experiencing our light. I'm like, okay, that's an interesting, that's an interesting
hypothesis that there are these demons out there that exist and they're kind of like cut off from
what's pure and beautiful in this world. So they have to infect part of that beauty to experience
it and in the end bring you down to their level. I'm reading all this stuff about archons and then
it says they've already infected the grays and the reptilians. And I'm like, ah, we're back to those
guys. But you know, they're saying that's why aliens tend to be quite cruel. Like the experiences
that people have of grays, they're just kind of cold with their medical experiments and they're
kind of just like emotionless. It's because they've been their entire race has been infected by these
archons. The theory is is that these things are so pervasive, they move from reality to reality
and plan it to plan it until they've completely infiltrated an entire species. And it's just
these tendrils coming out. They're generally viewed as slugs or snake like slugs. And once they
latch on to you, they're difficult to get off. Faith healers and mediums say that sometimes
they can see them and sometimes they've got infected with them themselves. And it's a really big
problem. And it's a cause of a lot of people's unlike there are people who have depression for
known reasons. And then there are people who have depression, they just can't figure out why. And
they're saying that the archons are kind of responsible more for the second type of depression,
just kind of that overwhelming depression. And the, you know, just problems in your life is
general. So are those solar plexus clown gliders? Is that why that's on that list? Because it is
this alien species that basically has destroyed other alien species. Is it this creature, this
demonic entity, this interdimensional creature that is just moving slowly through the universe?
And that's why it's so low down on the conspiracy iceberg list. Because to know of it and to be
aware of it is in a sense, depression enough that these things exist. And they're just overwhelming.
They've already conquered most of our universe, let alone other universes. I think I've seen one.
I don't talk a lot about my own experiences on this show. I actually was talking to my two friends,
Lana and Mitcham. And I said, Lana, I've told Lana a lot of stories that have happened to me.
And I said, do you think I should talk about my personal experiences on the show? And she goes,
no, you'll sound like a crazy person. And that's true. Because some of my experiences are kind of
crazy. This one in particular, this episode may run a little bit long, but I think it's kind of
important because it heavily relates to this idea of these solar plexus clown gliders, these demons
from another dimension. So when I was in college, I had an assignment. I had to sit in a courthouse.
I think it was a, I was, it wasn't criminal justice. It might have been journalism class.
I had to sit in a courthouse and watch a trial and take notes. And I'm sitting in the back because
I'm too cool to sit in the front. I'm sitting in the very back and they have those orange,
hard plastic chairs because who wants to be comfortable while watching your loved one be
tried for murder? I'm sitting in one of those orange plastic chairs. And I remember just kind
of had my arm up. It was, I don't know, just a more a weekday morning. Had my arm up on the chair.
I'm just kind of leaning back like Jason does. Cause I can't sit like a human again, too cool.
I saw something out of the corner of my eye, my right eye. And I'm alone in the back row. It's
just me and I'm sitting right at the aisle because I always like to be on the aisle in case I got to
go to the bathroom. And I'm sitting there and so I catch something out of the corner of my right
eye. And I remember turning to look and in the chair, maybe two or three chairs down from me
was a three foot long cobra. And it was like coiled at the base and it was,
you know, probably about as high as me. So it was wrapped up. It actually must have been more than,
well, no, probably about three feet. It was coiled at the bottom and then like its head was about
the height of me. And it made this super weird movement, almost like this hyper animated movement
that I don't think a snake could move in real life. Now, obviously there was real no cobra
sitting there. And I knew there's no cobra sitting there. I wasn't like, I just looked over and saw
it and it was such a weird thing. And at the time I was just like, I must just be tired. I must
just be dreaming. And to be fair, that's the most likely explanation. I was super tired as early
in the morning. I was bored. I always stay up late. I turn, I look, I see something out of the
corner of my eye and then my brain is trying to construct something really quick for me to actually
see because I'm basically in a dream state. I see a cobra and moves in a weird way and I don't
react to it. I just kind of look at it for a second. And here's, you know, another weird part. It
disappeared. Now, when it didn't disappear like it blinked or it faded or it turned to dust, it simply
wasn't there. It didn't just go, it's hard to explain, but it didn't like, it didn't disappear.
It simply ceased to be there because there's a difference. It was really weird at the time. And
I remember I just kind of turned back to watch the trial. I was like, you know, but yeah, it just
simply stopped being there. I got a sore back. I woke up the next morning with a sore back. I
remember being a little uncomfortable in that orange chair and I was like, man, these chairs are
really uncomfortable. I woke up the next morning. My back really hurt. I was like, oh, that orange
chair really, really hurt. Really hurt the small of my back. Now, at that point, I'd been like in
seven car accidents. So I didn't have the best back to begin with. I was like, that chair just
wasn't working for me. So I just had a sore back. I go to my doctor and I say, hey, you know, I have
a sore back and he's looking at it. I'm like, yeah, I had a hard time sleep. I think I waited a couple
days, but it was just sore. And I go, you know, I'm having this pain in my back. I don't know what
to do. And he's like, well, okay, here you go. He prescribed me 120 Vicodin a month for what is now
I know was minor back pain. And because the back pain didn't cease, it got worse. Maybe after about
five or six months, he upped it to 250 Vicodin a month. So this, you know, this was back in like
2004, 2005, where the doctors were prescribing over prescribing pain killers because they didn't
think there's anything wrong with them. That time period, when I look back at that time period
between 2000, it probably would have been around 2004, 2009, it was about five years,
was some of the darkest times of my life. And trust me, that's a high fucking hurdle.
I remember taking those pills and no matter how many pills I took, I was still in pain.
I would just get loopy. And I remember because that's back when I was doing my music,
I came to the point where I could not operate, could not do anything functional unless I was
taking that medication. And since it wasn't helping me physically, it was just making me loopy or
and loopy or and loopier. And I was just like, I mean, I was a, I had hard time, you know, working
on my next album. I had a hard time hanging out with people. I had to plan everything around my
pain. And no matter how much medicine I took, the pain got worse and worse. I was having huge
emotional breakdowns. I was having huge problems with being, I think you guys can tell I'm fairly
optimistic. I was having a huge hard time being even optimistic enough to wake up in the morning,
to go to work. I was completely just dead. I was walking dead. Now, what happened with the
medication was I ended up changing doctors. My new doctor was like, why are you taking 250 pills a
month? Your MRI shows that you should have minor pain, if anything, your pain tolerance is totally
screwed up. I'm going to wean you off the pills. You're going to hate me for a year, and then you're
going to feel better. And that's what happened. And I feel 100 times better. I still get a sore back
from time to time, but not how that was. I remember when I was really, really depressed about my
situation, like really depressed on the brink depressed. And I remember that snake. I don't know
why it popped in my mind. But I kind of in my mind started putting it together. I was like, all of
this pain started that morning in that chair. Like I remember that chair being uncomfortable and it
like just feeling painful. And I remember thinking, and this is again, weird, a weird thought. But I
was like, what if somebody left that snake there? What if somebody else? That was, it was so bizarre.
It was, I was thinking, what if it was like a curse? What if somebody else had previously been
sitting in that row? And they had dropped it off or something and had left whatever that was had
left them and came for me and caused me all of that pain for all of that time. Because I had not
only the physical pain, but then I had the mental anguish of not being able to do what I wanted to
do because I was so cloudy. My thoughts were just, I couldn't really think in that fog. I felt like
a different person on that stuff. But yeah, you know, it, I'm better. I'm far, far better. I'm back
to how I was. And I don't know why it would have left me or what I did if it really was something
like that. But what if that was one of these solar plexus clown gliders, this Archons, this
parasitic entity that saw me, someone else, who had left someone else, and saw me sitting there
and attached itself to me and said, I'm going to cause some chaos and I'm going to feed off this
man's fear for a while. I don't know. Most likely explanation is I had a pinched nerve and I went
to a doctor and he overprescribed medication and it threw off my pain tolerance and throws you down
that spiral and all of that stuff. But I still, every once in a while, think of that snake.
And wonder if it's somewhere else out there.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Our Twitter is going to be @JasonOKarpenter. So everyone have a great weekend. We're going to be
coming back up with some new content. October is going to start soon. We're going to have some
awesome stuff for you in October. DeadRabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and
true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it
today. Have a great one guys.