A creepy, true crime case has finally been solved.
Or has it?
And then we often ask the questions, alien life does it exist, has it visited Earth before?
And most of the time these questions are asked and answered by people who have never gone
to aliens home turf, aka space.
So what happens when one of the most decorated astronauts of the US space program comes back
to Earth multiple times and tells his bosses the truth is up there today on Dead Rabbit
Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I'm your host Jason
Carpenter I'm having a great day I hope you guys are having a great day too I hope you
guys are having tons of fun whatever you do on snowboarding I don't know what else you're
doing mugging bigfoot he does have that wallet full of roots and berries that everyone seems
to want.
Speaking of something that I seem to want coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now
give me some of that love and it's our newest Patreon supporter give it up for Wobb everyone
give a round of applause for Wobb Wobb Celestr no one cousin Wobb wobbles on into Dead Rabbit
Command Wobb you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't
support the Patreon that's fine too just help spread the word about the show that means
so much to the show and it means a lot to me so if you want to take care of your good
old buddy Jason Carpenter just tell your friends tell your family talk about it online and
I know a lot of you guys do it because we've seen massive increases in this show just in
the past week so thank you thank you very much for those of you who are doing that.
Wobb I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider we're gonna leave Dead Rabbit Command
we're gonna take a nice leisurely journey because this first story is a little rough
we're gonna take a nice gentle glide all the way out to Durango Colorado
and as we were headed out there I'm sure I'm sure you heard the sound of a couple people
letting go of Wobb's ankles they're like now I'm good I'm good I don't want to hear this
story this story is fascinating to me it's one of my favorite true crime cases and I've
been just with lack of a better word digesting every bit of information that pun will not
make sense now the people who are plummeting away from the hair hang glider they're like
I get it because they're aware where this story is going but I've loved this story it's
a tragic true crime story so as much as you can love a story like this but the mystery
involved has kept me the edge of my seat and I'm not saying any of that to downplay the
real tragedy of this story it's just as a true crime aficionado this one tell my attention
for quite a while it's been this ongoing process so November 18th 2012 in Durango Colorado
there is a man named Mark Redwine a divorced father of a couple boys from a couple different
marriages and he would have custody of his kids from time to time he was legally considered
a good pop so the court gave him custody on certain dates mandatory custody whether or
not the kids wanted to go they were legally obligated to go they had to that's the worst
it's almost like prison at that point now you hope that the kids would come to love their
dad despite all of his flaws like yeah mom and dad couldn't stay together sons but I
still love you you know it takes a court mandated order for to give me the time to tell you this
and maybe over time you will learn to forgive me for cheating on your mom or whatever but
in this case the obligated court ordered visitations were not doing Mark Redwine any favors because
a couple years ago his sons Corey Redwine and Dylan Redwine are at his house and he's
asleep it's late at night and they get his laptop I don't know it's very the story is
very interesting I don't know what sparked them to do this maybe it was just childlike
curiosity you find a laptop you're chasing his son along with wanting to use laptops what
are you talking about what are you some sort of Luddite all of a sudden they had his their
dad's laptop is locked and they bypass his security lock that's one and then they take
the laptop into the bathroom because they don't want the dad to know that they're on his laptop
maybe they're expecting to see porn maybe they're like oh dad might be into boobs right
you think dad's into boobs now I think dad's more of a butt person that they were having
this super disgusting conversation we shouldn't be but maybe they want to look at some porn
see what their dad who who who I do not I don't know if they're trying to find their dad's
porn but I'm gonna tell you right now that's what they found I don't know if that's what
they said out there just trying to download some V bucks app and they found their dad's
porn now it's not as bad as you think usually when we talk about stuff like this like finding
their dad's porn it's child porn it's not that bad but it is so gross it's so gross
that I go to true crime websites all this is so funny I with bated breath waited honestly
like half the year like six seven months for these photos because although crime websites
will constantly show video footage is like a young woman's walking down New York and
a man walks up and shoots her in the brain it's just like it's like an autoplay you go
to the website and this is a little like web m or this gift of this woman getting blasted
they refused true crime websites at least the ones I want to refuse to show the photos
that they found they would describe them but they would barely describe them they would
just say a sentence and the sentence wait what I want to see these photos and then finally
maybe like in June it was very very recently June of this year they said okay guys there's
a website to go to every day it's called crime online dot com it's really cool crime website
they go okay we're going to show you the photos but these photos are so disgusting we're not
going to host them on our website we're going to have a link to someone else's website so
get them while you can guys they may end up taking these down here were the photos these
boys because they boys take the laptop into the bathroom they see these disgusting photos
and Cole the older brother pulls out his cell phone and starts taking pictures of the photos
now this whole part of the story is happening like a 2010 I think 2011 so it's like really
not the best film quality camera but it actually makes the photos so much more creepier and
I with with great suspense I know you guys are waiting for this the photos are imagine
you find these photos of your dad the photos of anyone would be gross finding these photos
of your roommate would be unsettling but if they if you found them of your dad and you
were trapped in his house right now you're both minors it'd be horrifying what they find
are photos of this there's a photo of Mark Redwine and he's wearing women's clothing
that's fine that's not that's crazy thing a man's ever done it's not that he's wearing
women's clothing just to build the mood and he has this brown material all over his face
you're like I didn't know my dad was in chocolate and fish the annatto and then there's like
a close so I'm going off memory I'm already seen him twice and they're disgusting so it's
a little bit closer and you can see more chocolate someone is face that there and the third photo
looks like it looks if if a black metal album from Sweden has their cover people would go
too much bro too much that one with your bandmate you committed suicide yeah that was that was
okay but this one it's a close up of a man of not a man Mark Redwine with a poop filled
diaper this was described all the time on crime online like he did Cheerios I'm like
I want to see those photos it's a picture of a man with a poop filled diaper stuffed in
his mouth and easy the poop there you go Jason Jason you haven't seen two girls one cup Jason
I've seen way worse stuff on this website blah blah blah blah well here's the thing one probably
yeah I have seen two girls one cup is absolutely disgusting I hated it I didn't finish watching
him super gross but it was super glossy look like they shot it at evil angel studios or
some porn place right this was this because the cinematography of it was so grainy and
made it even creepier and it was two girls one cup right you're like Rebecca no it was
just two models that got paid to do that they were probably into it and they're having a
good time it was disgusting I think it was the beginning of the end of Western civilization
if you ask me I think that you talk about 9/11 everything changing I think two girls one
cup I should have never said on that I actually think that that was the first push towards
oblivion for civilization I really think of I've never seen it so widely accepted something
that disgusting that was real but anyways you know to this day there's a lot of podcasts
called like two girls one ghost or two girls one true grand podcast and they're playing
off that it's that much of a meme and I do think that that was the beginning of the end
of civilization but I will talk about interesting concept try to remind me I'll probably forget
to talk about it but I'll never forget I do I do think that I think that was a site op
think that was that was promoted on it naturally not a naturally because of the fetish I think
that it shouldn't have gone viral and it did and I think someone or a group was behind it
for some reason or another but we'll talk about that another time were we talking about oh
yeah yeah poop poop eat a poop filled diapers I forget what we're talking about I just talking
about two girls one cup and so it's not only is it somebody you know in this video or these
photos and it's it really gross cinematography which does add a creepiness layer to it these
photos may have led to a murder and let me add there is one more photo to of him wearing
the poop filled diaper that's a de-escalation though after eating it after you're eating
it he's like num num num now you know it'll be really gross if I use it for its intended
purpose but I think the prosecutor because the photos were laid out the prosecutor probably
should have shoveled them to make it like less gross to most gross but maybe the maybe the
prosecutor hates sitting in poopy diapers and so he's like that was the worst photo guys
I almost didn't show that to you and everyone's like as he's eating he's eating chipotle at
the trial he's like as long as I have to sit down and poopy diaper everything's a okay
creepy story but this has led to murder allegations November 18th 2012 in Durango Colorado Dylan
red wine has to go spin Thanksgiving with his dad Mark and he doesn't want to he doesn't
want to for two reasons one one the photos I mean you just don't visit a guy who you're
stuck with like if you have a friend who's into this and you can leave you can leave
whenever he starts going I'm hungry you're like okay dude I'm out he's reaching for the
denizen's chili he's like making a marshmallow diaper you can leave but you don't want to
be stuck with someone who's eating poop I'm just assuming my audience could be like I'm
unsubscribing to this podcast he obviously doesn't get me he doesn't understand the
deliciousness of my fetish you'd I you wouldn't want to be there but also he was hated the
way that his dad was talking to his mom he could hear him arguing over the phone and
he was like this is just a piece of trash you don't want to be with him the mom is like
it's court ordered you have to go November 18th 2012 he goes to Colorado Mark Redwine
picks him up they go to I think a McDonald's in a Walmart there's surveillance footage
of them going to a couple different locations in 956 a text message was sent from Dylan's
phone and since then no one has ever seen Dylan again and that's where the mystery stood
from 2012 to 2013 so that first half a year first six seven months you had Mark Redwine
go and listen we got in a fight we did but Dylan ran away he just left the house you guys know
that he hates me first off officers do you have anything to eat do you have anything to eat
because they happen to be can we stop at the maternity ward on the way to the police station
I'm famished but then he goes listen he ran away and who knows what happened to him we live in
this mountainous region we're in Colorado for crying out loud there's like bears and mountain
lines in the area and the cops are kind of like looking at each other and they're like yeah I
guess but they don't have enough evidence to charge him in 2013 though about five miles away
from the Durango household of Mark Redwine they find bones a couple bones some clothing
and they test it and they are the bones of Dylan Redwine and at this point Mark Redwine goes I
told you guys that I told you I told you guys exactly where the location of the body would be
no he goes listen I told you he ran out it was most likely he got attacked by some sort of
animal which is rare but not unheard of and he's a 13 year old boy who's running into the wilderness
anything could happen he goes on the Dr. Phil's show Mark Redwine goes on the Dr. Phil's show with
which god bless Dr. Phil's heart but I really wish his shows were available online I get it
it's not an easily accessible show to watch but I watched a couple clips from this episode
and it's what you would expect from this type of story his family saying that he's gross and a
murderer probably more they probably more accusing him of murder first and then him going I didn't
do it I didn't do it he took a polygraph test and then I couldn't find I couldn't find the
polygraph test but I'm assuming he passed it or was inconclusive or anything like that because
because he's still walking around free in 2013 in 2015
they find Dylan's skull
and when they're looking at the skull they see what appears to be blunt force trauma
now could a wild animal cause blunt force trauma it's unlikely like the swat of a bearish paw
that's like about 10 baseball bats hitting the side of your dome but it's enough for the coroner to
rule he probably got his head caved in and it probably wasn't a wild animal in 2017
Mark Redwine is finally arrested a good five years after the event his disappearance
and then prosecutor Fred you know prosecutors defense lawyers they're really they're salesmen
they're speech givers they're politics that's why lawyers make sedgeka politicians I want to read
you this bit of prosecutor Fred Johnson's very short quote here talking about this trial or
talking about this event I love this type of stuff quote after 9 56 that evening all communication
from Dylan Redwine stopped that night under the shadow of middle mountain the defendant murdered
Dylan Redwine unquote that's really cool I'm not saying that it's cool that he murdered this kid
but it's very visual it's very evocative isn't it and apparently he also lived near where the
dwarfs hide all their gold middle mountain blood all over the house there's going to be blood all
over your house it's just going to happen he's like oh no that blood came from when he was clipping
his finger and he got too close to the skin that was when he stepped on that nail and you can kind
of explain a bunch of stuff his there's such an interesting trial because it does make sense
that a kid running out into the wilderness could die of natural causes and the evidence against
mark red wine was there was blood of the boy in his house a house that he lived in
that he drove his atv down a road where they eventually found the body it was an av it was
an atv road it wasn't just some random road it was like where you'd go atv and the family saying he
didn't seem too concerned about finding dylan and he was the only one with the motive he's found
guilty based on that's so circumstantial now I think he was guilty I do think he was guilty but I
don't think there would be enough evidence there to prosecute him for that he was just found guilty
in July 2021 and I missed it because I was on vacation I wasn't reading anything I've been
waiting to cover this story but I wanted to wait till the end of the trial I wanted to wait until
it was done before I shared it with you I wanted to find out what the conclusion was but he's going
to be sentenced on october 8th I mean obviously the sentence is either life in prison without parole
or death fascinating story though I love it because it's a mystery it lasted for years
it's actually a pretty good alibi that's really good defense I didn't do it the bears did and it
would make in that area it's not gonna work in downtown Sacramento it's a good defense it is a
good defense and the weird fetish angle to it as well if it was a guy just killing his kid you
it happens every single day but oh man those photos so a true mystery it was he really the guy I
think so but who knows the truth of the story could still be out there on middle mountain somewhere
evidence that would show that mark red wine is not a murderer but just a totally disgusting dude
he's gonna get into prison he's like all this prison food reminds me of home everyone's like
dude this stuff's super disgusting he's like yum yum yum yummy in my tummy can I have some of your
foods sir wobble let's go I swear I'm shocked I still get paid to get some orders because it is so
so random what episode you end up on wobble is already sent it off they're like nah I'm good
I'm totally good well let's toss you the keys of the carpenter we're gonna leave behind Durango
Colorado and we are headed on out to the very edge of space
carpenter copter is taking us off to where the blue meets the black where the atmosphere slowly
gives away to the icy grip of the abyss I could be a prosecutor I would much rather be a defense
lawyer I think it's way more fun but I can say snazzy stuff too it we're in zero gravity so
we're kind of floating around and wob is slowly I don't think we've ever taken the carpenter
this high up we're floating into space we're just kind of floating around it's a having a good time
right throwing a beach ball we're throwing the slowest thing we can't even tell it's in zero
gravity you're like Jason why aren't we throwing like anvils or something if you threw an ant if
you're in space and I threw an anvil to you would it kill you like in real life if I dropped an
anvil on your head you die but if I dropped an anvil your space suit gets all shattered I was
like I'm just testing it bro you can't breathe I mean but think about it if you dropped it in
space it would just kind of float there right there is no dropping it I wonder if you could
play baseball on the space station this is why this is why they'll never allow me anywhere near
any technology I'm like oh what does this button do it's CERN I bring Nelson Mandela back to life
all this craziness so anyways we'll we'll let the space nerds I'm sure I'll get a ton of emails
explaining stuff to me and I do love those emails I often get them usually from English majors
and people who are correcting my grammar this is one of those fascinating stories that is packaged
in such a bizarre way I just don't understand it we recently talked about it on yesterday's episode
about how journalists are supposed to write their articles in an inverted pyramid and you put the
best information the most important information at the top and it gets less informative as you go
down so the editors can edit it or the reader can stop reading it and they get the gist of the
information at the top the problem is is that paranormal in particular paranormal writers
are not journalists but they churn out articles constantly now they may be good paranormal researchers
but they're not they're not journalists they don't know how to structure an article in a classic
journalist way drives me up the wall drives me up the wall and I don't want to call out certain
web I'm going on a website now but a lot of the paranormal websites they're just a mess their
articles are just really really poorly written no and I'm not in a informational way they're just
formatted they're not even written like in a magazine format they're just written as if someone
was I don't I don't even know how to describe it they're headache inducing for me and I have to
read them to get stories for this show but it's fascinating you guys if you're a paranormal
researcher just take a journalism class or buy a journalism book for crying out loud but anyway so
here's a website that I go to all the time it's a great website called howanwise.com they have a
lot of really good information on here I found a lot of cool stuff and this is an article called
well I won't tell you the title right now it's written by a journalist named Vicky Verma
again I'm not calling you out for being a bad researcher but it's just such a bizarre it's not
a very well-structured article I'm reading it and it starts off with quoting a Gaia article with
Gaia if you don't know is middle-aged mom metaphysics it's a website that specializes in just the
hokeyest of the hokey so unless they're sponsoring this unless they're sponsoring my podcast where
I'm on their channel one of these days then it's the best source of information around but as of now
when they're not paying me just a bland repackaging of paranormal and consciousness and stuff like
that at best then they have stuff then they have stuff that's just straight up fictional but passes
as reality like the guy who says that he was an Alantean warlord and this article that they're
referencing Vicky Verma talks about a transcript between Buzz Aldrin and Neil Armstrong as a
young as they're exiting the lunar module on Apollo 11 and it's like here's a dramatic
reenactment of what Gaia no recording of this by the way I looked I looked Gaia I tried verifying
it future future bosses I tried find verifying it Apollo 11 those are giant things no no no this
is not an optical illusion no one is gonna believe this this is NASA command what what what the
hell is happening what's wrong with you they're here under the surface who's there calling Apollo 11
we saw some visitors they were here for a while observing the instruments repeat your last information
from it repeat your last information I say there were other spaceships they're lined up in the other
side of the crater and then it just kind of goes on from there right you're like Jason that sounds
super interesting keep reading me that what are they're nonsense what are they're nonsense are you
possibly trying to speed towards you gave that half-assed reading I know I know you can do a
better dramatic reading than that you're an actor for crying out loud what could what could be more
interesting than that well that is not true and the truth is always more interesting than fiction
if I could have found a recording of that oh that would have been awesome I would have done
what is this quit the show and started a new show where I analyze that recording every day
so in this article I'm reading I was like here's the thing I'm open to it and I tried finding this
I went to the Gaia website I went to the Gaia website subscribed I joined I joined I'm now an
Atlantean warrior but I try looking for the recording of this I tried looking for anything
that backs this up and there's nothing to back it up it's a transcript if this was true
it doesn't exist it doesn't exist but in this that's how the article starts off and I'm my eyes
are rolling to my eyes are rolling so hard they've basically achieved a zero gravity
but in this article after you read about that you get to doctor story you must grave and because
I'm already primed not to believe what's coming up next because I'm already like that isn't real
and I've checked it out it wasn't that I just read that I'm like what aliens those don't exist
I stopped I go wait that's weird and I started looking for other versions of the transcript or
an audio version or any proof that this existed and it doesn't and then I go back to the article
and I'm already primed to be like this is made up I almost didn't finish reading the article
then we get to doctor story must grave
this guy goes on the record there is a voice recording of him talking about what he saw
doctor story must grave you may not know who is maybe you do he helped design
essential space shuttle equipment like spacesuits and life support he's been to space six
different times he's been on six different space missions he is the only astronaut the only us
astronaut to fly in all five shuttles including challenger before blue not afterwards that would
be the feet you flying in a go shuttle ma and if none of that impresses you he was also a guest star
on home improvement the headline of this article retired NASA astronaut claimed to have seen snake
shaped UFOs during two missions in space starts off with this bizarre fictional account of this
UFO float what was it I don't remember how they were on the lunar crater and some alien showed up
totally fictional so when I get to this transcript of what doctor story must grave said I was like
what that's not true but but how's and why is includes a link a video link to an episode of
a old show called sightings and let me read you this transcript this really should have been
all the only thing the article was about let me read you this transcript on two of my missions
and I still don't have an answer I have seen a snake out there six seven eight feet long
it is rubbery because it has internal waves in it and it follows you for a rather long period
of time the more you fly in space the more you see an incredible amount of things out there and that
sort of brings to you really a certainty that other living creatures are out there some incredibly
primitive more primitive some just just proteins coming together amino acids and and some just
single cell organisms and other civilizations that have been around for a million years that
are doing unimaginable kinds of things unquote and while he's doing this while he's speaking about
this on the sightings video they show what appears to be real footage from a shuttle in space and you
see this weird snake like object floating far far far above the earth next to the shuttle
it's fascinating sorry and I've seen footage like that before and I've seen the weird orbs and all
this stuff that seemed to be outside of the earth's atmosphere absolutely fascinating stuff and here
we have one of the most highly decorated astronauts ever coming forward in a non-faked transcript on
audio saying this is what I saw there's snakes in space he also does an interview with forbs later on
and he at that point he's talking more about traditional aliens what we think of as like
graves and reptilians and stuff like that he is he finds it odd that they would come to earth
not because of any sort of technological limitations he just thinks that they're out there but why would
they come to earth like what would make us so special for them to come here in the first place
which is a very scientific way to look at it it's special to us just like when we're flying in a
plane or driving down the road and we we drive past Patawah Idaho but you would drive past you
wouldn't think anything of it you only stop there if you needed to but you're probably going to stop
by a bigger city but to the people of Patawah Idaho it's their town it's their home the fighting
huskies is their local football team and they got all this pride there and blah blah blah blah
to that we're basically Patawah Idaho in the galactic scheme of things but we do sure love our
huskies there is a reason think think about this story for a second there is a reason why one of
these is more popular than the other right there is one of these why we know all about the bases
on the moon or ancient aliens or crop circles this is all alien lore 101 this is something you
learn when you first start researching aliens you learn these conspiracy theories but organic
aliens in space floating around like that single cell organisms kind of clumping together and and
evolving in the atmosphere that's a more of a high-level conspiracy theory and it shouldn't be
because people are willing to go people who have been to space are willing to go on the record
and say this is what we saw this should be well known knowledge this should be conspiracy theory
UFO lore 101 it should be one of the first things you see when they talk about it before we get to
Betty and Barney hill before we get to cattle mutilations before we get to a entire series
based on ancient aliens this should be ground zero the building blocks for life have been seen
in outer space right next to our planet by people who are trained observers and seen on two different
missions so you can't say oh it was just uh he had some he had a worm in his eye he's like ah
I shouldn't have been swimming in that swamp right before takeoff I find it interesting I don't know
if it's by design that the the true stuff is pushed aside by the nobly false stuff even in
this article itself by vicki verma that is apparent this should have been the top
we didn't need the people on the moon the the base whatever was the aliens on the crater I've
literally already I literally already have a hard time remembering what that was because it's just
fake and this is so fascinating this was real so why are we as a UFO community as UFOologists why
do we do it as well continually push away the stuff that is real for the stuff that isn't
I mean there have been massive massive flaws pointed in the ancient aliens theorem and I'll
put this link on the show notes again there's a guy he did a three hour long video breaking it down
almost episode by episode showing how this stuff is not aliens over and over and over again no one's
watching that people just want to hear about ancient aliens and I have no problem I love aliens I have
no problem discussing it but we should be discussing the stuff from first-hand observers in space
it's sure it's not laser beams sure they're not building pyramids or creating crap circles or
mutilating cattle it's a just a lie we don't even know if there's any consciousness in it
it's just a snake floating around in space but it's real may not be flashy may not be dancing
with a little top hat it may not be plotting to take over the world but it is life outside of the
planet earth and even in a website even in an article named after it the headline is on it it's
buried in that article itself is this just because we don't have a big attention span is this just
because we want the flashy stuff or is it more sinister than that is someone trying to hide
the real stuff from us to sell us the independence day alien invasion or the space brothers coming
to cure all of our diseases or the sinister men in black it's all well and good it's very entertaining
but the reality of just miles above us right now there are proto life forms slowly evolving
at the edge of space may not be enough for a whole series on history channel
or to sell a book but dr story must grave solve these things with his own eyes and put his
reputation on the line to talk about them that shouldn't just be an episode of an obscure
television show from the 1990s that should be something that all UFOologists know it should
be common knowledge among the UFO community but it's not and the mystery is why
I
do
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also put us up at
facebook.com/dead rabbit radio tiktok is at dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and truth friend podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but
I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys
you