Is there an audio series out there that can create an alternative personality in your brain?
One of a mindless bimbo?
And are the mountains we see around us really the stumps of giant trees today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. I'm having a better day.
Every episode, you know, was probably the most, is definitely the longest I've released.
And I ended up working, I started, I think I started recording around 11 o'clock at night.
And by the time I was finalized, it was maybe one in the morning. I'd actually tried going to bed,
couldn't sleep, woke up because I wasn't going to do the episode. Woke up, did the episode.
And that's probably honestly the most authentic episode of the series. That's probably the closest
you would get to actually talking to me where I, at a certain point at the beginning, I was like,
some of these facts, they're somewhere on my notes, but I'm just going to say what I think.
I still don't know where the Isle of Man is. And the yawn in the middle. By the time I got to the
yawn that pops up in the middle of that episode, it was about 1230 when I was editing it. And I was
like, there's no way I'm going to be able to cut around this. I think I yawned in the middle of a
word and then started the next word. There's a lot of editing that goes on in this podcast.
I usually, the episodes usually run about 30, 40 minutes, and then I'll chop out 10, 15 minutes
of it to get into the range I want, which is generally around 25 minutes. But last night's
episode, I was like, I, there's, I can cut here and there, but I'm just going to let the episode
stand. I really need to go and get some sleep. But I think it was probably my favorite episode so
far because it was just kind of a moment. It was kind of a moment. And I liked both of those stories.
Jeff the talking mongoose and my history of Stanley Hotel. And I woke up this morning, you know,
I feel bad at people who comment on YouTube. I can respond really quickly and people who comment
on Gmail. I can respond really quickly. But the pod being website, which is where this podcast
is hosted, I don't know how to respond to people. But after the last night's episode, or I was pretty
down while I was recording, and it definitely cheered me up while I was doing it. And then I
got down again as I was editing it up until one in the morning. I woke up this morning and podcast
user and forgive me if pronounced your name, but ariana blackmon21 just did good episode.
Gave me a little comment, good episode, which is nice. I'm glad you appreciated it. I love
reading comments like that. It was something nice to wake up to. So I appreciate that. Thank you.
Thanks to everyone who reaches out. But I wanted to go ahead and highlight that one because I had
no other way to respond. Now, I talked before about how to unleash your gay lust demon, I think
was the name. It was a video that if you watched was supposed to turn you gay. And I watched it.
And it didn't have any effect on me. Except like I said, it made me realize that everyone in the
world has a bigger dick than I do. But there's another audio program. This one has no video
attached to it. And you know, the how to unleash your gay lust demon, all the comments were like,
yeah, this video totally rocks. I'm totally gay now. There's another thing out there. It's called
Bambi sleeps. Now, if you know what Bambi sleeps is, if you've encountered it in the past,
and you don't want to be reactivated, I just skip ahead 10 minutes because we're going to talk about
it. We're going to play a little bit of an audio file from it. So Bambi sleeps. What it is, is it is
a series of audio files. There's quite a lot of them that you're supposed to listen to while you're
awake. They have there's so many of them because they're supposed to be for different phases.
First, you listen to from what I understand the series. And then they have a file that's like
a rapid induction that just kind of like puts you into the hypnotic state. These ones focus
specifically on hypnosis. And you listen to them when you're awake. So you're conscious,
then you listen to them while you're sleeping. And what it does, what the pitch is, is that it
creates a new personality inside of you called Bambi. So it creates this new personality inside
you named Bambi. And she is super horny, and she's really dumb. She's a bimbo. And her only goal in
life is to be stupid and flirty and dress up in nice clothes and have sex with as many men as
possible. So again, we're back in the gay, sissy, mind control thing. And that is a fetish of that
community. So it's not you go, Well, how come there's no like, hypnosis to, you know, want to bang
two girls at the same time, because that's not part of the fetish. It's some people in the sissy
community, which is, which is different than the transgender community. Sissies are generally,
it's it's it's the hyper sexualization of transgender, you can be transgender and say,
you know, I'm a woman, I'm as a male born woman. And I want to be identified as a woman. And this
is how I want to live my life. And sex is a component of that the sissy side would be the
opposite. I want to have the sex is the overriding goal of it. And I'd be identified as a woman
only in the context of having sex. So it's not about, you know, equal rights and restrooms or
political access or anything like that. It's all sexual. It's a sexual fetish. They have entire
websites dedicated to sissy hypnosis, sissy hypnotic videos, it's a huge subset. People watch
these videos, and they, you know, jack off or they go off and blow dude, I don't know. But
Bambi sleeps is different than that. Bambi sleeps is meant to create a new personality inside of you.
Now, because there's such this sissy hypnosis community, it took off. People are like, oh,
this is totally awesome. Like it will finally turn you into that brain dead bimbo slut you've
always wanted to be. But user reports have started coming back saying, don't ever listen to this.
It ruined my life. This is true hypnosis. This created personality disassociative disorder things.
Stay away. This is not fun. People have reported, you know, I was reading one report, the guy's like,
I called in sick to work the other day and just listened to Bambi sleeps for eight hours on a loop.
Other people have complained that they don't, they can't walk as well anymore. Like it's ruined
their motor skills. They kind of walk like a their man who presents themselves as a man to the world,
but they find themselves kind of moving in the way of an exaggerated bimbo. A lot of them have
complained about getting dumber. They've said I have a hard time spelling. I have hard time,
you know, saying proper grammar sentences, things like that sentence structure. The even the positive
like reviews will say this video will give you the IQ of the equivalent of 75 to 85 IQ points,
which is retarded. Like that is that's retarded. I'm not using that word as a slang that is
medically retarded. If you're at 75 IQ, you are retarded. I can't think of any other word for it.
You are mentally challenged. I guess I could use that word a hundred times. But so and also like
if you're not dressed up in girly clothes, you'll get angry. And they say so the video, the audio
files, when people have reviewed them, some people again review them glowingly. This is the person
I've always wanted to be. Another people have said the files are created in such a way because
there's transcripts and everything like that. The files are created in such a way that the more
you try to think when you get to a certain phase of listening to the audio clips, there's
safety mechanisms, but not safety mechanisms for you. Safety mechanisms for Bambi. The more you
try to think about how you used to be, Bambi will come out. And the more you think about Bambi,
Bambi will come out. So no matter what you do, you can't override the programming. These are the
first file. These are the names of the first set of files that comes with it. Rapid induction,
which puts you to sleep and gets the process started. Bubble induction. And that is where
it's really bizarre. You take, it tells you to take your earliest childhood memories,
put them in a pink bubble, and then you pop it and the memories go away. Then you take your
middle school memories, put them in a pink bubble and pop it and then those memories go away. And
it goes through this whole process. And what it is is it's clearing the slate, clearing your mental
slate for Bambi to have room to grow. So again, that's way different than, you know, Suck a Dick
for Satan. It's, that was just like, suck, suck, suck a dick. This is like actually going through
a process of like a mind wipe. Next one is bubble acceptance. I think that's when they're creating
the new memories. It goes on a bit. We have Bambi IQ lock is one. So that's where it's kind of
locking you into that stupid phase. Bambi body lock is again, where she's starting to take control
of the way that you move. Bambi attitude lock is starting to make you more slutty. Bambi uniformed
is actually, I know where you have, I know from reviews, I have not listened to these in full
yet, but Bambi uniformed is having to dress up in girly clothes. So if you find yourself at work
and you're wearing a suit and tie or, you know, you're at school and you're wearing like jeans
and a t-shirt, you'll start to get angry. You can't wait home to put your bra on. And then
all these videos are designed to basically like break down your normal personality and create
this Bambi alter ego. Bambi takeover is basically you're allowing her access in your body. And then
the last two are Bambi cockslut. That's where they after all of these files, they finally introduce,
now you got to go off and have sex with all these dudes. And the last file is Bambi awakens, where
she takes full control. Now, obviously, it's not like you listen to it one time and you're like,
I'm Bambi, want to have sex with me? It's you keep playing it over and over and over again.
Now, what happens? People have said, again, anecdotal, but the battery views have come in and
they said that, you know, you get addicted to the audio files. And they just be, they take over your
life. You can't wait to listen to them again. You'll just listen to them on loop over and over
and over and over again, until it actually does begin to wipe your memory. You have a hard time
concentrating and remembering things like that. And you're like, Jason, that is the most ridiculous
thing in the world. None of that stuff sounds like it'll, it'll work at all. Here's my thing.
You're probably right. I think that the battery views could be again, part of the fetish.
I think the battery views are people go, this is the worst thing it's taken over my life. It turned
me into a total cockslut. My name is Bambi now. And that's part of the fetish. So they're like,
Oh, I can't wait to listen to Bambi sleeps. But you know, people, there's always been that thing
like hypnosis doesn't work on people, you can't make them do anything that they wouldn't want to
do. And first off, obviously, these people would like to do the stuff. That's why they're listening
to these files in the first place. But I think, I think you can hypnotize people standing right
in front of you. I think hypnotize is kind of the wrong word, but social engineering is a better
word. You can stand right in front of someone. And with the right combination of words, not magic,
just persuasion, you can get them to do things they might not otherwise do. I can't walk up to
someone to convince them to commit murder. But I can walk up to someone or anyone really can do
that. And you through the combinations of words, the combinations of empathy and the way your body
posture is and everything like that, you can actually convince people to do things to make
small decisions. So the mind can be hacked. You may not be able to swing a watch in front of somebody
and hypnotize them. But I think in between the level of social engineering and the level of somebody
who knows the maximum potential of social engineering and how the brain works and how like the
theta waves and all that stuff goes around, I think you could create a file. I think you could
create some sort of audio or visual presentation that could push susceptible people over the edge.
That's my first theory. My second theory, this is going to get out there. But what if, what if
there's something more sinister behind it? This is kind of sci-fi, a horrorish, but what if it was
a way to like break down your brain so much that some sort of entity could lock onto you. And for
some people, they accept the entity. I know you're Jason, you're like Jason, you've totally lost your
skepticism hat this episode, but wait for the next segment. What if it breaks you down so much on a
level that some sort of entity could latch onto you and basically ruin your life or possess you or
something like that? I don't know. It's really weird. Knowing the superstition and again, I said the
two theories that it could be someone who made it, who really knows how to brainwash people or knows
how the human mind works on a biological and a emotional level. It could be some sort of like
evil conspiracy by demons to take over people. I think both of those are not very likely. I think
that it probably is an effective fetish audio clip that turns otherwise susceptible people
to take their fetish a little too far. Here's my question. Would you listen to this series? It's
going to be linked in the show notes. Now I'm part of the conspiracy. Would you listen to
all of Bambi's sleeps? I don't know if I would. I'm going to. I'm going to have to. I didn't want
to listen to it before this episode because I would run out of time and I kind of wanted to
talk about it and then come back to it. But I was like, what if I listen to it and I get
dumber? Like what if it is possible to, and let's put it this way, it is possible to break
people's brains and create disassociative personalities and then we know it's possible
because it happens on accident. And if it happens on accident, I'm sure that governments and other
institutions have figured out ways to do it on purpose. But if you abuse people constantly,
they will create a separate personality to deal with that abuse. It doesn't happen all the time,
but we do see that it happens. So Bambi sleeps. Would you listen to it? I also have another
question when I was listening to this. There is even a subset of Sissy Hypno community where it is
videos and audios to make women sluttier, like you listen to it, and it makes them dumber
and them want to sleep a bunch of people. Where do I find those? Where do I find those videos and
clips? You'd be like, hey, have you heard the new Ariana Grande song? You have to listen to it for
eight hours straight and you have to call in sick to work. But here you go. Let's just move
let's just move on to the next star. So
there are no forests. Now when you hear that phrase, you're like, what? No, there's there are
forests to see them all the time. I saw Robin Hood and there are forests, obviously. But what we think
are forests aren't forests, they're bushes. There's just a bunch of bushes in a confined area,
like a hedge maze. So when you go to like Yellowstone, it's just bushes everywhere.
And you go to what's another famous forest. Or you go back to Yellowstone, you go there again,
it's just bushes everywhere. The real trees have all been cut down. And you've seen these
trees. They're called mountains. So what this theory is is that trees, the mountains, the
mountains that we see used to be giant trees. And if the mountain is like craggly, it's because the
tree fell over. And I can show you a photo of a tree that fell over with a craggly stump.
And then I can show you a picture of a mountain that's all jagged and they look exactly the same.
So then you go, Jason, that doesn't make sense. And I go, well, I didn't finish showing you photos
on a podcast yet. Maces, plateaus, those are trees that have been cut down. Did you know that?
Those are trees that have been cut down. Because I can show you a picture of a stump
of a tree that's been cut down. And then I can show you a picture of a mesa.
I go, hey, look at it. It looks the same, doesn't it? These two things that are made of
completely different materials, completely different sizes. Guess what? These pictures
look the same. And then you go, Jason, that's quite clever. You're right. You've shown me now four
photos and I'm quite convinced. However, what about volcanoes? Hmm? I've never seen a tree with
hot lava in it. And I go, wait, hold on. Volcanoes, the hot lava is nuclear waste. And it's a chemical
waste that's burning in it. And they basically just put waste in the trees slash mountains.
And then you go, whoa, whoa, whoa, who's they? And I look at you and I go, the giants, of course.
So what this theory is, it's an offshoot of flatters, but it's actually gaining steam among
other conspiracy theorists is that mountains and maces and all that stuff used to be giant trees
that went 10, 20 miles up into the sky. And we could calculate it, they would go that high because
of the size of the base. And what we're seeing basically to the giants of the old world, that
our forest, our puny little Homo sapien forest would look like just little bushes or weeds compared
to these 10 mile high trees. The giants who used to live here, not only cut down the giant trees
and use the wood to do giant stuff, I guess, they also all of the gorges of the world
or quarries impact sites, a meteors, nope, quarries. That was actually giant stinging stuff out of the
ground. Did you know that if you look up at the map of the earth, that all the deserts,
all the main deserts of the planet are in a line? And that's not because the way that the equator goes
around and the temperature differential and certain, no, no, no, no. It's because that is where
the giants threw all their sands from digging. I'm not making, well, I'm not making this up.
Somebody did. This is a really fast growing conspiracy theory. So deserts are where the
giants like they dug up a quarry, they dug up the Grand Canyon and then hauled the dirt to the Sahara.
It's ridiculous. And I also might push, well, there's a thousand pushbacks on this, but why is
it that it seems that every gorge has a river running through it? It's not because the river cut the
gorge. It's because the giants did. Now, what's weird about this theory, other than the fact that
people are trying to claim that there are no forests, is that, you know, I've talked to a
couple people about this one. I'll run into people and they'll say, what are you working on for your
next episode? And I'll say, there are no forests. Trees used to be giant and I go into the whole
spiel I just went into. And I've had more than a few people go, hmm, I'm like, what do you mean?
Like, hmm, they're like, it's a very comforting thought. It's like, what? Because, you know,
I approach this stuff, like I said, as I'm reading it, I'm thinking, okay, I'm going to go into the
mindset of someone who believes this. And then I start to shred it apart. But when you throw out
conspiracy theories to people who don't normally talk about conspiracy theories, they can have a
wide range of reactions. Oh, and I want to say right now, this story comes, I've heard about this
conspiracy before. But the idea for doing this as a story comes from Matthew, from Gmail. So
Matthew sent me an email saying, hey, you know, I saw this on 4chan, why don't you cover this?
And so I appreciate that I always appreciate people throwing up story ideas. Jeff was also a
recommended story. So thanks, Matthew. I talked to a couple people and they were like, hmm.
And I read an article. And it was interesting, as I was doing my research, this article was saying,
it was talking about it in conjunction with Flat Earth. They said, there is something comforting.
There is something comforting to know that the world was once more lush and vibrant and beautiful
than it is today. That nature was so out of control that trees could grow to touch the night sky.
And we're living on the husk. We're living on a planet that's a husk. And when we look around,
then we see wildlife being taken away and housing developments go up. And I think that's why this
has taken hold. The first real, this is a fairly, fairly recent conspiracy theory. It started with
a YouTube video from like Crimea. That's really where it kind of took off. And then an English
translation of the video came out. And since then, it's really taken off. Now, yeah, 2016 is when
this conspiracy theory took off. So it was about two years ago. So this video came out and it
basically was a video showing a stump of a tree and a mesa and saying, name 10 differences.
You can't, you can only name two, material composition and size. Look at these hexagons.
This can't be done by anything other than a tree. This, look at this. And the thing is,
it's the same thing with Flat Earth where they'll throw out, like I'm watching the video and they're
like, look at how this stone is like a hexagon. This is impossible anyway other than a tree. Now,
I don't know a lot about how trees grow or how rocks form. So if I didn't, if I, one, if I was
already suspicious of the scientific community or two, I really didn't care. I would watch them go,
whoa, yeah, he's right. That is how only trees can look like that. But when you look into the
science of it, they'll go, no, you know, it has to do with like this type of flow and this type of
composition of rock and the weathering and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. They've done hundreds
and hundreds of years of research on why these rocks form the way they form. But to know that,
I'm going to have to go and Google a bunch of stuff or I could just watch this video and you
just throw out fact after fact after fact after fact and it wears you down. Sometimes the, the
knowledge barrier between the laymen and the scientists does get a little impenetrable. So
you bounce back, you hear the conspiracy theory, you try to research it scientifically. You don't
really get it and then you jump back down to the conspiracy theory. I think that's why stuff like
these things really take hold. Also, it is something that you can look at something and go,
I don't see a horizon on the planet. People are telling me there is a curve, but I don't see it
at all. So any information I get is going to be based on my physical senses. I can look at this
photo of a mesa and look at this photo of a tree and they look the same and I know trees can get
petrified and turned into rock. Using my knowledge of science, I can make that comparison. And the
weirdest thing is the people who say there are no forests say, oh no, there are regular mountains
too. Just some of the mountains were giant trees. What? So how do I know which ones? Because see
some of them just peek out. They don't look like broken jagged mountain ranges. It's just
a giant mountain. And they go, no, no, Mount Everest is real, but this other mountain used to be a
tree. We'll see what type of traction this conspiracy gets. I honestly think it's going to take off.
I think it's going to get really, really big because I think people find it very charming to
think we live in a planet that is not living up to its full potential. I was reading an article
there actually saying that a lot of old myths are based around the idea of, you know, Tiamet,
who we talked about during Anticosmic Satanism, but I think he's from Babylonian mythology.
He died and our world is based on his guts. Like our world is created from his death.
And they were talking about other creation myths where something had to be destroyed for the world
to become what it is. And they're saying that that's another reason why this idea is so attractive,
because we're living in this world that is simply a ghost of the power it used to be.
I think it's going to take off. I think Flat Earth is fairly easy to debunk because you can just be
like put a GoPro on a balloon or whatever. And they go, no, the GoPro lens, it's fish-eyed, fish-eyed,
but you can say, people go, well, no, of course I'm a globe because it took a plane from here to
there. However, I did see a mesa once and it looked like a tree stump. I think that this may
overcome Flat Earth as far as the most popular dumb conspiracy theory, because it has a natural
attraction, the visual evidence is there, and the scientific language to explain how, I mean,
you can explain how gorges are formed, but then people are like, well, what about this? And what
about, it's like with 9/11. They are never happy. You explain one thing, they're like, what about
this? What about this? What about this? Eventually, scientists go, well, you know, we have a theory
about that and people go, a theory? That means it's not true. I believe that giants mind that,
gorge, and the science just walks away. Well, how do these hexagons grow in this plateau? Well,
it went like this, went like this, went like this, and then we have a theory theory. It used to be
a tree. So get ready for a whole slew of books, videos, all sorts of stuff on this thing. Trees,
are bushes, mountains, are trees, and the desert was dirt from all the quarries of the world.
It does have a nice magical ring to it. Middle Earth, Pandora, these worlds of just like unbridled
nature. But we have to accept it's not true, as much as it sounds nice, because that's just
it's foolish. It really is foolish. A mountain is not and never was a tree.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/deadrabbitradio. Twitter is @jasonoparpenter.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye.