Today we take a trip to New Jersey to find the portal to hell and then we take
a look at an urban legend that we've all heard but turns out to have more
gruesome origins than we could have ever imagined today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio I'm your
host Jason Carpenter I'm having a great day I hope you guys are having a great
day too I almost feel like I have to record this episode as quickly as
possible. My laptop is making some clicking sounds the hard drive is doing
the little bit of the click. You know I've all you know my the
Ravatron 3000 is out of commission right now I have to order my power
supply for that I probably should do that tonight. You know if the laptop goes
and I don't have the power supply for the desktop yet my backup plan is as
odd as this may sound is just to record many episodes on my phone many as in
small not many as in numerical just to keep the show going so hopefully we
don't come to that hopefully don't come to that I don't have enough money to buy
a laptop I do have enough money to buy a power supply for the Ravatron but my
concern is is that when the power supply went out on the desktop that it's not
just the power supply that went out that it may have taken the motherboard with
it and so then that would be an additional cost and all that stuff so
that's what's going on so if you notice a huge drop in audio quality in the
coming days it's because I'm recording it on my phone but let's go ahead and get
started with this episode but let's go ahead and get started with this episode
here now this episode is supposed to be I feel like I'm totally losing the plot
on the show these past two days because one I actually really liked yesterday's
episode but this is day two of me trying to deal with this nicotine withdrawal I've
basically just been sleeping all day long and eating my weight in chewy chips
ahoy cookies I'm more cookie than man at this point but I know I'll be fine in a
day like I know it'll all be over in a day so I'm just gonna have to write this
out I sat here for an hour in the silence of my apartment thinking should I
just go buy some more chewing tobacco that'll at least I'm not on the Los
Angeles anymore right and I'm thinking Jason that's stupid but I had to let my
brain go through that entire hour-long process to not do it super bizarre and
I was bargaining with myself I was like I'll go back on keto right now go back
on keto right now if you go and buy some chew and then like and then go back up
see the problem is I have an oral addiction so that's what I that's really
what I need to get rid of because when I was chewing the tobacco when I went to
the Los Angeles and now I'm like I'll just eat food for the next couple days as
much food as I want and then I just have to get over I can't keep having these
oral fixations because then it's the two things that I can't do I can't overeat I
can't be on nicotine so anyways all of that being said let's go ahead and get
started with the episode let's go ahead and get started with the episode if this
one might be short I might cut out the urban legend story I don't know because
again I was feeling fine I'm until the point I started recording and now I'm
like feeling like super anxious like I want to claw someone's eyes out so let's
go and get started with the first story and possibly the only story right now
thanks guys for sticking with me this won't be a long-term thing if I go back
on the chew or I start doing the Los Angeles again I just start doing it
again and we regroup later but for right now I have a patch nicotine patch taped
to my foot that's where we're at right now so let's go to New Jersey let us all
jump in the Jason Jalopy we're gonna take a long car ride from Oregon to New
Jersey now so in New Jersey in the city of Somerset County sorry this is not a
city in the township of Bernard's Township in Somerset County New Jersey
there is a mountain road or the mountain road or mountain road might be the
name of it and on this road is a tree but not just any tree not just any tree the
devil's tree don't don't don't I should say now that pretty much all the
information I have involving this tree is from backpacker verse backpacker verse
is a website that we've covered before that just basically seems to make stuff
up out of whole cloth just totally fictionalizes the whole thing and you're
like Jason you're probably only gonna cover one story this episode you're
covering a story that is from a website that you know is fraudulent just roll
with it guys just roll with it I'm starting to develop like hot sweats
right now just think of it this way guys think of this episode as a cautionary
tale towards getting addicted to anything just a think of it and think of it
don't don't get addicted don't get addicted to anything don't get addicted
to happiness or joy or love anything because somebody you'll have to wean off
of it anyway so backpacker verse backpacker verse is this website we've
covered a couple times now although the fact that they make most of the stuff up
I don't know if this is made up or not this one might be true but whether or
not it's true it actually has the best tree intro I've ever read and I can't
say I've read a ton of them but I was like this is the best intro I've ever
read and it made me think it made me think so let me read it to you this is
from the website this from the article trees have been symbolic motifs some
nice words there trees have been symbolic motifs since the dawn of time
ranging from creation stories including the Tree of Knowledge in the Bible and
Yadrassil the world tree in North North some mythology to the Buddhist Bodhi
tree and ancient tales about being people being transformed into trees like
this is quite the overview quite the overview we're not even finished yet the
majority of these tales have been mostly positive and charming which makes the
following report one of the darker if not the darkest story involving a tree and
it's funny cuz I read that and I thought that's not true there's plenty of
stories where trees are bad or dark dark tree stories and actually sat in the
coffee shop and I thought I can't think of any like what is the worst tree story
that you've ever heard now obviously lynchings are gonna be high up on there
but this story has that so you're thinking what and I was thinking well I
mean the chop down a tree and turn it into a cross they cross my Jesus on that
but I think that's kind of stretched because then because then you can say
like a tree got chopped down and became a guillotine like I think they're talking
about actual trees but it did make me think yes since the beginning of time
the trees are a symbolic motif used in all of these things we don't really have
any bad tree stories this might be one though this might be one Bernard's
Township so little Township out in the middle of New Jersey has this tree no
one is the Devil's tree so the local legend is that Bernard's Township used
to be the headquarters for the KKK in the entire state of New Jersey they all
came here to do their KKK stuff the Ku Klux Klan if you don't know what that
means and you know originally they were supposed to be the ghost of dead
Confederate soldiers that's why they were kind of dressed in those white
gowns they're supposed to be spooky ghosts that would chase people off their
land and then they just basically became an unarmed militia so anyways that was
the legend whether or not that's true we don't know for sure but according to
backpacker verse it is if it's not I think Bernard's Township has a really
good lawsuit actually you know I think that the Devil's tree is actually a
real tree because they are photos of it there are photos of it but again it's
this website kind of adds a little bit of flavor to this stuff so if any of
this article is incorrect and you happen to work for the City Council of
Bernard's Township I will be a witness during the trial because this definitely
makes it look like a place I will not go headquarters to the KKK and because it
was the KKK they're hanging people from the tree so that was where like this was
the tree they picked it was out in the middle of nowhere that's where they would
hang up all the black people so what is interesting about that a lot well let's
think about this logically it is the headquarters of the KKK for the entire
state of New Jersey how many black people do you think we're living there
in Bernard's Township to begin with think it logically think about that so they
would have to then import people from other cities to hang there like I don't
get it I don't get I don't get that like if you are the headquarters of the KKK
you're not gonna pick a diverse city to to set up in you're gonna find the
widest place possible and then you're gonna run out of minorities to hang
quite quickly so then you're gonna have to import I this is getting grim the
logistics of the lynching history is getting grim but again I'm dicey on
whether or not that it happened at all but now we get another famous website
that we've covered in the past that just puts out like the most bizarre stuff and
not in a good way not bizarre stuff like the Ocean and the Night or Ageless
Travel they'll put out stories that just don't make any any sense when you think
about electrically weird New Jersey also has teamed up with backpacker verse to
cover this story weird New Jersey is a monthly or I think it's monthly like an
online magazine they might have a print version we got we got tingled up with
them huh that is a pun intended when we were looking at spider gate cemetery and
they just wrote the weirdest stuff the weirdest weirdest stuff anyways weird
New Jersey comms states that people had driven by and seen ghosts hanging from
the tree so the idea was that there was ghosts of the people that had been hung
there by the clan but they also stay in there's no attribution to this because
otherwise I'd be able to list the link backpacker verse has a nasty habit of
saying where New Jersey says and they'll have a hyperlink and you'll click on it
and it'll be like 15 definitions of the word says so it's like they trick you to
thinking that if you click the hyperlink it takes you to back up what
they're saying they did that they do that all the time it's super frustrating
but anyways they say where New Jersey says that people were seeing ghosts of
black people hanging from these trees but at least one time it turned out that
what happened was the local football team at Bernard's Township hung effigies of
the rival team from that tree now I do like logical answers if someone's
driving by and they see a silhouette and they think it's the ghost of a black
dude hanging from a tree and then they find out that it's a team a football
team that was hanging effigies I do like it when we're able to logically have
these things spelled out my question is okay if we accept everything that's been
said is truth right now how much do you have to hate your rival football team
to hang them from a tree where historically black men and women were
hung from like that's a love that is a level of hatred that is nearly barbaric
like I can't imagine hey I can imagine it may be hating somebody or an
organization like that but not a rival football team the only difference
between you and them is they live in a different neighborhood and so they're
attending that school but think about it you hate this team so much that you're
like you know what we should do we should steal their mascot and they're
like no no no no we should like throw eggs at their car no no no and some guys
like know that tree that they hung all those black people from let's hang them
from let's make dummies of that team and hang them from a tree where multiple
people lost their lives only due to their skin color and everyone else just
feels that's a great idea why didn't I think of that let's do that so bizarre so
you've got this tree that may or may not been accused by the clan that may or may
not have been used by a football team but we'll accept both of those is true
because whatever the point of this episode as much as it's gone off the
rails is that it's known to be now a portal to hell it's not just any tree
it's not just a lynching tree it's not just a tree that is inappropriately used
by high school football teams so anyways the that all being said there's
apparently a legend of dude kills his family hangs himself from the tree makes
the tree haunted or the tree was already haunted and it commanded him to do that
but technically when where he killed the people like he should if you're gonna
make these legends up the tree should have killed the people the tree not like
it's walking around like an int throwing boulders at him but it's like he shoots
the family and then he hangs himself you'd think where the innocent people
were killed would be more haunted than the tree where the evil man hung himself
unless like his spirit went into the tree but if we're making it up just make it
up to the tree possesses people they can tell that they're possessed because they
they stand there all the time they have to console they're constantly
dehydrated they're like I have to drink water have to drink so much water and
they're like why aren't you eating anything is like yeah anyway I joke
went nowhere also people say that if you touch the tree trust me this is going
somewhere this isn't totally this isn't as rambly as he thinks it is people say
that according to the website if you touch the tree it's still there if you
touch the tree you get an oily stain that is nearly impossible to wash out I
call 100% BS on that there'd be tons of photographic proof you'd have chemist
out there you'd have all sort of scientists out there being like what is
this amazing pain thing like a paint that never wears out they'd be suckin the
tree dry of stuff it's totally at parts one I can guarantee that parts 100%
made up there is nothing on the planet that you touch that is super oily okay
that's not true there's lots of stuff on the planet that may be impossible to
wash out but this tree isn't one of them absolutely 100% fake made up backpacker
verse I'm so tired of this one woman this is hilarious according to this
website one woman unsourced put her ear to the tree for whatever reason it's a
haunted tree that is so oily it can possibly stain your your skin black
yeah go ahead and put your ear up to it this woman puts her ear up to it she
heard the sounds of screaming from inside the tree so again of course that
either she can hear termites she made it up or it's true and you would have
ghost crews out there they'd be hooking microphones up to it and all this
stuff like that and you're thinking Jason you're being a little harsh and or
kind of beating the dead horse that is the devil's tree but hold on getting
somewhere give me a few more minutes of your time before you click up now also
they say that nowadays if you get too close to the tree a black Ford like a
black Ford pickup truck like an old-timey pickup truck shows up like just
drives up the road and watches you for a while but then once you notice the
trucks there it drives away now that is such a stupid detail I don't think it's
made up they call him the Sentinel from hell like people and not they people
have said oh maybe that's like the devil's guard keep an eye over the tree
make sure no one's messing with it but I'm thinking what kind of Sentinel just
drives away when you notice it but you know what's funny that is such a stupid
detail and it doesn't have like when the way that this website normally works is
and then the doors of the car opened up and blood spilled out everywhere and
then you were the blood you'd be like what blood fills everywhere and then like
a bunch of bats fly out of the glove compartment or whatever they always make
stuff up so I'm thinking this detail almost seems so lame it's probably true
this car shows up watches you for a bit drives away now again that's not super
suspicious but it's also not totally normal it's kind of like in between so
you go Jason why did you talk about the devil's tree for nearly 20 20 minutes
I'm sure I'm gonna edit out a lot of that but he talked about this devil's
tree for 20 minutes you tease us with an urban legend story that I'll talk about
tomorrow this tree is real I know that for a fact and now it is encased in wire
and fencing you can't go near it can't go near it at all covered in graffiti
people have tried cutting it down people have tried touching it people have tried
listening to it and it is protected from all of that now so that's when I thought
okay there might be something to this a tree is a tree is a tree yes I get it
some people don't like trees getting chopped down and some trees are like
this tree was around when Jesus was born I actually wonder if any trees are that
old but trees have been around for like this 500 year old tree this big-ass tree
just sitting in the middle of nowhere don't chop it down but if a tree was
known again and let's assume that the historical parts are true this tree was
used to hang people which is not a huge stretch of the imagination logistically
yes getting black people into the KKK headquarters into the city probably be
kind of difficult but I'm sure that people were hung and trees everywhere I'm
sure some trees were better suited for like you couldn't hang someone from a
fir tree right because they're like a Christmas tree like they have to have
branches but anyways just imagine Charlie Brown's Christmas and someone
going we can't hang anyone from that but that's you have to go find a hanging
tree so anyways the point being is that if you have a tree that historically
known to been used by the KKK why is it being protected the whole and that's the
thing that's the thing like I was reading off all this stuff and you're
thinking great Jason's just gonna end it with saying isn't that stupid but no I
think there's a reason why this tree is being protected I don't think it's
necessarily a portal to hell but what okay put on your little paranormal caps
but I'm a little paranormal caps with me here you work for a city council your
city council of Bernard Township and you've driven past this tree all your
life you get elected at the Township Council things are going good now when
you were a kid people used to hang out by the tree and tell ghost stories about
the tree and stuff like that as you got older and kids got ready they started
spray painting the tree and stuff like that you have this group this
conservation group come to you and say we need to protect this tree this tree is
like part of our local heritage you have to protect this tree and you're thinking
it's just a tree for one and two the heritage that we know of is not something
we really want to be associated with we know the stories that black people were
hung from it during the dark days of this city and the state and in conservationists
are like no no no no like you have to understand like this tree is a living
thing we have to protect it yes it may even used against its willful horrible
things but this tree is a living thing so you got so you can't chop it down you
can't move it it's not an again not an aunt that's the I love the ends but anyways
it's it's there so you have a couple different choices you can put a security
guard up you can hope and educate people enough to preserve the tree
themselves or you can surround it in fencing and in case it almost in metal
around the trunk around height human height size so they can't do anything to
the tree that would damage it permanently or even just to face it but
the whole time as a city council person you would think why is this even worth
the money like why is this even worth our time discussing about it's just a dumb
tree it's just a stupid tree and trees get chopped down all the time trees get
initials carved into them trees older than this have been chopped down so why
do we care about this and then that's when you get another visitor from the
conservation group and they say listen the trees a tree tree you're right there's
millions billions of trees on the earth cutting down this tree to facing this
tree won't change anything but the stories about the tree are more than just
stories and you kind of laugh you know you've heard these stories all your life
but person you're talking to is just stone-faced and they say a story is
about the tree are true we don't know how we don't know why but it appears to be
some sort of not necessarily portal but some sort of containment device it does
leak some sort of oily substance we can't identify it we've heard reports of
people saying that they're screaming if you put your ear up to it and we can't
necessarily verify that but we've had more than one report and I heard it as
well we could chop down the tree we could have let every ghost hunter in the
state every ghost hunter in the nation here these rumors come out here begin
poking around at the tree and identifying all of this stuff and making it this big
ghostly landmark verifying this verifying the noises verifying the oil
verifying the apparitions that have been seen from the tree we can have all of
this stuff happen and then we're going to have national attention on this tree
that we don't know what will happen when we cut it down or when it burns down or
when someone cuts it in half we don't know or we can pay $200 put some fencing
up around it and forget any of this ever happened it'll be relegated to some sort
of local legend that people will believe in some website may talk about it some
podcast may talk about a couple YouTube videos and that'll be it there'll be no
way to verify it because you won't be able to get close to the tree I'm not
worried about the conservation of the tree is some sort of article of nature
I'm worried about the conservation of this town and what will happen if we
chop that tree down or if it gets damaged in some sort of way so I'm going
to ask you again to protect that tree because we don't know what'll happen if
you don't the tree is protected from anyone to touch it or cut it down or
deface it a local legend true portal to something else something dark and deep a
symbol of how evil humanity can become or something worse than all of those
put together we may never know but all that fencing and all that protection
around the tree may be to protect us from it
dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit
us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is @jasonocarpenter
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime
podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it
today
you
(upbeat music)