What happens when you mix teenagers, millions of dollars, and a loaded handgun?
And then we take a look at the story of a man who stabbed another man.
Now, the victim was drunk, the victim was harassing a 9 year old girl, and the victim was acting by all accounts extremely agitated.
Normally it would be a clear cut case of self-defense.
But when Ed and Lorraine Warren find out about the crime, all bets are off.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys are having a great weekend.
Or had a great weekend.
Although I guess if you live in a tight different time zone the weekend may still be going on, I don't know.
Or maybe it's already over.
Anyways, the point is, whatever you're in, whatever time or place or space you're in, dimension, whatever, hope you guys are having a great time.
I'm gonna start this episode off. I haven't done a Dead Rabbit Recommend in a long time.
This is gonna be really, really short. I just watched this movie last night.
I don't know what year it came out. I think it's fairly recent. It's called Head Count.
And for people who like creepy pasta, for people who like creepy short stories online, there's been a particular flood of a time.
There's been a flood of a particular creature called a skinwalker.
I know it has different types of names, but it's known to be a shape-shifting creature who like slowly learns.
Like let's say you go to a party with eight people and it can kind of affect your brain.
So eventually there's nine people there and no one can ever remember who the ninth person is.
Like they go, "No, no, no. That ninth person left the house. We came all the way up here with nine people."
And the person will always be like, "No, I know there's only eight. The movie headcount is that.
The movie headcount is this creature is summoned to this area.
And it's done a little bit differently where there's ten people at the party and the monster isn't fully human.
So it doesn't act human. Basically like it can assume human shape and it will stand in the corner of the room
or do something weird with its hand as it's like learning how to interact with humans.
In the background you see the actual human like playing beer pong,
but we're in the living room with this group of people and this creatures like playing a card game.
And it's, originally I wasn't going to recommend it because the ending was kind of cheesy,
but actually it's been about 24 hours since I've seen it and it stuck with me.
And I actually watched a movie after it and headcount had me so wound up
that I was watching this documentary called Kid Icarus, which is another good movie.
It's about a young filmmaker making his first short film. That's a really good movie too.
But as I was watching this documentary, I was looking in the background at other people.
So headcount is a really intense movie. I really recommend it.
If you're a fan of the skinwalker mythos, I would check it out.
If you're a fan of good contained horror movies, I would check it out.
It has some great visuals. It's creepy. It's not super scary, but it's a good flick.
I would definitely recommend checking out headcount.
So that's my beginning. That's my did or ever recommend.
Let's go ahead and get started here with this episode.
So this story actually just happened. This story happened on June 6th.
We're in Anchorage, Alaska. And let me say this is all alleged.
This is 100% alleged because it's such a recent thing.
Actually have written in my notes, "All alleged" in all caps.
So I don't keep saying, "That person sure is guilty.
Hey, better go to the electric chair."
So we're in Anchorage, Alaska. There's six teenagers in total.
We have Denali. We have Cynthia. We have Caden, Caleb, and then two other juveniles
who are too young to be named by the law.
Denali and Cynthia are really good friends and they'd say, "Let's all go hike.
Let's all go on a hike together."
Everyone's like, "Yay, let's go on this hike through Anchorage, Alaska."
I don't think they wanted to walk the Pacific mile or whatever.
They weren't going on this grand hike. They were just going up into the wilderness for a day.
Probably not even the wilderness, probably just the outskirts of town.
So they're on this hike and they're just walking along.
Now there's six people on this trip, but one of them doesn't know the real purpose of the trip.
At a certain point along the way, Denali pulls out a handgun.
And she orders the other four to tie up Cynthia.
Cynthia Hoffman was 19 years old. See where this is going.
And after Cynthia Hoffman is completely bound up,
Denali, who's only 18, pulls out a video camera and then shoots Cynthia in the back of the head.
Allegedly, allegedly. This is all alleged.
Dump her body into the river.
Now, it's really hard to get away with a crime of somebody you know.
It's really, really hard to kill somebody that you know.
If you're going to do it, don't do it, but if you do it randomly, it's a lot harder for them to catch you.
But if, you know, six people go on a hike and five come back, it doesn't take much to go,
"Hey, where's Cynthia?" And they're like, "Oh, we don't know who? Who are you talking about?
I don't know who you're talking about. That obviously won't fly."
And it didn't fly for them.
The cops begin looking for Cynthia because she's reported missing.
They find her in the river where they dumped her body, just floating around.
And they very, very quickly started arresting these teenagers.
So the first question you're going to ask is, "Why would you kill your friend?"
And Denali, allegedly, allegedly, this is what's come out.
Denali met a man online named Tyler.
This gets creepy.
Denali met a man online named Tyler, who's a millionaire.
And he began talking to Denali and he goes, "I'm a millionaire and I will pay you for some footage."
And Denali's like, "Okay, well, what footage do you want?" And he goes, "I want some child porn."
So first off, this guy online is asking her to start producing some child porn for him.
And she does that.
She produces two videos where she's molesting younger people.
And then he goes, "Oh, that's all well and good. But what I really want is I want to see a video of you killing somebody.
I'll pay you $9 million for that footage."
So at this point, allegedly, Denali's eyes popped out with little dollar signs on them.
And her tongue's like, "You know, like, I'm trying to make this part as light-hearted as possible."
It's involving some pretty heavy subjects anyway.
So Denali turns into a cartoon character and her eyes are like, "Ching!"
And she hatches this plan and she tells these four other kids, "If you help me kill Cynthia, I will give you part of my $9 million."
Now, obviously, I think you know where this is going.
So she gets caught, her friends get caught, they go, she starts telling them about Tyler.
They look on the computer, they find the child porn she made.
The police find Tyler. And his name's not Tyler.
His name is Darren Schillmiller. Darren Schillmiller. Only 21.
So here we have this range of people from 21 to probably about, we don't know how young the youngest people are involved,
but we have Denali's 18, Caden and Caleb are probably around the same age, and then two other juveniles.
So we're going to say probably like 15, because I think they can start naming them around 16 or something like that.
But, and Darren's 21. And they're all in jail now. Darren's getting ready to be extradited to Alaska for this trial.
They're both facing life for not only, Denali's facing life for the murder and the production,
I think 20 years for the production of child pornography.
And I don't know what Darren's being charged with, but he'll definitely be charged with the child porn charges,
and they may charge him as an accessory before the fact of a murder or whatever.
But I remember reading that article on the thing, and what a bizarre, like, it's almost just a comedy of errors.
The internet has allowed us to access people all over the globe, but it's also allowed idiots to access other idiots,
and cause like a foolish tsunami. Like Darren in his own hometown wouldn't have been able to convince somebody to do this.
And Denali wouldn't have been tricked by anyone in her hometown either, that they would pay her $9 million to murder somebody.
Obviously both these people are extremely broken in some way.
One, to want to watch that video footage and entice, and willingly lead someone down the path, entice them to murder.
And the other person, it probably didn't, allegedly, take much for her.
Like if someone came up to me and says, "I'll give you $9 million if you show video of you killing someone,"
I'll be like, "No. That trade-off's not good enough for me."
But, you know, these people are facing life in prison, and there's video footage, and there's evidence, and all these other people.
It's just a weird story, and it's just one, again, another one of those ways that the internet seems more like a cursed object every single day.
Allows me to do a podcast, but I don't know if that, actually, I don't think that trade-off's not worth it,
if it's going to allow effects like this to happen to affect people then, you know.
Well, that's the end of that story. That was a great segue, Jason.
That's why you're such a genius podcaster, because you come up with those brilliant segues.
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story here.
Now, the next story is really interesting, and it's one of those stories that's interesting on a few different levels.
One, let me just go ahead and get into it. Okay.
The year is 1981, and we're in the town of Brookfield, Connecticut.
Brookfield, Connecticut, tiny little town, I don't know, it might be a normal size or a big town,
but it's a town in Connecticut, February 16, 1981, two days after Valentine's Day.
A lot of people had a lot of fun on Valentine's Day, but now their hearts are broken, and they're...
You know what, here's a tip. Here's a tip for you guys.
Never buy the girl the giant teddy bear. Girls hate the giant teddy bear.
Girls loathe the giant teddy bear.
The only people who ever buy girls giant teddy bear, and I'm talking like human-sized teddy bears,
teddy bears that you could cut the stuffing out of and wear as a super Halloween, those giant...
Women hate those. I think at some point every guy has purchased a girl a giant teddy bear,
because we see it in movies, but don't do it, because now they have...
Generally, the only people who do buy it are people that guy...
They usually get them from guys that they don't like.
And I'll admit, I made that mistake. I bought a giant teddy bear for a girl who was an enemy,
and now they have actually... Now let me say it again, that's actually a perfect gift to buy someone you don't like,
because what you're doing is you're gifting them 200 pounds of foam and fur that they don't know what to do with.
They don't want to throw it away because that seems rude, but they can't...
There's no place they can put it.
So if you don't like a girl, if you want to get back at a girl, buy her a giant teddy bear.
But don't, guys, do not buy girls giant teddy bears.
I actually don't buy girls anything. I very, very, very rarely buy flowers.
I don't even buy chocolates, none of that stuff.
I'll buy candies for friends. If I'm dating you, that's your gift.
That's a gift that keeps on giving.
If you can get away with it, don't buy them anything, but if you do have to buy them something, don't buy them a giant teddy bear.
That... That rant had nothing to do with anything else. It's just a rant.
February 16, 1981. We're introduced to Debbie.
Debbie's sister, Wanda.
Debbie's nine-year-old cousin, Mary, and Arne.
So we'll get into Arne.
Well, okay, so Arne's a complicated fellow, but Debbie, Wanda, Mary, and Arne are all hanging out together on this day.
Debbie works at a grooming clinic. They all go to her job.
Now Debbie's boss is named Alan, and Alan says,
"Hey, you know what? Let's go out to... Let's go out to a bar. Let's go get drinks."
Now remember, this party includes a nine-year-old girl. There's so many weird details in the story.
100% true, though. At least this part is 100% true.
Alan goes, "Let's go out to a bar."
So after they all get sloshed and the nine-year-old girl's like, "Give me another milk."
And the bartender's like, "I'm done. You're calling it. You're 86."
And she's like, "Oh, she's fighting the bouncers."
And the nine-year-old girl, they go back to the grooming shop.
And while they're at the grooming shop, the girls say, "Let's go get pizza."
And I'm thinking, "Weren't they just at a bar?"
Now if I was reading this on any other website than the websites I read it on,
which was like Wikipedia and then a website specifically about this criminal case,
I would think, "Are they just making stuff up?"
But no. This was all revealed in court.
So they go out to a bar, they get hammered, then they come back to the grooming shop,
and then the girls say, "Let's go get some pizza," which maybe it's the soak up the alcohol,
but still, like, why don't you just order stuff at the bar?
Anyways, the girls go to get pizza.
And while they're there, they leave Arn with Alan.
And Debbie starts thinking, "You know what? That probably wasn't a good idea.
Let's hurry up and eat this pizza."
And they get our drinks refilled and have a salad bar.
And maybe we'll order some Sundays.
But anyways, after a certain point, they do decide to leave the pizza parlor.
They got like 100 tickets. They're like looking for stuff to get.
Debbie's like, "Oh, wait, I forgot. A horrible tragedy is coming up."
They leave the pizza parlor. They go back to the grooming shop.
And Alan is totally drunk. Six sheets to the wind. He's a louse.
"Bleh, I love you, man. I love you, Arn. I love you."
And he starts acting weird.
Now, Arn is already a little agitated himself.
But when Alan grabs Mary, because the girls have come back now,
they're bringing a giant teddy bear that they won at the pizza parlor.
The little girl is walking around. Mary's walking around.
Alan grabs the little girl and won't let her go.
He's totally drunk. He's now assaulting a little girl.
Not violently, but still. I mean, you're grabbing someone.
They want to leave and you're not letting them go.
And Arn starts being like, "Let the girl go, man. Let the girl go."
And Alan's like, "Never, never let her go."
But eventually, Alan does let her go because he's like, "Ah, whatever. I'll just let her go."
At that point, they're still saying that Alan is very agitated,
but Arn starts growling and then barking like a dog,
pulls out a 5-centimeter blade, little pocket knife,
and begins stabbing Arn violently, eventually killing him.
Arn flees the scene of the crime. He's arrested by the police.
Now, you can imagine Arn sitting in a jail cell and telling that story to a defense lawyer.
And the defense lawyer goes, "Oh, this is going to be open and shut." It's self-defense.
I mean, you have a little girl who was being assaulted.
You had a guy who was drunk and being belligerent.
You had one of his employees, Debbie,
thought there was such a problem that she left the pizza parlor "early" to come back
because she thought it would be a problem.
We have him grabbing a 9-year-old girl and not letting her go until you guys beg for him to let him go,
and then he's just acting agitated.
And you have the knife in your pocket. It's not like you had to go home or go to home depot to buy one.
Like, it was an instinctual act.
You acted in the defense of yourself and others around you.
Who knows what he would have done if he hadn't done that.
Open and shut case, self-defense were totally fine.
And then, just as Arn is about to agree that that's a great case, that's a great way,
Ed and Lorraine Warren bust through the door and go, "The devil made him do it."
Now, Ed and Lorraine Warren, quick overview if you don't know,
they're the ones that are featured in the Conjuring movies.
They are world-renowned psychic investigators.
They are world-famous for this type of stuff.
I think they investigated Amityville Horror.
She's the psychic investigator. She sees visions and she communicates with ghosts and she talked to Bigfoot.
We talked about that in an earlier episode.
Ed Warren is basically the guy who drives her around.
He's basically like, she has all the mystical powers.
He's the dude who's basically like, "Ah, just get in the car, honey."
I like to think that Ed Warren was a total skeptic and didn't believe any of this stuff,
but his wife was hot and really good in bed, so he just humored her.
Like, all good husbands do.
It's like when a woman's like, "Oh, I want to do scrapbooking."
And the husband's like, "That sounds like a great hobby, honey."
"You know it's a waste of time and money, but you're not going to tell her that."
And if she can make money scrapbooking, all the better.
So if your wife's like, "I can see ghosts. I can see the demons walking through the yard."
You'd just be like, "Oh yeah, honey, sure. It's perfect.
At least you're not scrapbooking."
So that is my version of the Warrens.
Probably not that accurate, but he probably believed in all this malarkey as well.
But anyways, so how did they get involved in this case?
So in 1980, we're going to meet Debbie's son, David.
David and Debbie move into this house.
They're rented this new place.
And I got really confused about how Arne knew these people
because he just kind of seemed to pop in and out of the story, almost like an oracle character.
He just kind of showed up halfway through, but apparently he's her fiance, Debbie's fiance.
So David's stepdad. Whatever, soon to be stepdad.
So Debbie, Arne, and David get this rental property.
And this is so funny.
So David's there. He's kind of cleaning stuff up and he's like, "I don't want to clean up."
And then this old man approaches him, right?
This old man appears out of nowhere and begins like pushing David and like knocking him down.
David's like trying to stand up and this old man's like putting him down and be like,
"You gotta leave, kid. You gotta leave. Go away. Go away."
And David's like, "Oh man, get off of me, dude."
And he's pushing. Nobody sees this happen.
But David runs to his mom and says, "I don't want to live here.
I was just working cleaning up my room and an old man came into my room and started beating me up."
And Debbie and Arne's response is, "Quit making up stories.
We know you don't want to clean stuff up. Quit being lazy.
Go back in that room where you may or may not have been assaulted by an old man and finished cleaning up."
Like they assume that he's just being lazy when the kid's like,
"Some stranger just came in and assaulted me."
So they totally don't pay attention to this kid, which I found absolute.
Talk about a soul crushing experience.
You're like, "Yeah, you don't want to do it, but you're like cleaning up your bedroom
and an old man climbs through the window and just totally just like beats you up."
And then you crawl out and you're like, "Mom, I got beat up."
And they're like, "Go to your room." That's so bizarre. They just totally brushed that off.
But they moved into the house and they started hearing creepy noises in the attic.
And David's like, "It's the old man. It's the old man in the attic. He wants us to leave."
And they're like, "Listen, we know you hate the place, but you don't have to be a jerk about it.
There's no old man." They're finding like, an oval teen all around the house.
They're finding dentures and he's like, "No, look at this is old man stuff."
So David starts having nightmares, which is a given.
He's being assaulted by a man no one else can see.
He starts acting weird. He starts barking.
And then after all of that stuff, finally what clues Debbie and Arne that something's going on,
he's appearing with scratch and bruises.
After all that other paranormal stuff, finally he comes home with a scratch.
And they're like, "It's a ghost!"
So they end up calling some priest to come and do an exorcism on the home.
And they also call up the Warrens.
Now the Warrens, I've talked a little bit about them earlier, but I want to take another note out.
They've been criticized for being like, looking for cash cows.
They've been criticized for looking for people with whom or from whom to make money.
I find it very suspicious that first you call up the priest in your area,
and then your second phone call is to the most famous psychic investigator and her husband at the time.
So there could have been some sort of financial thing in there. We'll get to that in a bit, but they call up the exorcists.
They call up Warren.
This has been only 12 days since the old man first appeared to David and started her like,
"rassling him in his bedroom."
Lorraine shows up and she goes, "Oh my God, I see something.
I see a black mist standing behind your son."
It's just kind of rolling his eyes. He's like, "Oh, again with the black mist."
Nothing's ever original with you, Lorraine.
So she says there's an evil entity following the boy around.
And she said, this is again one of the stories that she's watching in her psychic mind,
i.e. her imagination.
She's seeing David get beaten up and then David's like, "Oh!"
And he takes his shirt off and he's covered in bruises.
And Lorraine's like, "That's weird. That's what I just imagined in my head, was you getting punched?"
Then a bruise showing up.
So they basically are like, "Okay, we've got to do an exorcism on this kid."
For some reason they come to the conclusion he's possessed with 43 demons, 43 demons in this little boy.
And they're saying he's growling and he's hissing and he's reciting Bible verses.
And then passages from Paradise Lost.
I mean, there's no verification of any of that.
But anyway, so I was reading this one article and they go,
"How would an 11-year-old boy know about..."
Did I say how old he was earlier?
"How would an 11-year-old boy know passages from Paradise Lost?"
And I thought, how would an adult know passages from Paradise Lost?
Like, if someone could come up to me and start quoting Paradise Lost and I'd be like,
"What? What are you talking about?"
If someone could come up to me and go, "Truly, this was a Paradise Lost."
I'd be like, "What is that?"
Is that from an episode of Transformers? I don't get the reference.
Yes, an 11-year-old kid may not know a quote from Paradise Lost, but most humans wouldn't.
So I think it's a made-up detail.
I think that detail is just made up to make it more scary.
So Ed and Lorraine Warren and the local priests end up exercising the boy of these demons.
And then on their way out of town, basically, Lorraine calls up the police,
the local police, and say, "This might end badly."
So keep an eye on that family.
And the reason why she had her suspicions was,
"Tell me if this isn't the biggest bone-headed move ever."
Let's say that you believe-- I believe in demons and I believe in demonic possession and stuff.
Like, maybe this kid was possessed. I don't know.
He may have been possessed and some of the details are made up.
Well, actually, we'll get to that at the end, because this story has a real interesting twist to the ending.
No, it's not that it was all a dream.
So she called it-- this is the dumbest thing possible.
So you're standing in a room where your stepson, your soon-to-be stepson, is possessed by demons.
43 of them. And he's like, "Aah! Paradise Lost Quote! Paradise Lost Quote! Blah!"
And Arne starts challenging the demons to a fight, being like, "Hey, knuckleheads, why don't you come and take on a real man?
You're tired of-- you can't fight someone your own size? Why don't you come over here? I'll give you a 1-2."
And Lorraine Warren's like looking at him like, "What are you-- this kid's floating five feet off the bed.
There's five priests here throwing holy water at him, and you're sitting there maldun off."
But he did. Arne was like, "Yeah, man, come on. Why don't you go? Let's go, bro. Let's go."
And he basically-- Lorraine Warren, she called up the police and said,
"Something bad might happen to this family, because we're doing this extra-system.
Arne was maldun off to the demons, and one of them may have left the boy and gone into Arne."
Any-- I can just imagine the cop getting that phone call and just being like,
"Okay, ma'am, you have a nice day too." Click.
You'd be like, "Woo, woo, woo, what-- what world do you live in where you get phone calls like?"
I guess police probably do get crazy phone calls like that.
But he ends up saying, "Yes, I got possessed by a demon," and it was kind of in control of me,
but apparently there was a haunted well-- they ended up moving out of the rental property after all that,
but apparently there was also on this spooky, spooky rental property there was a spooky, spooky haunted well.
And he says he walked to the well one night all by himself after this extra-system,
and a demon rose out of the well and they looked eye to eye, and he goes,
"After that, I really don't remember much. Like, I was fully possessed after that point."
Which is a good way to get out of credit card debt, because then you could be like,
"Hey, I didn't buy all that stuff. I was demonically possessed."
And you think that's-- you think that's a stupid joke?
That's basically what happened, because after he kills Alan, the Warrens come back and they go,
devil made him do it. He was possessed by a demon, and he-- they go to the family.
They go to Debbie and this family, and they go, "Listen, we are going to prove in a court of law
that he is possessed by a demon. We're going to get these exorcists from Europe.
We're going to get all these hy-- We're going to subpoena the priest who were at the original exorcism
to say that he was doing this stuff. We're going to get all these experts from around the globe
to prove that the reason why he went out of control and stabbed that guy to death was he was possessed by a demon.
And you can imagine the family saying, "It would be much easier self-defense."
And Warren's like, "No, no, no, no. You're only looking at half the picture here."
Because when we prove that he was demonically possessed, not only will he be innocent,
not only will he not go to prison, book deals, movie deals, we'll have writers come out here.
I know this is not as big as the book deals and movie deals. I just ran out of stuff to list.
We will have cash coming in. This can be the next Amityville.
And Debbie goes, "You mean the next big hoax?" And the Warrens are like, "Wogah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
We know that it was irrelative and unscientific, but you could not ever prove someone was possessed.
Therefore, you can't use it as an argument in a court of law.
So then the defense lawyer goes, "Okay, self-defense. They have the trial, and there's a 15-hour deliberation.
He's found guilty." First degree manslaughter, he's sentenced to 10 to 20 years in prison,
but ends up only serving five in his back out. They did have a movie come out.
Tell me if this doesn't sound amazing. I need to find this movie. It's called The Demon Murder Case.
That's a pretty generic title, but it stars Kevin Bacon and Andy Griffith.
That's the original Conjuring. That's like the prequel to the Conjuring universe.
That sounds absolutely amazing. A book came out called The Devil in Connecticut.
Big hit. Not like a super big hit, but you know, it was relatively big.
Family didn't get a ton of money for it, but they got some, and the Warrens got some money,
so it definitely was a money-making venture. A man lost his life, but that was almost,
that wasn't part of the plan. But what's an interesting twist to the end of the story?
In 2006, they reprinted the book The Devil in Connecticut, which makes sense,
because now all the Warren stuff is getting big again. I think that's around when the Amityville horror came out,
or the haunting of Connecticut and all that stuff is getting, horror movies are getting big again.
They reprinted the book The Devil in Connecticut. David, the boy who was originally possessed
by the 43 demons, and his brother came forward and said, "None of it was true. It's totally fake.
That book actually is libelous, and it's an infringement on our privacy."
Because they were kids when this book was written, so they couldn't sign any contracts.
But now jump ahead, in 2006, their adults, they're working their professional lives,
and all of a sudden their buddies are like, "Hey, bro, heard you had 43 demons in you.
Like, they're sitting at the water cooler, and now they're being reminded of this made-up event that happened
20, 30 years earlier." So they sue. Now the family breaks in half, because Aaron is out of prison,
and he does interviews. He was on a Discovery Channel show talking about this particular case.
So he's out there talking about it. The boys, though, the young kids are like, "No, it was all fake."
The older people are like, "They just want their cut of the money, and they're not getting part of the hoax money."
I mean, the ghost money is what I meant to say. And eventually in 2016, it was settled out of court,
so we don't know how. They probably just gave the kids some money to shut them up.
So half the family says, "Totally fake. Never happened. It was a total cash cow.
We got ripped off by the Warrens. We were sold to bill of goods, and we went down this path, this legal path,
and it didn't work out." And the other half of the family, so you have David, the original possessee,
saying it was totally fake. And then you have Aaron, the guy who was challenging the demon of fight
and lost, saying it's real. Bizarre story. Totally bizarre story. Now you could say that the kid was too young
to really know what was going on, or that he was possessed. Maybe there's one more demon in him,
the demon of doubt and skepticism floating around in him. He turns to the camera and his eyes are like,
"Ahh." Not his eyes are laughing, but they like gleam. He's like, "Ehh, gotcha."
But it's most likely that it was a hoax, and even an 11-year-old boy realized that people were lying around him.
And you know, he probably was just like, "I'm just--maybe he made up--maybe he didn't want to clean up.
He made up the story about the old man, and then he just kept digging the hole deeper and deeper,
and then eventually he realized that his lies had already created a monster.
A monster of an old man that ended up resulting in the death of another man.
You--it's such a--I think the story's so interesting, because it's one of the stories that really blends the paranormal with the real world.
Was there really a demon of an old man running around this house, pushing kids, keeping them from doing their chores?
Which that sounds like a great Disney Channel movie. But was that really happening?
Did the kid make it up because he didn't want to do his chores, and then the story just got out of hand?
And right when he's here, they're like, "Hey, remember that whole thing with that demon jumping out of your body?"
And David's like playing Nintendo. He's like, "Oh yeah, that was a hilarious joke."
And they're like, "Yeah, I guess he went in an arn and he just stabbed a man to death, and then he just dropped the controller."
[imitates a demon]
If it was a hoax that got out--if it was a hoax that got out of hand and ended up with a man getting murdered,
because an other man thought he was possessed by a demon that came out of a haunted well,
if there was no old man ghost, no haunted well, no demons, just a little kid who told a story that just got out of control,
and then another dude just kind of bumbles into that story, and is like, "Yo, yo dude, ghost, fight me, fight me, demon, fight me."
And David's laying on the bed pretending he's possessed, and he's thinking, "Aren't you idiot? There's nothing here."
And then that guy, that arn guy, ends up murdering another guy while he's growling, being like, "I'm possessed by the devil, I'm possessed by the devil."
There's very few--if that is what happened, which is kind of my read on the situation.
Allegedly, I don't know, I don't--don't sue me, guys, but if that is what happened, the kid just made the story up, and it spiraled out of control,
this might be the worst example of the boy who cried wolf.
Is that--would that be it? The boy saying there's a demon, there's a demon, and no, I guess it would be the opposite of it.
This might be the worst example of someone telling a lie, and keep going along with the joke until it's not funny anymore,
until someone's bleeding out in their place of business.
And, if Arn honestly believed that a demon was inside of him, he may have been more prone to act out like that.
He may have thought, "This guy's making me really angry, and he's doing something that I don't like."
And normally, as a normal adult, I would leave the scene with this nine-year-old girl and my girlfriend--and my girlfriend's sister--
and call the police and let them handle this.
Because the situation was diffused, Alan let go of the girl, everyone can just leave.
But, if I believe there was a demon inside of me--
[Alan laughing]
If I believe the beast was inside of me, anything's possible.
[Alan snarls]
Sometimes the lies we tell ourselves to excuse our decisions can take control of us more than any demon can.
To this day, Arn still believes that he was possessed by a demon.
That it wasn't self-defense, it wasn't some sort of mental breakdown, it wasn't a child's trick gone wrong, that a demon actually entered his body.
So, in his mind, he never killed Alan. Something else did.
Which begs the question, if Alan is right, where's the demon now?
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
@deadrabbitradio is our Twitter now. Same Twitter, like if you're a current follower, it'll be fine, but from now on it's @deadrabbitradio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
[Music]