If you find yourself traveling down an unmarked gravel road in Alaska, you may find yourself
witnessing a terrifying and bloody sight.
And they would travel to Texas to visit the New London School District.
While the students were learning and the teachers were teaching, little did anyone know that
a tragedy was about to strike that would change the world today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carmoner.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I am having a great day but I'm sick and currently sick.
I don't know how much of my illness is spraying out of my mouth right now onto my microphone
and I don't know what it is.
Nowadays whenever anyone is even slightly under the weather, people go, "Is it COVID?"
I don't know.
It very well might be at this point.
I've just been getting kind of sicker and sicker.
I have some tests, COVID tests coming in tomorrow through Amazon.
So we'll find out but I mean again, like if I do have it, I'm hoping that it's just,
you know, nothing.
But I guess we'll see how much I sweat out while I'm in this closet while I'm recording
this episode.
Maybe it'll make me feel better.
Probably won't.
I'll probably get progressively more and more sick as the episode goes.
My morning, I didn't even go to work today which people who know me, it's like pulling
teeth to get me to not show up to work.
I spent about four hours watching Dragon's Den on YouTube.
That's pretty much been my entire morning and I said, "Okay, let's at least be slightly
productive here.
Let's get some work done."
So here I am recording another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio and someone who is joining
us this episode, walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our legacy Patreon
supporters.
Everyone give it up for Super Fine, Volpine.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in Super Fine, Volpine.
Welcome back to Dead Rabbit Command.
Super Fine, you're gonna be our Captain Art pilot this episode.
You guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
Trust me, I do.
Just help spread the word about the show.
You have no idea how much that helps out.
Super Fine, I'd probably say that's ten feet away from me for this episode but I'm gonna
toss you the keys.
So the Jason Jalopy, go ahead and catch him in your little furry foxy hands.
Let's all get on board, drive us all the way out.
Two.
Everyone hop on board, let's head all the way out.
Alaska.
Pup, pup, pup, pup, pup, pup, pup, pup.
Driving on up to beautiful Alaska, the snows falling, catching snowflakes on our tongue.
Doing all that stuff.
Maybe you should shut your mouth if you're in a car full of people.
Well, anyways, you guys tie me up in the trunk.
We finally get to Alaska, specifically we're headed to Chugyak, Alaska.
Chugyak, Alaska.
Now, Chugyak is an unincorporated area in Alaska.
You can find it on a map but it's not technically a city, it's just like a town that's sitting
there.
Now a days, it's a modern town, right?
The buildings, they have walls, they have things like that.
But back in the day, we're headed all the way back in time to like when this town was
first being set up, right?
You had to build your own house.
You had to go out to the woods and like chop down trees and then put them in order.
I've played with Lincoln Longs, I know how it's done.
But we're going to meet this family that's in this area and we have a father.
We're going to go ahead and call him Joey and then his daughter, we'll call her Madeline
and then there's a wife and a son and they're not really in the store so they don't even
get names.
So you have a wife and a son, little baby boy, they're back at home and Joey and Madeline
are out chopping down firewood for their fireplace because it's Alaska and it's super duper cold.
Now Madeline always loved to help her papa, right?
She was always like, "Dad, can I help you chop down those trees?"
And he's like, "No, of course not.
You're a little girl.
You can't do that."
And then she'd be like, "Dad, can I help you hunt bears?"
And he's like, "Absolutely not.
They'll eat you."
Although I could use you as bait.
But he loved his daughter, right?
So he wouldn't just, it was not the fact that she was constantly trying to help him out
that was annoying him.
He did love his daughter.
They went on these little adventures together.
On this particular day, he was chopping up firewood.
He was getting firewood, right?
This was back in the day when we don't actually have a date for this story.
This is one of those stories that just took place sometime before the 1990s.
Chopping down trees to make firewood.
So he's chopping down trees out in Alaska in the Chugyak area.
He's chopping down trees and then chopping up the trees to make it little logs, little
pieces of wood.
Cords of wood, I think is what they're going.
So him and his daughter can huff him back to the cabin and everyone could stay warm.
But as he's cutting all this wood down, making all these little pieces of wood, he, obviously
he needs to take a break because muscles are getting sore and stuff like that.
So he knows that he needs to rest.
He knows that he's a biological human and he needs to take a break every once in a while.
However, he's also smart enough and I'm sure experience has taught him that Madeline, his
five year old daughter, he needs to be aware that her eagerness to help out is sometimes
dumb, right?
Obviously with the bear example.
So as he's chopping down the trees and chopping down the wood and then he decides to take
a break, he takes his mighty axe and he cleaves it into a nearby tree.
A thunk!
And he did that specifically because he is thinking, okay, if I leave the axe on the
ground, Madeline's going to pick it up or she's going to trip on a rock and fall on
top of the axe or she'll slip in the snow, fall right on the blade.
Like she's just a clumsy kid.
I need to put this axe away.
I don't have a toolkit.
So he wedges it into the tree as hard as he can.
And then he leaves, not like he didn't go back home and leave her there, but he kind
of like turns his back to the tree and starts to walk away so he can sit down and enjoy
a break.
Well he's just turned his back for a few moments when he hears a sickening thud behind him.
The cold Alaskan air whips around him.
A squirrel is shaking his head.
Here's the sound of a squirrel going, oh no.
Is he shaking his head?
Joey turns around and sees his daughter laying face down in the snow.
The axe that he had wedged into the tree is laying next to her body.
And though Lily White Snow is quickly melting as warm human blood covers it.
Madeline, Madeline, he yells as he runs over there and he flips his daughter over and her
head has been cracked in two.
What had happened was Madeline did a Madeline thing and she saw the axe in the tree and
she goes, oh you know I know Papa needs to take a break.
I want to help.
I don't understand anything about human strength but I'm sure I can wield this axe and chop
down a couple trees.
And she grabbed the axe and he didn't let it in as much as he thought he had and she
grabs the axe and she actually pulled it down and it split her head open.
And when he flipped over his daughter her face is completely covered in blood.
It's still squirting out.
He's like, oh my new shirt, oh no my new shirt.
He picks up the body of his daughter.
I gotta get the jokes in when I can't because trust me this is the most lighthearted story
in this episode.
He picks up the lifeless body of his 5 year old daughter and begins sobbing, sobbing openly
over his little girl.
All she wanted to do was help out.
She cleaved her head in two and killed her instantly too.
There was no hope for this girl.
It wasn't like maybe I can get her to the doctor.
She was clearly dead immediately.
Apparently, according to the story, he sat there and held the body of his daughter and
never moved from that spot.
He mourned and wailed and sobbed for days and days and days until he finally succumbed
to hypothermia and died in the middle of the forest.
His daughter still cradled in his arms.
They say to this day, if you head out to this area, they say there is an unmarked road called
the Darker Road.
It's not on any map, but it's a gravel road and it's located in the Chugiaq area.
It's actually off of South Bertwood Road if you're in the area.
They say that to this day, if you drive out to this area after 3.30am, you may see the
ghostly image of this father still cradling his daughter.
Her face still dripping with blood.
Her lifeless corpse just kind of hanging their limp.
But the father's ghost is still wailing in the night, mourning the loss of his 5 year
old girl.
This is a really interesting ghost story for me because this is a story that, I mean again,
I got it on theshadowlands.net.
We don't know how much is urban legend, how much is real, what are the verified sightings
of this ghost.
But let's take a look at it as a ghost story.
You'll find this in other places other than theshadowlands.net.
But you know, did it actually happen?
Is it urban legend?
But let's assume that, let's assume for the sake of the argument that this is a ghostly
encounter that people do have.
Very, very fascinating story.
I think this would be, when I was reading this I thought, okay, I had to go back and
check a couple of times.
I was like, okay, I could see definitely any parent losing a loved one, losing a child
and not leaving the spot.
Like they just die of a broken heart.
Well he didn't die of a broken heart, he died due to exposure.
But I had to keep checking.
I was like, but he had a family at home, right?
Like he had a wife and a son at home.
And I thought, I go, I'm sure he was broken up about it.
I'm sure that he openly mourned for the loss of his oldest daughter for the rest of his
life, right?
It's something you really never get over.
But I'm sure he also knew that he had a wife and son at home and they needed the firewood.
Remember he's out there cutting firewood.
They're in Alaska.
I'm sure at a certain point he would have gone home, right?
Obviously would have went home and told his wife what happened and their lives would have
went on.
I don't believe that he sat there for days and days and days and days and died of hypothermia.
I don't even think it would take days and days and days and days to die of hypothermia
in Alaska.
But what I think this is, is this is a classic case of psychic energy recording an event
and playing it over and over again.
I believe the little girl soul has moved on and his soul has moved on.
What we're seeing is this moment in time frozen because of this raw psychic pain leaving its
mark on the universe.
If you went out to this area and saw this aberration, I don't believe you could interact
with it.
I don't believe you could talk to it or move it.
You're not taking selfies behind it.
You're like giving him bunny ears.
I don't think any of that could happen.
Even though he may be moving, even though his chest may be heaving and tears streaming
down his face, I don't think that you could interact with it in any sort of way.
I don't think it's a ghost in that sense.
And that can confuse a lot of people.
So if somebody came out here and saw the bloodied girl, you'd go, "Well, obviously she died
here."
And you're seeing the ghost of a man holding the body.
Now he could have died in Nebraska.
You know, him and his family could have been like, "You know what?
Let's go somewhere else."
They go down to California and find a bunch of gold.
They could have went anywhere else.
But what we're seeing is not his ghost and her ghost.
It's just a recording.
We are ghost aficionados.
If you're listening to Dead Rabbit Radio, you're not just a casual -- you just don't
have a casual interest in the paranormal.
People who listen to this podcast really know their stuff.
And that's why you listen to this podcast.
So I think that we know that there are different types of ghosts and there are recordings and
there are actual spirits and there are demons disguised as ghosts.
And they're just like mental illness or mistakes, right?
That there's not really a ghost.
But we can see -- I think what happened was people were seeing the separation in the area
and they made up the last part of the story.
They made up the part saying, "Oh, and then he died there, too."
Because that would be a way to explain why his ghost is there.
But it's not his spirit.
There's no one's spirit there.
It's just this image.
But to a casual person who doesn't have a lot of interest in ghosts, someone who's just
driving on this road late at night and saw that, they would go, "Well, she must have died
there because she's bloody.
She looks like she's dead.
And then he must have died there, too, because his ghost is there."
That's not how ghosts work.
Assuming this story is true, right?
This story could be complete urban legend.
I can get 100 emails after this episode's recorded saying as such.
But I think if the story is true, it's a perfect example of that psychic recording.
Because we talk about them from time to time on this show in general.
But also in general, they're quite boring.
A lot of times it's just a ghost -- there's no dead kids.
There's no bloody kids.
I'm like, "Boring!"
A lot of times it's just a ghost walking on a hallway or something like that or footsteps
down the stairs.
That's a recording of an event.
That doesn't really make for a good audio podcast.
But when a kid's been cleaved with an axe, you have such a dynamic scene, a man in the
snow cradling his kid.
Just for the record, and considering what I'm going to talk about on the next segment,
I'm not pro kids dying.
I just feel like I have to put that out here, out there.
But this is such a dynamic scene.
And it is a perfect example.
I don't believe -- I think both of their spirits have moved on.
But this left an indelible fingerprint in the landscape there.
So a creepy story coming out of Chugyak, Alaska.
If you do happen to see it, I don't think you could interact with it.
However, I would not put that to the test.
Don't go out there and go, "Jason said this is harmless and start kicking him in the head."
You figure your foot's just going to pass through him and then he gets mad and he starts
using his daughter as a club, trying to knock you down.
Don't put it to the test.
Don't put it to the test that Jason said it's harmless.
But I think it might be.
But again, I wouldn't bet money on it either.
I wouldn't go out there and start goofing over them either.
Superfine, Volpine, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the world famous Carbenter
copter we are leaving behind.
Chugyak, Alaska.
Take us all the way out to New London, Texas.
[imitates car engine]
This is a story -- really, this episode isn't what I talked about last week that I thought
was too depressing to have on a Friday.
I really don't know what happened on a Thursday makes it any less depressing.
We're headed back to March 18, 1937.
And we see a, as of the time, back in 1937, a state-of-the-art school.
This was -- New London was one of the richest school districts in the United States.
And the reason why was they had oil money.
So you had all these oil barons and all these oil pumps and all these oil workers and everyone
had a bunch of cash in their pocket.
So we're gonna build the best school we possibly could.
So they built the New London School.
Now, New London School was built back in 1932, and at the time it cost them a million dollars
to put together.
I don't even think a modern high school cost a million dollars.
And back then, that was equivalent to 19 million bucks to build one school.
Now the way it was built, this is a story that there's so many mistakes made.
And then we get to this huge cataclysm.
We get to this horrible event.
And you think any one of these things could have changed, and none of this would have happened.
But this is an interesting story because had this not happened, what could have happened?
What could have played out?
The New London School was built on a slope.
So what that meant was you had the school built.
It wasn't like a teeter-totter school.
You're like, "Oh, it's time to go to science class."
Everyone rolls to the other end.
It was built on a slope, so you had this giant gap of airspace beneath it.
It wasn't like a basement.
It wasn't any...
I mean, the building was built around.
You couldn't go skateboarding underneath it, but you had just like this giant empty space
between the ground and the school because it was built on the slope.
And this is oil town, baby.
You got oil, you got natural gas, you got all this stuff.
So when they were built in the school, they said, "You know what?
Hey, I got a good plan.
I got a good plan."
What if...
What about instead of building the building so we need to bring gas into the school?
So like our heaters need to have gas pipes going in and our ovens.
I don't know what else you would have in a school that would need all this natural gas.
But they go, "What if we just tapped into an existing natural gas line?"
Because we got them all around.
We're right in the middle of oil and natural gas fields.
Why don't we just have...
Why don't we just literally tap into one of these natural gas pipelines?
This is so insane.
Why don't we just tap into one of these natural gas pipelines so we're getting pure, unfiltered
natural gas into our school?
We'll save a ton of money.
We spent a lot of money building it.
And they say, "Yeah, it's a great idea.
That is a great idea.
We'll just use the resources we have around us, all this natural gas, to heat the building."
The thing is, is that prior to this event, and this event is the reason why we do this,
natural gas had no smell.
The store I'm about to tell you is the reason why when there is a gas leak you can smell
it.
Because naturally, natural gas is completely undetectable.
It's tasteless.
It has no smell.
Basically, you're walking around the canary and when the canary dies you leave.
That was the way you detected it.
Nowadays, they've added an ingredient into it so you can smell it and you can go, "Uh-oh.
There's too much natural gas in this area, which in most places is any, right?
You don't want any natural gas just floating around."
Because of what happened at New London School is the reason why you can smell natural gas.
It's odorless.
It's colorless.
You can't taste it.
But it does affect the human body, right?
It can kill you if you get too much of it in.
Now New London School, it was weird.
It went from K through 12th grade.
It was all of the possible age groups you could have in there, which I imagine the Boolean
would be hilarious.
You'd have seniors pranking second graders.
They're like, "Why are you picking on me?
Because you're younger throwing them in the toilet and stuff like that."
You also had a huge...
I don't know if they actually had a huge Boolean problem.
That's what I would have done.
But they also had a weird outbreak of headaches.
Students were constantly complaining that their heads hurt.
Now to the administrators, they probably figured, "Oh, you know, maybe it's flu season.
Is March?
No one to be a flu season in Texas?"
It's weird that people keep complaining of these headaches.
It also seems kind of weird that the shorter they are, the closer they are to the ground,
the headaches are worse.
But I don't know what could it possibly be.
Couldn't be that we have this massive crawl space that's 253 feet by 56 feet underneath
our school that no one ever goes to.
It can't have anything to do with that.
Or the fact that we're sitting on a bunch of natural gas or that we've tapped into said
natural gas to heat our wonderful school.
It would have nothing to do with that.
So kids are constantly walking around holding their heads.
And the administrators are like, "I don't know why you're complaining."
They're looking at these kids that are so short to the ground.
They're like, "What does my head hurt?"
And the six foot tall adults, I don't know.
Anyways, the epidemic of headaches continues for a while and nobody really knows what it
is.
No one thinks for a second.
It could possibly be the fact that these kids are inhaling natural gas all day long at school.
Well, on March 18th, 1937, it was 3.17 p.m.
Now the way the school was set up was that you had it divided, and most American schools
are like this, you had it divided into a set of different buildings, right?
You have a gymnasium, then you're going to have these buildings over here for administration
and these buildings here for certain grade levels and so on and so forth.
At 3.17 p.m., most of the school had been dismissed already from classes.
So K through 4th is gone at this point.
They've gone home.
However, you still had 5th through 11th grade, which I don't know if the school just went
to 11th grade.
That's weird too.
There's just had a senior ditch day this day.
But 5th through 11th grade was still in classes.
So we're talking about between 500 to 650 students are still in school.
And there's also 40 teachers there as well.
Now it's interesting to think, how do they not know how many students were there on that
day?
That's a pretty big gap in numbers, 500 to 650 students.
The reason why they don't have a clear number is because this was oiled field territory.
You had a bunch of traveling people who would work different jobs and they'd move their
families out to this oiled field.
They'd work there for a while and then they'd move on.
So we don't know for a fact because people would show up, take their kids to school,
go about their job for three months and then move on.
We don't know how many students were actually in this building.
There may be people who were victims of this event that were literally wiped out of the
history books.
Just completely vanished.
No one knows their names.
No one knows where they came from.
Between 500 and 650 students and 40 teachers are here at New London School, still attending
class about 100 feet away from the main buildings.
There's a gymnasium.
And in this gymnasium there's a PTA meeting going on.
So you have a bunch of parents and teachers here attending this.
Right a few students still in classes with their teachers.
And in the shop class, in the wood shop class, Lemmy Butler, the shop teacher, turns on
an electric sander.
People outside the school, because this is right in the middle of a residential area,
right?
People who are outside the school.
What they see is, you have this main school building where all these hundreds of students
are in and these 40 teachers, you have this main school building.
What they see is the walls bulge out.
You're looking at a building and you don't really hear anything at first.
You just see the walls bulge out of the building.
And then they bulged out in such a way that the roof fell completely into the building.
And then you watch the walls crumble in as well.
What happened was when Lemmy turned on that electric, this is what we assume, right?
This is kind of what they put together.
When Lemmy turned on that sander, it started an electric spark that ignited the natural
gas that at this point had completely filled up that massive crawl space.
And when he turned on that sander and that gas ignited, it was such a violent explosion
there was no flame.
The building just bulged out, the roof came down and then the walls collapsed in on it.
And people saw no fires.
There was no idea of what could possibly have happened, but this explosion, the sound of
it was so loud people could hear it 12 miles away.
People who did hear this, right?
People who heard this explosion began to head out to the area.
What in the world was that?
What could have made such a huge boom?
And as people start coming into the area, they see people running out of their houses
towards New London School.
As they're continuing to drive their car down the road, they see parents who would run out
of the gymnasium after this explosion, they're already digging through the rubble with their
bare hands.
You had calls go out to all of the oil fields in the area.
Grab your gear and get to the school.
And it was such a local event too, right?
This is a local school and the people who are trying to get the rubble out of the way
they're trying to save lives also knew the people in the rubble.
You had the story of a bus driver, Lonnie Barber, who was driving his bus just dropping
kids off.
It's another normal day when the explosion happens.
He continued his route, even knowing that he had four of his own children in that building
when it blew up.
He needed to get these kids home.
That was his job.
That was his duty, right?
And he goes along the route dropping off these kids until finally he gets to the school where
he is able to help in the rescue effort as well.
Out of the four, three of them were totally fine, but he did lose his son in the explosion.
You begin to have people come from outside the immediate area because at this point
it's become statewide news.
Pretty soon this is going to be international news.
At the time this was one of the worst catastrophes in American, if not in world history, because
what we're looking at is possibly 650 kids and 40 teachers blown up in an instant.
You had rescue crews coming from all over the state.
You had everyone from the Texas National Guard to Boy Scout troops headed out there, removing
rubble, rescuing people, and pulling out dead bodies.
This explosion was so violent, there was one kid the only way they were able to identify
he was in the building.
Obviously the parents were looking for him.
They never found his body.
They found a piece of his clothing that he was wearing that day.
That was all that was left of him.
And his parents remember him leaving in those pants.
He was completely vaporized.
Because this is such a huge story, eventually the reporters show up and when reporters show
up to start reporting their instantly given orders start digging.
Put down your microphone and start digging.
Walter Cronkite, world famous journalist who went on to cover World War II, which was
really right around the corner, this is 1937.
Walter Cronkite who covered World War II and the Nuremberg Trials.
Later in life said, "I did nothing in my studies nor in my life to prepare me for a
story of the magnitude of that New London tragedy, nor has any story since that awful
day equaled it."
You're walking around grieving parents, removing rubble, looking for their child.
I mean, it boggles the mind, right?
It boggles the mind.
And you're hoping that they're alive, but each hour that passed that hope grew dimmer
and dimmer and dimmer.
Again, we don't know how many students were at the school.
The number goes from 500 to 650.
What we do know is 294 students were killed in the explosion.
And then another 112, 115 suffered serious injuries and 130 escaped serious injuries.
You had people trying to sue the school district, but those lawsuits really didn't go anywhere.
It's something that we can look at now and go, "Well, if they had done these things,
it could have been preventable."
But at the time, you know, it's been hard to sue corporations back then, companies back
then, but none of the lawsuits went anywhere.
The superintendent, you know, he was held ultimately responsible.
He had to quit because he was told if he didn't quit, he was going to be killed.
The mob, the people were just going to do mob justice.
Which you may figure, yeah, you know, he's in charge.
He's the one ultimately in charge, so he's the one you're going to hold responsible for
this incident.
And I can see that it's also tragic that he lost his own son, a niece and a nephew in
the explosion.
So this wasn't some guy sitting on the edge of town in a high-rise being like, "Ah, another
day, another dollar."
Like, he lost people here too, but he was the one who was deemed ultimately responsible
and he should have made better decisions and he was forced to step down.
But this event, this event shocked the world.
This is the reason now why natural gas has a scent added to it.
That's why.
Because it filled up this school for so long and filled up this crawl space for so long
and people could not detect it.
And 294 children were blown to pieces that they've now added this element.
So this is one of those stories that it's an absolute tragedy.
And I got a couple things to say about this and then we'll wrap it up.
I know it's kind of depressing, but it's an absolute tragedy, obviously.
You have to think like, "How did this not happen?"
We wouldn't have added the scent agent into the natural gas or at least not have been
doing it that early.
So you wonder, by this school blowing up, did it prevent even greater catastrophes
down the road?
I mean, I'm never, I'm not saying that that means it's good.
But you know what I mean?
Like, detecting, being able to smell.
Imagine this.
Imagine if every so often a single house blew up.
Or maybe not even that dramatic.
Imagine if every so often a single house, a single household died because of a natural
gas leak and they couldn't smell it and they couldn't taste it and they couldn't see it.
If you had 200 households over the course of, say, maybe four years spread across the
country and they had these natural gas leaks and they just died, you would still have companies
going, "Well, how are we going to fix it?
You should just be responsible for that odorless smell you have in your house."
But if you had 200 households and each household had four people in it, that's 800 people
dead from the same thing.
It's the dynamic nature, right?
It's the dynamic nature of this tragedy, the instant death of all of these people that
make people go, "Wow, that's unsafe.
Let's fix that."
You had people dying in car accidents for years and years and years and years and years
and years and people were like, "I don't know what we're supposed to do about it."
It wasn't until I remember as I was a kid, they were like, "Maybe wear your seatbelt."
There was like a Sesame Street or there were like commercials for kids to start wearing
their seatbelt and then eventually it became a law.
But there was never like a thousand people died in a single moment because they weren't
wearing their seatbelt type of thing.
That would have mandated it right away.
So we have that.
And this idea, one, it's just a crazy story about like just little things that can go
wrong and they weren't even knowing they were wrong.
They only have a story that really saves lives.
In the long run, I think more people have been saved because they can smell gas, right?
Natural gas.
But then the other interesting thing about this story is it's pretty much completely
forgotten.
The fact that Adolf Hitler, Chancellor of Germany at the time, sent a letter of condolence,
a telegram of condolence to the United States to be like, "Hey, I'm sorry, that school blew
up."
This was an international tragedy.
People around the world were looking at this and being like, "I can't believe like those
poor families, those poor kids, what a horrible tragedy."
But no one remembers it.
I had never heard about this.
I had always heard that we put a smell into natural gas.
Like that is not a natural thing.
That's something that humans add so we can detect it.
But I didn't know it was because a school blew up.
And you have this national, really international tragedy that was on everyone's mind.
And now here we are less than 100 years later and it's just completely forgotten.
Or maybe it isn't.
Maybe everyone's like, "Jason, yeah, everyone knows about this."
I didn't.
Now I'd be surprised if it was common knowledge.
Just completely forgotten all these deaths.
We remember that this additive was added because we encounter it quite often.
Hopefully not a lot because that means you're exposed to a lot of natural gas.
This horrible tragedy that everyone wept around the world is now just a lost memory.
A Wikipedia page, right?
Just like that story of that man in the forest with his daughter may have been the talk of
the town for a while after it happened and eventually just fades away.
This becomes an obscure ghost story you find mentioned a couple of times online.
All of this human tragedy has been reduced to a whisper of a memory.
Fascinating stuff.
And I wanted to end this episode not with my traditional Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com,
all that stuff.
I wanted to play a clip from a newsreel.
Not to depress you even more, I just kind of an oddity.
I wanted to end it with this.
This newscaster might be one of the most callous newscasters that I've come across.
He is talking about these kids.
I think he uses the term "blown to bits" at least once.
At least once.
It's fascinating.
And again, this was a huge story at the time that changed the world in the way that we
interact with natural gas.
It's saved countless lives, but in the end it's been forgotten.
But let me play this news clip for you and it's just weird.
I just want to play this news clip for you.
I can't imagine a modern broadcaster talking like this.
But yeah, it's just weird.
Let's go ahead and roll that.
It is with deep regret that we bring you these graphic appalling scenes of one of the greatest
tragedies in American history.
Hundreds of school children and their teachers killed and mangled some of them literally
blown to bits, others crushed by falling masonry.
When their new consolidated grade and high school in the center of the rich East Texas
oil field was shattered by a terrific gas explosion.
Had the blast occurred ten minutes later, school would have been dismissed.
Even the death toll small, perhaps.
But it struck when only the lower grades and a few others had left, catching almost the
entire student body in an inferno of flying debris and falling walls.
There was no warning.
Before the eyes of persons in the vicinity, including scores of parents assembled for
a meeting in a nearby building, the schoolhouse, one of the finest rural structures in the
country, suddenly burst asunder and collapsed.
There's scarcely a home in the entire school district untouched by the disaster.
A disaster caused it is believed by gas pockets which had collected in the school's sub-basement.
In the long list of American catastrophes, this is one of the worst.
The entire nation bows in grief.
[Music]