What would you do if you thought one of your siblings was possessed?
And then we meet a group of convicts who have broken out of a penal colony in Tasmania
and are trying to make their way to freedom.
They're on the run, they're running out of food, and it's an interactive adventure today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys have weekends coming up,
Hope you guys have some cool stuff coming, Thanksgiving's coming up pretty soon too.
You know, normally I do a Thanksgiving special, huh? I don't even think about it.
Am I doing a Thanksgiving special this year? Maybe.
Like that? You like that commitment to the show? But you know who's always committed to the show
is one of our newest Patreons coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now.
Give it up for 580VDC. Everyone give a big round of applause.
Three numbers, three letters. That's all you need. 580VDC. Thank you so much for supporting the show.
You're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand. Just help spread the word about the show.
Really, really, really, really helps out a lot. I always love seeing you guys talk about the show online
and I'm seeing it more and more often. So thank you so much for that.
580. I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the Hair Hang Glider.
Let's go ahead and leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're gonna take a nice leisurely journey all the way out
to Grandma's house.
We're just flying the breeze all the way out and there we're gonna meet a 5 year old boy
standing in his grandma's house. We're looking through the windows.
We're all being super creepy. We're hiding in the bushes.
This 5 year old boy is walking around his grandma's house and the rest of the family is in the kitchen
kind of talking. This little boy is walking through the house and he's looking at all of these pictures of the family.
This little boy, did we give him a name yet? We're gonna call him Timothy is walking through this house
and he's looking at all of these photos and he says there had been like 30 or 40 pictures honestly. Just tons.
Now at that point your grandma is less of a loving matriarch. We're kind of like a creepy stalker.
They're like, "That's weird grandma. Why don't you take this picture? It's from outside in the bushes."
There's a bunch of leaves in front of the camera and it's this little boy trying to sleep.
Anyways, so we may have stumbled across another conspiracy theory here, but Timothy's walking through this house
and he's looking at all these pictures and when he's walking down the hallway, he sees a photograph of his older brother
but in this photograph he was much younger, even younger than Timothy was.
And he's looking at this photo of his brother and his brother is just standing there
and he sees something begin to move in the photograph.
A tall blackish figure, a shadow man, begins to walk across the picture.
This figure is just casually moving across the background of this picture.
The other people in it are frozen in time, but this shadow man is moving.
Timothy's watching this and he says, "The shadow man gets to where my brother is and then sits down."
Timothy freaks out. He has no way to really comprehend what he just saw.
It doesn't make sense. It goes against anything you would think of a photo could do.
Move, right? That's one thing photos famously are. Not moving.
He begins running through the house, screaming at the top of his lungs
and when he gets to the kitchen, everyone's like, "Dude, what is the matter? Why?"
But he was so terrified. He was sobbing. He actually couldn't even explain what he saw.
They're trying to get him to calm down and he can't.
He just saw something that his little brain could not comprehend.
Even an adult would have a hard time dealing with that.
I think as an adult you would look around and assume, was that a reflection of something behind?
There's a giant shadow man behind you. You're like, "Woo! That was close.
I thought you were only in the picture."
And then once you kind of took it in, you would probably just like back away from the photo.
You might also go screaming down the hallway, but to a kid that can't comprehend it,
they see this thing and at a certain point they realize,
"I can't get the words out to describe this and even if I could, no one is going to believe me."
So this was posted online by someone known as Lil Corn and Beans
and this is basically the first time apparently.
They feel comfortable telling this story. It's through an anonymous account.
Right? No one's going to be able to trace it back to this person
who saw a shadow man walk through a photograph.
It's an interesting story and it opens up a whole lot of pathways to explore.
My thing would be if the shadow man was in the photo, does that,
as I said in the intro, does that mean that the shadow man is next to his brother in real life?
Like, was the shadow man trapped in the photo and just walking behind me
like all my legs are so tired of me walking through eternity through this background?
Or did it symbolize that the shadow man is behind the brother in real life?
Maybe even possessing the brother.
Maybe this photo showed the truth.
Is the photo haunted? Is the brother haunted? Is the house haunted?
And then we have to look at is this just a we've been covering stories recently about children.
What was the one we did not too long ago?
It was about the young kids seeing something weird.
It's basically the entire premise of this podcast.
I don't remember what it was.
Thing was last week, but I came across another story just recently about a young girl.
I think this story took place in Argentina. I'll put it in the show notes.
This young girl is over at her friend's house and her friend's grandpa's there
and he's going to take the dogs for a walk and the girl goes,
"Oh, can I go with you?" and his nighttime and the grandpa goes, "Yeah, sure. You can go with me."
And the young girl runs the door and opens it and the moon is like sitting three feet from the door.
She said it was small. It was obviously much smaller than the moon really is,
but she goes, "I opened the door and I looked and there was the moon about three to six feet away from the front door just sitting there."
And I turned back to the grandpa and I said, "The moon's here. I really want to...
Can I go out and play?" and the grandpa just goes, "No. I don't think we're going to go out tonight."
And he walked and he shut the door.
So is that a kid misremembering something?
Or is that a paranormal event like the photo that actually happened?
Do these things happen more often, but kids see them and they can't process them?
They don't really know how to communicate that?
Because an adult's sire, if an adult opened their door and they saw a moon,
that is a reality breaking thing because we know that's impossible.
But I remember a long time ago I was watching this documentary about martial arts.
I think it was the art of Bushido or something like that or Bushido, the art of killing.
I think that was the documentary. And the person said, "Marshall arts should be taught to children
because children still believe in magic. They still believe that anything's possible.
And martial arts is making the impossible possible?"
I'm paraphrasing obviously. You said it more eloquently.
But as an adult, we know you can't shoot fireballs out of your hands,
but a child, they just think that's maybe three or four lessons away.
And they're putting so much focus into it.
I know that I can't do a spinning jump kick and knock out five goons,
but a kid thinks they can, right?
And so they approach martial arts differently.
And so is it something like that? Like, you, as a child, you believe magic is more real.
You believe that all this stuff is literally just maybe a day or two away.
Your life may become some fantastical adventure.
You open the door, you see a moon. That's just part of the magic of being a child.
Is that what this is? And that's why these children are seeing things like this?
Do more people have these experiences of kids?
But then when they grow up, they go, "Oh, that was impossible. I must have misremembered it."
I remember very, very clearly at one point walking into my backyard when we lived in Alameda.
I walked in my backyard and it looked up and there was a 747 flying so low.
If I had a basketball, I could have hit it.
And that's impossible. I would have been like 10, 11 years old, maybe like 11, 12 when I saw that.
That's impossible. I mean, if the plane was that low, I obviously would have,
you never would have heard from me. The podcast never would have been made.
I would have been swept up into a jet engine, but I clearly remember that.
Now, as an adult, I know it's impossible. I know it's impossible. But what did I see?
So who knows? It's very, very interesting. But it could be a childhood memory thing.
It could be that children are more open to the paranormal, which that isn't a obscure belief.
People are, that's pretty fairly well known in the paranormal world.
But like this, was this kid actually seeing a shadow man next to the photograph?
And does that mean in real life, his brother has a shadow man next to him?
Just bringing it back to that. That's the creepy part.
If the photograph had moved in some weird way and they seemed to interact with each other for a moment,
that would be weird and definitely notable.
The fact that an alien entity, something not in the photograph,
walked into the photograph and sat down next to his brother.
What does that mean? Truly a terrifying story.
And one that may be more common, just we've seen stuff like that when we were kids
and when we grew up, we'd go, "That's impossible." We kind of locked that away.
580 VDC. I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys of the carboner copter.
We are leaving behind Grandma's house. We got all the snickered noodles we can carry,
all of Grandma's great food. We're leaving behind Grandma's house.
We are headed all the way out to Australia.
So I want you guys to pick a number between one and ten.
And you guys got to remember that number because that will be your fate during this next story.
And as you're picking that number, as we're flying out there, I do want to do a special shout out for this.
There's a YouTube channel called Corridor Crew. I watch them all the time.
It's a bunch of special effects artists.
And a lot of times they do like good and bad CGI from X type of movies or good and bad CGI from, you know,
and because they're special effects artists, they can kind of analyze stuff
and they do stuff with stuntmen and fight choreography. It's a really cool channel.
What they've started doing recently though has been really cool. I talked about them a while back.
They did one where they debunked, or, you know, attempted to, you know, your mileage may vary,
but they debunked the Pentagon UFO videos, like all that stuff that was coming out about the tic-tac.
They were showing how that could be done.
What visual tricks or what CGI or whatever. And that was really cool.
I recently did one just before Halloween, ghost videos.
They watched a bunch of ghost videos on YouTube and they were trying to determine, "Is this fake? Is this real?"
And what I really like about, there's different types of debunking.
There's the debunking, the people go, "That's not real. Shadowmen in pictures, that's not real."
That's not fun to me. It's super boring.
The cool thing about Corridor Crew is because they're watching these videos, there's one where a ghost flies by a car.
And they're looking at it and they go, "Well, you know what's weird is that if I had to build that effect, I wouldn't have done this.
I wouldn't have thought about doing this." So it is weird.
Maybe someone was smoking and the smoke came by.
And they were watching this video over and over again and they figured it out what it was.
And to the homeowner, they probably never even thought this.
Well, they're kind of working it out and they go, "I bet you anything, there is a balcony above the camera
and someone stepped down on it where someone dropped something hard and dust fell through the slates.
The slates of the balcony and the dust came down in front of the camera."
And once they explained that and they re-show the video, that's exactly what it looks like.
And they go, "Yeah, look, there's more dust. Someone walked out there."
So it wasn't faked to get attention, but they were able to break it down.
That's the type of debunking I like because it's easy for them to just go, "Ghost don't exist. Come back next week."
And they also had an interesting point that I don't think I'd thought of if I had really sat down.
Maybe I would have come up with it, but they go, "It's weird that when ghosts move things like open drawers or doors,
they do it with the exact same physics as if you had a fishing line tied to something."
And I go, "You're right. Like, whenever you see a stool move, a ghost would pick up a stool like a human would,
because they were formerly human. Would they simply grab one of the legs at the very bottom and pull it?
Would they grab it? Would they pinch their fingers around it and yank it a bit?
Or if you had to move a stool, how would you do it?"
Now, do I think it disproves all ghosts? Absolutely not.
Do I think it disproves all the even the videos that they looked at? Absolutely not.
There may be one or two in there, but I love that type of debunking, and I think it's really, really cool.
So you guys should check out those videos as well. They'll be in the show notes.
580 VDC is taking us to Tasmania. Tasmania is part of Australia.
We're specifically headed to the McCorry Harbor Penal Station. It's September 20th, 1822.
So this is still when you're going to Australia. It wasn't for a vacation.
You were headed to this area because you were being transported for crimes you committed in the British Empire.
September 20th, 1822. You picked a number between 1 and 10. Remember that number.
We're at the McCorry Harbor Penal Station. This is a prison island within prison territory.
Like, the entire place is basically the real life no escape, starring Ray Liotta.
But even though there was no escape, you still tried. The human spirit persevered.
I'd rather die in the wilderness than spend another day in this penal colony.
So on September 20th, I don't know if they had alarms back then.
I think they just pulled on a calisthenic tail really loud and that alerted the guards.
Escape, escape, escape. 9 dudes all team up to break out of this penal colony.
They weren't all friends. We're just acquaintances as we will learn very quickly.
They weren't all friends, but when you heard that there was a possible chance of getting out of this madness, you took it.
Robert Greenhill quickly appointed himself leader of this band of fugitives.
And what made him the leader wasn't his eloquence or charisma. He may have had those things. We don't know.
History has not recorded that. They did record that he was the only one with an axe.
So if you're escaping prison with a bunch of prisoners, yes, the guy who's in charge is the guy with the axe.
And they make their way out of prison and they're now wandering the wilderness of Tasmania, trying to find civilization.
It's out there somewhere. They just got to find it. They don't have a map. They don't know where they're going.
They do have an axe though, and that will come in quite handy.
Now Robert Greenhill did have an ally. He was the only person who really started this off with someone watching his back.
And that was Matthew's Travers. They were friends in the joint. I actually think they were friends even before they both got sent here.
But they were on the move for 15 days.
And the authorities are looking for him. It wasn't just like, "Oh darn it, they got away. Ah, they'll get arrested by someone else."
They're being hunted. And they're on the move for 15 days in the Australian wilderness.
They have an axe, but no food.
That's not magical, right? It's not Minecraft. You just can't walk up an axe to chicken.
They probably would have if there were chickens, but there's nothing at all for them.
For 15 days, these nine men marched through the wilderness with nothing to eat.
So it's time to draw lots.
This is called the custom of the sea. And apparently it also works on land. What it is, is you draw lots.
So you have all these sticks of different sizes, and whoever gets the shortest stick gets eaten.
You're completely out of food. You need something to eat.
So they take a bundle of nine sticks. Could you imagine the stress of this, right?
You're already starving. It's already been days since you ate, so you're not already in the best mood.
I'm a little angry. You're like ribcage is showing you're like, "You're more than a little angry. You're about to die."
There's nine sticks being held in a hand, and one of them means you're not only going to get killed,
but you're going to get eaten reaching into that bundle of sticks.
Thomas Boddenham pulls one out, looks at it.
If you picked the number two, you just have a second to glance at that stick,
and you realize you've drawn the short straw.
It's just a minute. You comprehend that. You are now about to be murdered and then devoured.
You're going to be set upon by your fellow convicts and be digested.
And before you can really comprehend that, Robert Greenhill splits the back of your skull open with an axe,
and the men start a fire to cook your meat.
Yeah, this is what I guess I kind of came out of nowhere. Did I mention that there's any sort of cannibalism in the intro?
You're like, "Ah, this is horrible." You just sat down with a big rotisserie chicken.
You're like, "Yummy, yummy, yummy. Eating lunch and listening to Dead River Radio is my favorite thing."
Why didn't you get meat right off the bone? This is delicious.
Now, there were three people who-- there's nine people in total.
One of them is currently being spit roasted, and that is not the sport-- that is not the porn version.
That is the original version of spit roasting. They're turning them over with a stick.
I don't think they had an apple in its mouth. I don't think they were cooking them.
Like, they just slaughtered a hog. They're probably just cooking, like, thighs and arms and things like that.
One rump roast, please. You'll have a slow cooker. Everyone's all eating. They're all starving.
You're like, "No, I'd rather have eight hours. I want this meat to get nice and juicy."
Put thrown carrots in it. Three dudes saw this, and they're like, "We're not going to--
Okay, we're not going to be part of this, right? We're super, super hungry, but we're not going to eat this guy."
And here's the thing. We're 15 days into this.
We may not find civilization for quite a long time. Who's to say we're not next?
So three dudes bounce.
Alexander Dalton, William Kennerly, and Edward Brown run away.
So if you picked four, five, or six, you don't even get to taste sweet, sweet human flesh.
You run away. You cowards, what? You're not that you were a foodie, that you love new experiences.
You guys are running into the bushes. So if you picked four, five, or six, you're safe.
However, I will say this. If you picked four, you die of exhaustion.
The other two guys eventually get re-arrested.
So you can take this as a true show of an adventure. You can take that as a win, right?
You can be like, "Well, I didn't get to eat delicious convict, but I also didn't get cooked."
And you get re-arrested. And that is actually the best ending you could possibly get if you picked five or six, because it's all downhill from here.
So now we have Robert Greenhill and his buddy Matthew Travers, and two more.
John Mather and Alexander Pierce.
Oh man, that was so delicious. Oh, Tommy. Tommy, I'll always remember how delicious you were.
There still are eating the meat right off the bone.
The guy's juggling his testicles. He's wearing the penis like a fake nose.
He's like, "Look at me. I'm a big old clown." I don't know. Here's the thing. Here's the thing.
I really something read in this story. I don't think that happened, but I really something read in this story.
Being killed, knowing you're about to be eaten, right?
If I was killed and then afterwards someone ate me, I probably wouldn't care, because I'm dead.
But if I knew before I died I'm gonna get eaten, that would kind of concern me a bit, right?
That would make me be like, "Oh man, I'm gonna become poop."
But I'll tell you this right now. The only thing worse than being killed and eaten
is being killed and eaten the second-- the second guy to have that happen to you.
Because the first guy, it's an abstract thought. We've never really put much thought into being killed and eaten by another human.
Maybe so often you imagine someone being like, "Eating your eyeballs" and be like, "Hmm, I'm sorry. This episode's super disgusting."
But you know, it's like a gusher. Someone's eating your eyeballs like gushers and maybe they're like,
"But they have your legs like stilts. They're like walking on your legs. Look at me, Ma. Look how tall I am."
Everyone's laughing because you don't really think about that stuff, right?
Normal human never should. But if you're the second-- so you have now killed Tommy and you've eaten him
and you're sitting there with a belly full of your fellow human and you're sitting there and you're thinking,
"Oh my God, if I die they're gonna be doing all these eye jinks with my body."
Like, when they're eating you, when you're eating someone else, you're just eating meat off of a bone
but imagine them doing that to you. You're like, "No, I really like my legs attached to me."
You know what I mean? You had no context. When you have to go to bathroom later that night, you're pooping out Tommy.
And now you're realizing, "Oh my God, when I die someone's gonna poop me out too."
So the only thing worse than-- to my remaining listeners who are probably completely aroused by this story now,
everyone's quit the podcast except for my two listeners who are really into VOR.
So you freaks out there. After a certain point, I would rather die first and be eaten first than die second
and be eaten because I'd be like, "Because they're gonna play jump rope with my intestines and stuff like that."
I'm assuming, again, in most of the trouble situations, they don't play with your corpse, but they might.
And being turned into poop, you turning someone into poop, you know that's gonna happen to you.
And it's not an abstract thing. So remember, Green Hill and Travers are friends.
And there's only two other dudes. Now are you gonna draw lots? Probably not. It's two on two.
Green Hill and Travers are not gonna say, "Let's draw lots. We'll give an equal--"
"Mathor and Pierce know one of them are on the chopping block."
But they still got a lot of flesh of Tommy. They're turning in a beef jerky. They're like, "No, no, no."
They're still eating some of Tommy. They have this meat on the go, but that meat is also running low,
and there is no safety in sight. Pierce and Mathor know that one of them is next.
And John Mathor realizes that the power dynamic has changed.
If you picked number one, you realize at the very last second that it wasn't two on two. It was three against one.
If you picked number one, Alexander Pierce went behind your back because your back looked so delicious
and formed an alliance with Travers and Green Hill.
And Mathor feels that axe chop into his body, hacking away at him.
His last thoughts are of him turning into poop.
I don't actually know. He might have been thinking of his mom or his long-lost wife, but also poop,
because he just ate a guy a couple days ago, and now that same thing is gonna happen to him.
The very last thing? He's like, "Oh man, I really shouldn't have juggled that guy's testicles
and worn his penis like a fake nose."
If you picked number one, you are roasted over the fire that night.
Mmm, John is tastier than Tommy.
John really worked out. John really worked out his glutes.
He was eating you up, and later that night, under a sea of stars, all three of the men start pooping you.
I don't know why I'm so obsessed. That would be so horrifying.
I mean, I know we get turned into poop anyways, like I get eaten by worms, and then I turn into worm poop,
but that's totally different, because I think about all the times that I've pooped, and there's never been people,
who never eat a person, but what if it was?
Right, that would suck, right? I'd be like, "Johnny, no, you were my best friend, why did I eat you?"
But I have to go to the bathroom. I probably shouldn't have eaten you and taken all that X-Lax. It's making it even worse.
People are not eating me. I apologize. Even the four people have left at this point.
Now, Alexander Pierce knows that he sure he was able to last to the next round, but Travers and Greenhill are ride or die.
They're ride or eat. They're gonna eat Pierce at some point.
But here's the thing. They can't kill him right now, because they're gonna be able to preserve all that meat,
so they're gonna keep going as far as they can, and they might not have to eat him, right?
If they were able to find civilization, that would be ideal. They don't want to eat this dude,
but he can stay alive until they run out of food, and then they'll kill him, because they'll need fresh food.
But what happens before any of that? If you pick number three, you or Matthew Travers, and you get bit by a snake,
[makes snake noises]
the fangs go deep inside your flesh, poison, injecting into your skin.
I have to poop. I have to poop. You say you run into the bushes. They're like, "No, don't poop. You still need to digest some more of Johnny."
At this point, Alexander Pierce realizes that the game board is set. Travers is not gonna be able to make it.
Greenhill, though, because this is his buddy, says we're not leaving him behind, and they carry him,
or more specifically, Greenhill carries him for five days, hoping to find civilization, get his buddy some treatment.
But by the fifth day, they knew that they couldn't save him.
So they kill him, and they eat him.
I'd assume they didn't eat where the snake bite was. They ate around that part.
And now it's one on one.
Well, it's one on one with an axe, because Greenhill never gave up possession of that axe, but they have no alliances now.
They're walking through the wilderness together. Maybe we'll get somewhere. Maybe they won't have to eat each other.
That's the goal! It's to get free. This wasn't a cannibal expedition.
You have to sleep, but can you, with the person next to you wanting to kill you?
You run out of food again. You're weak. You're moving through the wilderness. You're starving. You can't sleep.
You can't think. You're running out of energy.
If you pick number seven, you're Robert Greenhill. If you pick number nine, you're Alexander Pierce.
And at one point during this cat and mouse game, which takes over the course of days, Alexander Pierce gets that axe and splits Robert Greenhill's head wide open.
If you picked number seven, you're laying on the ground, gasping for air.
And Alexander Pierce is standing over you with that axe, and he goes, "What are you doing? You're gonna think of anything clever to say?"
I could have had a hundred different, I don't know, bone appetites. He maybe said that.
Maybe he said, "You know what's happening to you, bro? I'm gonna eat you and I'm gonna poop you out."
And Robert Greenhill's like, "Ugh." And dies.
Alexander Pierce goes to work. I mean, think about it. All these other bodies he had to share, now he gets a hundred and what?
Sixty-hundred and eighty pounds of just meat, just human flesh for Alexander Pierce.
But you know, he doesn't want to be eating this stuff. This is a survival thing. But he doesn't. He's making skewers.
He has a little barbecue going on. He's eating this meat. He's preserving this meat as best as he can.
And he continues through the wilderness, and then he sees some sheep.
And he knows now, civilization is nearby. There must be a farm nearby if he's seeing these sheep.
And not only does he stumble across this sheep ranch in the middle of nowhere, he knows the guy who runs the sheep ranch.
This dude is also a criminal who runs a sheep-russling scheme. They're stealing sheep.
So Alexander Pierce comes out of the wilderness. Full belly. He actually weighs more than when he broke out of jail.
How'd you escape? Oh, it was just me. I just ran away and I survived.
He becomes part of the sheep-russling scheme, and then they get arrested, and then he gets re-arrested for a total of 113 days.
All of that stuff happened in 113 days. They broke out of prison through the time he got re-arrested as being a sheep-russler.
Now, when his friend met him, he's probably just like, "Yeah, I just broke out of jail. It was just me. You know how awesome I am."
But authorities know for sure there was a lot more people who escaped.
At this point, they already arrested, Kennerley and Brown. Remember, they came out of the wilderness, they got re-arrested, and they said, "Well, Dalton passed out, died of exhaustion."
And the reason why we left is because those other two had killed a guy and we were about to eat him.
So when Alexander Pierce gets re-arrested, they go, "Hey, we know that this guy was murdered and you guys planned on eating him. Did you guys do that?"
And Alexander Pierce is like, "Yeah, yeah, we ate him." And he goes, "Okay, well, where's everyone else at?" And he goes, "Well, we ate them too. Everyone got eaten but me."
And he admitted to it, but the authorities didn't believe him. They thought he was covering for his buddies.
They actually didn't believe him. They thought they were still out there somewhere in the bush, so they continued looking for him.
He's like, "Guys, listen, if you direct me to a toilet, trust me, you will see the remains of these people come out of my butthole."
I don't know why that would be evidence and not like an eyeball would come out and wink. They're like, "Robert Greenhill's eye."
So Alexander Pierce is locked back in prison, but he's not being charged with this stuff right now because as far as they know, these guys are still alive.
Like, sure, they have witnesses that they killed this one guy to eat him, but he didn't do it. Alexander Pierce didn't do it.
Remember, Robert Greenhill clubbed him with the ax.
And while Alexander Pierce is back in this prison that he escaped from, he comes across an inmate, a young man known as...
Thomas Cox.
If you pick number 10, you're good old Thomas Cox, who decides to team up with Alexander Pierce for a prison escape.
Yeah, man, I totally want to blow this joint. This place sucks.
Well, I did escape from it once, young man, and with your help, we can escape again.
And they do. They break out of this prison colony once again.
But this time, they're only on the run for 10 days before they're re-caught.
And when Alexander Pierce is caught, he's alone.
They go, "What happened to Thomas Cox?" And he goes, "Well, we got to the river and he couldn't swim. And I realized he was a liability, so I killed him."
But when they were searching him, when they were searching Alexander Pierce, he had only been gone for 10 days.
They found him in possession of meat torn from Thomas Cox's body.
Just pockets full of Tommy.
And he had food on him as well.
He had murdered Thomas and was eating him, even though they weren't starving, even though they still had provisions.
He is quickly charged with murder and cannibalism.
He was sentenced to be executed for his crimes.
And on July 19th, 1824, Alexander Pierce is headed towards the gallows, his last words before that noose was slipped over his neck, his last words, "Man's flesh is delicious."
It tastes far better than fish or pork.
[Sounds of cutting]
Really, really creepy story. It's funny when I was reading it.
The initial, and this is really, this is actually a really popular story, like a true crime story in Australia, but I hadn't heard of it before.
And it's creepy because when you're reading it, you're like, "Oh, this is just kind of like a group of men pushed to the limits. They're slowly starving. What would you do?"
Would you rather be the pooper or the poopy?
But then the story, the guy's a monster at the end. Like, I can understand you're in that survival situation, but then he becomes a monster.
He didn't need to kill that kid, but he wanted to taste that human flesh again.
He wanted to taste that meat so badly, he broke out of prison just to eat that guy.
I do like Chipotle, but I won't even drive an hour to get it.
He broke out of prison and within a matter of days, that was the reason why he broke out, because he wanted to eat that guy.
Insane story, and you have to wonder, was he always a monster?
Or was he just a low-level criminal, a thief, a scoundrel, who one day ate human flesh and became a creature?
I mean, that's the origin story of the windigo, is you devour human flesh, you become a monster.
He became so addicted to the taste of human meat, his last words were about how delicious it was.
His last words were a yelp review for human meat.
And was it the taste, was it the texture, or was it the power he derived from digesting another human, or all of it combined?
Truly a terrifying story and a true story about a man who became a flesh-eating monster.
But in his view, he's basically saying, "Don't knock it till you try it."
And that's the scary thought. What if the most powerful drug in the world isn't heroin or fentanyl, but human flesh?
You just can't stop it, one. Gotta eat 'em all. I'm lovin' it, whichever catchphrase you wanna use.
What if human flesh is the greatest delicacy that you could possibly imagine?
Now, I don't think that's true. I've never eaten it, but I don't think that's true.
But to Alexander Pierce, the taste of human meat was so intoxicating.
He sacrificed his life for just one more meal.
DeadRabbitRadio.com is gonna be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
TikTok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]