Tom Hanks, actor, comedian, and Illuminati operative who was killed in Guantanamo Bay
just last year, has a clone walking around.
That's why he's been in a bunch of movies since he died.
He has a clone walking around, but does the Illuminati have even darker plans for this
doppelganger of America's favorite actor?
And then we take a look at two terrifying yet erotic stories of love from beyond the grave.
Is it possible that even the dead want to boink today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Marviner, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
It's the official beginning of season 19.
We had that crazy breaking story last week about the Georgia Guidestones and I could not
wait to tell it to you.
What a crazy story and it's developing.
Developing story, we'll see if any more news comes out of that, but right now someone coming
out of something, I'm sure he's coming out of somewhere, give it up for one of our newest
Patreon supporters, everyone on your feet for Dyspozy.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in Dyspozy.
I just imagine like a big ol' garbage disposal walking in, eating everything up.
Dyspozy, you're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally get it, trust me I do.
Just help spread the word about the show that really, really helps out a lot.
Now Dyspozy, let's go ahead and we're gonna give you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're gonna drive all the way out to a secret Illuminati party.
I hope you guys are armed because we're going into enemy territory.
Driving on out there.
Now I brought an Illuminum Baseball bat, I probably should have brought more if we're
going up against the Illuminati.
We're driving on out to this Illuminati party, we're gonna have to make sure that we're
in disguise.
We're gonna dress up like some big weirdo freaks from Eyes Wide Shut.
And we pull up and it happens to be at Lady Gaga's house and we're walking in and everyone's
sitting back, they're chilling and they're injecting Adrenaline Chrome straight into their
neck.
This is a really intense start to season 19 and we have like little syringes full of
Kool-Aid, we're just pretending right because we're not really gonna do Adrenaline Chrome.
You're like Jason, don't inject Kool-Aid in your veins, I'm like too late.
I have instant diabetes.
So after I'm on dialysis for the next two weeks, we go back to Lady Gaga's house, we're
walking around this Illuminati party and the reason why we're here is because breaking
news from the world of the Dark Outpost.
The Dark Outpost is a website we've covered a lot on this show, it's hosted by a man known
as David Zublik and he tells us the truth that the lamestream media is trying to hide
from us.
The first truth is don't inject Kool-Aid in your veins.
And secondly, that Tom Hanks, actor, comedian, has he ever directed anything?
I don't know.
But anyways, actor, comedian, director, question mark.
He is a top player in this Illuminati game trying to take over the world but we don't
have to worry about this so much, right?
Because as you guys all know, it's been almost a year since I exposed the truth that Tom
Hanks was caught for all of his nefarious crimes against humanity and was killed at
Guantanamo Bay.
We did that episode, it was like episode 700 or something like that.
I'll put it in the show notes and close call with that one, right?
I mean, who wants a freak like Tom Hanks walking around?
Well, I wasn't thinking very clearly.
I was thinking like a normal person that when the military executes someone at Guantanamo
Bay, they're dead.
But the Illuminati apparently has a cloning facility underground and luckily, luckily
they had a clone of Tom Hanks.
And that's why you see him in movies nowadays.
Remember this whole thing?
I guess I have to do a little bit of a review on this.
He was Tom Hanks, actor, comedian, director.
And then he went to Australia to shoot a movie and he caught COVID.
And then this whole conspiracy theory started that he was acting.
You guys remember this?
You see that he was actually under house arrest because he was shooting these TikTok videos.
He asked COVID, he's trying to do, he's trying to floss, he's coughing.
And in the background of all these videos, there was a door and people go, wait, that
door only opens one way.
That's not a door of a hotel room.
That is the door of a prison cell in Guantanamo Bay.
Do you guys remember?
This is what I love about conspiracy theories is they blow up.
They're super popular.
You see them everywhere and then like two weeks later, they're gone.
And people pretend that they never happen.
Tom Hanks once had a little bit more legs, but there was that whole thing.
Ellen had like the ankle bracelet she was under house arrest.
We were all under house arrest.
The whole world was locked down due to COVID.
But anyways, they said, look it, he's clearly in a prison cell, not a hotel room, which
is a great advertisement for whatever hotel he was staying in.
But that whole thing.
And then the theory just kept on going that he didn't have COVID, that that was actually
an excuse so he could go to this military tribunal in Guantanamo Bay.
And I was thinking, why would the military be like, listen, we're going to execute you
in three days.
You have to make 11 TikToks before then.
So we have this cover story.
But anyways, so that was how this whole Tom Hanks thing started off.
I think Isaac Cappy was the first person to say, Tom Hanks is a pedophile when Isaac Cappy
listed a bunch of people, Seth Green and all these guys.
I've talked about this before on the episodes.
I'll put it in the show notes, but quick overview.
So he got dragged in all this, the very next movie he did, he was accused of being a pedophile
who was kidnapping kids and injecting Adrenaline Chrome to extract Adrenaline Chrome from the
frightened children to inject into his own body.
The very next movie he did, the very next movie he did, the movie he was in Australia
shooting was a Western about he had to protect this young girl from these people who were
trying to kidnap her.
And it was so interesting to think that's weird that the conspiracy theorists are pushing
so hard on this Illuminati Adrenaline Chrome thing.
And the next movie he comes out, he's trying to protect a child and nobody talked about
it.
It was the weirdest thing.
Like they didn't even go look and he's hiding in plain sight.
This clearly in this Western movie underneath this cowboy hat, there's a bunch of Adrenaline
Chrome vials.
Anyways, then he went on to make Elvis and all that stuff, but he didn't.
It was his clone.
It's his clone actually walking around it right now.
As Tom Hanks was being led up to the gallows, they were going to execute him and he said,
his last words were, "This doesn't matter.
There are a ton of us out there."
And they hung him.
And I think at that point everyone thought he meant like there's a lot of Illuminati
agents left out there.
No.
He actually meant that there's a bunch of, he doesn't want his actual last words by
the way.
He's still alive.
But if you accept the conspiracy theory, he was referring to his army of clones because
if you do have cloning technology, you're not going to clone a bunch of world leaders.
You're going to clone 80 Tom Hanks.
You have all these Tom Hanks and everything like that.
So another one has been released from the cloning.
But that's not news, right?
That's pretty much a given in the world of conspiracy theory.
The reason why we're talking about it right now is because this clone is dying.
And this was actually the plan.
So apparently according to David Zublik, this is what the story is.
Tom Hanks is, this is, this is so, if you know what I said was insane before we haven't
even started yet.
Tom Hanks clone walked out of the cloning facility and the Illuminati put a switch in
him so he will die at a certain point.
And what happened was Tom Hanks died before the whole Australia thing apparently.
And then it was Tom Hanks clone.
They did a little bit of like retroactively retconning.
That's the term they kind of retconned the story.
Tom Hanks clone was when he stepped out of the cloning machine already had COVID.
He already had COVID and that was part of the plan.
So the clone met Tom Hanks wife Rita Wilson, I think is her name.
And Wilson, he said she's dating a volleyball.
He comes out of the cloning machine with COVID, which doesn't sound like a really good plan,
but he comes out coughing everywhere.
The scientists were like, ah, and then they go, oh, clone Hanks, we need to give you a
vaccine for that disease that we gave you.
And when he got the COVID vaccine, then people often email me and they go, how come your
show is not bigger?
How come YouTube is constantly limiting your stuff?
It's probably because I talk about stuff like this.
It's probably because I don't talk about, there's conspiracy theories, there's mainstream
conspiracy theories, and then there's this.
Tom Hanks clone came out with COVID.
They gave him the COVID vaccine, which gave him Parkinson's disease.
So that's where we're at right now.
Tom Hanks' clone has Parkinson's and for proof, David Zublick shows a video of Tom
Hanks on stage like doing this comedy routine and he's shaking from a video tape of Tom
Hanks kind of shaking on camera.
He got, he concocted this whole story that Tom Hanks clone has Parkinson's and he got
it from the COVID vaccine and all, what?
But he apparently he really was shaking because apparently Tom Hanks said, yeah, sorry about
shaking, sorry about shaking during that.
I guess he has diabetes and he go, and he's had diabetes for like 20 years.
I actually have to look this up right when people make these insane statements.
Okay, let's look it up.
Apparently he does have diabetes and apparently he said it wasn't really taking the right
medication I needed to be.
So that's why I'm shaking.
I don't actually have Parkinson's and I'm not a clone.
The reporters are like, what?
We didn't even ask anything about the clone and the clone walks up to him, starts strangling
him, coughing in their face.
So that is the story of Tom Hanks clone.
But again, that's not even the weirdest thing.
I talk a lot about dark outposts and real raw news.
And the thing is, is that when I'm talking about these things and I'm reading them and
I'm laughing, I really don't think you're getting the essence and really what, how seriously
people take this stuff.
Real raw news is another website like Dark Outpost.
Real raw news is a blog.
Dark Outpost is a daily show.
It's like three to four hours each day.
David Zublik will go on these rants basically.
And so I'm telling the story and I'm laughing and I'm joking and seeing stuff about the
COVID vaccine that I'll get the show taken off of YouTube.
I think it, I want to play a clip for you of David Zublik, the way that he talks about
this stuff because it shows how sincere and how much these people believe in it.
And the, both of these real raw news and dark outposts have huge audiences, huge audiences.
We're talking 80 to 100,000 people, right?
A huge scope of people.
Real raw news makes about $5,000 a month just through donations.
Minimum $5,000 a month just through donations.
And I don't know how much money Dark Outpost is making, but I want to play you this clip.
Now the set up for this clip is that some of you guys may know if you're of a certain
age, there was an old television show called Buzzing Buddies.
It was Tom Hanks' first big show.
I liked it.
I thought it was funny.
Tom Hanks and his co-star Peter Scolari are dudes who, their house gets knocked down by
a construction crew.
And so they have to live at a women's dormitory.
So they're not homeless and they dress up like women, but then they like fall in love
with some of the girls.
So each episode they're like changing clothes between women and men, women and men.
And great theme song by Billy Joel.
I love it.
So we have this show called Buzzing Buddies and they truly were Buzzing Buddies because
I'm about to play you this clip.
When Tom Hanks was arrested, Peter Scolari got all of his devices confiscated.
I guess they were at the same airport.
I said, "That's a whole other story."
But anyways, when Tom Hanks got arrested, Peter Scolari was there.
They took his electronic devices but let him go.
And then when they were going through his electronic, Peter Scolari's electronic devices,
they had to re-arrest them because they found this video footage.
This is a clip from the Dark Outpost where David Zublik is telling you what they found
on this footage.
One video, our source said, depicted a collaborative criminal venture, garbed in drag, Hanks in
a red evening gown and heels, and Scolari sporting a floral ensemble.
The sadistic duo stood above a young child who was strapped face down to a metal gurney.
Pretending to be acupuncturists, they jabbed holes on the child's back and looked like
pores on a sponge.
The loud of the child screamed.
The deeper they pushed the steel quills into his back.
They stuck the kid for 30 minutes, according to military sources, which had his back look
like a slice of Swiss cheese.
Then Scolari smothered the child's face with a pillow and apparently snuffed the life
out of him.
But even that act of cruelty did not satisfy the devious duo's barbarous cravings.
For a coup de gras, Hanks held a silent pistol to the kid's head, shouting, "Life ain't
like a box of chocolates.
It's like a bag of shit."
As he squeezed the trigger and blew out the child's brains, a red pink mist filled the
lens field of view in this horrific video.
So I mean there's a lot of questions with this one, right?
There's a lot of questions with this one.
First off, I don't know if I should go point to point or just get to the big one, just
get to the ending.
I find it really weird that Peter Scolari, first off, I'm not gonna wear this tape even
exist and obviously doesn't.
But you listen to how sincere he is, right?
How he's like, "Yeah, yeah."
And then this happened.
He's actually recounting something he saw.
It almost sounds like "Buzzing Buddies" creepypasta.
It almost sounds like this actually was Squidward's suicide from 1982.
But you have this, you have Peter Scolari and Tom Hanks dressed up in dresses and then
they're pretending to be acupuncturists.
And I think, I mean listen, I'm not a zoomer, I don't know what kids are into these days.
I think he would probably recognize that that was Tom Hanks.
I don't think Tom Hanks could be disguised as anybody.
He's been around for decades now at this point, well him and his clone.
But the boy, like, how did they disguise themselves as acupuncturists?
Acupuncturists just look like normal people, right?
So anyways, and they're poking holes in his back and they make it look like a sponge.
It's just so gross to the way that he's like, "Mmm, yeah, sponge."
It's like he's a little, David you're a little too into it.
You're a little too into recounting that story.
But you have him turn this kid into a sponge and they're like, "Hey kid, look, you're
a SpongeBob SquarePants."
He gets like, "No, I always wanted to be Patrick."
The story really lingers on the boy's torment, which is super creepy.
Right, super creepy.
And then obviously the coup de gras, the quote, right?
The quote.
Life isn't like a box of chocolates.
It's like a bag of shit.
Of course, I had to play this for my Patreon's on the Patreon Discord before we ran it.
And one of them, Caspine Montague, said, "Did he do other Tom Hanks quotes?"
Which I don't know.
I mean, there might be other videos out there of him quoting other movies.
What else would be quotable?
You got a friend in me?
No.
And blows the kid's head off.
What other?
That's not even really good.
Peter Scholar, he's like, "Well, that was a lame one.
I don't even know any Tom."
You thought you were in the burbs?
You're actually...
Pshh, you're the kid?
I don't really know that many Tom Hanks quotes.
Saving Ryan wouldn't...
Whatever.
Okay, we're done.
The kindness is that I love that Tom Hanks, before he kills people, he quotes his own
movies.
And he doesn't have that many quotable movies.
At least Arnold Schwarzenegger would have all these one-liners and stuff like that.
How come Arnold Schwarzenegger's never been in...
That's actually a very interesting question.
Arnold Schwarzenegger, human orc?
A man who's like six foot three and nothing but solid muscle even though he's like in
his seventies now.
How come he's never accused?
He did inject steroids.
We know that he injected stuff into his body and he was a successful political candidate.
Taught movies are...
How come he's never been accused of doing a terranochrome?
How come it's always these skinny little wimps like Tom Hanks and Seth Green?
But anyways, that is the story of Tom Hanks' clone.
That's the story of Tom Hanks and how he murders people.
But more importantly, that's the story of how these people take this stuff.
We're joking about it and stuff like you're like, "Yeah, Jason, you joked about killing
kids for about 20 minutes."
But I think it's so creepy when they talk about it, when real raw news and darkout
books talk about it, this is the tone of voice.
This is super serious.
Again, Patreon Discord, we were talking about it.
Rudy Jazz said, "Do you think that they actually believe this stuff?"
And I do think David Zublik believes this.
I do think David Zublik, when he was reading this, actually believed that this happened.
And he's spreading that message to tens of thousands, hundred thousand people a day.
Creepy stuff because listen, I know there are people who don't like Tom Hanks.
I know there are people who believe that to be successful in Hollywood, you have to do
all these deals with the devil, the lulunati stuff.
And that's one thing, right?
We can discuss that.
But to think that Tom Hanks is actually walking around quoting movies and shooting kids in
the head, that's a totally different thing.
We can have a discussion to be famous in the world.
You have to make a deal with the God of the world, aka Satan.
We'll have that discussion.
But if someone goes, "No, no, no, I honestly believe that Tom Hanks, Tom Hanks' clone,
is walking around coughing COVID on everybody."
And the reason why he was cloned, because the original Tom Hanks was shooting people,
shooting children while he was quoting his own movie, that's just so insane.
That is insane.
I'll still have a conversation with you about it because it's so insane to find an entertaining.
But that's a bridge too far.
It really is.
That really, really is.
So, disposies, like why did I have to be on this episode?
Trust me, disposies, it gets worse.
They actually feel bad.
Usually when I have an episode like this, I usually don't have a new Patreon.
I have someone who's already been a member of the Patreon for a while.
Disposies, let's go ahead and toss you the keys of the Carvenercopter.
We are leaving behind Lady Gaga's house.
We're headed all the way out.
Actually it's probably in the same area.
To Los Angeles, California.
I've been doing it before I even started this segment, I guess I should say.
This segment is not appropriate for young children.
It's not like the last segment was appropriate either, but I forgot to say that.
But this segment, definitely not appropriate for young children because we're going to
be talking about sex.
We're going to be talking about what Salt and Pepper was always trying to get us to
discuss sex.
Not just sex, as in biological sex, but the question is, do ghosts want to have sex?
It's kind of an interesting question because ghosts are constantly all kind of the idea
with ghosts is that they come down and maybe it's unfinished business.
That's why they're here.
There was some sort of horrific event and they're like, "Soul is trapped here" or
it's an emotional recording of the event.
One of the big factors in being a biological creature is to reproduce.
Even if you're not actively dating or actively trying to have children, people are always
engaged in some sort of sexual activity, sexual thought, what have you.
It would track, I think it would actually make sense.
Humans spend so much time thinking about sex or engaging in sex or masturbation or whatever,
that why would that stop just because you were dead?
Now, there's always stories about people saying ghosts come to them in the middle of the night
and they have sex with a ghost and things like that, but we've covered that before on
the show.
I'll put one or two of those episodes in the show notes, but a lot of times it's like weirdos,
right?
A lot of times it's like in the Daily Mail or the Daily Star, some British tabloid or
some woman's like, "I married a pirate ghost" or whatever.
But we hear about that, but it's actually super rare when we talk about all the amounts
of ghosts that are seen around the world, all the ghost stories.
We counter a disproportionately low amount of sex ghost stories.
Now it could be that people don't want to talk about it, or it could be that they just
don't exist, but I think that there should be more ghosts that want to have sex.
So we're going to take a look at two ghosts that may be the exception to the rule or there
may be more out there and people just don't know about it.
Who knows?
Because these places are both kind of weird, but the reason why we're first going to LA
is in LA there is the LA County Museum of Arts.
So disposed of these flying the carbon helicopter, we're landing on Wilshire Boulevard.
There is a legend at the LA County Museum of Arts that there is a ghost of a woman there.
And if you're at this museum, you're walking around, you're like looking at, I don't know
exactly what they have there.
It's a museum of arts, so it's probably arts, but it's probably like modern art, right?
It's probably like a statue of like a circle and then like some dudes facing it and people
are like, oh, that represents the soul.
And you're like, oh, whatever, where's the mastodons?
Where are the mummies?
They're like, sir, just because it has the word museum in it does not mean that there
has to be mummies.
I'm a mummy, mummy, walking around knocking over all the art at this museum, according
to security guards at this museum, because officially they have no statement on this
place.
They don't, they go, we don't want to talk about the ghost.
But security guards at the museum says every so often, this woman shows up, this ghost
woman shall be standing there and you'll be like in the hallway or in the bathroom or
you'll be tearing apart art and she shows up and she wants to have sex with you.
This ghost woman is constantly trying to bang the dudes who work there and who visit there.
Now I came across that on theshadowlands.net, which is a great repository, but a lot of the
stuff you really kind of have to dig through to see if there's any truth to it.
What's super interesting is there seems to be some truth to this one.
There are reports of both a female and a male ghost at the LA County Museum of Arts.
They're floating around in there.
Officially she's not trying to bang you, but I think that's something they leave off the
brochure.
Women would constantly be like honey can we go to the museum again and they're like oh
great are you going to try to have sex with that ghost?
No.
I want to see if they find out there's mummies in.
But then once you get in you run away from your wife and you're like ha ha trick to and
you're just walking around empty hallways looking for this ghost to bang.
But apparently there's some truth to the story.
Back on June 22, 1989, a woman was murdered there.
Her name was Evelyn Wasserstein.
She was 79 years old.
Let's put it out as something that was a sexy ghost the whole time.
You thought it was a ghost that looked like Daphne from Scooby Doo or Anya Taylor Joy
floating down the hallway.
No.
Sorry to burst your bubble.
I should have explained this earlier.
As you're listening to this episode you're like oh yeah, sexy episode of Dead Rav Radio.
She's 70.
It's Phyllis Diller basically.
It's a 79 year old ghost woman who's trying to have sex with you while you're trying to
ease the bathroom where you're like a security guard there and someone goes hey can you go
get some stuff out of the supply closet and you're like fine and you go in there and there's
this old wrinkly ghost woman trying to have sex with you.
Evelyn Wasserstein.
She's 79 years old.
So originally this place used to be a department store and it had a restaurant on the bottom
floor.
May Company was the department store.
1989 Evelyn Wasserstein was playing cards with a bunch of her friends in this restaurant
downstairs and her estranged husband, Jack Wasserstein, walked in.
Estranged if I understand this correctly means they're still married.
They're just like not together, right?
Estranged husband Jack Wasserstein walked in and she apparently this wasn't reported
in the LA Times but apparently she was sleeping around on him.
That's why they were estranged and she was like what I'm 79 years old.
I'm gonna tomcat all around town.
He walked into the restaurant and he couldn't take that his wife was sleeping around on
him so he shot her several times while she was playing cards.
This was like in the middle of the day and then he put the gun in his own head and killed
himself.
And then Tom Hanks.
Tom Hanks showed up and he goes there's lots of types of shrimp.
And then he went away.
He went away.
What does that reference even mean?
Shoot himself he dies.
So we do have a recorded murder.
We do have a the stats kind of fit right?
We have someone who was murdered here who apparently was sleeping around on her husband
and now her ghost still wants to have sex.
And that is so interesting because I read that and I go why don't we see more of them?
Why don't we see more elderly phantoms floating around the golden girls are gonna haunt you
tonight and they're like ooh which one are you gonna have first and after you get them
vomiting you're like uh you.
How come there's not more ghosts trying to have sex?
Because that is such part of the human condition.
And again even if you're not having sex you're doing other sexual things.
But that's not all.
That's not all because you can't just have one sex ghost.
That would be an outlier.
What if I told you there was two sex ghosts?
What if I told you?
Out of my entire decades of paranormal research I have two sex ghosts that I didn't find on
an article in the Daily Star.
Let's travel over to Garden Grove.
That's another city in the Los Angeles area.
We're gonna drive over to Garden Grove and we're gonna check out this place called Midnight
Adult Books.
An adult bookstore if you guys don't know it's not an actual bookstore.
They have videos, they have DVDs.
I don't know what they sell now because they used to sell DVDs.
I guess Blu-ray.
Would you want to watch 4K porn?
4K OLED porn on your giant 52 inch monitor gooning to the greatest degree you can.
Midnight Adult Books stored.
They don't sell books, maybe magazines.
They're mostly known because not everybody knows this.
They're mostly known for having video arcades.
It's not like you're going to play Gallagher.
You're not gonna play Dragon's Lair.
There are usually these rooms that you go in.
This is so archaic.
It sounds so weird now.
Still super popular.
You pay $5 to go into the video arcade room and it's a booth with a television set and
like a DVD player, VCR, whatever it is, streaming.
I don't know.
And then you watch porn in your own little booth.
That's what the adult bookstores are for.
It was a place so you could watch porn and you wouldn't have to worry about your wife
finding out.
Like in 1982 you go in there and you take some video tape, you stick it in there, you're
taking tapes from home.
You're like, "Finally I can watch Top Gun and Peace."
You got your headphones on.
You're like, "Hi, what are you doing?"
No, you watch porn movies in this little...
But that's not even what they're for.
That's not even what it's for.
That's what it is on paper.
That's what the business is on paper.
The truth behind adult bookstores, all of them, is that you don't buy books there.
You can...
A lot of people go there and buy sex toys, but even then, you know, you can buy the
stuff online nowadays.
People go there.
Men, predominantly.
Men go there not to watch porn in their own little booth.
Disposies left.
Disposies like, "Nope, I'm out.
I know where this is going.
I don't want to have anything to do with this."
Flying the carbon helicopter away.
You go to these adult bookstores to have sex with other dudes.
So you can't call it "sex with other dudes" store.
You have to call it an adult bookstore where there's no books.
You have a booth.
We're getting to ghost.
There is...
They were like, "Check in there and watch."
I'm like, "Okay, Jason.
When's the ghost showing up?
The ghost will appear soon."
You go into this booth to watch porn, but then there's like holes in the walls and
other dudes are doing things and you're having sex with multiple people in these booths.
Basically, you pay $5 to walk into a room to have anonymous sex with somebody.
That's what an adult bookstore really is.
So when you're driving down the road and you see an adult bookstore on the side of the
road and everyone laughs and goes, "Hey, maybe we should go check one of those out."
Just for laughs.
Be very aware.
You're walking into a place where people are randomly having sex.
People are constantly coming and going and there's security cameras everywhere.
So when your buddies are walking in, you're like, "Oh, this is going to be so much fun."
Ten years later, when you're trying to become a local senator, just know that that videotape
will show up.
So midnight adult books.
It's actually...
This is super interesting because I really try to find out where this place was.
Not because I'm like, "I need to do some on-the-ground research."
It's because I'm trying to verify stuff.
If you look for midnight adult books, there's actually two different addresses that pop
up for it.
And I don't know if it's still in existence, but it didn't turn into an Arby's or something
like that.
It seemed to have turned into another adult bookstore.
It's either on Josephine Street in Garden Grove or Garden Grove Boulevard.
But I have two options of what it could be.
It could be Garden of Eden adult bookstore or Romantic's adult book and video.
There's a lot of these stories in the area, apparently.
When we talk about ghosts, we're always talking about emotional energy.
And you figure...
I think the idea that theaters are haunted, dance studios are haunted, those things always
make sense because they're constantly generating so much energy.
So you would imagine a place where people were having lots and lots of anonymous sex,
probably cheating on their wives, right?
They're going down to the adult bookstore.
That must generate a ton of energy.
A ton of emotional energy in these places.
You walk into this room and there's a television set there, but you're not worried about that
because two or three guys are coming in.
I found a website where people review these adult bookstores.
And I've really questioned about whether or not I can actually put in the show notes
because apparently I found out recently that even the stuff in your show notes...
YouTube did that to me once.
Stuff I had in my show notes, YouTube tried shutting my channel down.
But there's a website where they review cruising spots, places to go.
And when you read reviews of Romantics Bookstore, a guy's like, "Yeah, it was really cool.
I was in this room and I got raped by three dudes."
And you're like, "That's not cool.
I mean, it's not...
That's...
I don't know what people are into this day, but that's not cool, right?"
And it's awful.
It sounded awful even by his description.
It sounded absolutely terrible.
It sounded absolutely terrifying.
And that's a guy who left a review.
That's a guy who left a review.
That's a guy who's like, "I think he actually gave it four stars."
So you can imagine the people who go there and it's not good.
It's not good.
He was totally...
He was like, "I didn't expect it, but it happened.
Four out of five stars.
Absolutely bizarre."
So you can imagine the type of emotional energy that's floating around this area.
Midnight Adult Bookstore.
Whether now it's Garden of Eden Adult Bookstore or Romantics Adult Book and Video, it's one
of the two.
It's haunted.
I mean, shouldn't surprise anyone with everything that I've been talking about.
Shouldn't surprise anyone.
Apparently, this place used to be a nightclub.
So before it was an adult video bookstore, people would go there to dance and hang out
and do blow and whatever.
And that's kind of what happened was there was a drug deal gone bad in this nightclub.
And a man was stabbed to death.
"Ohh!
Sorry, sorry, the drug deal didn't go good.
That's how they're supposed to go.
And he died."
And when the nightclub was torn down, or when the nightclub stopped operating there, I'm
assuming they just used the same building.
And it became midnight adult books and video.
A man, like late at night, maybe in the afternoon.
I don't know if they didn't specify time.
I imagine the spookiest time at night in adult bookstories in the middle of the night.
The clerks who would be working there would see a man in a cowboy hat walking around.
And then he would walk into a booth.
So remember we had that video arcade booth thing.
He would walk into a booth.
And that the staff knew was occupied.
Now officially the rule is that you're not supposed to have sex there.
Because it's illegal.
It's having sex in public.
It's actually illegal.
Cops will sting these places every once in a while.
They'll go undercover.
They're like, "Oh man, do I have to do that?
I just read the reviews on this place.
This place is horrible.
Johnson, you're the new...
Plus, first off, you're Officer Johnson.
You have to go.
But secondly, you go down there.
You're the newest one on the force.
You go down there, you're undercover.
And when someone tries having sex with you, you go, "Stop.
Police.
You're under arrest."
So because you're not supposed to do it, it's sex in public.
So officially these businesses aren't supposed to let you have sex in their little tiny disgusting
rooms.
You're supposed to get a hotel room across the street.
So when a staff member sees two people in a booth, you have to break it off.
That sounds like a resume for PTSD.
How much do these clerks get paid?
Could you imagine sitting there late at night, you see a guy go in a booth and another five
minutes pass, another guy goes in the same booth, you're like, "Aw, man, you would have
to work in a place with horse binders."
Because otherwise it's like trying to separate two ladybugs who are having sex.
These dudes are here to have sex.
You're going to walk into this tiny booth and be like, "No, stop it.
Stop it."
But that's the rule.
That's the law.
They're supposed to stop the sex.
The clerks have to stop the sex.
So when they would see...
And I'm assuming that people are sneaky about this.
But this cowboy man would always be seen.
He would never walk into a booth that was unoccupied.
He would walk into a booth that was occupied.
But when the clerk would go in and open the door and said, "Guys, you can't do it."
You would just find, instead of finding the cowboy and a man, you would just find a man
watching porn.
And the clerk would be like, "What?
Oh, no."
And the dude's like, "I paid $5.
Can you at least shut the door?"
So yeah.
You watch this.
That's the ghost story?
Yeah, it is the ghost story.
But I find it super fascinating because why would the ghost...
The ghost can go anywhere, right?
The ghost is in the porn store.
It's always going into a booth that's occupied.
Which in my mind makes me think the ghost is trying to have sex with these dudes.
The ghost is constantly trying to go into a room with another person and the staff has
to go and break it up.
But it finds out there's only one person in the booth.
So this ghost wants sex.
This ghost wants to have sex with dudes.
And I'm wondering, the guy in the booth, does he see anything?
Actually, that's actually...
That kind of blows my mind now that I'm thinking about it because from what I gather from the
one paragraph that actually is the story on theshadowlands.net, it's basically like a
paragraph.
I had to tell you what an adult bookstore was in the first place, but it says that the
staff sees the man in the cowboy hat enter the booth that's already occupied.
But if you're sitting there at your workstation, you're at a porn store, and you turn and you
see a man in a cowboy hat, phase through the door.
Like he actually walks through the door like it's not there like a ghost does.
You wouldn't be like, "Oh, that must be a real biological human.
I need to go stop him."
You would look, you would see a cowboy through a door and you'd be like, "Ah, it's the ghost."
And then you would just go back to reading your magazine or playing with your phone,
right?
To actually be confused that this was a real person, he would have to open the door of
the adult video store.
But the guy in the room, the guy who's currently pleasing himself while he's watching this
porn, he didn't notice the door opened.
He didn't notice anything.
So is the ghost creating some sort of optical illusion for the worker?
Like does he actually see the door open or does he phase through the door?
Does the guy in the booth, does the door open or is he just so entranced by whatever video
he's watching?
He doesn't notice the door open?
I don't know.
It doesn't say any of that.
It's literally just a paragraph that says when the guy walks in, then he disappears.
But I think the point of all of this is, ghosts must constantly be wanting to have sex.
I imagine because it's such a, and you could say, "Well, Jase, sex is a physical sensation,
right?
Sex is a physical sensation.
So why would something without a physical body want to do it?"
Yeah, but ghosts are always screaming in pain and stuff like that and covered in blood,
calling for their mom and stuff like that.
Little kids like appearing in your closet going, "Where's my mommy?
Where's my mommy?"
So I mean, they at least missed their moms, right?
They at least missed their moms.
But forget that one.
That was an weird example.
But if they're covered in blood or they're screaming in pain, then there is still some
connection to the physical.
There's still some connection to the physical.
So you would also think that these guys must constantly be wanting to have sex because
it's the one thing you can't do as a ghost.
That and I don't know, probably play basketball.
There's actually probably millions of things you can't do as a ghost.
But sex is the one thing that everyone thinks about at least some of the time, right?
And then is engaging in at least some of the time and you just go on and on.
Whether you're with a partner or you're headed down to the local adult bookstore, and especially
again, like these people, that's what they're there for.
They're there for quick, dirty, anonymous sex.
So the energy just must be like flipping around in there.
The emotional energy, you're in there, you have anonymous sex with three dudes, you're
pulling up your phone to rate it four out of five stars.
And then you're thinking, "Oh, dude, I hope my wife doesn't find out."
Like all of that emotional energy just being deposited into these rooms over and over and
over and over and over again for decades.
This place must actually be a hot spot.
I'm basically saying I want to see Zach Baggins or the Ghost Adventures head on down.
I want to see Taps at an adult bookstore with all their EVP readers asking, "Is anyone there?"
You're going to knock on the wall, you're going to knock on the wall and you're like,
"Oh, I don't want to look over there.
I know something's poking out of that hole."
Yeah, I do think that ghosts must always want to have sex.
And maybe these are good places to check out because you can go to all the haunted asylums
and haunted dance studios and graveyards that you want.
But a place that's open 24 hours a day where people are constantly having sweaty, sweaty
sex, anonymous dirty sex in these rooms, it has to generate a lot of energy.
And if you are a ghost, especially if you were a ghost that was killed there, it would
be the perfect place to manifest.
You're actually feeding off all of that energy.
So do ghosts want to have sex?
Is being dead the shut off valve to actually wanting to do the dirty?
I do think that maybe ghost hunters should stop going to the abandoned spooky house on
the edge of town and instead going into the inner city adult bookstores to find ghosts.
Even if they don't catch an EVP, even if they don't see a full body apparition, I can almost
guarantee that any room they go into, they will find a lot of ectoplasm.
DeadRabberRadio.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Tiktok is at DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
[Music]
[MUSIC]