Was the UN General Assembly recently briefed on alien contact?
And then we kick off Request Week with something from the conspiracy iceberg, and personally
one of my favorite conspiracies on there.
Medieval found footage, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode, and not just any episodes, it's the premiere
of season 4, episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you're having a great
day too.
Now, I think I actually, while cooking dinner, disproved evolution.
How long have humans been cooking food?
100,000 years?
Probably.
50,000 years, most likely.
Yet I still need a pot holder to pick up a hot bowl.
If evolution was true, my hands should be able to withstand the hottest food.
Possible.
Now obviously, there's a limit if the food is too hot, like the hot is the sun, or hot
is hot lava, I couldn't eat it.
So there is a ceiling of how hot food can get while still remaining edible, and yet
I had to spend 10 minutes looking for the single pot holder that I own so I could take
a bowl out of the microwave.
Your move Charles Darwin.
Now you could easily say, "Jason, why do you only own one oven mitt when you have two
hands?"
And two, how do you lose a thing that's bigger than a human hand?
And my response to that is, "Your move Charles Darwin, you can't judge me for my pot holder
losing this?"
Or the fact, well that should explain why I only have one pot holder, because I lost
the other one.
"Your move Charles Darwin."
Okay, let's go ahead and jump into the first story here.
Actually, before I do that, my friend Mitchum sent me a trailer for a movie, the title sounds
completely ridiculous, but the movie looks incredibly good.
I've seen movies like Helen Keller vs. the Night Wolves, which I couldn't finish it,
it was so bad.
And I saw FDR American Badass, which was actually pretty good.
So when Mitchum sent me a trailer for a movie called "The Man Who Killed Hitler" and then
"The Bigfoot", I had really low expectations, but the movie stars Sam Elliott, the trailer
looks great, it looks like they took a ridiculous plot and are playing it as seriously as possible,
it looks beautiful as well.
This man, you go back in time, not literally, but you see him kill Hitler and then the government
enlists him to kill Bigfoot, who is spreading some sort of deadly pathogen across the wilderness.
Looks really good actually, so I'll put the trailer in the show notes, check it out.
Now our first story, we had a couple big stories pop up while I was taking my vacation.
And this was one of the ones that popped up.
And at first I was, a lot of people are going to go, "Oh, I already know how the story ends
because you know you're following it on 4chan, but give me a second because I found a new
piece of evidence."
But for those who don't know anything about the story, what happened was on January 29th,
the video was uploaded January 29th, 2019, I should say in case you're listening to this
episode 10 years in the future.
This video was uploaded on January 29th, 2019.
And it is a video of the United Nations General Assembly and it starts off saying, "There's
no videotaping allowed, this message cannot be reproduced anywhere, it's like a crime."
You see a young woman walk up to the podium and get stuff ready.
You see an older gentleman off to the left standing there and as he moves backwards his
hands kind of sway side to side.
And you see a very attractive woman sitting in a chair waiting for her turn to speak.
Now that woman's name is Alia Prokofyeva.
I bet you missed those mispronunciations for a week.
Anyways, she describes herself that she is ahead of something called Galactica.
I went to her LinkedIn profile, she is trying to set up the first city in space.
So she's kind of like this expert, self-proclaimed expert, I'm not for sure.
So you do have experts go to the UN from time to time, not everyone who speaks there is
a world leader.
She goes up to the podium and she says, she reveals this message and the video quality
is really bad because it was supposedly recorded on a cell phone.
Every so often you see a black image move in front of it and the idea is that the person
who's recording it is trying to shield the cell phone camera from view and the audio
quality is bad as well because it's not an official video.
So you're basically just getting the audio from the phone.
She goes up to the podium and says, back in December a pyramid shaped UFO was sighted
over the Pentagon in Washington DC and we don't know what it was.
It's possibly extraterrestrial.
What makes this visitation curious is that the pyramid began broadcasting a pattern that
matches a pattern from a nearby star system.
Now we do have things called pulsars.
We don't have them.
Nature has them.
The universe owns them.
But there are stars that rotate and they can let off these radio bursts.
We pick up when we first discovered them, we thought it was alien life because of the
pattern.
But it turns out it's just a pulsar spinning in space.
But she says this pyramid shaped UFO matches that frequency.
Now there were videos that came out in December of a pyramid shaped UFO hovering over Washington
DC.
Those videos themselves are interesting because one, they look real-ish.
Nowadays anything can easily be faked, especially because you're running on a cell phone camera.
Any special effects you put in there, any irregularities in the special effects, a believer will just
chalk it up to the bad quality of the video.
When I saw the video over Washington DC, my first thing was that Washington DC is heavily
populated so why am I only seeing a couple angles of this thing?
There should be thousands of videos, even if the mainstream media didn't cover it.
The thing was huge.
So she says this is what happened.
Now the video got uploaded to YouTube on January 29th and it set the UFO community
abuzz.
They're like oh my god look at this leaked footage that came out of the UN.
Now when I'm watching it I'm thinking if this video footage is real, YouTube would take
it down.
The governments of the world would immediately go whoa, whoa, whoa, that video is not supposed
to be up.
It wasn't even supposed to be videotaped.
Can you please shut down this, take this channel offline?
And it's still there.
It only has 60,000 views so it's not a ton of views but it's there.
It was on 4chan.
4chan is generally known to be monitored by at least the US government.
So the fact that it's still up kind of takes away its credibility.
If you go to that video and all the links are going to be in the show notes of course,
but if you go to that video it links to an original video, that channel is taken down
but that could be part of the LARP.
I could easily set up a channel, delete it, and then link a video to it and be like oh
the original channel was deleted but this is the video, so that's easy to fake too.
But UFO people, especially on 4chan, were like oh my god what do we do with this, here's
this woman talking about this thing.
Now the debunking to it, and this is where people are like yeah I know this part but
I have to go over this and don't just skip ahead because there's something, there's another
additional detail to this.
The debunking to it is earlier in the year I believe, it might have been the previous
year, Erdogan, Erdogan I believe is the president of Turkey, if I'm pronouncing his name right,
which I'm most likely, I'm not.
He gives a presentation to the UN and when he is talking to the United Nations you see
a young woman walk up to the podium, get everything ready.
You see a man, an old gentleman kind of stand into the side and he steps back and his hands
are kind of moving.
It's the exact same video, except for a few key details.
One, the young woman, uh, Aliyah, is not giving the speech, she's nowhere present in the video,
instead it's Erdogan.
The film quality is much better, it's digital video, it's basically high end digital video
because it is the United Nations, it's not like they have money problems.
The sound quality is much, much better, the cell phone video is really tinny because it's
supposedly on a cell phone, and there's no hand ever kind of blocking the view.
And so the debunkers go, "Lookit, this is the video that they took the president, Erdogan,
out of, put Aliyah in as a deep fake.
They digitally removed one person and put another person in, dropped the video quality, dropped
the sound quality, and presented this as proof.
You guys are idiots, you guys should never believe this."
So when I was looking at, I saw the original video, I was like, it shouldn't be online
if it's real.
I think it's kind of suspicious that there's the black hand keeps moving in front of the
camera, and I'm thinking that could be to clear up, like to kind of block any irregularities
in the video that they're trying to put out as real.
So, we talked about deep fakes before.
Now, it's funny because the first time I came across deep fakes, ICE was seeing pornographic
images of Gal Gadot's face on a porn star's body.
Natalie Portman's face on a porn star's body.
Daisy Ridley's face on a porn star's body, and they were taking these huge celebrities
and basically turning them into porn stars.
And very, very convincing, very, very convincing technology.
I had never seen a full body deep fake before, but it's the same idea.
You take thousands of images, you have a source image, and then you have the image you want
to insert, you remove one image in the porn videos, it would just be the original actress's
face, put the new face on top of it.
You could do the same thing here.
The Alia speaker, she has a shadow, she looks, it looks convincing.
Again, if she went up and talked about wheat products or the production of corn in Germany,
I would have had no reason to disbelieve it.
If the video hadn't started off saying "please don't record", I would have had less reason
to doubt it.
But the fact that they're like "we're going to prosecute anyone who puts this out", I
was like "okay, they're kind of hyping it up a bit".
But here's the interesting thing.
So that's the story with that.
When I first saw the videos, I was like "oh, I'll cover that one, the break's over".
It's pretty cut and dry.
You have a, what looks like a fraud when you look at all the evidence.
You have a video that seems suspicious, and then you find the exact same video at higher
quality of a different person giving a boring speech.
Totally different speech.
So I go "well, that's pretty cut and dry".
But what happens next is what makes me suspicious about everything.
January 29th is the you and video uploaded to YouTube.
At least the one we can see.
I don't know about the one that supposedly got the account terminated, but on January
29th is the video you can watch.
Video I have a link to.
January 29th was the same time they're like "nope, this is fake, here's the Erdogan video
video".
That whole story kind of happened relatively quickly.
But also what makes me suspicious about the story is on January 30th, a viral news story
goes up.
Look at these wacky deepfakes.
Look at Steve Buscemi's face on Jennifer Lawrence's body.
What?
This is crazy.
Look at this wacky technology.
And it's weird because they could have had that same story.
If you wanted to cover deepfakes that day, if you wanted to make that a viral story,
the UFO video is a more convincing deepfake.
Because when you see the Steve Buscemi/Jennifer Lawrence thing, it looks grotesque.
It looks really really weird.
It's not convincing in any way, shape or form.
And I thought why a day after the you and video comes out, which is most likely a fake,
are they now pushing the story of deepfakes back into the media and showing us a ridiculous
example?
And they did the same thing over the summer.
Over the summer is when the trend began of the famous actresses being put on porn stars
bodies.
But when the media covered it, when they showed examples of it, they'd say, "Look at Nicholas
Cage's face on all of these movie stars?
What?"
And I'm thinking why don't- I'm not asking them to show porn on CNN, but why don't
they show at least still clips and they could be like, "This is this actress's face."
This is Gal Gadot's face on Biloxi Blue's body or something.
That's convincing.
The skin tone's the same.
You can't tell the difference.
The only reason you know it's fake is because Gal Gadot has never done porn.
That's the reason you factually know that video is not real.
So why if they have that did they push the Nicholas Cage's face on in the middle of
Game of Thrones or whatever it was?
Why when they have a semi-convincing deepfake of someone giving a speech to the United Nations
General Assembly about UFOs do you show how wacky deepfakes are because you have Jennifer
Lawrence with this grotesque- sorry, Steve Bishammy, but like this weird looking face?
I think because ultimately deepfake technology, they warn us about it.
I think their concern is rogue actors using deepfake technology.
I think the government, I think certain powerful people want to use it for their benefit, so
they don't want to really show us how convincing it can actually be.
Because this Ewan video, like I said, if she went up and talked about trade tariffs and
someone showed me that video I'd be like "why are you showing me this?
This is super boring."
And then they go "that never happened.
That's fake."
I'd have been like "what?"
It's very convincing.
I think deepfake technology is being planned to be used and people go "oh it's going to
be used for Pizzagate if Hillary Clinton never gets videotaped eating a baby.
I don't think it's ever going to be anything like that."
I think when deepfake technology actually is used it's going to be something super mundane
that no one will really question.
When you talk about UFOs and satanic worship and all sorts of this crazy stuff it's easy
for a skeptic to go "well that's obviously not true."
But if they want to have a video of the president talking about a new trade plan with Italy where
we're going to basically give them all of our money or that's kind of ridiculous too,
but you know what I mean?
Something relatively boring, people won't question that.
And I think there's an actual effort to warn people about deepfakes but not warn them at
how realistic they can be.
Very odd timing.
The Steve Buscemi video was uploaded the same day as the UN video.
The story got reported the next morning.
So while all the UFOologists were still debating over the authenticity of this UN General Assembly
video all of these news websites were like "pfft look at this technology can you believe
it?
It's 2019?"
Weird.
Very, very convenient timing.
Very convenient timing.
Okay, let's go ahead and move on to our next story.
Now our next story was actually a request from Joshua from YouTube and it is one of
the ones that I have found the most intriguing on the conspiracy theory iceberg.
Just the idea I've always found interesting.
Medieval found footage.
The phrase itself is very evocative because it makes you think of one of two things.
Level 3.
One, it's fake.
It's totally made up.
It's just three words strung together.
But that's boring.
People always go "what?
That's just fake!"
And I'm like "yeah probably!"
But that's not a fun podcast.
They'll just be like "ah it's fake."
Like either it's fake for a reason or you go "it's fake" but let's pretend it's not
for a second.
So it is possibly just three words strung together.
However, this one has a bit of meat to it.
So it's one of three things that's either fake.
It involves time travel which is a nice theory.
Which is nice, it's evocative.
And then there's one that I think is more accurate.
And it's pretty cool.
So we've already addressed maybe it's fake, maybe it's something people put together,
whatever.
I don't like it, maybe.
But that's boring.
Time travel.
The idea of time travel I think kind of touches people on a personal level because it is a
it addresses two things.
It addresses changing the past because everyone has regrets.
Time travel touches on the idea that we can change our past.
And two, I think a lot of people don't necessarily wish they could live forever.
But for me, I want to see what comes next.
I personally think it would be more fascinating to travel into the future to see what happens
next.
And time travel plays on both of those.
I could fall asleep and wake up a thousand years from now and be like oh my god this
is awesome there's robots or apocalyptic wasteland, everyone's dead and I'm just kind of stumbling
around until I fall and my glasses break.
And I go all the books in the world.
That's what interesting thing about time travel.
It kind of plays on both of those things.
So let's address the time travel theory first.
And that would be that some archaeologists are digging around in England.
They got their shovels and the cops are like oh you don't have a permit and they're like
ah whatever we're archaeology thrown dirt in the cops face.
They keep digging, the cops are trying to arrest them.
Not the hammer, the shovel goes ding ding.
Hit something and the cops are like what's that?
Archaeologist goes, it looks like some sort of film case.
Test it off.
Pull it out and it's a reel of film.
And they're like hmm do you have a projector?
The cops are like no we don't even have guns over here.
Why would you think we'd have a projector?
Eventually though the archaeologists pay their bail.
They go to a local cinema, put the film on the projector and what they see is literal
found footage.
They see film of these medieval people kind of dancing around doing their stuff, making
clay pots, looking miserable all the time.
Knights are beating them up, they're all dying.
Every movie ends with them dying of the bubonic plague.
The end.
And the archaeologists are like this is impossible.
It's in case in this metal tin, it's shot on this camera that we were actually able
to string up to a projector.
Maybe it's on like super IMAX film.
Maybe it's digital film from the future.
But it's found footage and the idea would be that at some point somebody traveled back
in time to the medieval period, filmed them doing their things.
Maybe they were hamming it up for the camera, maybe it was a little Punch and Judy show.
Maybe, maybe they were videotaping something and the time travelers dressed up as medieval
people walking around their hidden camera.
They're seeing this young boy writing stuff and they're like hey, what are you writing?
He's like I'm a writing stuff.
And they're like well that's obvious that you're writing stuff.
What are you writing?
He's like oh nothing.
I just have stories in my head sometime.
I call this one Romeo and Juliet and they're like your hand name doesn't happen to be William
Shakespeare.
He's like they call me Billy.
That's in the found footage and obviously apparently it has audio as well.
But anyways they find this footage and for whatever reason they leave it behind.
For us to find because if it was just time travelers going back in time filming a bunch
of dudes dancing around and Billy Shakespeare and then went to the future we wouldn't know
it was there.
So that theory is completely ridiculous obviously and not because I don't believe in time travel
because I do to a sense but this would require one time travelers to travel back to medieval
times.
Two, to time travel back to medieval times and use technology that we would be able to
view.
We can't even view right if someone gave me a laser disk right now I'd be SOL.
Like I'd be like hey, things.
What am I going to do with this?
It's a giant coaster.
I can't even view laser disk technology.
By the time we have time machines going back and forth in time they're not going to be
using SD cards.
They're not even going to be using film.
What would they use?
It would be the same thing.
Yeah, actually if I had a cell phone, if I went back in time and I left my cell phone
in the 1980s and I pulled down my SD card they'd be like well okay your fingernail fell off
robot man.
Like they'd have no way of even knowing what was on it.
So that theory while it is interesting because it's sci-fi-ish it's not very likely at all.
And I don't think that's what medieval found footage refers to.
I've seen that theory bandied around a couple times and they're like oh it's about time
travelers going back and forth.
I don't really think that it is what it refers to.
But I do think the theory has some meat and I think this version is more interesting because
it's quite possibly true.
Let's say the year is 1568.
Couple peasants running around in the field.
I apparently in my version of medieval times they just dance and run and don't do any work
but it was actually quite grueling.
They worked from sundown to sun up or the other way around.
That would be working to the night.
They've worked from sun up to sun down and then they sit at home in front of the fireplace
and try to forget their miserable existence.
So but anyways in my version they're just running around through the fields.
They're like Gerald Gerald get back to your chores and he's like no way I'm out of here.
It's 15 whatever year I stand before I don't even remember at this point.
And these peasants are playing in the woods and this night.
I don't know what this effect was.
This night rides up to the peasants and is like the king requires your service peasants
and they're like oh yeah whatever you say night what are we supposed to do and the night's
like the king is making a movie.
Peasants be like what?
What's a movie?
The night's like I don't know.
You know how hard it is to shrug in armor but I'm gonna do it anyways.
I don't know.
The horse is like they all go back to the castle.
Now we know the history of film.
It's very very well documented partially because film is a document in and of itself.
It's a chemical process and I'm not gonna bore you with the details of it because it's
easily you can find on Wikipedia again all the links are below but we can trace it back
quite a while and before we were capturing because really I say I'm not gonna bore you
with the process but all film is is a series of pictures and there's it's weird on film
I don't know if it's the same with digital but on film there's a black bar between each
frame but our brain doesn't pick up the black bar because we have this thing called like
continuity of image and it's weird now because think about it when you sit down and you watch
a film you're actually seeing a black image what is it 32 frames per second so you're
seeing a black image 32 times every second and your brain just doesn't process it and
what's weird is I'm sure some people's brains do I'm sure there are some people whose brains
don't work right and it must be maddening to have to watch a movie because they'd be
like oh my god people like this like I'm just seeing a bunch of black every once in a while
normal people don't see it but anyway so all it is is a series of photographs played very
very rapidly same thing with like you guys know what film is so between film we can go
all the way back thousands probably about a thousand years if not farther to something
called the camera obscura and that was film without film it was only what was going on
outside that was basically a black room with a people not like a pervert's people but a
people that allowed sunlight to come in and the image was like reversal in the wall it
got real complicated for me to follow on this stuff but that allowed you that if you sat
in this dark room through this looking against the wall you could see what was going on outside
now obviously you just leave the dark room and see what was going on outside but it was
an early form of a projected image people say that cave paintings on walls could have been
brought from some sort of camera obscura that religious practices could have involved the
camera obscura thousands of years ago could have been the way to tell stories of myths
and legends by basically creating this type of room and having people acting it out and
then it's like appears on the wall so the camera obscura Leonardo da Vinci used one a bunch
of other old people used one I think Leonardo da Vinci was the one who actually like made
it popular he made it fetch like he created the mainstream version of it and then in
1827 that's when some guy says you know I'm gonna use that same process but I'm gonna
take a piece of polished pewter plate with Peter Peckle it's gonna help him with this
a polished Peter plate and he covered it with something called bitman of Judea the sunlight
hits the plate using the same thing as the camera obscura and after eight hours he's
able to wipe off everything that the sun didn't burn in this is weird process and then he
has an image on a plate of what was outside that is the first like here is a here's an
image you didn't have to be here to see this here is this image now the limitation obviously
was that it took eight hours so they didn't have any pictures of people back then so you
go Jason you said you know camera obscuras existed for a long time and then in 1827 is
the first time we have a photograph and a photograph is a stepping stone to a film so
how do you equate that with the medieval times well to do that I'm actually going to talk
about another recommendation I got a while back I got an email from a gentleman named
Gary and we were talking about Terare the guy who could eat anything which I love that
episode he ate a gold fork and the gold fork never came out and so the idea is is that
he dissolved it and Gary emailed me and he sent me a link to something called aqua regia
now aqua regia was a chemical it was a chemical combination that could be used to dissolve
gold and platinum and completely dissolve it so aqua regia was this chemical that was
made and you're like okay that's a cute story but what does that have to do with anything
you're talking about it was first mentioned in 1300 AD and then in 1600 AD the next time
we see a reference to this it was written out not as a chemical composition or how
the chemicals work together it was instead a riddle it was a drawing that explained this
advanced chemical process as an image and the process said the process showed a dragon
and then a fox eating a rooster and the rooster eating the fox and then this is how they deciphered
this it said the rooster symbolizes gold and the fox represents aqua regia obviously there
was some sort of key code some guy just wasn't looking at it and going oh yeah that's what
that means but the repetitive dissolving heating and re-dissolving the rooster eating the fox
eating the rooster leads to the buildup of chlorine gas in the flask the golden crystallizes
in the form of gold chloride whose red crystals were known as dragon's blood so you had the
initial recipe of what it does in 1300 AD you then have this coded drawing in 1600 AD
the reaction was not listed in chemical literature at all until 1890 so in that time period people
had invented the process or discovered the process in 1300 it was referenced again 300
years later and then it took another two what is that yeah it took almost another 300 years
before anyone ever wrote it down again but it was still being practiced and in that time
period if those original documents were destroyed for whatever reason it would have been lost
until it was quote unquote discovered in 1890 so who's not to say that the film all film
is is a chemical process involving light and material and a chemical dark rooms and stuff
like that you're mixing these chemicals together you take an image onto a piece of there's not
magic now I get it the magic of the cinema and all that stuff it's great it's silver
screen all that nonsense but it's not actual magic it is a chemical process who's not to
say that the chemical process wasn't discovered in 1827 but it was discovered before then
the proof we have that it was discovered is gone is that a supposition absolutely do I
have any proof of that no I can look at these other things that were lost and then rediscovered
I can say well this stuff happened the biggest obstacle to the idea of medieval found footage
is this that it took eight hours to produce an image back then I don't want to say well
maybe they found a quicker way to do it because that's taking it more into the fantastical
I want to stick with the technology we know they had they had a magic lantern not not
the literal they had a thing called a magic lantern that you'd have a little image it's
basically a side projector back then the magic lantern was like in the 1500s it was in the
medieval times in the medieval times they have this thing called the magic lantern it was
a projector it was the evolution of the camera obscura but instead of seeing what was outside
you could have a little piece of glass that was hand painted and you'd put it in and you'd
put a candle in it or sunlight or whatever and it would project the image on the wall
just like a slide projector and then people said you know what let's put two slides in
it and you could show like a little cartoon guy juggling so the basics of the technology
were there projection glass slides animation to a degree you would definitely see the black
switch there is the machine slowly clicked over but this technology was in wide use so
the only thing we have to add to have medieval found footage is the real people they have
the slides of the two people juggling or whatever they want to do the two little cartoon people
dancing but for found footage I want footage of people is it possible that there was film
footage of people in the medieval times again the biggest obstacle to it is people having
to stand still for eight hours but that's why I use the king example because you're a peasant
you're going to get your head chopped off if you don't stand in the same spot for eight
hours and then you just move slightly for the next one and move slightly for the next
one and move slightly for the next one it would take you know a month to have a good
five minutes of footage and you know you figure maybe they're sitting down in chairs but it's
not an insurmountable hurdle to have someone sit in a chair for eight hours and then after
that move their arms slightly and it would be a great would imagine going to a king's
house and he's like you know you ever heard of a witch and his guests are like well of
course which is a real thing we have to like kill twelve of them getting here and king
goes have you ever heard of the Blair witch and then he has this found footage movie well
it's not found to him he owns it he made it but imagine going to a royal court and people
being like oh look at my magic lantern it's two images of this cartoon guy juggling the
kings like that sucks here's transformers for it took me eight years to film but I did
it it is possible even using the technology the only thing that's not possible is you
have to go along with me on the journey that the technology got a little more advanced between
fifteen hundred and eighteen twenty seven regarding that chemical process and the fact
that we can I can say here's another chemical process that was not mentioned for two hundred
years people were doing it in that time period but it wasn't mentioned for two hundred years
I think there is medieval found footage I think that it is very likely that some archaeologists
found this stuff why it wasn't released I don't know now I want to put my I think it's
likely but I want to put money on it but it may be out there there may be footage of the
real Blair Witch there it is a documentary it was an actual witch they were chasing around
King standing in the corner of the castle at the end camera falls breaks it's over I
think the idea of medieval found footage is very intriguing and I it's one of those conspiracy
theories that I actually really like because it's a good one it's a happy conspiracy theory
it's we are more advanced than we think we are we're more clever as a species than we
think we are that 300 400 years before the official invention of something someone came
up with it used it for entertainment for documentation whatever there's not a lot of positive conspiracy
theories out there but one of them that we're actually smarter than we give ourselves credit
for that's a good conspiracy theory dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be our email
address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @jasonocarpenter
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast you don't have
to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today have a great day guys
you
(upbeat music)