When a group of ghost hunters descend upon a haunted, abandoned hospital, they have no
idea their investigation is about to go from the world of the paranormal into the realm
of true crime.
Now we take a look at the bizarre conspiracy that there is a secret government program
that has one goal to stop the law of attraction today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garbiner and I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
Hope you guys are having tons of fun out there in the world.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now is our final member of the Christmas
livestream.
Yes Christmas of 2021.
Livestream contributor everyone give a round of applause for Sega Metzi Mogomotzi.
Woohoo yeah come on in yeah walk on into Dead Rabbit Command thank you so much Sega
Metzi.
Now honestly I might have already given you props for your donation but I wasn't for
sure.
I saw your name on a pad that I'd written all this stuff down and I was like let's
I'd rather err on the side of caution.
Sega Metzi you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't support
the show financially I totally understand I really do.
Just helps spread the word about the show that really really really helps out a lot.
Now Sega Metzi I'm gonna go ahead and start off by tossing you the hair hang glider.
Grab that in your little hands.
We are jumping off the highest point of Dead Rabbit Command and glide us all the way out
too.
Vicksburg Mississippi.
This is a very interesting story not just for the story itself but I found it by accident
and I was actually trying to verify yesterday's story about the kids or kid.
We still don't know how many kids disappeared in the bathroom in Colorado Springs Colorado
and I was trying to I always try to verify these ghost stories.
I tried to verify if any kid actually did magically disappear in the bathroom.
This popped up and I was like wow I hadn't heard of this story this story is a different
type of ghost story.
This is a boots on the ground type ghost story not haunted boots that'd be hilarious though
they're doing a little dance.
It's June 28th 2015 we're in Vicksburg Mississippi.
We're standing outside the Coon Memorial State Hospital.
This place has been investigated by a lot of paranormal investigators and we can understand
why we're standing outside this hospital it's late at night it's abandoned and you just
see like an owl sitting on top of the building.
Hanging out up there and we're like oh that's kind of spooky.
We're not owl investigators though we have to go inside and look for ghosts we got our
EVP recorders we got our temperature gauges we're walking around flashlights.
Looking for ghosts.
This is actually considered by a lot of ghost hunting groups as one of the most haunted
places in all of Mississippi.
I'll try to put some of the stuff in the show notes but there's been articles written
about this place videos EVPs but we're actually not here for the ghostly activity itself.
We're here to take a look at another group of ghost hunters who were also at Coon Memorial
State Hospital on June 28th 2015.
This group of ghost hunters they head out here because again this is a standard ghost
hunting location.
They're walking around the abandoned hospital late one night.
Walking through it shining their flashlights holding out their little tape recorder is
anyone here?
We'll play back later to see if we picked up anything.
Let's just keep walking around this hospital to see what we can find and what happens is
they get to where there's the staircase leading up to the second floor.
And despite the eerie reputation for this place it is a huge abandoned hospital so of
course you know there's going to be vagrants there.
There's going to be probably wild animals stuff like that.
So you might run into a living person you might run into a living pack of dogs that
was always my biggest worry when I was ghost hunting these type of places.
But what this group finds is far more worrisome.
When they get to the staircase that leads up to the second floor they see dripping down
the stairs.
Fresh blood.
When I say dripping it's not just like a little Halloween effect it clearly looks like someone
dragged something large and bloody down the stairs.
Not too long ago either.
They're shining their flashlights and they actually see this blood trail kind of smear
across the floor right in front of them and they see it lead out of one of the exits of
the building.
So the ghost hunters are like okay this is definitely gone from zero to sixty really
quickly.
They begin to follow this blood trail out of the building and it rounds this little corner
and there under the light of the Mississippi moon they see a dead woman.
They rush to the local police department and they say hey listen, oh it's an abandoned
hospital we know we're not supposed to be there that's why we went late at night around
this ghost expedition.
However you can arrest this for trespassing but there's something far more important going
on there.
They found the body of this dead lady.
Around the same time like within a matter of hours of this happening there is a traffic
stop.
There is a police officer driving on the road and he sees a car that he has suspicions about
and he pulls them over.
And sitting in the car is Akeem McLeod he's a twenty year old man and Raphael McLeod thirty
three years old.
They were related.
He pulls it over and when the cops is running the plates and checking the license and registration
all that stuff he realizes that Akeem and Raphael are driving a stolen car and they have
a weapon in the vehicle.
The police radio is at in and says hey I have this stolen car I have this firearm.
You guys might want to check on who this car actually belongs to because I think something
bad might have happened.
So then the police go to they follow the registration.
They go to the house of Sharon Wilson this sixty nine year old woman.
She's not home.
The police are kind of linking all of these three things together.
We have a stolen car we have a woman that's missing and we're also getting the report
of this body out in the middle of this abandoned hospital and they are able to ID that woman
as Sharon.
She had been murdered at the hospital.
Akeem and Raphael are arrested like this is all happening in just a very short amount
of time.
They're arrested for the murder of Sharon about a week they're both being held about
a week later Akeem is released in the murder of Sharon.
They don't think he had anything to do with it.
Actually that's not true.
They said we can't prove it.
We can't prove he had anything to do with this.
So Raphael is held for Sharon's murder.
Now what's really interesting is I came across this thing on accident.
It's from 2015 and I read that article and I was like wow that's really creepy haunted
locations are usually haunted where people don't want to go there.
They're usually in the middle of nowhere and other than the occasional ghost hunting group
who would have thought that if you had disposed of a body at this hospital anybody would have
found it.
Or in any real matter of time.
It wasn't like they left her on the front porch.
They took her to the hospital.
I read this story and I go okay that's really cool.
I mean that's not cool for Sharon or her family or anything like that but I thought ghost hunters
run into this and then I'm like well it's 2015.
I wonder how this story's played out.
It's always neat to look back and read these different articles to see how the story ended.
But it turns out that Raphael, what the charges were was that he did murder her right or he
allegedly murdered Sharon and the way that it was set up was like this.
He was stalking her.
Her husband had died just about I think it was three years ago like in 2012 and they were
both residents of New Orleans and they left because of Hurricane Katrina.
So they ended up in Mississippi, start life over again.
She loses her husband.
She's living alone and then this creep is outside in his car and he watches her where
she has a hidden key underneath a rock.
One day he sees her lift the rock up, take the key open the door and go in.
So he decides to do that as well.
He gets the key.
He lets himself into her house.
He attacks her.
He rapes her and then kidnaps her.
He forces her into her own car, drives out to Coon Memorial Hospital and executes her.
Then he came back to her house and he tried to burn.
He figured he probably left some evidence there so he tried to burn it down.
So he was getting charged with rape, kidnapping, stalking because he was kind of lying and
waiting and watching to see what her patterns were and murder.
And Arson.
Did I say Arson?
Anyways he was charged with all of these different things.
The question, it was weird.
The articles didn't ask this question so much.
I did because you know I'm thinking like paranormal spooky stuff but I can understand
him dumping the body in the middle of nowhere but why did he take her up to the second story
of this haunted hospital?
Killer just to have to drag her back down the stairs because that's how they found her
body.
If he had shot her and just thrown her in the bushes around the same hospital they wouldn't
have found it.
At least not in that sequence of events.
Now again they did get pulled over in the car and Sharon was missing and all that stuff
but they wouldn't have been able to prove that she was dead for quite a while.
But he took her upstairs, he shot her and then dragged her back down the stairs so a
weird detail.
He is a murderer.
I mean he is a rapist and a murderer.
He's not the most sane person on the planet but I thought it was weird.
What was that part of it?
So I read that article and I was like wow that's really interesting so because times
past we can actually see more about the information it's not a breaking news true crime story.
And then the story gets even crazier.
Because then I find out what happens next.
Let's jump ahead to March 2nd 2016.
So less than a year later.
Raphael is being held in Warren County jail.
The trial is going through the process.
I don't even know if it's gone to trial at this point but you know lawyers are talking
and prosecutors are talking and stuff like that.
March 2nd 2016 Raphael who's being held in the Warren County jail gets a shiv, overpowers
a guard and escapes from the county jail.
This man who murdered a 69 year old woman is now loose in the city with nothing to lose
because he's facing horrifying charges.
There is a massive manhunt for him.
March 10th 2016, 8 days later.
There's a guy, this is still in the Vicksburg area, this guy comes out of his house to get
in his car and all of a sudden Raphael runs up to him, puts a shiv to him and says we're
going inside.
And the man's like this is not how I expected my morning to start off.
Raphael leads the man inside of the house where this dude also has his wife and his 5 year
old son.
Raphael ties up the dad, ties up the mom, throws them in the bathroom.
At some point the mom gets permission to leave the bathroom.
I don't know exactly why he did it.
I'm glad that he did considering how this story turns out it does have an ending.
But he allows the woman to leave the bathroom and she leaves and he's still in there with
the dad, the husband.
And Raphael, because he's a lunatic, begins stabbing the dude.
He's tied up, he's tied up still.
He begins stabbing the dude, stabs him in the shoulder.
The mom, they don't reveal these people's names in the newspaper, but the mom comes
in holding a firearm she went.
I don't know what excuse she used to leave the bathroom, but I'm glad that she was able
to.
She comes in with a gun, begins shooting at Raphael.
And they're in this really small bathroom, but she misses him.
But she shoots at Raphael.
She frees her husband.
She hands the gun to her husband.
And he executes Raphael in the bathroom.
Crazy, crazy story.
I mean again I use the word execute.
That's pretty much self defense at that point.
You've been stabbed.
This guy's a lunatic, he's already killed one woman.
I don't even know if they knew who he was, right?
He just comes in with the homemade knife and is like, "Get in your house, get in your
house."
The dad shoots him to death in the bathroom.
End of story.
What a fa- I mean that's just insane story.
That guy truly was a menace.
He's running around committing these horrific crimes.
He's taking family sausages.
He kidnaps this woman and rapes and kills her.
Horrible.
And it's interesting because this memorial hospital, this haunted hospital stood there
for years and years and years.
Empty.
Ghost hunters are showing up.
Like I said, it's considered one of the most haunted locations in Missouri.
In 2019 they demolished it.
They knocked it down.
They said, "We're not going to let this lot go to waste.
We're going to build something else here."
A lot of times you have these haunted locations knocked down for economic reasons.
But I think this was also partially this legacy, right?
You had this guy who committed this heinous crime at this location and that probably did
speed things up because it was empty for so long.
And you just had, you know, every so often you have a security crew sweep it or something
like that and you'd appear in all these ghost hunter shows and YouTube channels and stuff
like that.
And yeah, they ended up demolishing it in 2019.
They smashed it down.
I don't know if there's anything there in that location right now.
What a crazy story.
It does suck.
I mean, outside of the true crime element, when you have a place that is regarded as
extremely haunted, improvably haunted, you can get all these EVPs and all of these weird
photographs and video footage and stuff like that.
And it's demolished, right?
In a paranormal world, that's the equivalent of, you know, finding a burial site of a long
lost group of people.
Just smashing the bones and putting up a tract house.
Like I understand why, obviously.
You need to build stuff there that people are going to use.
You can't have a building there just for ghost hunters.
But you know what?
Maybe if there is a building right now, it's haunted by the ghosts of insane patients of
a hospital that's all we can hope for.
Sega, Metzi, Mogomotzi, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the carbonar copter we
are leaving behind Mississippi.
Fly us all the way out.
To a basketball court.
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
And at this basketball court, we don't have this guy's name, so we're going to go ahead
and call him Michael.
Michael is sitting there and he's dribbling a ball and he's looking at the hoop and he
throws it up.
I can't do a sound effect for a ball in a hoop.
And we're like, "Hey bro, you want to play some one on one?"
He's like, "Yeah, sure."
And I'm like, "I'm not going to basketball either now, all of a sudden you're playing."
I'm like, "I have $100 going on you buddy, keep playing."
You're all sweaty and stuff.
You're like, "Dude, I'm wearing slacks right now trying to make all these shots."
And as I'm enjoying your discomfort, Michael, you notice as he's playing the game, he seems
decent, or I use decent basketball player, but you notice like every so often he goes
up for a shot and you're like, "That's weird."
I could have sworn he was shorter.
A couple minutes ago.
And he gives you a little wink and then he does like this cool double back basketball
move on you and he makes another shot and you're like, "Wow, dude, this guy's totally
tongueing on me.
I hope Jason didn't really bet any money on me."
And you see him, he's like, "Oh dude, yeah, you want to keep going, you want to keep
going."
You realize, "Wow, I'm looking right at this dude and I swear, I don't know how this is
impossible, he's taller mid-sense."
Like as I'm looking at this guy, he's growing at least an inch or two.
And I'm walking down from the stands and I go, "That is why we're here.
That is why we're here."
You see Michael over there has unlocked the secret to growing taller.
Now Michael says, "Listen, I have a lot of body issues.
I have a lot of issues with my parents and things like that, but the one thing that people
who know me very closely know that I'm the most self-conscious about is my height.
I've always been self-conscious about my height."
And what I did, I tried everything right.
You do all the spine stretching exercises, you do the yoga, you do maybe you're looking
into the medical treatment where they're breaking your legs.
You're like, "Okay, no, I look too far, I don't want to go that far."
But I want to be taller and I'm looking at all this stuff that I could positively do.
Michael then stumbles across YouTube videos and things like that about using hypnosis
to become taller.
And that takes him down the path of the law of attraction.
He goes, "Can you actually, if you can law of attraction a more successful life, if
you can law of attraction a suitable partner, you can law of attraction a better job, but
could you law of attraction growing taller?"
And he starts to find case after case after case after case after case of people who claim
that they can do this.
He starts to find these stories about people who are using the law of attraction to physically
change their bodies.
And not just their height, like that's what he's concerned about, right?
He just wants to be taller.
But he starts to find reports of people growing bigger breasts or bigger penis.
Skin is clearer than it used to be.
Their nose is smaller.
Some people say they've even been able to use it to beat back baldness and even regenerate
body parts.
Now it's funny, if I told you that, right?
If I told you the law of attraction was capable of doing these things, they do get more and
more incredulous, right?
I think there's a big difference between enhancing your boobs through the law of attraction, getting
a bigger dick, versus growing back a finger.
And that opens up a whole question about what the law of attraction is capable of.
If you are in prison, can you law of attraction yourself out of the prison?
The idea of the law of attraction is to see what is real in front of you and not to believe
it.
To create a mental image that is more powerful than reality.
So I think it would be hard to be in prison.
It wouldn't be impossible.
I mean, short answer to this.
You would have to believe you are out of prison so truly that you are now out of prison.
But you're having your scheduled lunch, right?
Everyone has to go into the mess hall to eat.
And then you have your work time.
Slave labor really is what it is.
But you go in there and you work for 14 cents an hour.
And then you have like checks, bed checks.
And then you have head counts.
And it's 10 p.m. and the lights are off and everyone goes to sleep and all this stuff.
And so it's so regimented that even if you were able to convince yourself you were no
longer in prison, eeeh, that alarm goes off and then everyone has to get up out of their
cots and stand up as the guards come through.
It's so heavily regulated, it would be hard.
It's almost like there was a constant reminder that you are in prison.
It's almost like you are not given enough time to truly concentrate on the idea that
you're not in prison.
Now, those things are there to keep some sense of order in these institutions.
But is it possible that these types of constant reminders that you are locked up may be a
way to defeat something like the law of attraction?
To make sure people don't just believe themselves out of prison.
You know Jason, that's ridiculous.
Obviously those things are the afternoon head counts, otherwise people are escaping.
Just a story about a guy who escaped.
So let's look at the guy who's missing two fingers.
Simple thing, right?
You're missing two fingers.
You can still game.
You're good, right?
As long as I'm only losing my pinky and my ring finger, I can hold a controller, I can
lose them on both hands.
I'm totally fine.
I can still play video games.
I'm good.
But let's say I was self-conscious about it.
Could I be able to look at my hand and believe that those two fingers are actually there?
Could I regrow those fingers?
You would have to believe more than anything that they were there.
Could you do it?
Because you're constantly seeing that they're not, and you're constantly getting the sensation
that they're not there.
Or lack of sensation, really.
At the same time, I'm a huge believer in the law of attraction when it comes to exercise
and weightlifting.
That is something that every bodybuilder will, to every bodybuilder, will tell you you have
to visualize.
You have to eat right, and you have to work out, and you have to do these other things.
But if you do the other things and you don't visualize yourself in that perfect form, it
will not work.
That's bodybuilding, where you can build up to it.
Can you regenerate body parts?
Can you make your nose smaller?
Can you make your penis bigger?
Interesting question, right?
Interesting question.
Michael, like I said, though, is really, really concerned about his height.
And he says, "Listen, I've been self-conscious about it since I was a teenager, and he was
willing to do the weirdo leg-breaking stuff."
He goes, "I was willing to pay any price to be taller."
He's reading all this stuff.
He's doing all this research.
He's collecting reports.
Because now he believes, "Wow, this is actually possible, and not only do I want to try it,
I want to help other people try it too."
In 2011, he meets a 25-year-old woman who went by the internet name Zexia.
And she said, using meditation and breathing practices, she was able to grow four inches.
That's exactly what he was looking for.
He's finally finding...
I mean, yeah, he's walking around with a bigger penis and a smaller nose, but he really wants
that height.
He finally finds someone who's talking about becoming taller.
And he continues to collect these reports.
He's really digging into the law of attraction culture.
He's a part of all of these Facebook groups that deal with the secret and the law of attraction
and all of this.
He meets another guy who got taller, four inches, four inches taller, using the law of attraction
and nofap.
He just stopped masturbating.
And he believed that he could channel his sexual energy into height.
It's a very interesting thing.
You see this a lot in the law of attraction communities.
The question...
You see this question...
So, I love the law of attraction.
Like, whether or not it's a thought experiment or it actually works, which I believe it does
work.
It's very, very interesting.
I save it so often and I really, I save it so often.
Every day, every day when I'm looking at these law of attraction communities, somebody will
ask the question, "Does masturbating affect me manifesting?
Does masturbation or any sort of sexual activity negatively affect my ability to use law of
attraction?"
And every day I see the exact same answer.
It does if you believe it will.
If you believe that masturbation and law of attraction are completely opposite things,
then they will have no effect on each other.
But if you do believe there's a connection, then they will affect each other because you're
manifesting that connection.
It's very, very interesting philosophy.
But anyways, for this guy, this guy here, his name, his internet name was Lightning Coq.
The Lightning must have been shut off for a while because he got four inches taller by
using law of attraction and nofap.
These are two of the standout people that he talked about.
He listed quite a few others and he has taken all of the reports he's assembled over the
years and he's put them in a drop box.
I'll actually put all these links in the show notes.
You can take a look at this if you're more interested in seeing on how to use the law
of attraction to reshape your body.
He's been collecting this because he's like, "If this can help me, then I want to be able
to help others as well."
And I'm looking at all these reports and these people are saying that it helped them.
So maybe there is something to this.
And Michael started to realize he's seen a very disturbing pattern.
When people go online and talk about them using the law of attraction to modify their
bodies, they disappear.
Zixia and Michael spoke for a while and then she completely cut off all communication with
him, went radio silent.
A lot of these other people, according to Michael, after they had posted their results,
disappeared from the internet.
We've been robbed of the future knowledge that Lightning Cock could have given us.
Michael begins to notice this and he can't, he doesn't really think anything.
People leave the internet all the time.
People stop going to Reddit because they've recovered from their brain injury and they
realize it's a garbage website.
People disappear from the internet all the time, whether they just stop responding to
emails.
That's the most worrisome, right, when someone stops responding to emails.
But when someone just stops updating their Facebook, I mean, then they've just stopped
updating their Facebook.
They're doing something more important.
But Michael realized this was an issue.
Again, at first couple times you go, "Oh, you know, people just leave the internet."
And he had seen this girl, this Russian girl talking about how she had used the law of
attraction to make her nose smaller.
And she posted photos of her nose.
He saved the photos because at this point he's collecting, he has this huge repository
of stuff.
He saves these photos.
And then she also disappears.
She stops posting anything online.
She's not responding to any communications.
She's gone.
Michael's like, "What could this possibly be?
Why are these people just leaving?"
Like they're in a group that's dedicated towards this practice.
And it's not a huge thing, right?
This is a pretty niche thing.
It's not like they're like, "I'm gonna go over to the other law of attraction group."
I mean, there's more than one.
But you know what I mean?
It's not a super common group.
Especially, you know, there's a lot of people who believe in it and they can't manifest
anything and they quit.
These are people who are actually having success stories and they're sharing success
stories with other people who are having success stories.
She posts the photos.
She stops popping up online.
Michael saved the photos and then a couple weeks later posted them in a Facebook group
dedicated to law of attraction.
He goes, "Hey, you know, there is this girl from Rache.
She said she used this to make her nose smaller.
Look at this."
He said two days after I posted those photos, that Russian girl popped back online specifically
to message me.
She contacted him and said, "Take the photos down.
I don't want them up and don't ever, ever share them with anyone ever again."
And then she just disappears again.
He did take the photos down.
They're not in the drop box.
That's not any of the stuff he posted online after the fact.
He told her he would take them down and he did.
So he goes, "I don't know what's happening."
He posted this online back on January 19th, 2020.
He goes, "I don't know what's happening.
This is so weird and I don't know what to make of it."
He posted this in the Neville Goddard subreddit.
Neville Goddard is a big proponent.
One of the major figures of the new law of attraction.
He was in the '40s, '50s era.
I'm more of the old school 1890s to 1920s manifestation stuff.
I'm a hipster when it comes to the law of attraction.
I'm not a huge fan of Goddard specifically, but in the Neville Goddard subreddit.
And he posted it as, "I'm sharing all my success reports about height increase and changing
physical appearance."
He posted this drop box link and he's talking about all the stuff.
And then he mentions in it, "This is a weird aside.
It wasn't his main reason for talking about it in the first place."
He goes, "But it is weird that everyone who talks about this disappears."
But here you go.
These are all the resources I found.
He does have a couple theories of what could actually be happening.
He goes, "On the one hand, you could have..."
These are both super valid theories.
I'm not saying that they're true, but they're both...
I can see either one happening.
One, reality is a collective experience.
Everyone is experiencing what we consider to be reality at the same time.
And it's very tenuous what reality actually is, but there's this what he calls the collective
unconscious.
And if you have people spark out of it, right?
The law of attraction that you use to get a better job, to find a better partner for
you, to get a newer car, to get what you need.
But most of the time, these are fairly relatively small requests in the grand scale of the universe.
So it would be growing back your fingers and having bigger boobs, but it could be such a
shock to the system because we expect people over time to get better jobs and to find people
who are suited towards them, to have loving partners.
We expect these things to happen.
We hope they happen.
And if Joey from Work Showed up one day and he has an arm, he didn't have an arm Tuesday,
that's a huge shock to the system, to the unconscious reality that we've all created.
So it was impossible that if you law of attraction in your body in an incredibly radical way,
that the collective unconscious of the universe affects you.
It makes you in a way that makes you either...
Well, so it's...
I don't even...
Because the thing is, is like we have the example with the Russian girl, she disappeared
but she came back.
So we can't necessarily say that these people blink out of existence.
And you can get bigger boobs with a boob job.
You can fix balding with implants, with toupees, or not just shaving it like Jason Statham,
right?
You can...
We can make these modifications to your body.
Other than, you know, regrowing limbs, that's like the most radical change.
But you could take the theory that if I walked into work one day and I was four inches taller
and everyone at work couldn't understand how I wasn't that height the day before.
These are generally gradual changes.
I'm...
This is kind of a strawman argument.
Zixia, she grew four inches over the course of about a year and a half, which would be
hard to see.
But let's say that you didn't notice it and then one day I walked in and you're like,
"Dude, how are you four inches taller?"
It's like, "Oh, well, over the past year and a half I stopped masturbating and here
I am."
Is it such a shock to the collective unconscious that you actually...
I don't want to say get blinked out of reality, but you're a star that's shining so bright
the universe has to dole it somehow.
Because otherwise it's just drawing too much attention to it.
But then again, we have people who do do radical body transformations.
You can modify your body and all certs away within a 24 hour period.
Walk in with a full face tattoo and you don't just disappear in front of everybody.
And then the idea with bodybuilders and stuff like that.
But again, imagine if your coworker walked in tomorrow and he was a full on 1980s oiled
up bodybuilder.
Like just raw muscle, like 2% body fat.
You're like, "Bro, what happened?
He's like a lob attraction."
It would be unreal.
You wouldn't be able to process it.
Mindfuls, he goes floating in your building.
So we have that theory.
We have that theory, but even like that theory, like how does it end?
Because these people don't disappear.
The Russian girl popped back up and she said, "Take the photos down.
Don't ever share them with anyone again."
And then disappeared again.
Which makes us say that they're not actually physically leaving.
They're not being imprisoned in some sort of way.
But maybe they're being threatened.
Maybe they're being threatened to be silent.
And that gives us the second scenario, which is what I talked about in the intro of the
show and most likely titled the episode along the same lines.
Is there a secret government group that monitors this?
And really it's for the same reason as the collective unconscious theory, right?
If you knew for a fact.
Let's say that we'll give it a year and a half.
Your coworker walks in and he is four inches taller than he was last year.
He's not in middle school, right?
You're not working out of middle school.
He's four inches taller.
Your guys are all working investment banking.
And you go, "Dude, how in the world did you grow four inches?"
And you're checking his shoes.
You're making him strip down, checking him for scars on his legs.
He goes, "I swear, please let me put my clothes back on.
I swear I used the law of attraction to do this.
I believed that I was taller and I refused all information to the contrary.
I want to hold all the carnival rides I wanted to and nobody could tell me that that seatbelt
wouldn't hold me.
I believed that I was taller and whenever I came across any sort of information, any
sort of real world scenario where I should have realized I wasn't six foot three or whatever,
I ignored it.
Totally ignored it.
I believed that I was six foot three when I was really five foot eleven and now I'm six
foot three."
You know for a fact this isn't Fruit of the Loom, Cornucopia.
You and him took photos next to all these yardsticks one day.
It's a weird place you work for, a weird investment banking firm.
You know for a fact that a year and a half ago he was four inches shorter.
You know that for a fact and now you're looking at him and he's four inches taller.
What would that do to you?
And then Betty comes in, her nose is smaller, you're like, "Did you get a nose job?"
She's like, "No, law of attraction."
You would be seeing physical proof that through thought alone, not just really thought, you're
believing what is opposite of the real that you can change everything.
It would be incredibly dangerous.
Imagine if you had a major world religion that was scientifically provable, observably
true.
Just one.
And every other religion talked about faith and talked about, well, we'll get our rewards
in the afterlife and stuff like that.
But there was one religion, worldwide religion that was absolutely identifiably true.
You could take the most ardent atheist and say, "Remember that statue?
Remember that statue?
It was only five foot nine a year ago.
We didn't modify it.
Now look how big that statue is."
And if that's what it is, and that would be what would be happening, if we have dozens
of reports of these people changing their bodies, what if there were evidence of hundreds
of people, of thousands, of millions of people using something as simple as a law of attraction
that is really not that simple?
Because again, you have to look at reality and discard it and then substitute your own
on top of it, which is really hard.
It's really hard to walk into your own dirty bathroom and go, "I live in a mansion."
And then you have to do it constantly.
But if you can achieve it, you can be taller, richer, more powerful, more good looking, whatever
you wanted.
And the governments of the world don't want you to be those things.
Now I'm not going to, so let me back up because the way I stated that was pretty, I don't know
if this conspiracy theory is true, right?
I'm just like putting ourselves in the shoes of Michael.
I could, one, I could see a government doing something like this.
Governments don't work if everyone is in the top 1%.
It's unfortunate, but governments have to have the downtrodden.
I'm not a borderline anarchist.
I'm trying not to go off on a rant.
But you know what I mean?
You do have to have, and it's a horrible part, and I wish we lived in a Star Trek utopia.
I really do.
And maybe someday we'll get there through the law of attraction.
But you can't have everyone driving the nicest cars and eating the...
Again, I'm saying this stuff.
I'm not defending it.
I wish we could, but a government wouldn't allow that.
A government needs to have the downtrodden.
A government needs to have the other, the people that you hate.
The government needs to have all these things to function.
And if you just had someone go, "Hey, did you pay your taxes this year?"
You're like, "No, I love attraction, then."
They don't even know, they don't even know that I work at this company anymore.
And you're like, "What are you talking about?"
You're like, "Love attraction, bro."
In the IRS, they're sitting at their office and they're like, "They literally don't have
the paperwork for this guy."
If the law of attraction is being used at such a level where people are just disobeying
laws and they're like, "Well, sure.
Sure, your honor.
I killed all those people.
I did kill all those people.
Or did I?"
And the judge is like, "Oh, no.
Are you one of those law of attraction guys?
They're worse than sovereign citizens."
The deeper you would get into the system, the harder it would be, obviously.
We know that we have to pay taxes.
We know that if we kill a bunch of people, we go to jail or at least go to court.
You'll get off.
But it would make sense for there to be a secret government group that was shutting
down evidence of this.
I think honestly, if a religion popped up all of a sudden and you had a Messiah who was
working miracles, and I don't think this is a stretch.
I think most people would agree with me.
But all of a sudden, in the middle of the Yucatan, you had this dude show up and he starts performing
these miracles and he's bringing people back from the dead and he's assembling this congregation
and that dude is deader than a doornail eight months after he starts doing all this stuff.
Somebody, someone high up is going to take that dude out.
If you had a miracle worker who's actually performing miracles, they are not long for
the world.
They also better be a psychic because some CIA goon is going to be dispatched to put
a bullet in his head.
So I could honestly see that the government would be trying to shut this stuff down.
I don't know, right?
We're just, we're basing this off of Michael's information and it's interesting because these
people, as far as we can tell, aren't being executed.
If anything, they're just being told, "Take the stuff down."
Or we will execute you.
There's a little laser beam on them whenever they log into a messenger.
They're like, "Huh?"
I don't know if this conspiracy theory is true.
I think it's awesome.
Not awesome if it's true, but I'm really digging this conspiracy theory.
There's a secret government group that's silencing people who have proof that the law
of attraction works.
When Katy Perry's like, "Yeah, I always knew I was going to be a big singer when I grew
up," or Eminem's like, "Yeah, I cut out all the pages of Source Magazine.
I had them up all over my room and every night before I went to bed, I knew I was going to
be a huge rapper."
And then he's a huge rapper.
That's so abstract because we also know that these guys sweated and they worked their way
up.
A lot of people think Katy Perry's the same worshiper, but you know what I mean?
They did use law of attraction.
Most of the people you see in the media, whether on purpose or on accidentally, I don't think
when Marshall Mathers was sitting down every night before he went to bed looking at all
these pages of the Source Magazine, that is the law of attraction.
The most powerful part of law of attraction is actually doing it right before you go to
sleep.
He manifested that.
I honestly believe that, but that's so abstract.
It's not like someone's going to take him out because it also included a lot of hard
work.
And again, you could go, "Well, yeah, you know, someone's got to be a rapper," right?
So it makes sense.
And it could be, again, like going to that prison example, it's so regulated to keep
knocking you back into reality.
So you don't have a chance to manifest yourself out of prison.
And I don't mean physically like you're in jail cell one day and the next day you're
standing outside.
Like you're like, "Woohoo!
You can manifest it."
So take the prison example and then we're going to wrap it up.
Let's say you're in prison for killing somebody and you don't believe you're in prison.
You 100% don't believe you're in prison.
You would manifest the reality where your lawyer found out that one of the jurors hated
you.
Like, it was your bully from elementary school.
You didn't recognize him because he beat you so badly.
And then the lawyer's like, "Oh my God, we can do a retrial on this."
And then at this point, 10 years, 15 years have passed since the crime.
The prosecutor's like, "Okay, you know, we did murder somebody, but..."
And then you're out.
There is a mechanism behind it.
It wouldn't be that you just appear outside prison because then you're just an escaped
convict.
They're just going to get you again.
But you could just believe you're not in prison and then the universe takes care of
everything else.
Law of attraction I find absolutely fascinating.
This conspiracy theory is badass.
I think this is dope.
I mean, I guess I shouldn't say that as much as I talk about law of attraction and how
much it works.
But I love this conspiracy theory.
Is the government taking out people who have physical proof that the law of attraction
works because they need to maintain the "reality" that gives them power?
That's an awesome conspiracy theory.
I've never heard of it before until Michael posted it.
I would love to see if Michael's dug up some more information on this stuff.
I'd love to talk to Michael just even through email to see what other information he's pulled
up not just from the conspiracy side, but other people who have used the law of attraction
to physically change their body.
I'd really like to read about the guy who re-grew body parts.
I'd love to find out more.
But guess what?
Michael is missing.
He's missing.
[MUSIC]