Did the red baron himself shoot down a UFO?
And then we traveled to Mexico to look at a field report prepared by the Center for the Study of Extraterrestrial Intelligence.
Dr. Stephen Greer, one of the most renowned names in UFOology,
traveled to Mexico to investigate some lights in the sky.
But instead, him and his team had a conversation with Alien Life today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
*Music*
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a lot of stuff to cover,
so we gotta start rolling into this. First off, the Minecraft server is back up. It's actually a
different IP connection address, whatever they are, but it'll be in the show notes. The number one
question people ask is, "When am I playing?" When am I playing? I do have a pretty regular schedule.
Generally, I play for about an hour or two after I upload the episode. So, generally, I'm playing the
game from like 6 p.m. to 8 p.m. Pacific Standard Time, maybe sometimes 7 p.m. to 9 p.m. Pacific Standard Time.
So that's when I'm on, but feel free to go about do your own thing, build little mansions or cities or...
I don't know, fight goblins? They're not goblins, but do whatever you want. Do whatever you want in
the game, and we're gonna keep it going for a while. I think it'll be fun for people to kind of hang
out in, so the Minecraft server is back. And as long as everything goes smoothly, we're gonna keep it
open to everyone, and so far everything's been going quite swimmingly. So join us in the Minecraft
server, even if I'm not there. There's a ton of other cool people on there. And now we also gotta
say thanks to our newest Patreon, Catherine Bellingham. Catherine Bellingham. I'm going to assume
that is a proper British name. I don't know if she's British, but that sounds like a British
name, right? Catherine of Bellingham. So, Madame, thank you for supporting the show. Really,
really appreciate it a lot. If you can't support the show, you can, even if you don't have a British
name, you can support it if your name was like Tiktok McGee. But if you can't support the show,
regardless of what your name is, you can always help out the show by getting the word out.
Getting the word out. So if you can't support the Patreon, that's fine. Just help get the word
out. That really, really helps a lot. Catherine of Bellingham. Here are your keys to the carbon
acopter. Let's fire that baby up, and not only are we taking it up into the air, we're going back
in time. We're gonna have fun. To be fair, this isn't the most fun time period of human history,
but I'm a particular fan of the subject matter of this first story. So turn that dial back to
March 13th, 1917. Go ahead, turn on that carbon acopter. Take us off. We're now back in time.
It's just before dawn, which war-torn Germany landscape. And the red Baron himself,
Baron Manfred von Richthofen, is getting ready to take flight. Now, I'm a big red Baron fan.
I actually, I'm thinking about starting writing again. I'm actually, I don't really have a lot
of time. I don't know when I'd have time for it, but I kind of miss writing. When I was in my 20s,
I wanted to write a screenplay about the life of the red Baron. He's quite an interesting figure.
And I started doing all this research, and I had an outline for it. It was just pretty historical.
But I remember I was telling my little brother about my script, and I was like, "Yeah, yeah,
I mean, I didn't really write much of it, but I think I wrote a couple pages of it. But I
had done all this research and outline and stuff like that." And we were talking about it, and I
said, "He has a really fascinating character. He was the first at this new device had been invented.
An airplane had just been invented, and he was the best at it." Like, he, he created air warfare,
and just the whole idea of air warfare. First off, you had them use the scouting missions.
Then you'd have a dude sitting in the back with a pistol, and then the other people started flying
their planes. So now they're carrying rifles, and they're shooting at each other. One guy's flying
at the other guy's trying to hit a plane with the rifle. The planes are made of paper and wood,
and then they built machine guns on the front. You had to time it so the bullets were shooting
as the propeller, like it was timed so the propeller would move and the bullets would fly
in between the blades. And you're flying like 40 miles an hour, thousands of feet in the air,
and you're shooting. The whole thing was nuts. It was that this insane escalation of technology
within a matter of like a few years. They had to do all this stuff. How much armor do you put on a
plane? And in the midst of all of this technological changes, some rich dude was like, "Oh, I can do
that." He was flying planes around because it was a toy of the rich. And he's like, "Oh, yeah, I can
total." He had like 80 kills in a, in a weapon of war that had never been used before. Fascinating
character. The problem was, was that he fought for Germany. So the only thing, the, the story
itself is super interesting. And in an isolated bubble, I think he would be considered this big
war hero. I think regardless of what side you were on, because he was a villain to the allies,
but they, there's still this grudging respect for him. And in Germany, in Austria and all that stuff,
he was the hero. But any story you tell with the red baron ends with him dying heroically in battle,
and then like a couple years later, Hitler takes power. So it would be a hard sell. It basically
like at the end, he's like, "I may die, but hopefully, hopefully Germany is eventually victorious.
Even though I have been shot down, hopefully someday the German people will rise up and take
revenge from my dad." Like it's really, it's really hard to make that movie, right? So I, and it's
also really hard for a guy in his 20s living in an apartment in North Island Sacramento,
which if you know North Islands is not a place you want to live, to write a screenplay and get a
green lip by Hollywood. But it's, there's stuff like that's happened. I think that is more likely
than me getting my, but it was dope dude. He was like fighting blimps and stuff. And I had like the
tagline, it was like before stealth he was a ghost. Like, I mean like you couldn't stop this dude.
And so I love the red baron. I absolutely love the red baron. I love that story.
There was a movie made on it, but it was kind of like a romance movie. And I'm like, "Ah man, I want to
see like planes flying and British people being like, "Oh bloody hell, where is he?" And then blowing
up and then, but again, like it's all British people blowing up. The problem is, is the side he
was on. So I love the story of the red baron. I definitely recommend looking into it, but
that long intro goes into this because I have a real passion for that story of the red baron.
It's been a good chunk of a year looking into it. And I never heard the story before.
March 13th, 1917, the red baron and his wingman, Peter Weitzrich, are getting ready to go on a
pre-dawn scouting mission around war-torn Germany-controlled areas. So now they're flying
around. I'm just going to make that sound for the rest of the episode. And they see in the horizon
a disc-shaped craft. And it's coming towards them. And they see like lights ringing the rim of the
ship. Now, obviously we're talking 1917, war of the world to come out, but they're not thinking
anything like that. Flying saucers, that terminology didn't come out until the 40s. It was just this
weird thing. The aircraft that the red baron and Peter were flying were about 50 feet wide.
This thing's 150 feet wide. And they're flying the most advanced human technology on the planet,
and you're seeing this. Now, red baron being the dope dude that he is just opens fire.
Bullets riddling the UFO ship. The aliens probably said we don't know what they said,
but the bullets just shred right through extraterrestrial technology. High-quality German-made
bullets. The ship begins varying from side to side. And then crashes, clips two trees,
cuts them right in half. It's coming down with that much force.
Crashes. Now, remember, these planes are going quite slow. These planes weren't built for speed,
or they were, but it was just the fastest they could go. They watch this UFO crash,
and they're kind of flying around the area. And Peter says, he sees out of the wreckage,
what he calls, quote, "two little ball-headed guys," unquote, crawl out of the wreckage and run away.
They go back to base, and they're like, "Sir, you literally won't believe what just happened.
We don't even know what a flying saucer is. We have no terminology for that."
But this is what happened. Red Baron here, this dope dude, shot this thing down, and it crashed,
and then two little bull dudes ran out. And the brass, the top brass. Would it be brass in Germany?
The top iron of the military said, "You can't ever tell anyone this story." And the Red Baron,
being the noble soldier that he-- I'm gonna get a bunch of people who are like, "My great-grandfather
was killed by the Red Baron. You jerk." But anyways, the Red Baron just slightly nods. He's seen a lot
of horrors of war. This was nothing to him. He's just a dope dude, so he just kind of nods, walks away.
And Peter goes, "Oh yeah, yeah, like he said, like he said, ooh, whatever the Red Baron wants,
I won't say anything either." And he also leaves. He's a big kiss-ass. So, but obviously someone
says something. We have this story. Turns out that in 1999, Peter gave an interview to a newspaper
and said, "This is what happened. Me and the Red Baron flying around and we shot down the UFO.
We actually-- the Red Baron did, but yeah, we did, we did it. I put the bullets in the gun.
That means I helped." So this story has been reported in a couple books, "Military Encounters
with Extraterrestrials, the real war of the worlds." That's a real book. I checked that out,
not from the library. I mean, it actually exists. "UFOs of the First World War." It's another book
that this was publicized in. But this story comes from one source, the Weekly World News.
Okay? So, if you don't know what the Weekly World News is, do you know what the Sun is,
or the Daily Mail, or the Daily Star? Imagine something more fake than all of those.
Imagine-- imagine if someone came to you and said, "I saw a documentary the other day.
Did you know that vampires sparkle when they walk on the Sun?" First off, did you know vampires
exist? Secondly, do you know they sparkle in the sun? Weekly World News is 100% a fictional newspaper.
Okay? And I'm reading this UFO insight. I'm-- I'm upset, dude. I'm reading-- I wake up this morning.
I'm reading this UFO insight, and I've done a lot of stories from UFO insight.
I'm reading this article, and I was like, dope! My boy! The red baron shot down a UFO. And what's
funny is the first thing that pops in your head is, but wait, how did he shoot it down? Like,
sure, bullets are bullets, but-- and the-- I'm not gonna say who wrote the article, but in the
article, it's like, yep, UFOologists do wonder how the red baron was able to shoot down a UFO,
but it kind of moves on to the next point. I'm like, fine, whatever. Then he gets down to the
point about halfway through the article where the author points out that the source for this story
is the Weekly FN World News. That's where Batboy comes from. That's where-- that's where-- you
know, like, the stories about tabloids, like, "Bigfoot is my secret lover," "The president is
really a moleman." That is from Weekly World News. Weekly World News, they don't publish it anymore,
but it's hilarious. I did an episode about a skeleton on the moon, which is also-- it's on
the conspiracy theory, Iceberg, is also from the Weekly World News. It is 100% made up and in this
article halfway through says, "Yeah, I was in the Weekly World News. Here's a quote from this
article." This really pisses me off. This is a quote from this article here. "There were several
points that would hurt Waite's ricks chances of being taken seriously." And this is talking about,
like, whether or not the bullets could go through the ship and things like that. Just little points
in the story that people go, "Oh, that doesn't make sense." So back to this. "There were several
points that would hurt Waite's ricks chances of being taken seriously. Perhaps not least, that the
account initially appeared in a tabloid that had a history of pushing, quote, unquote, "tall tales."
The Weekly World News. At this point, my blood pressure was going sky high when I read that, but
perhaps not least of the account initially appeared in a tabloid that had a history of pushing
tall tales, the Weekly World News. This was as Waite's rick would later explain,
because no other mainstream newspapers would run the account. That's a lie. That is 100% a lie,
because there's no such person as Peter Waite's rick. He doesn't exist. He never existed. We,
the German aces, very, very well documented people. They were war heroes. There's none of them. There's
not even a German pilot by the name. Well, maybe he was gone long from Hungary. He doesn't exist.
There's a photo of him, and it's really another pilot, but his face is certain. I was furious at
this point. Now, that's a lie. That's a lie. I'm not saying necessarily that the author goes, "Well,
yeah, but this poor 80-year-old man was like, "The world needs to know that my buddy shot down a UFO."
So he goes to the Tribune. He goes to New York Times. He goes to all these newspapers, and eventually
no one will publish a story, so then he goes to the Weekly World News. And when he walks in,
Bat Boy's sitting in the waiting room, and he's like, "I have a story. No one else will publish it."
That's 100% not true. Now, I don't know if the author of this article added that detail in.
I don't know if it came from one of those books, "Military Encounters with Extraterrestrials"
or "UFOs in the First World War." Those books also apparently both sourced the story,
because this article sources those books as well. One of those books may have said, "Well,
yeah, but Peter, the intrepid young, not young, he's like in his 80s, but the man who wanted to
get a story out walked into the Weekly World." It didn't happen. Whoever reported it first,
it's 100% a lie. This pisses me off. And it's not just because I have an emotional connection to the
story of the Red Baron, because I really, really think it's cool. This is the problem with this
whole industry. I'm not going to go on a big lengthy rant, but this is the whole problem.
You know what's funny? A long time... So when you quit Patreon, and let me say this to you guys,
if you guys quit Patreon, I don't care. I might have said this before, but I don't care. You donate
a couple bucks, you're doing it for a month or two, and then you have financial trouble, or...
I don't care, dude. It doesn't bug me. If I think you're gaming the system, if I think you're donating
a dollar every two months to hear your name over and over again, obviously I care about that. I
think that's rude. But one person said, "I'm too skeptical. They stopped donating." And again,
you totally have a right to stop donating and show this whole thing. But they said,
"I'm too skeptical of stuff that I don't already believe in." This is why I'm very skeptical.
This is why. The Charles Dawson story that we covered, the Civil War, the world,
I thought that was funny, that he kind of hoodwinked people. They didn't mean to do it. It was published
on April 1st 10 years ago. It was a joke. This is an article that was published a couple weeks ago,
and it's been repeated in books. This is why I'm skeptical, and this is why you should be skeptical.
So I double-checked stuff. When I did double-check this article, I found a forum about someone
mentioned it on a World War I forum, and they said that he didn't fly the airplane during that time
period, that pilot didn't exist. But it pisses me off because most people don't do it. Most people
don't have the time to double-check this stuff. Pisses me off. And you know what? That gives me
the perfect lead-in for my next story. Catherine, fire up that carbon helicopter because I'm heated.
I'm heated. Catherine's like skewn to one side of the helicopter. No, no, no. I'm not heated at you.
I'm just heated at this whole... Catherine, go ahead, take control of the carbon helicopter.
We are headed out to Mexico. We're specifically going to the Las Mitras Mountains. Las Mitras
Mountains. This is back in the year 1994. It's a period of time between December 11th and December
14th. Now, Dr. Stephen Greer, I think even if you follow UFOology, if you follow paranormal,
you know that name. You may not know the exact context, but he is pretty much the leading UFO
researcher. He's the head of the disclosure project, which is a way to get, like, civilian
specialists and members of the government, members of the military to come forward and talk about
how aliens are real. He's also the head of the Center for the Study of Extraterrestrial Intelligence.
And... oh my god. This story is this story.
We can't take this...
When the leading people of the group are nuts, allegedly nuts, you can't take anything seriously.
And I feel bad for the military officials and for the scientists that are getting wrapped up in this
stuff. And they go, "Yeah, you're right. I do think that there might be some technology that's not being
exhibited to humans, or I believe that maybe some sort of extraterrestrial..." And then C-Seti is like,
"Yes, and did you know?" And you're getting these rational people who are roped into this
utter nonsense. C-Seti are the ones who believe in this thing called coherent thought sequencing.
So you sit out in the middle of nowhere and you focus on, like, aliens, like telepathically
talking aliens, which I would be shocked if these people don't just focus on aliens all the time.
"Hey, what are you having for lunch? Aliens? What's on television? Aliens? That one's true,
because there's actually aliens on television." But you sit in the middle of... It's more detailed
than this. Let me say this. It's more detailed than what I'm about to say. It doesn't make any
more sense. It doesn't make any more sense. You sit in the middle of nowhere and you go, "Aliens,
aliens, aliens." You have a little pinnit that says "aliens" on it. And then you see lights in the sky.
And you're... Okay. Okay, here's the thing. The people who actually... Military officials aren't
going to do that. And here's the thing. If that works, if that does work, then that's not an
alien ship. That's some other phenomenon. One, because people think about aliens all the time,
right? James Cameron, for example. But UFOs aren't buzzing his house. If you can sit in the middle
of nowhere, and I'll tell you exactly what it is, actually, like, it's you... Maybe now's not a good
time to do this story because I'm fired up. If you sit in the middle of nowhere and you're thinking
about pot pie, and you're looking up or pulled pot, pulled pot's pot pie, you're looking up on
the sky and you see a light, you probably won't even register it. You're so hungry for a brutal
dictator's chicken pot pie recipe. But if you're focused on aliens and you're imagining aliens,
and you do that for, say, three hours, you're eventually going to see a light in the sky.
You know, it's... It's bias. And also, it could be your insanity creeping in because you're just
staring up in the sky going, "Aliens, aliens." But anyway, so that's coherent thought sequencing.
And so you have this weird philosophy that goes, "Aliens are like from somewhere within the psyche,
man." And then you have military officials being like on August 2nd, 1999, a UFO. So what is it?
Are they big old metallic discs that have crews in them? Or are they stuff you can summon with
your brain? But anyways, at the C-City headquarters, they have a thing called the C-City Rapid
Mobilization Investigation Team. So these guys are ready to go. I imagine like some guy sitting in
the home tick, tick, tick, tick on some alien forum, watching alien porn at the same time
in another window, gets a phone call, "Bring, bring!" picks up the phone. C-City Rapid Mobilization
Investigation Team is calling. Is Joseph there? And then, "Joseph! Your buddy's from the UFO thing,
are on the phone again! Mom!" and he runs up the stairs, picks up the phone. This is Joseph. He
changes, makes his voice super deep. Once his mom leaves the room, this is Joseph. Joseph, cancel
your plans. We have a rapid mobilization thing to do. And Joseph's like, "I'm with C-City. I have
no plans." Click. And so they all hop in the van and they drive out. This team involves the executive
director of C-City, which is named Sherry. We have Dr. Steven Greer. There's an unnamed woman from
New York. So take a pic. What are they? Like five million people there? Any one of them? A named
woman from New York, a cameraman. And then there's some people from this group called the Avni Club,
which is a Mexican UFOology group, UFO hunters. So they're going out to the Las Mitras Mountains,
December 11th to December 14th. And they go out to the Las Mitras Mountains. And for the first two
nights, they just see some lights in the sky. And Steven Greer turning around. See, I told you,
we came out here looking for lights in a sky. And guess what? There's lights in the sky. They're
called stars. But no, no, no, I'm not talking about those. I'm talking about that one that moved
in a straight angle and then disappeared. Did you stop thinking about the aliens?
That's why it disappeared. And when it's thundering, that is God-bullying. Everyone's like, oh,
Dr. Steven Greer, you totally know what you're talking about. So anyways, for the first two nights,
it's just lights in the sky, right? So then Dr. Steven Greer, Sherry, they're walking, this is
December 13th. It's 1am. They're walking down a dirt road. Remember, this guy talks to like
generals and stuff like that. Okay. This is like a high-ranking member of the UFO community.
People who actually fly fighter jets and see UFOs like 30,000 feet up talk to this dude. So Dr.
Steven Greer, I'm sure he's a nice guy. I'm sure he's a nice guy. Dr. Steven Greer, Sherry, all these
other people. The woman from New York are walking down this dirt road and Sherry starts to feel energy.
She's feeling energy. Now she begins to "perceive" small square-shouldered creatures in the bush.
She doesn't see them. She can't see them. She just perceives them. And then she gives us a full
description of them, which if you perceive something and you can't see it, but then you can
totally describe it, it's called imagination. Okay. But anyway, so these small square-shouldered
creatures, they come up to her knees. She says they have uniforms on that are either a dull orange
or a rust color. Again, she can't see them. She can't see them at all. But she knows what color
their clothes are. And she's standing there. It's 1 a.m. She's with all these people. Dr. Steven
Greer is there. And Sherry's like, no, Sherry goes, "Stop. Stop what you're doing. Stop what you're
doing." There are aliens, little aliens perfectly, aliens that can perfectly hide in this bush that
I'm standing in front of. I can perceive them. I see these aliens in my head. No, before people
run over to the bush. No, no, no, just in my head, but they're over there. And you can't videotape
them. You can't videotape them because they're scared of cameras. Now, I imagine at this point
that Sherry's like Steven, or she probably calls him Dr. Greer. Dr. Greer, I have made contact
with bush tall aliens. The talls of bush conveniently in this bush blocking their view.
And Dr. Greer goes, "Damn, I wish I would have made that up. I mean, I wish I would have discovered
that as well. I wish I would have been closer to the bush and had the power that Levar Burton
always talked about, the power of imagination. But alas, I don't. I do not have that power." So,
Sherry is talking about these guys. Now, she has this great quote. She has this great quote, "These
rich, rare exchanges with what appear to be extraterrestrial lifeforms are very delicate
scenarios. Any sudden rash or extreme emotion or movement can thwart the entire event and bring
it to a screeching halt and the extraterrestrials vanish." These guys fly UFOs through radioactive
storms. They traverse asteroid belts that go on for light years. Alien crafts have flying past
dying suns, but don't get mad at them. Don't get mad, right? That might scare them as they travel
through the interdimensional barriers between sanity and insanity. But don't frown. Don't frown.
They'll run away then. They'll get back in their ship and fly back through a black hole,
a light destroying black hole. But don't get mad. So, again, this is absolute nonsense.
Top-level groups. C-SETI is one of the most respected groups in UFOology, and I think part of it is
people don't look into the weeds. They just see this field of all of this research. But this is
the type of research that's coming out of this group. So, the aliens are telling Sherry telepathically,
"We're having a hard time adjusting our energies to you. Like, we want to have a more of a
communication with you, but there's something..." Let me read this next part to you, because I just
can't. There's no other way. I can paraphrase this. This is going to be a long episode. It's going to be a
long episode. "I can mentally hear concerned conversations going on amongst the small beings.
They eventually conveyed to me the message. Again, mentally, she's very, very clear. Now,
this stuff can be proven in any way, shame or form. They eventually conveyed to me the message,
again mentally, that they were having difficulty adjusting our energies in preparation for a
meeting, because my physical energy was concentrated on my stomach, trying to digest some food.
Just before all this began, I had eaten half of a power bar, a dense protein energy food."
So, first off, that's horrible product placement for power bars, right? Because you would think,
if you're going to be walking around an area for three days pretending there's UFOs in the sky,
you're going to want to have food that's easy to carry. But don't bring power bars, because if you
eat a power bar, aliens cannot telepathically communicate with you. That actually should be an
advertisement for, like, cliff bars. They should be, like, "Our bars are easily digestible." I'm,
like, "Power bars that make it so aliens can't convince you they're really there." So, she's
standing there, she ate half, if she had eaten a whole power bar, we could have been looking at an
intergalactic incident. They may have just opened fire on her. But she has half a power bar sitting,
and this is real, by the way. This is from a real report. It's not real in the sense, these events,
these people were standing in the mountains, okay? I know that, but I mean, this isn't something,
I didn't get this from the Weekly World News. This is something that C. Setti prepared. This is a
report they prepared. Cherry ate half a power bar. The aliens can't communicate with her. So then,
she's focusing on the, I also like how she describes it as a dense protein energy food.
First off, we know what power bars are, but if we don't, I've never, ever heard of them refer to as
a dense protein energy food. She's trying to make it sound scientific. I ate a piece of poop
that tasted like chalk. There's power bar. That's the description of a power bar for you.
Anyways, the aliens are like, "We really want to talk to you, but you have a half a power bar in
your stomach." So then, she gives them these delicate life forms that have the ability to not
only construct UFOs, but then to fly them through supernovas. They don't like power bars, though.
Too much power. She says, "She doesn't say it again. She thinks it." So there's really no proof of this.
Quote, "I give you permission to take it out of my body." And then this is the rest of this passage.
Suddenly, I felt as if someone was standing some distance away with a fishing line whose hook
was inside my stomach. It felt as if someone was slowly reeling in the line as the food came back
out the way it went in. She just threw up. But now she says, she let's us know, she normally hates
throwing up. As opposed to those people who love it, right? Everyone hates throwing up, unless
you're at like 0.001%. Everyone. You don't have to. You don't. I didn't. When I was reading the story,
I wasn't thinking, "Bup, she's probably one of those people who loves throwing up." I'm a skeptic.
Nobody wants to throw up, especially in front of their buddies, especially not half of a power bar,
because I think those things are just, they reform, like the T-1000 in your stomach. You take bites
out of it, but in your stomach, it just becomes that black brick again. Anyways, this invisible
fishing line pulls it out and she goes, "Bruh!" Throws up the power bar. Now, Dr. Steven Greer,
he watches his executive director, who's currently believing that she sees, quote unquote, "sees"
bush high creatures conveniently hidden in a bush. She throws up. And then she feels better,
right? Now, it could have just been that she ate a power bar, which is what made her throw up. But
no, no, no, no, it's the aliens. And then, again, another very convenient thing that's going to
happen is that the aliens instruct Sherry and tell me, oh, tell me, this is 100% a little red writing
tactic. Let me read you this thing, quote, "Soon the little beans sent," not beans, like little
kidney beans, but like human beans or in this term, alien beans, "soon the little beans sent both Dr.
Greer and I." So now they're contacting Dr. Greer. Now he noticed she kept winking at him.
She's like, "There's aliens in the bush, wink, wink." And they're communicating telepathically,
wink, wink, Dr. Steven Greer is like, "What are you talking about, you insane?" Oh, I can pretend to.
The woman from New York's like, "Oh, he's so cool." Anyways, now Dr. Steven Greer is also getting
messages from these made-up creatures. And the made-up creatures, let me go back to this,
"Soon the little beans sent both Dr. Greer and I the message that if we removed our glasses,
we would be able to see them better." What? That is something like that's not, you know,
the demons in your corner and be like, "If you really want to talk to me, you have to use the
wigs you bought at 3 a.m." Oh, okay, thanks. If I'm in the middle of nowhere and I hear a voice
in my head saying, "Take your glasses off and you can see me better," I'm not, I'm putting on another
pair of glasses, right? Because now I'm getting rushed from the woods. But these guys are like,
"Yes, alien overlords, we will defeat humanity for you and bow at your feet." What else do you
request? The aliens also asked them to take their hats off. So I'm starting to, I'm not making that
up. I'm not making that up. The aliens go, "Mmm, yes, your glasses are up. Now how about take your
hats off?" Now at this point, like some blue mist shows up and Dr. Steven Greer and Sherry
perceive, they become aware of something in it. And she goes, "Although again we could only see
him dimly, he appeared to be very humanoid." They're not wearing glasses, by the way. It's 1 a.m.
They don't have their hats on. I'm sure Dust is getting in their eyes. They see a mist and they go,
"Yeah, he's a tall humanoid with long, straight and silverish hair. He seemed to be wearing a light
blue and silver uniform." But so this, now this blurry image, this blurry image in front of two
people who don't have their glasses on, is floating there. Now he goes, the alien goes, or their
imagination goes, "I would love to fully physically form in front of you. I would love to be caporial."
We could have a discussion. But somebody in your group, I can sense somebody in you. That's
almost inception. Your imagination has an imagination. But anyways, I can sense someone in your group
would be dangerously frightened if I just appeared. Not frightened that they're stuck with two lunatics
in the middle of the Mexican desert who say that there's tiny creatures telling them to take off
their glasses in their hat. That doesn't scare them. Or that the blue, and that they do it,
that they totally do what these things in the bushes are doing. Not that blue mist is showing
them, but if he pops out of the mist and goes, "Tada!" Someone's going to have a heart attack. So the
alien's like, "I'm not going to do that." And then Stephen Greer and Sherry, "Urrrgh!" They think about
it. They think about it. I almost imagine it's like, you know, when two people are trying to
remember the lyrics of a song, but neither of them know anything about the chorus. And they're like,
trying to--these two people, they're putting on a show, right? You got the Avni, you got the UFO
club there, you got a woman from New York, you got a cameraman, too. Remember, there's a cameraman
here. The footage is just of a bush and maybe a cloud in the mountains. But anyways, there was no
footage. There was no link for the footage, which shows how useless it is. But you know how like
two people are trying to remember the lyrics of a song, but they are just waiting for the chorus,
"Hold Me Close Your Tiny Dancer." And they're like, "I imagine them going like--" And then the alien goes--
Yeah, yeah. And the alien's like tall and tall. Yeah, yeah, yeah. And it's like silv--
Blue, blue. No, yeah, yeah. Silver hair. You're right. Silver hair. And he's saying that we should
go shopping. No, no, no, no, no. Not shopping. We should not be scared. Yeah, yeah, yeah. And the
people in the background are like, "This is amazing. Hold Me Close Your Tiny Dancer." This goes on for a
bit. They eventually go, "Well, if you won't come to us, can you take us somewhere?" And the alien
goes, "That would also-- That would also-- That would also equally terrify this person."
This would also equally terrify this person if you guys magically disappeared. Now again, Dr.
Stephen Greer has met with members of Congress. He's met with military officials. He's met with
high-ranking people. And the end of the story is them going like, "Ah, shucks. Like, I almost had the
chance to talk to an alien, but someone was too scared. It was the New Yorker. It was the New
Yorker girl." So because what happened was the New Yorker girl was totally freaked out by this
whole thing. And she said, "If I saw an alien, I was just going to take off running through the
mountains." And so they're like, "There you go. Now you military official who has to risk your
entire career to come forward and say that you saw this thing, you should do that on camera. But me
and my group, yeah, we just took a couple pictures of a bush and then we did a game of yes and for
probably about 20, 30 minutes and then we just quit. But you, sir, go on the record. You risk
your entire career and national ridicule. I'm just going to hang out. I'm just going to do this,
right? And tell this story." The next day-- They do a television show the next day. I don't know if
they bring this up because the audience would be like, "What? Intarnation? It's all sponsored by
Powerbar." They're like, "Uh-oh." But obviously the story is ridiculous, but he's a super famous dude.
And again, I'm sure he's a nice guy, right? He's definitely put in the work to build up his following,
but this is the reason why people are skeptical, okay? I know that you can watch the disclosure
documentary or the serious documentary. He has a new documentary on like Amazon, Netflix called
"Close Encounters of the Fifth Kind." So he-- I mean, I'll give him respect. He's built a name.
He's built a brand. And I'm sure he's a nice guy. I'm sure he's a smart guy. But come on. This is--
This is obviously-- There's not a documentary about this, right? Because anyone in their right
mind would go, "That's super convenient that everything-- You took your glasses off before
you saw an alien or they were conveniently sized. They're bush-sized, we had a bush." Well, anyways,
the next day they're doing all of these television interviews and things like that.
Now it's 11.30 p.m. They're driving back to their home. Now, their videographer, their cameraman,
was not here. What? He wasn't here for this part. What? Whoa, no. What could possibly happen now?
The guy with the ability to record things isn't here. That's wacky. So what happens is, while
there's no proof, Dr. Stephen Greer and Sherry and all that stuff, they see like a bright lights in
the sky and Dr. Greer jumped from the suburban while it was still rolling, like an action hero.
And then he like did a barrel roll and he-- his hat. He picked his hat up off the ground and put
it on and then two screaming eagles flew overhead. At the exact same time. He had a 500,000 candle
power portable halogen light. He's lighting this stuff up and then the light is lighting up and then
they're like talking. Like he'll shine the light and then the light shines up and he shines the light
and the light shites up and he goes at a certain point. There's like-- we see like this beam come
out of the sky and we see shadows walking in front of the beam and-- but no cameraman! What? Oh no!
Oh shucks! You guys want evidence? What? No, just ruin your military career. But I don't have a
cameraman! I don't have a cameraman when I'm in Mexico to do an investigation! But no! And then
they travel back to where they're staying and they get up on the roof and they watch lights and this
kind of stuff. I'm not doubting that it was probably fun. I'm sure it was beautiful out there.
You're out in the middle of nowhere. You get to see the Milky Way and all of its splendor and all
that stuff and you-- listen, I believe in UFOs. That's one of the things that I don't deny. I don't
know if they come from other planets and I think a lot of those big UFO stories have a lot of holes
on them like raw stuff like Roswell or Rendlesham have some definitely big iffy things. But I don't
use those to discount UFOs across the board. Like I do believe that-- first off, I do believe there's
unidentified fine objects and I do believe that there is life outside of Earth. I don't know if
alien-- what we perceive as aliens are actually from other planets if they're from other dimensions.
If they came here millions of years ago and they're in some sort of cave system. I don't know. I am
ghosts and demons and stuff like that. I believe this conversation could be the same thing. You're
up in an area that it's haunted and there's a ghost. But see, it's funny because there's a--
people who believe in UFOs believe for the most part of it. See, C. C. Setti's kind of pushing the
goalposts. Pushing the goalposts. There are people who hunt Squatch. They're Sasquatch hunters and
they look at them as a biological creature that has a tribe and mating habits and a diet. Then
there are other people who believe it's some sort of spirit. Some sort of nature thing. That would
be more where I'm going. I don't buy the biological Bigfoot thing. If Bigfoot sightings are real,
it's some sort of paranormal activity as far as like ghost goes or related to alien activity.
High strangeness. Ghosts though have the ability that you don't see them. People can go their entire
life without quote unquote "seeing a ghost" but still go "I live in haunted house. I hear stuff
late at night. I've never seen anything fly around. I've never seen anything super dramatic."
Aliens fall more into the biological category. They have races and fleets of ships and they have
command structures and the uniforms and things like that. But groups like C. Setti
realize that that bar is incredibly high to prove. Bigfoot, the thing with the biological
Bigfoot thing, you find footprints and you go "Well, that's what-- you deer leave footprints,
people leave footprints, found a footprint." That's evidence enough. That's evidence enough for a lot
of people who are squash hunters or hare because sometimes you'll just find trappings of animals
in areas. You may not see an elk in your area but you'll see elk footprints. Ghosts can just be like
"I bought a teacup and ever since then I've had a runny nose. Yes, it is May and I do live in a
high allergy area but I bought the teacup the end of April." So aliens demand biological proof.
Wreckage of ships, alien bodies or their aftermath, crop circles, catamolations,
stuff like that. C. Setti is trying to push the goalposts, being like "No, no, no, no, no, no.
Aliens can also be in your imagination. Aliens can also be this thing you sense more than you see."
And they've built their whole group around this and it's interesting because C. Setti seems to be
different than the disclosure project even though they're both spearheaded by the same guy. C. Setti
has that "We can sit and we can imagine the UFOs, man." And again, a four star general is going to
be like "What are you talking about?" Like I just had an F-18, do they still even make those?
I just had an F-22 get outrun by something and I don't know what it is. I don't know if it's for
my RAN, Russia, but I need to know. I don't think the pilot was up there being like "Dude, I can sense
an unidentified area vehicle in front of me." And then one just appeared. That's not what they want.
So C. Setti's moving the goalposts. The disclosure project is getting people in the military,
getting congressional members to push for alien disclosure. But one group is fanciful. And the
other group is what people normally think of as aliens. It's a biological entity that has a fleet
of ships that comes from a location. Whether or not they're from another dimension or they're from
another planet, they have a location, they have a society, they have a culture, they have mechanics,
they have doctors, they have soldiers, they have leaders. This imagining people in the
bushest thing is not that. And you... So to really wrap this incredibly long episode up,
you have to be skeptical about this stuff. You have to be skeptical about this stuff. Because
this is the type of stuff you're getting, right? You may get someone who is releasing the TicTac
video because disclosure project has been all over that and so has to the stars. And that's the
thing. I get a lot of requests from people going "Why don't you cover to the stars?" That's Tom DeLonge's
UFO group that wants to push for disclosure. The reason why I haven't covered it is because a
nonsense like this. That I just really need to look into why the group is... I know a lot of people
think it's a soft disclosure CIA group, but people were saying that about the disclosure project.
And disclosure project is run by people who believe that bush-sized aliens hide in bushes and can't
talk to you because you eat power bars. So you've got to be skeptical. I know it can take the fun
out of it sometimes, but if you're not skeptical, you go "You'll be... aw, shucks! Did you hear the
red baron shot down a UFO?" Because that's been repeated a couple of times. It's in two books!
It's in two books that have been published and are out there and people are reading them.
Now, I've made mistakes on this show before as well, the Lone Pine Devils and the Civil War
Aliens. And both of those mistakes, I was like, "Oh, I made a mistake. I got other information.
I was wrong." Now, I can get it if someone... I'm back to that stupid red baron star and I can get it
if someone came across a red baron story, but they referenced the weekly world news!
You can't excuse it saying this old... Okay, I can't talk about the stupid red baron story anymore,
because I'm just kidding Madigan. The point is, is that you have to pay attention to this stuff.
Now, I'm going to end it on a good note. I absolutely loved reading this Mexican mountain
article because it really, one, thought it was absolutely hilarious. And two, it confirmed my
bias that a lot of the people who are into this stuff just use their imagination. And like LeVar
Burton said, imagination is a powerful tool. It definitely kept me entertained. I was laughing
out loud as I was reading this article and I hope you had an equally fun time with me talking to
you about it, because I think it's absolutely ludicrous. But the next time you hear about the
disclosure project or C-SETI or any of this stuff, and they're trying to get these high-level
government officials to come forward and to risk their career to talk about secret documents and
stuff that they saw, just remember, just remember, that cold night in those mountains in Mexico
when a C-SETI member threw up a power bar so she could talk to an alien.
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
Bye.