Does an old French ghost story actually have terrifying implications for everyday life?
And then we travel to the Soviet Union to follow a group of KGB Special Forces out on
a mission.
When an island is mysteriously shrouded in fog and people go missing from time to time,
the government wants to know why.
Little did they know that this investigation would turn into a bloodbath today on Dead
Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a ton of stuff to cover so we're going to get started right away.
First off let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, Joseph Zuts.
Joseph Zuts thank you for supporting the show.
He's actually just started listening to the show and he's a new Patreon that's very very
exciting.
You're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
You can't decoy the Patreon that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show that really really helps out a lot.
Now Joseph I'm going to toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Robot or an ore.
Catch!
It's a huge ore but he's a strong guy.
Toss you an ore.
We're going to take the Dead Rabbit Robot but first off I want to give you an update to
yesterday's episode Samson Forever.
So yesterday we talked about Samson the dog.
Samson is a long time listener of the show along with his best friend Sean.
We actually used one of his websites as a source a long time ago on the Gattington Canyon
story.
So he told me that his dog Samson had come down with something called leptocereiosis.
It's not it.
Leptoprosis and it's very common.
It's super common.
You usually get it by being a dog.
Just like your dog you're like swimming and you're chasing animals and stuff like that
biting squirrels.
You can get this disease.
It's so common among dogs that the vets say you should get them vaccinated once a year.
So if you have a dog talk to your vet about that because it can kill your dog it would
ended up causing internal organ failure in Samson and they were going to put him to sleep
on Wednesday.
So we rushed the episode out.
We put Samson in the cockpit of all of our vehicles and I wanted to let you guys know
that although Samson is no longer with us Sean was a I thought this was pretty cool.
Sean I sent Sean the email and he woke up the next day and he was going to take Samson
out to the yard one last time to play catch and he thought he had something in his head
going I should check my email and he saw the episode and so Samson got to hear that episode
with all of us this show isn't just me it's all of us so we all got to go on this giant
adventure with Samson and he got to hear it and he had a great time.
Sean said he just seemed so alive running around in the backyard.
So we're sorry to see Samson go but he may make returns in future episodes.
He may be a dog that pops up helps us fight aliens chase Bigfoot all sorts of stuff.
We're going to miss you Samson but you'll always have a place in the heart of the dead
rabbit radio family.
So Joseph I'm going to nod to you you nod to me you try to salute with the ore you bump
your head it's very comical to us not to you.
Let's go ahead and hop in that dead rabbit row boat we are going to row all the way from
America to France.
Joseph gets to stand on the bow of the dead rabbit row boat he's technically the captain
where we all have to row we're rowing with one hand drinking our beverage of choice in
the other.
And Joseph's like a man I'm going to have a drink we're like yeah sure but you got to
help row and he's like no I'm fine.
I brought my own water so we finally are making our way all the way out to France.
We're going back to the year 1710 and I want to give a shout out to two Twitter followers
burnt toast ghost and Lusurter Chuckle F word I can't they actually say the word but
try to keep the show not super explicit although I'll talk about horrible horrible disgusting
diseases that meth users have those episodes aside thank you so much Lusurda thank you
so much burnt toast ghost they helped do some translation for this episode.
So we're going back to the year 1710 we're in Brittany France we're going to get out
of the dead rabbit row boat we're walking through the forest we're specifically in the
forest of Ludock and we're walking through the forest and shh be quiet be quiet we hear
two people arguing in the distance we see two men poking each other's chest with their
fingers I love her and then the other guy goes no I love her and they keep poking each other's
chest we're seeing a fight this is how all the time people fought we're seeing a fight
between Pierre LaRoy and Jan Jan so they're like poking each other's chest I love her
no no no I love her more and we're like oh this is kind of like a lovers quarrel except
except the lover isn't there it's two dudes fine over one they're just poking each other's
chest and then we see a startling movement but we can't do anything because otherwise
I don't have a story we have to let this happen Jan Jan stops poking Pierre in the chest with
his finger and he reaches down he pulls out a dagger and goes this will be more effective
than my finger and he stabs Pierre LaRoy oh no my blood I need that to live Pierre exclaims
as he falls to the ground and uh p- Jan Jan goes I guess I win I guess I now have the
love of my life and he walks away so Pierre is laying there out in the forest and he's
bleeding and he dies oh wait no I looked at my notes that's not what happens we kind of
I skipped a step so Jan Jan comes back he's like oh I forgot this part of the story he
comes back and Pierre is dead he just kind of walked around the tree until he died and
then he goes okay I committed the perfect crime I murdered someone that's step one of
the perfect crime now I have to dispose of the evidence so he digs a grave right by an
oak tree deep in the forest and he buries it he's like ah ha ha now the perfect crime
has been committed step two hiding the evidence now step three to leave the scene but the
perfect crime is not what he committed because he's very shortly found out to have murdered
this guy I don't know why those details have kind of been lost to history or I didn't research
that part but the point of the story is he was found out and poor Jan Jan is executed
on December 11th 1710 now there's actually a record of his execution so we know this
part of the story is true and that's not in the realm of impossibility right so we know
that part of the story is true where we get into the legend is this at that oak tree in
the middle of the forest five holes appear in the ground that's the sound of a hole
appearing you know if you're not a geologist five holes appear in the ground right where
his body was buried I'm a suit actually now that I'm saying this out loud I'm assuming
they dug them up I'm assuming they didn't leave them buried there but for whatever reason
it was ghost ground five holes appear right by this oak tree now a legend started this
where the ghost story starts that if you cover the holes up you die within a year it's interesting
because we don't know how the legend started or even when it started we just have anecdotes
later on supposedly at some point like the first story we have about this is two drunk
dudes show up at the crime scene and they're like I'm more drunk no no no I'm more drunk
they're poking each other in the chest and then one guy starts reaching for a knife and
they're like whoa whoa whoa hey I don't know I don't know what you're trying to do but
first let's tempt this ghost story I heard that if you cover up one of these holes you'll
die within a year and the guy the guy's still reaching for the knife he's like you might
die right now and he's like yeah yeah don't don't do that let's let's continue the story
if we cover up these holes will die within a year apparently one of them did one of the
drunk guys decided to cover up the holes I don't know if he covered up all of them or
one of them or what but he died within a year now there's no names associated with the story
there's no dates associated with that story and that's really when you read about this
online they tell it's pretty much the story I told you dude gets murdered body gets dumped
holes appear legend starts and then they'll go for example two drunk guys once da da da
da da you're like okay just a simple local ghost story it's a legend if you go out there
you walk around a tree three times say boogity boogity ghost pops up the national forestry
office of France has the area roped off you can see photos of this there's four posts
put up there's a rope covering the areas and there's a sign there that warns people to stay
out of the area and that's what I was getting help from Lasserta and burnt toast ghost because
I was like I don't know French right that's actually a long story I might I might have
told that story before but I might know French but I definitely can't read it I asked for
a translation and people are like oh you know that's actually what it says it says beware
that some dude died here don't cover up the holes you'll die within a year so stay out
so the national forestry office put this up now obviously it could just be a tourist trap
but where are you spending your money at there's not like a person selling whole trinket around
the corner selling donut holes test your luck try to throw these into the rope dairy and
see if you can plug a hole up could be a tourist trap but it's unlikely it could be a legend
that nobody really wants to test it's interesting on two levels one it's a very very hard myth
to disprove because a lot of people die within a year your chances of dying in the next year
are actually quite slim if you're generally healthy and you don't do any sort of like
crazy things like drinking and driving and stuff like that but everyone has a chance
of dying within a year you can increase those chances plugging holes isn't one of them unless
you're plugging in like you know Godzilla's butthole then you might be in trouble but
for the most part plugging holes isn't a high risk factor you could have a hundred people
plug these holes a hundred people do this and then within a year one of them dies and
that was the 65 year old man who was drunk driving and trying to drive his car and Godzilla's
butthole so he was going to die anyways the other people who do it who keep on living
aren't part of the legend so it's like confirmation bias you're looking for the stories that back
up what you're looking for you could even say my uncle died and a year before he went
to the forest maybe he plugged one of the holes I think there's actually a scarier implication
to this story what we know is that there is a record of this crime taking place at this
area we have these five holes in the ground we have this legend around them how many of
these locations are out there that we don't know about the world could be littered with
paranormal landmines like this I'm not even talking about like haunted houses or sacred
ground I'm talking about places where someone was brutally murdered the crime was never
discovered it was the perfect crime bodies buried just feet under the ground and while
it's decaying into the earth it's releasing all of this vengeance energy because it was
killed because of a lover's quarrel basically fosters and grows so the chance of you stepping
on one of these or you're like spitting sunflower seeds and there's tiny little hole tiny little
bird got stabbed are quite high so I'm not asking you guys to be a gorophobic or anything
I'm just asking you to be a little careful around all those holes you see in your daily
life if you happen to see one just step aside because although you might think oh that's
just a hole there's no big deal it can't hurt me within a year you may find out how much
damage a hole can actually do I guess I said that statement out loud and yes I'm saluting
to Joseph Zatz he's saluting back we are going to give him the keys to the carboner copter
we are taking off and we are headed out to the Soviet Union to helicopter is flying out
Joseph take us high in the air as I do this introduction a while back I a long time ago
did an episode about the KGB fighting aliens in Antarctica I actually might do that episode
as a rerun because it's one of my favorite episodes and spoiler alert the KGB got slaughtered
they got turned into concrete pillars you know those things you see outside of like a Walmart
so people don't crash their car into the store that's what happened to the KGB they all work
a Walmart now these KGB soldiers try to shoot down a UFO with a rocket launcher and they
all got turned to giant concrete poles but see that can't be the end right that can't
be the end of that so also that story was fake that story was provably fake but this
story this story from a r u dot UFO for not r u a UFO is from a Russian UFO forum by Alexander
Glasunov now this story might be this story might be real doesn't end with anyone turning
into pillars of concrete this story actually is more in line with how the KGB would actually
interact with alien life because this is how they interacted with humans as well Joseph
bring us down low put on that stealth mode we're landing at Barsek Lemme's Island we're
in the Aral Sea of Kazakhstan and I know I added letters and mispronounced each of those
but it doesn't matter Joseph is our weapons master he's each given us the weapon that
we deserve most based on our skill set he gives me this cool cool looking rifle with like
all these laser pointers and there's just laser pointers taped onto the end of it and then
he's like giving you I don't know like shotgun you like shotguns he's asking he doesn't know
anything about weapons he's just handing out random weapons to people hey you look like
you could use a grenade launcher gives it to like a 10 year old kid Joseph is now handing
us all weapons we gotta check them because this is gonna be a dangerous mission guy we're
putting on our ghillie suits we're going off the year is 1976 and it's dark it's night
time and as we're sitting there in darkness we all got night vision on we see a boat come
up to Barsek Lemme's Island there's been a lot of this island is uninhabited but there's
been a lot of reports of people in the area I know that doesn't make sense but but I'm
assuming that it means other fishermen I'm assuming fishermen had reported other fishermen
going missing around this island the island itself was uninhabited but there were reports
from locals that people had gone missing in the area so the Soviet Union wants to know
what's going on here is it US secret spies here or US not secret spies you just walk
around with big shirts and say I'm a spy on it in this landing craft is about a dozen
KGB special forces troops these are the best of the best of the best they're being led
by a major we'll call him major Jones major Jones hot everyone's like dude that's an
American name I think he's the spy he's like what no I'm not I shift inside of side they
jump all out of the boat now major Jones is leading these 12 special forces KGB guys so
they're walking up this dark beach and now they're exploring the inner part of the island
and even though it's so dark out they can start to see fog begin to roll through the
area and the major describes a sensation of fear
he had never known before he's been in a lot of dicey situations breaking into people's
houses beating up peasants but he's never experienced fear like this so he holds his
hand up to halt his men the fog just rolls over him now they had an aerial footage of
this island they knew it was uninhabited that's why when the fog clears and they see a giant
fence in the distance the major knows something's up so they begin to make their way towards
the fence when they get to it's quite high the Russians actually have to climb over
it they all scramble over it and now they're on the other side of this fence there's a
rocky hill now going up and on top of it they can see in the darkness a 16 foot wide silver
sphere just sitting on the ground soldiers all look at each other the major just stare
straight ahead so major Jones commands his troops to get down get down get down and they
begin moving through the darkness weapons ready this wasn't supposed to be here the
fence was weird enough but now there's an alien craft they're walking up this hill very quietly
and when they get to the top of it they see what's described as strangely dressed people
there's three of them they're standing around this sphere the major sees these these strangely
dressed people standing around and they're wearing holsters and in those holsters is
what is described as a laser gun major Jones gives the command he goes listen what we're
going to do is we're going to walk up to them really really quietly and then we're going
to jump out we're going to point our guns at them we're going to take them prisoner
because I really want to know who built that fence it's a really nice fence we're going
to take a prisoner however men if they even think about reaching for one of those things
in their holsters you know what the KGB does best and everyone knows everyone nods in agreement
yeah they just shoot people so major Jones and his men start getting closer and closer
to these aliens it doesn't describe them as actually being aliens they're just strangely
dressed people could have been Amish for all we know but they generally don't have laser
guns eventually the soldiers pop out and they're holding their guns aimed at the ready at these
three strangers and major Jones has his weapon aimed at them as well one of the little alien
dudes starts reaching it's just a minute touch but his hand goes to that weapon in his holster
major Jones and his men know what they have to do they immediately open fire the aliens
are all screaming and stuff they slaughtered these three dudes now that is pretty typical
for the KGB right you can't knock them it gets results done they've been doing this
for years generally you kind of want to keep one of them alive maybe to like you know find
out secrets of the universe how to build spaceships things like that or you could just shoot three
dudes just because they're strangely dressed and might have a weapon on them just massacre
them major Jones really isn't worried about this at this point they have at least as giant
silver orb they can like hang out take pictures and and reverse engineer that's something
for the eggheads in Moscow to figure out what he's more interested in is that laser gun
so major Jones walks up to one of these previously alive aliens and he pulls it out and it's
actually like a wand he figures just by looking at it which direction whatever's gonna come
out of it will come out of it I mean he has a 50/50 chance right he's either gonna destroy
his arm or do something cool so he takes this wand type device out and he points it at the
ground and he presses a button and it goes and everyone at first is very very afraid
they don't know if he made the right choice it's 50/50 they don't know if this dude's
about to get disappeared but nothing happens they hear that whistle noise and everyone
is on edge even major Jones isn't exactly for sure what that whistle noise signifies
but there's no light there's no flash it's just the noise and then nothing and then major
Jones looks down and sees that the dirt where he had been pointing the rod at was beginning
to turn into glass so this wasn't in fact some sort of laser weapon major Jones puts it in
his belt I'm assuming it doesn't actually say that in the story but you're not gonna leave
that behind at this point he is stationed at this silver sphere and there are scouts
kind of surveying the area there are more of these things out there are there more of
these really cool guns are gonna be able to have a laser tag battle to the death eventually
one of the scouts comes running back and says major Jones major Jones found a cave I think
there might be more of them in there suit up boys get all their weapons ready they're
ready to go they begin making their way to this cave major Jones is leading his men through
and it's just a normal cave but then he notices that the cave stops being a cave the walls
stop being jagged and all rocking stuff they start to become smooth like walls as they're
walking through this tunnel they begin to see tables which while those aren't very sci-fi
everyone has one there's probably one in front of you right now you don't expect them in
caves especially caves with smooth walls if you see a table in a cave don't call a national
inquire that's kind of weird it's not super weird but they also saw a bunch of like weirds
alien equipment is how it's described they're walking through this tunnel they're starting
to see these tables and it looks like alien equipment is just being stored here it's not in use
but as they continue to walk through the tunnel they see it starts to open up and in this massive
open chamber it's full of alien technology view screens and control panels and all sorts of stuff
and this is being used it's lit up little lights flashing and in this
room they see a ton of these tiny little alien guys these guys are actually described as being
dwarf size these may actually be gray aliens the people in the first part of the story they
weren't described in any sort of alien fashion other than they were wearing weird clothing
they could have just been vacationers honestly and they were just flying around in a silver-shaped
balloon and i guess they also invented laser guns they were probably aliens but this part of the
story actually seeing what's described as several dwarf sized aliens so most likely a room full of
grays but it wasn't just a room full of gray aliens going about their business there was also two
giant aliens sitting at different control panels now both of these guys are six foot five so not
giant in the nephaleme sense like 13 foot tall but still six foot five is not something you want to
go in combat against sure you're the kgb you got all these weapons but still these guys are pretty
huge they're definitely familiar with alien tech they most likely have laser guns as well so major
jones is kind of running this game through his head he goes okay here's the thing we can retreat
because there's only 12 of us there's a bunch of these dwarf little alien dudes in here and these
two giant guys so we can retreat come back with better forces we could bomb it we could gas it we
could be like throwing gas grenades should have brought some of those but i didn't gas them out
take them back dissect them all that stuff or we could keep them alive we could go in kind of hold
them hostage that didn't work so well the first time just about 30 minutes ago but we can hold
them hostage we can actually learn from them maybe we can actually apologize for what we had done
before because we thought we were under attack maybe we can make first contact in 1976 we're at
the height of the cold war we could use all this stuff but this technology is so much more useful
if you can talk to the people who know how to work it out so he's running these games through
his head he's trying to think what's the best move what would vladimir linand do then he then he
goes what would stall and do his men pour into the room and begin to massacre everyone in it
these kgb soldiers come in with guns blazing not a single word said they direct all their fire to
mowing down all the tiny people the two chinese are still just sitting there they're not even
aware what's going on until half the grays are split in half by russian gunfire goes on and on
and on longer than i have breath for just play that segment over and over again put it in a loop
they slaughter these guys they blow them up it would have been an absolute massacre and after
they're done shooting everything smaller than four feet in that room the major then directs all of
his fire towards the giants this is happening so fast the giants are still at their control panels
when the first bullets come flying towards them it's in slow motion now these bullets
flying towards the giants the giants begin to turn and the bullets begin to hit them
automatic gunfire just hitting these aliens the aliens just start to stand up they start to stand up
concentrated fire from automatic weapons 12 kgb special forces aiming at two targets and these
giants are just getting up out of their chair cracking their back a bit oh yeah oh sit on the
computer too long and then they just begin walking towards russians the bullets have no effect on
these guys doesn't say that they're bouncing off of them doesn't say they're going through it's kind
of a moot point because basically from the point of view of the kgb soldiers who are telling this
story their bullets weren't working you weren't you weren't concerned about the physics of it
you just massacred a ton of aliens and now the two threats left are just walking towards you
like it's a bright sunny day so the kgb does something that's quite uncharacteristic they run away
they've been running through this tunnel they stop being kgb agents they become scared humans
they're running through this tunnel and these big giant aliens are chasing them
when they finally get out of the tunnel all of a sudden a white beam shoots from the sky
into the hill that the cave was burrowed into and then it turns red
and then it turns blue well usa action if i don't say so myself but then it turns multicolored so
then the patriotism leaves plus i'm pretty sure russia's flag is red white and blue doesn't matter
you're seeing this multicolored beam shoot out of the sky into the top of this hill that
hid this cave and they said they could actually it was this giant cylinder and it got smaller and
smaller and thinner and thinner until eventually it was like a just the size of a pencil coming out
of the night sky into this hill and then the beam disappears and the sky catches on fire
and major jones and his men just stood there watching this
completely bizarre phenomenon there would be really other than a nuclear blast there would be no other
way you would see the sky on fire primordial earth the sky was on fire and now this
they stood there for 20 minutes as this event continued just watching these flames
above this hill and then finally it is a clear night they get back to their landing craft they
do they don't go back in the cave because they're thinking oh maybe the aliens want to wait or
maybe there's reinforcements we don't know it's 50 50 i already tried my luck with that once they
go back to their landing craft go back tell their supervisors hey you won't believe what happened
to us over there there's a fence so we're like what okay that's fine no no you don't let me finish
there's something over the fence they're like oh i'm listening so the soviet union sends back more
troops they scour every part of that island it's empty nothing but an island sitting in the middle
of the soviet union stories like that i think are fun because they have a combination of stuff
that we enjoy to hear about aliens and then you got the combat attack attack attack attack
people shooting stuff your mileage may vary on that i do love combat alien stories but it's combined
with that these things are everywhere everyone's always looking at the sky for a UFO all these
UFO reports i mean that's why they're called UFOs but if you were planning any sort of long-term
operation you have to have boots on the ground for example this the cold war the united states and
the soviet union had sleeper agents in each other's countries in each other's allied countries they
had little safe houses the aliens are here for scientific purposes we go out to the jungles
and hang out with apes to observe them if they're here for military purposes we have bases as close
as we can as close as we can get undiscovered to enemy territory they're here for some like
subversive world conquering a long-term conspiracy reason then you would definitely need to have
boots on the ground so i think stories like this are a very cool part of alien lord it also has
the creepy factor so we have this story and it's action packed and not so much for the aliens they
all got massacred but you have humans gunning down aliens it's always great because you know humans
are better so this story is an action story but before the story starts it's a horror story
because we get that segment of it but we don't get the story before it of the fishing boat
floating empty in the aral sea and another fishing boat comes by it and they look
this is Yuri's boat where did he go fishing oh he went to the island i told him not to go there
let's bring his boat back and tell his wife a tugboat listing alone day and night day and night
abandoned for days weeks who knows people had gone missing in this area so much so
that the soviet union said we need to figure out what's going on out there and that's not one
missing person that's not three missing people that's a lot of missing people for a national
government to say let's figure this out so you would have to have a mass amount of people missing
before it even came to the notice of kgb and even then a few more to really get them off their butts
and figure out what was going on out there so we have the action packed part but what happened to
those missing people where did they go i can keep making jokes about the kgb just slaughtering these
aliens without any real contact with them but how many times did one of these fishing boats get too
close to the island and a fog bank rolls off the island and covers up the boat and they find themselves
on the island they're lost they're walking through the fog until they find a fence and hoping there's
help they scuttle over it but there's not 12 of them it's just one lone fisherman he's not heavily
armed he just has a fishing knife in his sheath what are the odds of him surviving any of these
encounters with these aliens they were obviously armed and they were obviously hidden so if they
need to keep their location secret they'll do whatever it takes how many soviet citizens
disappeared on that island their names lost to time until the kgb showed up and shot everything
with a heartbeat and remember these aliens just packed up and left they didn't leave earth they
had a mission they set up somewhere else and after a few humans came in and slaughtered their entire
staff save two giants the next location they set up they're going to be much more careful
about letting intruders in they're going to have better security and they're going to have better
weapons to fight off any adversaries but a byproduct of having an alien installation on earth
is that it breaks the realm of the normal and the paranormal and every so often a dimension
defying mist seems to spread out in the area so the next time you're out for your morning walk
and you start to see that fog bank roll through your area maybe you should turn that walk
into a run because while it might be a beautiful natural phenomenon it could also be something
darker and more dangerous a portal to an alien base and unless you're a member of the kgb the
chances of you ever being seen again are slim to none dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to
be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is at
dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
you don't have to listen to it every day but i'm glad you listen to it today have a great weekend guys
you