Grab those peanuts and crackerjacks, guys. We are going to a baseball game first off.
Is the sport of baseball actually a ritual that shows man's place in the universe?
And then we take a look at a bizarre story coming out of Chicago in 2013.
When the Chicago Cubs and the Milwaukee Brewers were playing a game, is it possible someone
actually flashed a spell in front of millions of viewers to change the course of the game today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a lot of stuff to cover.
So, play ball! We're gonna get this. There's gonna be a lot of those puns. Actually, that
I'm the only one and it wasn't even a pun. I'm gonna take my bat out and I'm gonna smack a ball,
and it's gonna be caught by one of our legacy Patreons, Ash Adams. Ash snatches that ball right
out of the air, pitch it back to me while I'm doing the rest of my intro. You're gonna be our pilot
this episode, our pitcher. If you can't support the Patreon, I totally understand that too. Just
help get the word out about the show. That really, really helps out a lot. Hit the ball. It's going
over. I'm not gonna just hit the ball. I'm like, "Hey guys, come listen to my podcast. It's gonna be
me making ball noises for 30 minutes." But we are gonna be talking about baseball and it's funny.
I've done a couple episodes recently about sports conspiracies. I'm actually surprised that it took
me so long to get to these ones. I didn't know they existed, but I was looking pretty hard at
sports conspiracies and these just both kind of popped up on the same day. So, Ash Adams, let's
hop in that dead rabbit dirgeable. We're gonna need an old, tiny vehicle because first off,
we're going back in time, going through the time vortex. We're going back to 1800s America. We see
a bunch of people walking around with bats and balls and then they start clubbing each other
with the bats. It's a very brutal time in American history. But when they're done destroying their
enemies with these bats, we're gonna take a quick look at the history of baseball. There was a bunch
of different versions of baseball going on. You have the Massachusetts version. You have the New
York version. I'm sure they had an Arizona version where they just throw in dirtcloths. Very short
game. All the balls keep exploding. Depending on what state you were in, the rules were kind of
played differently. There were similarities. Both New York and Massachusetts had the diamond,
had the baseball diamond. They had a ball, obviously, and bases. The funniest thing, though, was,
you know, the version we know today is the New York version. And in the New York version,
you have to run along the baseline. You have to run from home to first base to second base.
There's that line you can really can't deviate off of. In the Massachusetts version, you could run
anywhere you wanted to. You could totally, like, if someone's on first base, you're like, "Ah!" and
you're like running off into the outfield. And people are constantly throwing balls way out there
to get you. Everyone must have had really, really good upper body strength. You just run wherever
you're up in the stands. You're like, "Ah, I can't get me." You could. You could do whatever. Okay,
maybe not the stands, but you could run anywhere you wanted in the field. You're changing your
uniform real quick. You come out as a player on the other team. "Huh? What's going on?" They got rid
of that. The New York version was like, "No, we don't do that. We don't put up with that tomfoolery."
The reason why they settled on the New York version, because it was easier to bet on,
and you could put side bets on during pretty much any point in the game. "Hey, I bet you
this guy's going to hit a grounder to the left field." Oh, yeah, I bet you 10 bucks. It was a game.
It was considered a kids game for a long time until betting came into it.
Now, here's... I have to go off on this because I thought this was funny too. There's nothing to do
with the episode, but this has just become a sports podcast today. Ash Adams is like, "Great,
this is the episode I'm on. I don't even like baseball." Yeah, you do, Ash. Yeah, you do.
But this next part has nothing to do with baseball. American baseball is older than American football,
but football apparently goes back to the medieval times, right? And I thought this was
hilarious. This was the old version of football back in medieval Europe. You'd have two towns.
It's funny because you can see the parallels, obviously, to today. Well, obviously, there's
two towns, but you'd have two towns, right? And you had unlimited players. So one group may have
bring out their 13 biggest guys in town. The other town could bring out literally like two,
300 people and be like, "We know the Black Play decimated your team last year, but we still got
200 people." And they would take an animal's bladder and they would inflate it with air.
Whose job was that? How was that to blow into the sheep lung? And then they would try to get it
to the other person's town. I mean, how long did these games last? They're like,
"It's day three of game one." And you would run from your town, like you would start in the middle,
and then you would get this inflated sheep bladder or whatever it was. And you would have to run it
to their town. Now, you would pick where you wanted your goal to be. You had to jump over a
couple of pigs or whatever. That's our end zone. But the example that Wikipedia gave was, for example,
people may use the local church as their end zone, which is the best end zone ever, right?
They're doing mass. You're running with a sheep bladder during mass. You're knocking nuns over.
You spike it right in the altar. The coach gets a bucket of holy water dumped on them.
That would be, I would watch every medieval football game possible if that was still in effect.
If I lived in medieval times and I was able to walk from town to town, they're like, "Oh, great.
Turn over. You got to walk all the way back to your own town." But anyways, that has nothing to do
with baseball. I would just have no other opportunity to talk about that. And I found the hilarious.
Okay, so I've gone off topic. Let's go back to baseball. We're sitting in the stands. We're eating
popcorn and stuff like that. We're watching these guys play baseball out in the field.
Now, according to, there's a website called Southern Cross Review. And on this website,
there is an article written by Hannah M.G. Shapiro called "Baseball as an Esoteric Ritual."
This is an interesting one because it could be one of those exercises where you can literally
take anything and find really deep meaning in it. Or there could be something else here.
But before we get into Hannah's thing, I want to talk about this too. I saw this video on a
YouTube channel called Catholic Breakfast. And he was talking about, again, there's this dude
talking about deeper meaning in baseball. And that was interesting because he said,
"Most sports are designed as competition, like that medieval town thing, where like hockey and
basketball and football and soccer, you have two pieces of territory and you're trying to get
something into the enemy territory or get something into your territory, into your hoop."
Type of thing. He said, "Baseball is the only main sport that's not like that, at least in America,
where you're not trying to get into the enemy's territory." He actually said, "It's interesting
because it's one of those sports where the other team is not the enemy, the ball is the enemy.
You're trying to get that ball as far out. That ball is coming towards you and you're
trying to hit it and you're trying to get as far away from you as possible. And there happens to
be obstacles who are the players, but they're not the exact adversary. You're never invading their
territory in that sense as we think of football or basketball or things like that."
But going back to Hannah, she said that baseball is played in a perfect geometric square.
Other sports are played in a giant rectangle. So right there, baseball is already separate. And
also from that one video, you're not going into the enemy's territory to be messing with them.
There's four bases, and those four bases are supposed to represent the four elements.
Now, home is obviously supposed to represent earth. She says it's because it's dusty. I just think
that you're just kind of reaching to that point. I just think the very sense that it's called home
base. And basically, the ritual is this. God or fate is throwing a ball towards you. And you have
to use all of your inner strength to move that ball away from you out into the universe. And then
you travel through the universe. The third base is supposed to be the represents fire, because it's
known as the hot turn. But no one knows what the other two bases are supposed to be ever at
several websites, and they go, "Home is earth, and third base is fire." And then they just go on to
the next paragraph. I'm like, "What about first and second?" So you could say water, wind, however
you want to organize that. But the point is, is that the picture is basically God's messenger
throwing out esoteric secrets towards you, man. Then you have to run through the cosmos
and get back home with the knowledge you've gained while you were traveling around.
It's fascinating. I mean, it obviously could just be reaching too far. They also have this whole
thing about how there's three strikes. There's three outs. There's nine innings. There's nine players
without the designated hitter. So you have all those things. There's four balls, but you could say,
"Yeah, there's just four. Sometimes four appears too." But three strikes, three outs, nine innings.
It's also one of the very few sports games. It's funny recently when I did my episode about
naked baseball. A lot of you guys responded saying, "Baseball already takes forever if you
have to have sex at every single base that would go on forever." It's one of the few sports that
has no time limit. Almost every sport has a clock going. A baseball game can be as short or as long
as it needs to be. If you have three up, three down, three up, three down, three up, three down,
over and over and over again, you could have a baseball game done in what, an hour? If one team
gets one hit and then everyone else is just three up, three down, three up, three down,
or they could go on for eight hours. Because it's not about the time. There is no time limit.
You play until the game is done or until it's called for rain or until the heat depth of the
universe, but there's no time limit to it. That's another interesting thing about the sport of
baseball. It's interesting because when I was thinking about this story, I thought, "You're
right. Baseball kind of reminds you of the hero's journey where it's one person. Football, basketball,
all those other sports, there are two teams are going at it. You have one person going out onto
that base and that person is versus the entire team. All these obstacles out there in life.
You hit it as far as you can and you can get to home if you hit a home run, but even if you just
get on first base, the game is still then that next person who steps up to the plate. Who can
assist you in getting back home? The game is centered on that one person on home plate trying
to hit that ball. So it's like that hero, you're taking that journey. It is very esoteric. A lot
of times this stuff when they go like, "Oh, television. Get it? Tell a vision. It's all about
story." That's not where that comes from. Tell is over distance and vision is because I can see it. So
sometimes you can really make these things overrot. This one actually kind of makes sense. It kind
of makes sense that baseball is such an odd sport when compared to these other ones that there could
be some sort of esoteric meaning behind it. Hannah, when she was writing this article, it could have
been tongue-in-cheek because it's titled as an esoteric ritual, not is an esoteric ritual.
One is a statement saying, "This is what I believe." The other one is like, "Oh, you can look at baseball
under this lens." But I do think if you step back and look at the game of baseball, it does
seem very ritualistic. Now, all sports have rituals, but this one is so different from the other major
sports. Yeah, I'm sure rollerblading might represent man's place phony through the cosmos or something
like that, but I think even they have like time clocks. You're actively working against one team
versus another, things like that. Baseball is one man versus the universe. Wait, "una versus one against."
May do. Did I just blow everyone's mind, including my own? What if the universe is really the story
of us singular trying to figure our way out of it? Like, we basically each create our own universe
of obstacles. That's why it's called the uni verse. You're like, Jason, that's not even close.
Doesn't matter. That's it. I'm taking you out of my universe. I've just forgotten about you. You're
like, "No, you fade away. I like you. I bring you back in reality." You realize the void was real
in those brief seconds. You're never going to mess with me again. But anyways, you can do it with
anything, obviously. You can pick any word. You could, any show. You could say Smurfs is really
representation of man's place on the evolutionary scale and everyone's a gargamel. Whatever. Like,
you can do all sorts of stuff. But this one actually is pretty weird. Like, I gotta give
him credit for that. So tip of the hat to you. Tip of the baseball hat to you, Hannah. But that's
not all I have for you today. Because while that's just kind of a, this is an interesting
some facts about baseball hand-warmed football, as I was researching that, I came across this story.
Ash Adams, let's hop in that carbonicopter. We're headed out to Chicago.
We're flying around the beautiful city of Chicago. Nice and high. We're waving.
Kanye West is pissing on his Grammy. How have I not talked about that yet? I guess you guys are
like, "That's not what your podcast is about." Anyways, we're waving high to Kanye West for
flying around. We're going to land in Chicago. We're going to see the sights. And then we're
going to go see a baseball game. The Chicago Cubs versus the Brewers. This is June 25th, 2013.
They lose against the Brewers 9-3. Next day, Bob Vorwald, who's a journalist, covers sports
for WGN, writes an article for their website called Spell I-94 Bound. And he talks about,
"Hey listen, the Cubs have lost 19 of their past 21 games against Milwaukee, and they've lost the
past nine in a row. Things are not good for them. Is it time to cast the spell on Miller Park?"
So then Bob Vorwald tells a story about back in 1988, he was hanging out with the Houston
Astros. And they had lost 11 straight games. And he's like, "Oh man, this totally sucks. I actually
couldn't tell if he was a player because I was looking through their roster. I think he was just
a sports reporter in Houston at the time. But the Houston Astros had lost 11 games straight.
So he's walking down the street and he's like, "Oh man, that totally sucks." And he says that he
feels himself be drawn into a bookstore. He walks into the bookstore and he feels himself pulled
down this particular aisle and he finds a book on the occult. At this point in the article, there's
a picture. And it's from deposit photos. It's a stock image of various occultic imagery. So you
have the all-C and I. You have the Eye of Osiris, Freemasons logo, pentagram and inverted pentagram.
It looked like a either for clip art or one of those sheets you would see at a tattoo parlor.
It was just a white sheet with probably about 30 different random occultic images on there.
And then the article continues. So you have this image. He doesn't reference it in the article.
He literally just got some stock photo and put it in this article. He says when he's reading this
book, he finds a spell on how to put a curse on your enemies. And he chuckles and he goes, "Let's do
this. Let's do this. The Houston Astros have lost 11 games in a row. What do we have to lose other
than a 12th game?" So he assembles the ingredients for the spell. He needs three twigs from three
different trees. You have to spit on them. You take them to where you're going to go. He added
that part. That part wasn't in the spell book. He was just really like spitting on stuff. He goes to
the Houston Astros Stadium and there he's joined by two fellow "co-warlocks." They're actually players
for the Houston Astros at the time, Larry Anderson and Dave Smith. They spit on the twigs. He's like,
"Yeah guys, you're supposed to spit on them nice and slow. Yeah, no, slower Larry. Yeah,
get a nice big, big gooey one." They're like, "What? It's part of the spell. It's part of the spells."
His eyes shift from side to side as he licks his lips. They spit on the twigs. They light them on
fire and then they do this incantation. At that point, one of the... They really do this. At that
point, one of the other players comes out and tells them to knock it off. Quit doing that stuff.
It's kind of creepy and it's dumb as well. And also, why do you keep wanting me to spit in stuff,
Bob? He's like, "What? It's part of my journalism query. You just got to spit in the cup. It makes
the article so much better." He said that that night, the Houston Astros won the game and the player
who came out who poo-poo the whole thing pulled a hamstring at his first at bat and didn't get
to play. And he go... He finishes the article with this. "You will also notice that the winning
pitcher that night was Nolan Ryan. Always a good idea when casting a spell to have a hall of famer
scheduled to pitch." Unquote. So kind of tongue-in-cheek, right? Saying, "Yeah, we did this spell and
it was kind of funny. The guy who made fun of us pulled a hamstring and then, you know, I went back
there and took care of him, put it to his mouth and took out all of his spit. Told him it would help
his hamstring. I'm making up his spit fetish. Don't sue me, Bob." But he goes, you know, "Yeah, we
cast a spell, but we also had one of the best pitchers in baseball history there." So you know
what are you gonna do? So he writes this article and it's kind of a funny one. And in the middle
of the article he has that picture of stock image photo of just different symbols. So that article
came out on June 26th. The first game was June 25th. He writes this article on June 26th. That
night, Cubs lose four to five. So the Cubs still lose. What are you gonna expect? At this point,
they have lost 11 straight games against the Brewers. So their losing streak continues.
June 27th, though, the day after the article came out, the day after the Cubs lost yet again,
they're playing baseball. One last time, the Cubs and the Brewers. And the Cubs win seven to two.
And in the middle of the broadcast, the screen goes black. But it doesn't really go black. It goes
blue. Blueish, black. There's some sort of weird overlay image. And on top of that
is the stock photo sheet of occultic symbols. While the game is being broadcast out of Chicago,
this is going on. And you hear the commentators. They see it too. You hear the commentators go,
"I have no idea what that is." And then the other commentator says, "Apparently the baseball gods
did know." The image disappears. The baseball game is back up. I had to work really, really hard to
find any proof of this. Because what happened was I started seeing screenshots of these weird
symbols appearing during this baseball game. And I'd read this article and they would say,
"Click here for the video." And you click on it, there'd be no video for it. Before it News is a
website, which is the equivalent of the Daily Star, they just published a ton of nonsense.
They actually took their article down about this. Which made me think that it must be fake.
Because when I first came into the story, I had heard that these images were flashed during the
baseball game and there was like a blurry still photo. So I had to go back. I found this article.
I had to really go back and try to piece it. First off, I didn't know if it was real. If it was just
a screenshot, someone made it up. And then I find this whole story about Bob Vorwald,
you know, talking about casting the spell in 1988 and things like that. It took me a long time to
research this story, longer than normal. Longer than normal. A lot of times I'm able to get all
the information I need very quickly on this stuff. Then I just kind of fill out the details. I spent
a long time trying to track down this video. It doesn't exist in a pure form. Very, very weird
for something that happened in 2013. The internet was in the full swing of things. There was only
seven years ago. YouTube taken down, YouTube channel taken down, the video not existing.
I eventually found it in a 12 minute long video. The last about nine minutes into a 12 minute long
video, it plays. There is no clip of it in existence. You have to watch this video. I actually have it.
If you go to my show notes, you'll see the YouTube video. It's queued up. So you don't have to listen
to the rest of the video. You can. I mean, it's just that basic thing like Illuminati,
the control in the world. So the video itself, the clip itself that I couldn't find anywhere.
I had to find it included in this. What my theory is, is that some, this is, this is tracking all of
this back. This is my theory. WGN was broadcasting the game. And apparently this image appeared on
Dish TV as well, but they would have been, or Dish Network, they would have been getting their
signal from WGN, who was videotaping the game. That dates me, who was broadcasting the game.
I bet you somebody at WGN had read that article, clipped that image out, and then as a joke,
put it on the screen and it wasn't supposed to be broadcast. They may have put it on the screen
for the people in the control room to see, or for Bob to see. I think it would be funny,
but it accidentally got broadcast. Because these symbols, people have said, "Oh, this is proof of
the Illuminati city are using their magical powers to control games." First off, if the Illuminati
controls the world, why do they care whether or not the Cubs win? Or the Cubs would always win.
If the Illuminati control the world and they could do whatever they wanted, why don't they just have
one team win all the time? Right? Why would they have different teams win? But anyways,
also why would they use a depot? Because I tracked down the actual image. I was actually going to use
it for the episode, the stock image, but I didn't want to pay $5 for it. So I didn't. But it's literally
just a bunch of mishmash of... There are occultic images, but if that's all it takes,
it's just you can literally get a clip art book to cast a spell. Then again, everyone would be
doing it. I don't think that the Illuminati was using a spell to cast on this game. I think someone
at WGN saw that image earlier when that article was published and thought it would be funny
to pull a prank, but didn't mean for it to get broadcast. But it did get broadcast.
And so on that level, I think it has a very, very plausible answer. The question is, did that affect
the Cubs winning the game? There's actually a lot of questions here, because while I accept that as
the skeptical answer, because that's what the evidence shows. You have this image being shown
on this article, it's a bunch of mishmash. They're of different occultic ideologies, a pentagram,
and an inverted pentagram. Like, one of that just knock it out. And then you have, I mean,
you could obviously tell it's just a proof sheet. But why did someone work so hard to delete all
of the video footage of this stuff? Why did the For It News take down their article on it? They
published garbage on that website, right? Why did they take it down? You can really only find a
few sources on this. You can find an article on patch.com written by Mike Pazinski called
"The Colt Symbols Flash on Screen During Brewers Game." That was the first article that popped up
for me. And honestly, it was pretty much the last. Like, that's the last place out there that has
all this information. You have that, and then you have him linking out to other places and the links
don't work. There was another website called "Silence's Acceptance." And that is where I found
the video embedded that nine minutes into it actually had the clip that I wanted. This is one
of those stories where it's not the story itself that makes me believe in it. It's the cover-up
that makes me believe in it. This information should be out there everywhere. The fact that
somebody has gone through the trouble to copyright strike these videos, to have these articles taken
down, to really make it very hard to find information on. Very, very weird. It's not the crime, it's the
cover-up. It's not the fact that a cult image has appeared during a baseball game, which is weird in
and of itself. But the fact that someone has gone through a lot of trouble to keep that information
hidden, that is what I find so disturbing about this story. Yeah, it's not the crime, it's the cover-up.
So was it a harmless prank? Or was it a spell cast during an already esoteric ritual?
What happens when you combine two forms of magic at once and show it to millions of people?
We don't know the answer to that. But we know someone is trying to keep us from discovering this story.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio.
Twitter is @deadrabbitradio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime
podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
Bye.