A young man's journey into the jungle to find some guava
Turns in to a close encounter of the ferned kind get it cuz ferns jungles
That might have been a bit of a stretch
But then the next story we're gonna look at if you didn't like that one. Don't worry. There's another one coming
A young woman goes missing
Unfortunately things like this happen
Quite often but when her mysterious disappearance is linked to a haunted lighthouse
All bets are off today on dead rapper radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of dead rapper radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. Let's go ahead and move on with our first topic now
Let's go ahead. You know, we don't really have a jungle terrain vehicle. We did till I got blown up the carboner copter
But but we're just gonna have to hack and slash our way through the jungle here because what we're doing is we are going to
South America
specifically we are headed down to Brazil so
You're hacking and slashing. I'm just walking behind you because you know, I'll let you do all the grunt work
You're the one who wants to hear these stories hacking and slashing through the jungle all to help fight
Cougars or mountain lions. No, no, what do they call the jaguars?
Yeah, I'll fight those while you're hacking and slashing through and as we're going through the jungles of Brazil
We also go back in time to the year
1978 I was two years old when this story took place. So imagine me as a two-year-old baby
sitting watching
What was on in 1978?
Watching threes a company
Actually wasn't allowed to watch that show not just as a baby
That was one of the many shows that was banned in my house growing up
We weren't allowed to watch threes company, which it wasn't that funny. Anyways, I didn't care
And I don't remember what else probably because they were banned
But I remember there's a lot of stuff we couldn't watch nor how to crude was what my dad said that shows too crude
Oddly enough Meredith children. We got to watch that. I think my dad was more relaxed
But I'm that show came out anyways. So it's 1978
And as we're in the jungle we're basically cutting a parallel pep
We're basically stalking this kid really because we don't want to interact with them
We don't want to interfere with what's about to happen. There's a young man. His name is Luis Carlos Sara 16 year old boy
He's walking through the jungle and he's in the jungle specifically to go pick up some guava
Which actually sounds pretty dope
Imagine and we kind of covered this the Amazon is actually man-made. It was made as like a giant supermarket by the natives
hundreds or thousands of years ago
There's something compelling about being able to just be like, you know, what do you want for lunch?
I don't know a couple pears and just walk out and grab pears like I've never lived and I don't people on farm
And basically I've just explained like farm life, but I've never been like that. I've always been like, oh man
I want some guava, which I don't I've never even eaten guava, but let's say like oh, I want an apple
I have to walk to a store to get an apple or walk to a farmer's market to get an apple
I've never just been able to walk out to a tree pick an apple off a tree and eat it
I've never ever ever experienced that at all
Super bizarre now that I say that out loud, but I've never experienced that never walked up to a chicken shook it to an egg
Pop out and ate the egg have never done any of that stuff
So but anyways, he's able to Luis was able to go in he's looking for guava now. It's noon. The hot sun is overhead
beating down on his body
I don't know why he's paused like that. It was weird
Anyways, it's beating down on him and he's just going about his day and then all of a sudden he hears a
And it was louder than that. I was just trying to make a sound effect a dramatic sound effect
It was a loud bang, but I didn't want to blow your eardrums out loud bang
So imagine that clap with the bang on top of it times 20 because what it's loud enough that
Gets his attention. He's in the jungle if he's not paying attention to all the predators lurking around him
He's dead. He's constantly having to turn around so he never has his back to a giant jungle cat
This noise is loud enough to make him go up. I don't care about what's in the jungle
What's overhead because this loud sound came from overhead? He looks up and he says he says he sees something that is
Brighter than the Sun. It's a light brighter than the Sun now. It's interesting because
What he is seeing he doesn't know what it is, but we do we traveled back in time so we know the future
What he's seen as a UFO and then there is there's a couple interesting things about this right off of that one
broad daylight like broad broad daylight and to
At noon when the Sun's directly overhead to see something brighter than the Sun
Right above you almost seems impossible
Because you're already bathed in light and for something to be lighter than the light you're in
I guess if you're like outside in the day and someone strapped like flashes a strobe light in front of you
That's technically brighter than the Sun
But it just seems such a it seems so bizarre to have that be like I was looked up at the Sun
But then I saw something actually brighter than the Sun right above me
And then that wasn't bad enough if he wasn't his mind wasn't reeling by like how was this possible?
He starts to be pushed down. He said that he described it as if two strong hands
were holding his shoulders and
Slowly like pushing him to the ground
Pushing him down and he couldn't resist it and it finally gets him all the way to the ground
And now he's laying flat completely paralyzed and looking up at this super bright light
Now at this point you're thinking what could be work like what's gonna happen now?
Like what's gonna happen to this poor kid? He's been blinded. He's been paralyzed
Jungle cats are putting on their bibs getting ready to eat him, but then he slowly starts to lift off off the ground
Starts to levitate over the jungle floor and begins flying up into the craft now
That sounds kind of cool because you think like you'd be Superman and stuff
But it's not cool if you can't control it like Superman is only cool because he controls where he flies
If he had all his normal powers, but flex Luther decided where he went
He wouldn't be that cool and that was this dude this guy was Superman with no self-control
He ends up flying into the UFO like a big window opened up
He flies into the window he's actually terrified at this point. There's no dramatic music playing
Oh, I think Superman came out this year actually didn't come out like 77 78
Anyway, super not superman the boy
flies into the UFO
Defeats Brainiac the boy flies into the UFO and he's sitting there. He's not sitting there. He's actually a prisoner
He's still paralyzed. He says that he sees these three figures in metallic suits
Walking around the inside of the UFO can't understand what they're saying and interestingly enough. They also have visors
So he can't see their face
He can't really see anything. They're basically wearing armor and he can't understand what they're saying
So none of this telepathy none of this universal translators
He is their prisoner and they don't want him to know what they're saying now
I know right now you think of Jason you don't cover a lot of UFO stuff and there's a reason why I don't cover a lot of UFO stuff
It's not because I don't believe it. It's because most of it is I looked up in the sky
I saw light I couldn't identify it flew away or I looked up in the sky this little hover ship appeared and then flew away
I like this stuff where people are meeting stuff and abductions are always cool
But usually abductions are just like I got abducted they stuck something up my butthole and then I went home
And I'm like, yeah, this story is
Has an interesting connection to a story that I've covered in the past
And I want to see if you guys can catch it and I'll explain it if you didn't but I'm not just gonna end the episode
Anyways, so he gets he's talking to these eight. He's not talking to him again
He's just trapped these metal armored aliens are walking around they take
So and they're walking around the UFO is continues to fly and then he
flies like again being levitated flies back off like the little doctor table in the UFO
back out the window and as he's floating down what he sees is a giant
stone like a giant flat stone on the ground
surrounded by grass in all directions
So he's no longer nowhere near where he left
He has no idea where he's at and as he's being lowered onto this rock this big giant slab
This flat slab he looks up. He sees the night sky, but the night sky is just black
There is no stars whatsoever in the sky. So he's able to see this UFO hovering above them
It's the traditional disc shaped type UFO flying out the window. He sees below him the grass and the rock slab
He sees above him just pitch black no stars. No nothing and
He lands on the rock slab
He lands on the slab and the figures are standing back over him and they have this ball this tree
they it's described as a transparent ball full of strange liquid and they force the whole ball into his mouth and
He wakes up. He's on the jungle floor
completely paralyzed
Now he can't move and he can't really talk. He's just laying on the jungle floor
He's crying out for help. He can't move and finally a fisherman just walking by
Andy Griffith and his son are walking through the jungle and they see the 16 year old boy laying on the ground
He's like help me. I'll use the only word I know in Spanish
Agua Agua and I learned that from Sesame Street. So anyways to give him some water and he's like no no no water
I need help and you know they pick him up. I don't know what I'm saying. They it's only one fisherman
I love it when my fictional jokes end up becoming part of the story just one person one fisherman
There was no sun there. There was no barney fife either one fisherman just one picks him up takes the boy to the hospital
Three days this kid had been missing
He went out to go get the guava and three days later they find him on the jungle floor
The family thought he was gone. They had no idea where this kid went three days had gone missing in that period of time
He was floating around hanging out on rocks in the middle of nowhere
And for 10 days he was completely catatonic
He just sat there in bed paralyzed. He couldn't talk
Well, he could he could say Agua but I mean like he could he could kind of be like
I don't know what the type stuff but he couldn't move and he couldn't really communicate. He sat there for 10 days
And what the doctors noticed they noticed a couple odd things one his hair
Was gone and first they thought it was shaved off. But as they were looking at it closer
They realized it was burned off because he actually had burn marks along the tops of his ears
And four of his teeth had been broken shattered
And they think that it was fairly recent because they were still blood on his teeth like they were still fresh blood
So it was like he was a recent wound. Maybe the fisherman dropped him a couple times as he was carrying him
but
Eventually after 10 days the kid louise snaps out of it and tells the story of what happened now
Of course, some people believed in and some people didn't it kind of became this big brouhaha in the area and stuff like that
And it's just become a story that's kind of disappeared into ufology except for one detail
I did an episode a while back about a bigfoot being an interdimensional creature
And in this episode and in this story there was a hiker who was walking through the woods
He was walking through the woods. He walked through a portal which he didn't know was there and ended up in a
dense jungle area
Where there was a bigfoot type creature that was about to attack him from behind. He says I just saw the hand
I heard a voice go gotcha
And this hand reached towards him and then he stepped back out of the portal
But in that portal world where he went it was bright daylight during
When he was walking through the forest and then he walks through the portal and it's nighttime in this jungle
He said one of the most alien things about the whole thing was he looked up at the sky. It was pitch black
with no stars
Interesting detail and that's why I wanted to cover this story of louise
One I thought is an interesting story because he's like it has kind of these hallmarks of
Alien objections, but has that extra detail
He was also teleported to some weird dimension where there was just a flat rock and grass
Going as far as the eye can see
There's I mean it could have taken him to kansas, but that kansas has stars kansas does have a moon like
It's almost like that jungle world of the bigfoot creature and now this world that these aliens travel to are some sort of
Void some sort of nexus place where you can kind of filter in and out of
And then both having the same detail of
A black sky with no stars to me that is chilling
That too, I mean, I know there's like light pollution and stuff like that
So sometimes you don't see all the stars, but you see some of them
You know that they're there
But to exist in a world that's just a pitch black sky with no stars to me is is
Hellish it's so that is so alien to the human experience
So yeah, I mean that's just a creepy detail shared between two stories on different continents two
Unrelated stories involving unrelated creatures told by people who have never ever met each other
And these two stories have never been connected before this podcast
These are the these are the little pieces of what I believe are evidence
That some of this stuff
Is factual
Sure, two people can make up the exact same detail on accident
or
These people survive to tell their stories of this alien world
That's accessible from earth
It's not millions of light years away. You can get to it here through a portal through a craft
But one thing's for sure
It doesn't sound like a place that is hospitable to humans
It sounds like a place we should do anything to avoid
Let's go ahead and move on to our next story here now our next story is
It's quite chilling. This is a weird one and this one's still ongoing
The bulk of it has taken place, but there's still search efforts going on
We're going to Connecticut the state that never sleeps. It's may 17th 2018
So a little over a year ago this happened
A little over a year ago this happened
Headed out to Connecticut
So in Connecticut
There's a lot of people but we're gonna we're gonna look at two people in particular. So fia mackenna 21 year old model slash masseuse
And her friend spencer mugford is 20 years old and he was a sailing instructor
And he did like charter fishing boat stuff
So he was a strong swimmer. He knew how his way around a boat
They were good friends and they used to date and then they broke up and she got together with her ex
This is all important, but not just being a gossip. I'm like, oh, did you know spencer and so fia broke up?
I'm not trying to be a gossip. They're friends
And she has a boyfriend and he's just chilling. So on may 27th
They say, hey, you know, let's go on a boat ride. Let's go on a boat ride
So they end up taking and I'm a little I don't know if technically if they stole this boat or if he had permission
But they ended up taking a boat
From the university of connecticut's boatyard. Can you imagine having such a rich school that your school has like a boatyard?
I was lucky when I went to college. I was lucky if I could find a parking spot and now these oh
Oh, puffy. Did you bring your boat today? Like who has a boat? Who has a boat section of their college?
anyways
That was my rant
So it's just phenomenal. Are there colleges that I
I could understand a boating college having a boat. I'm not saying like nautical school
I'm like, why you guys have boats? But this is university of connecticut
This is where people go to get like degrees in english and welding and stuff like that. They have a boat section
It's just so bizarre to me. Is there like a public university that has like a helicopter section or they just have like 10
helicopters hanging out
anyways, so
The soffia and spencer go and they take a boat from the university of connecticut's
Bizarre boatyard
So they take one of these boats and they're headed off to a place called the new london ledge lighthouse new london ledge lighthouse
Now the new london ledge lighthouse is an interesting thing. It's basically a stone pier
In the middle of the bay and there's a lighthouse built on top of it. It's not an island
It's not like connected to the land which is what would make an island, but it's not like a natural island
It's just a stone a giant stone pier with a giant lighthouse. It's not just like a stick with a candle on it
It's like a fully functional
Lighthouse that people used to live in and then it went automated back like in 1987
But a giant lighthouse like you imagine a us lighthouse sticking on a big concrete man-made island in the middle of this bay
Now like all good crimes. This is why i'm a little i don't think he had permission to take the boat
But i could be wrong in that detail, but she began snapchatting the journey
So early that morning like around probably like 1 30 or something like that
she post a snapchat of
Spencer
rowing the boat
rowing the boat to the lighthouse
And then at 2 a.m. There is a snapchat photo of her
of sofia
standing in front of a no trespassing sign at the lighthouse kind of sticking her tongue out
Very playful photo
2 a.m. That photo was taken posted a snapchat
The next day sofia's boyfriend can't get a hold of her
And he's calling around and she's not picking up her phone. He can't figure it out
He ends up calling sofia's mom and saying hey, do you happen to know where sofia is and she's like i
Don't you don't know and they kind of have that
Normal conversation that starts off kind of like oh, yeah, yeah, but you can it starts to get panicked over time
Sofia's mom goes okay. Well, you know, i'll see if i can get a hold of her at that point
Earlier that morning
Sofia's sister a little sister had gotten the mother's phone. It was playing with it
So the mother didn't immediately see when she woke up that there were several missed calls seven missed calls from an unknown number on her cell phone
But when she starts looking for sofia she she does get her cell phone
And that is when she sees those seven missed calls from an unknown number. She calls the number back
It goes to spencer's voicemail
First phone call was made at 2 o 6 a.m. So six minutes after the photo was taken
Then 2 o 7 a.m
Three calls at 2 o 8 a.m
In the final call from 2 o 9 a.m. So the mother didn't have spencer's phone number in her phone
That's why it was coming up unknown but sofia would know the mother's phone
So she was calling from spencer's phone and it would make sense because at 2 a.m
Her phone that was posting the snapchat video was in the hands of spencer
So spencer has her phone takes the photo six minutes later
Spenser's phone is making phone calls to sofia's mother. So that chain of events makes sense
But they start this search the police begin searching for sofia is the first person who's reported missing
Eventually spencer is noticed that he's not there as well
And they're looking for him as well everyone's thinking the worst
As the as people are do you know where sofia is do you know where sofia is people go? Oh, you know, but look on our snapchat
This show she was on a boat
Late last night so they then see the photo of her standing in front of the no trespassing sign and people go
She went to the lighthouse like her and spencer must have taken the boat because they can even see in the video of the boat
They see the lights in the background so they can figure out where the boat was headed
And then there's a photo of her standing in front of this lighthouse
Sign no trespassing people recognize that because it's not a super popular tourist destination
But people do go there for a reason and we'll get to that in a second. So
The police go there and there's no one there. No one on this man-made island. This lighthouse. It's empty
It's been automated since 1987. So they have to start thinking what could have happened to these two people
His shirt spencer's shirt is tied around a mooring pole
At the lighthouse so where they would tie the boats down to morum
So where they would like throw it tied the boats down basically to keep them from flowing away
They found his shirt tied around one end of that. So that was like one clue that they had
48 hours after these two go missing so very shortly on they find the boat washed up
On a shore it just basically
crashed up somewhere
There were no
Footprints leading from the boat like across the
Cross the sand there was no footprints like leading off somewhere. So they go the boat must have been abandoned
So they start working with this theory. They go, okay, here's our theory
They got to the they did get the lighthouse. We have photographic proof of that
He tied the boat down with his shirt
And they got up on the island and at that point the at some point the
Shirt started to get untied and the boat
got washed away
And he jumped in the water after it, but he was probably really tired
From you know, the well rowing out there
He jumped in the water after it and she may have jumped in the water after him
We're going to find the bodies because they're they are not on the island. They checked everywhere
This is the reason why people knew to go there people
Recognize the area because the lighthouse has a reputation for being haunted
It is a place where people go to like meet ghosts ghost hunter shows have gone there
Paranormal investigators have gone there and if you can take a boat from your college or you just have an own a boat
You can go there too. It's not restricted property as far as well
I guess there's a no trespassing sign
But you know like teen is they're going to jump the fence and go into a graveyard anyway
So I mean you can go there you can well physically go there, but they go there to go ghost hunting
It's a spooky place in the middle of nowhere
So that's their working theory and they actually start to realize that that is most likely what happened
Because two weeks later they find spencer's body
Floating in the water
So they go okay, so this is what this is what happened like yes
He tied the boat down
And it started to break away and he jumped in to save the boat and she must have jumped in after him and they're done
And and what's odd it was very odd
It was they found his body on the day they were having his memorial service on the day of his memorial service
they find his body so
That does answer that question of what happened to him, but people are still trying to figure out what happened to sofia now
Now I guess tying down a boat with your
Jacket like I would think well, that's them. Why don't you just use a rope?
But I mean i'm not a nautical person. I'm not a sailor. I guess is the term i'm supposed to use
I guess a tie is a tie and this guy he wasn't some drunk frat boy like this is what he did for a living
So he didn't just like loop it around the boat a couple times and then jump upon this pier like he tied it down
The way you would moor a boat to a harb to appear
He's doing nautical knots is what i'm saying. He wasn't just all doing it all loosey goosey like he had it dialed in
But he unmoored it did get unmoored and it did float away. They know that
He jumped in they're assuming that because his body was found in the river the question still is where is sofia
People are going whoa, whoa, whoa if she jumped in the water after him
How did she make the phone calls like did she make those seven phone calls and then jump in the water to find him?
Please they're like we don't know
And and the mother was like there's no she wasn't a confident swimmer
There is no way she would jump into the water in the pitch dark
Trying to find someone who's a better swimmer than her she he she go the mother says she just want to do that
Two other men died
In the harbor that day two other men died just from because it's like memorial day weekend
So two other men died in boating accidents that they fell off their boats got drunk got hit by a boat whatever
Both of those bodies have been found as well
So we can we can presume that four people fell into the water that weekend
Spencer, sofia, and then these two other men three of those people were found which is giving more credence to the
Theory that she did not fall into the water because if she had fallen into the water she would have been found by now
So people are thinking maybe she was stuck on that island and another boat came and kidnapped her
Maybe she was stuck on that island and someone killed her serial killer or just a regular killer
maybe they were being followed the whole time
And someone untied the boat and there was a struggle and they throw Spencer in the water and they throw her on a boat and stuff like that
Those are all very very chilling
Things and I don't want to make light of this young woman's disappearance or the tragedy of spencer's death or anything like that
I'm not trying to do that at all. However, there is an interesting
paranormal note to all of this
Like I said, it's a renowned place
For ghost hunting, but not just that it's not just that
This place was hated by the people who worked there. So from it was built in 1909
And that was when the big pier was built and then they were building the lighthouse on top of it
And then in 1987 the coast guard went fully automated. So now it's just a computer system that runs it
Now the legend goes that at some point in the early times of this lighthouse in operation
There was a guy some people say his name is john some people say his name is Ernie really depends on who you're talking to so
Not super credible to begin with here, but some interesting
Similarities so there was this guy his wife cheated on him
So he jumped he climbed to the top of the lighthouse one night and jumped off and just
All over the rocks
And at that point people were like well, we got to get a new lighthouse keeper
So they send someone else there, but what happens is lighthouse keepers who are working there
Keep complaining about doors getting unlocked
Of bed sheets kind of flying off their bed
You'd make a cup make a cup of tea it fall down
Normal poltergeist stuff stuff that is quite annoying
So, you know, you can deal with it. You can you know, you wake up you wake up and your bedroom door is open
Which has happened to me quite a few times. It's because the wind is blowing through my apartment
It's still creepy like when I wake up. I know why my bedroom door got pushed open. It's still very unsettling
Imagine that on a rock in the middle of a stormy night and you're the only person in a spooky spooky lighthouse
How much more terrifying that would be
But this ghost also had another trick up its sleeve
What would happen was people who would be working in the lighthouse
Would go to leave and their boat would be floating in the harbor
No matter how hard they tied these boats down
Sometimes they'd get untied and float away
Super creepy detail
I remember when I was because I had looked at the Sophia stuff
I was researching that and then I started researching the haunted past of this thing
And just as like they're like the ghost does this the ghost does this the ghost unties boats the ghost does this and I was like, what?
So this ghost is known for untying boats
made by
Like nautical knots again. They're not just doing a little like cheap shoelace knots. They know how to tie a boat down
They go out their boat is floating away. They have to call for help
That coupled with the fact that this ghost
killed himself over
his wife cheating on him
And you have this spirit sitting there in the night
And a young man and a young woman show up at a pier
A young woman who and I'm not I'm not trying to cast any judgments on this person
But you have a woman and a man on a pier that's haunted by a ghost who killed himself because his wife left him
And this woman and this man on this pier used to be lovers
But she left him for her ex-boyfriend. She got back together with her ex-boyfriend
It's like this paranormal psychic pot
Just bubbling forward as you have this perfect storm of elements at 2 a.m
on this pitch black island
Is is Sophia somehow still there?
And again, this sounds totally insensitive, but is Sophia somehow still there?
Will they not find her?
Has she been
We talked about other dimensions portals in just the last segment
Is she caught somewhere between
our reality
and Ernie's reality
Is she trapped there?
By a spirit so bent on vengeance
That when the perfect victim
Just dropped on his doorstep
All he had to do
Was untie a boat
And let it sail off
Spencer jumps in
She's frantically calling her mom
on Spencer's phone
In the dark
Two in the morning
No one's picking up
Why did she stop placing those phone calls?
Did the battery die?
And then she's trapped surrounded by pitch blackness
And the sound of the sea around her
Did something force her to stop making those calls?
Somebody or something
No evidence of what happened to her has been found
No clothing, no blood
Nothing
But there is one little piece of evidence to the story of Ernie
Before the lighthouse went automated back in 87
The last lighthouse keeper wrote in a log
Rock of slow torture
Ernie's domain
Hell on earth
May new London ledges light shine on forever because I'm through
I will watch it from afar while I'm drinking a brew
You got to wonder if that lighthouse keeper still lives out there
But now safely snuggled on the coastline of Connecticut
And if every so often he looks out and sees that lighthouse in the middle of the water
remembers the horrific experience calling it the rock of slow torture Ernie's domain
What did that lighthouse keeper see and experience to write those words into that log?
It wasn't his journal, it was the log for the lighthouse
What could he have possibly experienced over the course of his job there that would make him call it
Rock of slow torture
Who knows?
But the frightening thing is
Someone else may be experiencing that same thing
Right now
With no chance of escape
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
Twitter is @jsonocarpenter
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]