Ghosts ghouls and things that go bump in the night and maybe some zombies today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you're having a great day too. Happy Halloween
You can tell I didn't really plan this out super well because technically the Halloween episode should have come out yesterday
Because most people listen to it at day late
This is my first Halloween you can the show doesn't have the best planning if you haven't realized that
But we get you good stories. I think I think sometimes they may come off a little the timing may be a little off
But you know that you get them. I hope you enjoy them. So some quick bits of news
I just reminder starting November the week of November 5th. We're not gonna have any shows. I'm gonna take that week off
I'm gonna do in it to
Partially to relax and partially to catch up on my research the iceberg topics require the most research
So that's why I try to do just one a week. Secondly starting season 3
We are renaming the show to the Walking Dead Rabbit. It is just going to be a walking dead recap show
Because that's all that matters. I'm joking obviously, but
Man, you know Sunday is Rick's last episode and I know a lot of people still aren't into the Walking Dead a lot of people have kind of
Given up on it, but I don't know man. You know, I've been watching it for nine years now and I've been on that journey with Rick
It's really the only television show I watch I watch the Walking Dead every episode
I watch every episode of it's always sunny in Philadelphia and I'll catch the occasional episode
The Simpsons the new episodes of the Simpsons. That's it other than that. I'll watch movies
I don't watch any other television shows. So Simpsons all kind of catch up
I'll watch like three or four episodes in a row when I remember
But it's always sunny in Philadelphia and the Walking Dead are the shows that I every week I watch them
I make time to watch them I get my little whatever I'm doing like gonna eat dinner or sit back and drink a soda
I watch those shows so it sucks to know that Rick is leaving and I saw the trailer for the new
For his last episode and it doesn't look good for him
And it looks cool because it actually looks like you're going back through his past memories as he's reliving them
It looks it looks great. So hopefully he doesn't die and he comes back
You know at the end of the show, but it doesn't really look like that's gonna happen
But I but yeah, we're not gonna be a recap show
But I do really enjoy watching the Walking Dead and I think you guys would too I had given another chance
If you've stopped watching if you already watch it, then that's cool
So I wanted to talk about some ghost stories today
I wanted to talk about some story because that's the one thing I think the show
Lacks the most for me is the paranormal aspect
We do a lot of conspiracy stuff and then a medium amount of paranormal and very little true crime
And I'm kind of fine with that, but I'd like to bump up the ghost stories just a little bit
The problem is is that a lot of times
I'm I've become in my age a little more skeptical of ghost stories
I think they're really fun and they spook me out. I love talking about them
But I can't help I can't help sometimes sometimes accidentally
Disproving them now not all the time
But that's one of the reasons why I'll look up a ghost story and I'm like, oh, you know, that's really cool
And I look at it a little bit more and I'm like damn it. It's totally not true and this is why it's not true
So for this episode
I want to look at one of my favorite ghost stories that I'd heard over the years and it is the flight
It's flight 401. So some quick background to this. This was a real event
flight 401 was an airplane it would well obviously, but I mean it was a
I think it was like a what was it a lock jet. Is that even a thing?
Okay, so back in the night back in the year 1972 there was a Lockheed
aircraft that was flying a bunch of people
It had 163 people on it and and the crew and they're flying and the
They're going to land in Florida now
What happened was they went to switch on their landing gear and there's a sort of light that's supposed to come on
To say that the landing gear is locked and ready for use and the light didn't come on and it's nighttime and the guys are like
Hey, you know, we can't really get visual on whether or not this is down yet
And they're fiddling with it and they call ahead to the air traffic control and they said hey
We're gonna circle around a bit and try to figure out what's going on with their landing gear and air traffic control goes
Okay, hit 2000 feet circle around the Everglades
So they took apart the assembly and they're looking at the light to figure out why it's not on
They send a guy down into the cone
Because they do have down there a way to visually look out to see if the landing gear is down and at one point the captain's like
Hey, put on the autopilot while we're doing this
So they clip on the autopilot and something goes wrong either the autopilot gets knocked off accidentally or shuts itself off some sort of glitch
But the plane drops a little bit in elevation and then slowly
Begins to glide down into the dark swamp and it's happening so slowly the pilots don't realize that the plane's descending and eventually
It just crashes into the Everglades into the swamp
The pilots and the flight engineer they died two of the ten flight attendants died and
96 of 163 passengers died some of them died on impact and some of them died
Because they like they're just bleeding out or they took them to hospital and there's nothing they could do for him
What happened was they took pieces out of this flight flight 401 and
They didn't have a lot of lockheed jets back then this was kind of a newer jet
So they began putting the pieces into other lockheeds that were in
Service I had always heard this story as one of the most verifiable
Ghost encounters because basically the story went that every plane that had a piece of flight 401 in it
experienced ghostly sightings
one of the most notable ones was
There was a plane I believe it was going to Mexico City and this woman was this flight attendant
She wasn't just a woman, but she's flight attendant
She noticed something out of the corner of her eye and she looks in the oven because she saw something there
And she saw the face of a man staring at her from inside the oven and it totally freaked her out
But I don't know if the man said it while he was in the oven or then popped out of the oven
But anyways, it was the ghost of Don repo who was the one of the flight engineers on fly 401
He said there's going to be a fire on this plane and as that plane was descending into Mexico City
one of the engines burned out caught on fire and
supposedly the ghost of Don repo then went or the captain one of the two ghosts went into the cabin and talked the
Pilots down so they could land the plane extraordinary story these other planes that have these pieces also had sightings of it
Including like the vice president of eastern airlines, which is the company that ran the jet and the fleet of jets that have these parts
He said that he saw the ghost of Tom loft
Who was the captain?
Stewardesses said that they saw ghosts passengers said that they'd be sitting in their chair and they'd look over and there'd be a
Like a person in a aviation uniform
What is that the right word a captain uniform? I guess sitting next to him and they'd be like
Oh, hey, I didn't see you there and then they would disappear and like other people on the plane would be like
Oh my god, totally disappeared
And so the conspiracy was was that eastern airlines like in any flight where they recorded in their logbook
I saw a ghost eastern airlines remove the logbook and replaced it with a new one
And the flight where the captain was in the cockpit talking the other pilots down the voice recorder for that
disappeared
So eastern airlines was making a concerted effort to
Shut down this investigation all of this came out when an author wrote a nonfiction book called the ghost of flight 401
And his name was fuller john g fuller. So he writes this book and it became very popular
they made several movies about it and
It's been considered one of those cases that could have been the most like
concrete way to prove the existence of ghost but
Eastern airlines they took all the parts out of all the plane like they cannibalized flight 401
And put the parts in these other planes and that's where the ghost was showing up
Well, they took all the parts out
And got rid of them because they were tired of the ghost stories
And so we were no longer able to verify this now
I remember reading about that story a long time ago and honestly I
Probably saw or at least heard of the movie as a child because it's an older movie
And it's kind of creepy because you're already on an airplane. You're already fairly trapped
And I was like this would be a good like halloween story
And so I started looking into it. I had a basic memory of it and then I had to kind of like track it down and stuff like that
and
There's been a lot of pushback on it in recent years that it's absolutely 100 fake 100 fake
And the pushback is is that
there was
another author who wrote a book about the history of eastern airlines and
Eastern airlines at the time they were so incensed the fact that this author was saying that there was a conspiracy to hush up ghosts
That they were going to sue him
They were actually going to sue him for defamation because they said it's completely foolish to think that one we would care about ghosts at all
and then two
Basically punished our employees for believing ghosts the eastern airlines launched their own internal
Investigation and began talking to people and everyone's like I never saw ghosts the book in the book the ghost of flight 401
All the names are changed so you can't track down the initial people he talked to
But eastern airline talked to pilots and all that stuff and they're like no I never saw a ghost. I read the book too. I heard about it
it's totally nonsense the wife of
captain loft
she tried suing fuller for uh
Invasion of privacy and things like that and that case got dismissed not because
It turns out the book was true
But because invasion of privacy really only works if the person's on a public figure
And you could argue that tom loft was a public figure. He was very well known. He was part of this accident
And so I'm reading all this stuff and I'm thinking okay
Well, maybe eastern airlines is just kind of covering like maybe they did cover it up
And now they have to cover their tracks that they covered it up
And so I'm doing this research and I was already kind of loot. I was like, oh man
You know, this is a story that I always liked and and there's some pretty pretty interesting pushback to it
But then I was reading another website and it put the nail in the coffin
They said there were no pieces salvaged from flight 401
None the plane on impact just got shredded and this website I was on it was called sceptoid because I'll look at the
The skeptical websites they really pop up at the top of the searches a lot of times
But I was going to tell the story initially and then once I found out that there was some controversy about it
I was like, well, let's see what the other site says
And they had an interesting point. They said one that's not common for
Items that suffer mass like a plane that suffers massive damage for anything to be salvageable out of it
And they said secondly least of all an oven like ovens are are fairly fragile things
So you're telling me that this plane crash that killed over 100 people or around 100 people
But the oven survived so perfectly you could take it out of that plane and then put it in another plane
And it would still cook it would still be operational
And I was like, yeah, I guess that makes sense. I guess that makes sense
So I mean I I'm leaning more I think that it's an interest in again the thing that trips you up with this stuff
And me especially is if the story is intriguing, it's more believable and it really shouldn't be that way
But it is if I had a bit money right now if there were ghosts from flight 401
If that really happened on other planes, I would say no, I don't think it happened
But I still think it's an intriguing story
And I would have well, actually here's my question if the ghost was on a plane
Wouldn't if the plane take off the ghost fall out of the plane like I still don't understand ghost physics
Like do the ghosts suffer inertia? Like if you know how you like you're on a plane and it kind of you kind of stumble sometimes
And it does something with the goat would that happen to a ghost?
I don't know still a creepy story
But I was a little disappointed because I was like, oh, yeah, I'm gonna talk about that on my show
But again, I like to present both sides. So there we go
Then the next two stories
You're like chasing that's a terrible way to have a Halloween episode
You just told us a spooky story and then you dismissed everything. Well
The next story we're gonna talk about
Is also ghost related
I believe it's true as in I believe this woman
Believes it's true
The flight 401 story I it could have been all completely made up and just in the author's head, but this story
I believe is 100 true that the woman believes it's true. So we're gonna go to
Britain now so hop in, you know, the carpenter copter is in the shop. I don't want to go flying right now. So let's take the
Let's take the rabbit rowboat and I know it's going to be a long journey
But I don't feel like flying after that last story. So we're in the rabbit rowboat
And we'll hire some dude. We'll hire a ghost to row us across the ocean
I assume everyone is when you're listening to the show, you're just in my neighborhood and you're like, dude, I'm in Lithuania
Well, you're in my neighborhood right now. So we're hopping in the
Rabbit rowboat and we have to go all the way around the tip of South America. I know it's poorly planned out trip
But in eventually we get to Britain and there we meet a young woman named amethyst realm
That is like a psychic name and a stripper name mixed together
Coincidentally, she is a psychic. So this woman was married and she's like, you know what? I need to try something else
This this this mortal man is not doing it for me anymore
And so she had sex with a ghost and she's like, hmm, that's hmm. Whoa, that was the best sex I've ever had
So she actually divorced her husband
And began hooking up with ghosts. Now you'd think Jason
I can understand someone being lucky enough to have sex with one ghost
She's hooked up with 15 to 20 ghosts. So she's getting around. I don't want to sludge shame
but um
15 to 20 ghosts
I mean, okay, let's let's I'm gonna be clear right now. She's just masturbating
That's all she's doing
She's masturbating and pretending a ghost is having sex with her and then she's saying there's a ghost
So by that metric I've had sex with a million ghosts, but that aside, she's masturbating and she's saying that
She's uh, she's being in ghosts. Now you're like, okay crazy woman. That's fine
But there's another twist to this story, of course
So she's been dating the same ghost for a while now and they went to australia actually, no, she met him in australia, I believe
and
He flew home with her in a jet
Not fly. Hey ghost on an airplane. I didn't even plan that
She flew home with him and they
According to her had sex in the bathroom now again
She just masturbated in the bathroom, but
She goes to the bathroom. She's got all hot and bothered. She goes in there. Her ghost lover comes in
There's a ghost watching from the oven. He's like, oh, yeah
so hot
So anyways
She bangs this ghost on airplane. They've been dating for nine months now
She's getting ready to marry the ghost. She's getting ready to marry him. I'm assuming it's a dude
So she's gonna marry this ghost and from what I saw the ghost didn't have a name
The ghost doesn't have a name from what I saw and I could have just missed it
But I've read several articles about this young woman. She's getting ready to marry this ghost and she had the quote
She's like it's not traditional. It's not like he got down on one knee because he doesn't have any
Why does he only matt does he only manifest from the the knees up?
If he only manifests from the knees up, does he stand the how tall is he?
Does he walk on his knees or does he float a good foot off the ground?
How does this work?
I'm glad that's my main question
Anyways, it's not a traditional marriage. He can't get down on his knee because he doesn't have one
And if you thought that lunacy wasn't enough
amethyst
Amethyst realm is planning to have
His baby
Yes, she believes in a thing called phantom pregnancy, which women have all the time where they get in pregnant
Ghosts
But they don't carry them to full term because they don't believe in them
But if she believes in them this ghost can get her pregnant
She can have a ghost baby the power of imagination
Is a wonderful thing and the power of sexual fantasies is great as well. Her friends and her family
They're like, oh, she's always been a little off, but we totally support her in anything she does and and that's fair
She's not hurting anybody if I had a friend who was trying to get knocked by a ghost
I'd probably be a little bit concerned, but if I knew all her life
She believed in ghosts and spirits and all that stuff and then she'd been telling me she was sleeping around with these ghost men
By the time she got to having a ghost baby, I probably would have become pretty in pretty calloused to her lunacy
She is planning on having this ghost baby now
I'm assuming because I've read stuff like this for so long
I'm never going to see this woman appear again in the newspaper
It would be interesting though to watch her like gain a bunch of weight
Just like those bridesmaids just like maybe she'll be wearing a tight dress and it gets
Tighter on her, but I'm assuming she's just simply going to put on a bunch of weight and then
Say a baby came out at some point
I think that's what's going to happen. She's just going to be eating donuts until she gets a bit of a belly
And then she's going to be like it's been nine months since I started eating jelly donuts
I just gave birth to this baby and she's going to hold air
And at that point everyone has to decide whether or not to just go along with it
Do you change a baby's ghost diapers? Does a baby ghost go to school?
Oh, does a baby ghost breastfeed? These are all interesting questions. Will the baby ghost
Have knees?
Will it be like Casper and just kind of be
Oh amethyst
You wacky wacky girl, uh, you know again
It's this is fairly harmless
The as long as she doesn't come to the conclusion that to be with her husband and her
Unborn child
Nonborn child however you want to put it is to become a ghost herself now. That's when obviously you intervene
but other than that she's just a
An interesting personality
Yeah, just yeah, does will she have a ghost umbilical cord?
There's a lot of questions I have about um the
The the um physics of a ghost in general, but the idea of a ghost baby
Where do you buy clothes for a ghost baby?
What type of toy dude that'd be creepy you like every doll you give it starts animating around
Okay, we're gonna go ahead and move on to the next story here because I'm just going to be discussing ghost babies
Probably for the rest of the night with people who would rather talk about anything else
So you're like Jason you told us about flight 401
And then you kind of debunked it and then you kind of said that it was creepy and you're kind of skeptical about that
So that's a that was a wash then you told us about a
ghost
Bangin chick and having giving birth to a ghost baby
And that's that so how are you gonna end your halloween episode jason? How are you going to?
To come back from such nonsense
Now i'm not i'm gonna double down. I'm gonna double down on my nonsense right now
I want to tell you
about a seriously
spooky story
to be fair
So there's a new group of paranormal
Investigators i'm not even going to be able to keep a straight face. There's a new group of paranormal investigators in town
They demand to be taken seriously because
They have proof a lot of proof actually of the afterlife now
What happened was this guy he just recently leased out or got a new place for his business
And they moved in they're just working there moving stuff in getting everything ready and they started to experience paranormal activity
I'm gonna quote this article here
Okay, so i'm gonna read this to you, but i'm gonna leave out a key portion of it
Lee says from the day they moved in and began to
blank
At the site he has experienced bangs moans repeated bumping and things coming right at me
According to leigh, so they moved into this place of business and from day one they're hearing
bangs and moans and
Things are bumping into them and things are coming right at them. Okay, so now i'm gonna read you the whole sentence
I was like this has to be a joke. I had found multiple articles on this unfortunately. It's true
This is the whole sentence studio owner lee
Says from the day they moved in and began to film porn movies at the site. He has experienced bangs
moans
Repeated bumping and things coming right at me
i.e.
Everything that happens at every porn set ever if i'm
A pornographer and i'm working late at my studio and i hear someone moaning in the next room
I'm going to assume someone's filming something if i'm getting bumped and things are coming right at me
Guys that's vivid. That's all porn studios ever but
okay
He's obviously talking about ghostly moans and ghostly things coming right at him fair enough still
They could have been anyways
So he says that all this stuff is going on and they're catching it on video
And he's been there late at night and hearing moans
He's hearing voices now
He's like we're catching voices on recording and you're like oh that's interesting and then he goes on to say that
It's from a spirit box, which if you don't know what a spirit box is it's basically a broken radio
It's a radio that constantly tunes itself. We talked about it on an earlier episode, but it's a radio that constantly tunes itself
It's like a high tech Ouija board. So
i'll say
Charlie charlie are you here and the radio will go
By toothpaste
Wal-Mart and i'll be like oh my god. He's buying toothpaste at wal-mart
So it's basically picking it's basically like bumblebee from the transformers movies. It picks up random transmissions and it's up to you to
Determine them. So if you sit a spirit box down and ask questions for an hour
You're going to get a couple hits just from random things just like sometimes
When I used to watch television more I'd flip through the station and you'd have I'd get five stations and the commercials would complete a sentence
Like you are going to go home now
And it's just because it's going to happen eventually
So anyways, he has a spirit box. He also says that he also gets straight up disembodied voices and stuff like that
But of course we need to see proof of that
And it's hard to say that someone's just not in the corner being like buy toothpaste at wal-mart and they're like, oh my god
We just picked it up. We just evp evp
Then he has stuff where atmospheric changes the taps turn on by themselves toilet flushed on floors people aren't on again
These are all
Things that happen just in general
But so you're like, okay a bunch of a guy has a haunted porn studio. So what he actually he's gotten together and he's formed the
Paranormal porn stars. This is a new ghost hunting group that is going to have
It's funny because the articles make it sound like they're going to have their own television show on amazon prime
But I found one article that made it look like they were
They it was them sharing the show with other ghost hunters
And they were all competing against each other
Well, I mean it's a marketing thing obviously he got some I mean incredibly attractive women
Incredibly attractive women to do this
I'm following them on twitter. I'm sure that
They're either completely making it up and it's a good marketing gimmick for them or they're experiencing things that they absolutely believe that are
Happening I'm skeptical just because I haven't seen it myself
But if I went out to their porn studio and and saw this stuff
I'm not so skeptical that I'm going to be like no no no that's faulty wiring or stuff like that
And if I don't have amazon prime
But if this show comes out and they're giving compelling evidence then I'll be like, hey, you know, it's true because I want this that's the thing
As opposed to most skeptics. I want this stuff to be true. I don't find any pleasure necessarily
I find I think it's fun to decode a puzzle
And to look at something and go that's why that probably happened
But I would rather it be
That there was a ghost on flight 401. I'd rather it be that a woman is sleeping around with ghosts
Well, she's just masturbating but again
And then I would rather believe that these super hot porn stars are actually walking around in the dark and picking up proof of life after death
So I wish them the best. I wish these guys the best
But again, I think it's an amazing publicity stunt, especially around october
So we'll see I hope they have fun and they do their thing and if it's a publicity stunt then
Hopefully that works out for them. Let's let's see some proof. Let's let's let's get some actual proof
And you know what it would be hilarious if after
decades of professional ghost hunters hunting for ghosts
These this porn company captures indisputable proof that ghosts exist
Like what if the ghosts do
They're just like they've the whole time they're just rattling chains and they see those hot chicks
And they're like, you know what we're gonna prove ourselves right now and they walk out of a room
And they're like we're ghosts laugh after death. I mean I used to be an airline pilot
That would be amazing
All of these all of this time and money put into these
Quote-unquote legitimate ghost hunting groups and these guys
Actually find proof of them. So it would be yeah, I would like to see this group
I think it would be hilarious so they actually could show up a bunch of these other paranormal groups
But again, you know, it's probably just so much people running around in the dark
With catching orbs, which I have no an orbs just dust give me
Give me a disembodied ghost or something
moving something around on screen
Or, you know, really anything that can't be denied by a normal person skeptics will go out of their way to deny stuff
Most normal people will just watch something and go, oh, you know, that's quite puzzling
So give us something if you give me something like that then I'm on board with the paranormal porn stars
And you know
You guys might just I'd be kind of cool
Maybe dump the porn star part and just become paranormal investigators that might be a a cool vocation for all of you
But dead rabbit radio wishes you the best of luck. Well, that is our halloween episode
I'm gonna maybe have some spooky music going on here
And I did promise you zombies at the end of this episode. However, we're running a little bit long
So I'm taking the zombies out the zombies will be on our season finale, which will be our friday episode
And I hope you enjoy it dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
Twitter is @jasonocarpenter
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a happy halloween guys
You
[MUSIC]