Are humans breeding with aliens to create a new race?
And the battle of the sexes heats up today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason
Carpenter, having a great day. I hope you're having a great day. You know, it's funny,
I'm a big stats guy. As far as kind of looking at the stats of Project Simonvolve that I don't
care about like statistics in general, but this is how I was back when I was doing music.
This is kind of how I've approached everything. I like to look at the stats. I like to look at
feedback. I like to look to know what people are responding to and what people aren't responding to.
And luckily with the podcast, I can see a ton of stats. I can see general, you know, countries
where people are visiting from, which is great. We're hitting all sorts of countries, countries
I've never been to, are listening to the show. States, I see people in all these other states
listening to the show. I've actually stopped naming those states and countries because I've
noticed once I do, viewership drops off. I think they're afraid that I'm going to track them.
But one of the things that YouTube allows me to do, the podcast just shows me downloads,
but YouTube will actually show me views and how long people are watching the videos.
And it kind of gives me an average. And we've been hitting about a four minute average on
YouTube and I'm taking the 20 minute podcast, breaking it into maybe two, six to 10 minutes
stories. So a four minute average is actually really good. Now the last episode I uploaded
the YouTube video, our porn star psycho, our porn star psychic sexual vampires.
Within a couple hours, it was my most viewed video with 140 views right out the gate. It had only
been live for two hours. And I was like, Oh, this is great. You know, I hope this isn't too clickbaity.
And then when I dug into the numbers, it had only been watched an average of about 10 seconds
at that time. It's, it's leveled off now. Now it's up back to around maybe two or three minutes.
So it's still under averaged. One of my least people are watching the video on average, less
than they've watched the other videos. And it's, I think what people thought it was, obviously the
subscribers know what they're getting into. People are coming back to this channel know what
they're getting into. But people who are recommended the video, I think they probably think it's Dad
Porn. Now when I say Dad porn, I don't mean porn with dads in it, incest or anything like that.
I mean porn that is made for dads, which tends to be very, very, very soft core. You see it a lot
on Fox News. They'll do news reports like what is your daughter doing at spring break. And you
know for the next five minutes is Tucker Carlson. Bill O'Reilly was notorious for this when his
show was still on the air. But you'll have, you know, Sean Hannity or whatever doing their segment.
And in the, in your hearing him talk, but for about five minutes, you're seeing these
young, beautiful 20 year old women dancing around on the beach. And it's so the dad who can't watch
porn, you know, some of them can't watch porn because they may have a moral objection to it,
or their wife doesn't let them, or they have child blocks on their computers or whatever. And some of
them may like to look at a beautiful woman, but don't want to see a prolapsed anus. They don't
want to see like that hyper porn that's flowing around out there. They just want to look at a
beautiful woman dance around on the beach. And it's dad porn is basically porn that if someone
walked in on you while you're watching it, you could be like, I'm just watching the news, honey.
I'm just listening to this crazy YouTube guy talk about psychic vampires and porn.
Haha. And I think they clicked on it and they heard my voice. Hey, everybody, welcome to
Dead Rabbit Radio. And they just clicked off within 10 seconds. But I really like that story and
I've actually gotten some feedback on it already. You guys are really fast with responding to stuff.
And I appreciate that. It's one of the things that keeps me going. But no, sorry, guys, you're
just clicking in because there was a sexy woman picture there. That was it. It was just a sexy
woman picture and then me talking about vampires for the next 10 minutes. So now we're gonna,
we got two stories again today. The first one we're going to talk about is something I just
found out about yesterday. And I know what you're thinking, oh, Jason has a hard enough time researching
stuff that he's been preparing. Now he's going to talk about something he just discovered.
But I think it's interesting. So the battle of the sexes takes all shapes and forms. It can be a
professional battle. It can be like a mental battle. But it can also be a who can manipulate who the
most. And that's what we're going to be talking about now. So I'm sure you're all familiar with
the term sugar baby and sugar daddy. What a sugar daddy is, it's a wealthy man or a man of means
who doesn't want to really deal with the act of like courting a woman or going through all that
regular role at dating. He's just basically I will provide you finances and you will be my girl.
A sugar baby is the girl is the one who's like, you know, I'm just looking for a rich man to
take care of me. That term has been around forever. It's changed into now it's almost like a professional
agreement. So there's a website called seeking arrangements. And it is set up for wealthy men
who get verified somehow their their wealth is verified. They post their profiles on there and
then young women who simply want to be taken care of in exchange for companionship, really sex.
But it's not like a prostitute where it's on like a case by case basis. It's a lifestyle choice. So
some of these women get paid and they get they call it an allowance of up to $5,000 a week. A lot
of people are talking about, oh, yeah, you know, I get $5,000 a week from my man and I'm reading all
these I found out about that. Well, I knew about that. I didn't know so much about there's whole
forms dedicated on how to be a better sugar baby and how to find the right men who are going to take
care of you who aren't, you know, total losers, warning signs to look for abusing people who are
abusers and so on and so forth. That in and of itself is something that I again, in general,
knew about didn't know so much about the how tos. What I found out yesterday is there is an opposing
side. There is a Skeletor to the he man of sugar babies. And the Skeletor is what is called a salt
daddy. So instead of a sugar daddy, you're a salt daddy. And I saw that term yesterday and I was
like, okay, this is going to be interesting. This is going to be something interesting of research
at 11 o'clock a night. Assault daddy is a man who pretends he's wealthy and seeks out sugar babies
and manipulates them into sex. And I'm like, oh, you know, the thing is with life is there's a lot
of times predators and predators bump into each other. I would consider somebody who is basically
trying. I mean, you can be a kind of you could say the relationship is
consensual, but there's something slimy about it on all sides, the sugar daddy and the sugar baby.
And now you have this third third predator in the group, the sugar assault daddy, who will
basically go on these websites, contact these women and be like, oh, yeah, you know, the Maserati
is in the shop right now, but I can pick you up in my on the cord that I borrowed from my butler.
Let's go to this hotel and have sex. And of course, a lot of the sugar baby forums, they're
like, how do I keep an eye out for salt daddies? You know, I got salted last night. I went out
with this guy. This was one of the salt stories, by the way, to me, this is a massive amount of
money. But this is one of the salt stories. So this woman, she met this guy who said he was a sugar
daddy. And she brought him, he brought her champagne, but he pulled it out of his backpack and it was
an expensive champagne. Then when they met up again, this time he brought red wine, which he also
pulled out of his backpack. I don't do rich people not have backpacks. Is that a stereotype? I don't
know about that. But anyways, and she said it was kind of a cheap red wine. Now to me, cheap means
like $7 wine. So I don't know if it was that cheap. I don't know if it was like Thunderbird.
Then she takes he takes her out to a fancy restaurant in her words, a fancy restaurant. So
he obviously has some sort of money. I don't even buy. I have a backpack. That's the only thing I
can share in common with this kind of story. I don't have enough money to buy wine to give to
people. But he takes her out to a fancy restaurant. And then that night, he says, Hey, you know, I'm
going to give you a little bit of a less allowance this time because I bought you dinner. Now the
allowance, these three dates they went on each time he gave her $500 cash. That's that's insane.
And she's saying, Oh, he must not be rich because if he was rich, he wouldn't ask for a discount.
Well, maybe or maybe he maybe you ate $400 worth of food. I don't know. The whole thing seems super
weird for me. Now when I think of assault daddy reading this, the definition that I got were
people who are actually like poor, not like just not as rich. Like maybe the guy said he made a,
you know, a million and it turns out he only made like $800,000. The shocker.
That's that's the tragedy of it all. I was thinking more of somebody like me who was pretending that
he was an astronaut, but I'm still in moon rocks for millions of dollars a gram. So I did find assault
daddy like that on the on seeing this is the opposing side, I found a website where a guy teaches
you how to be a assault daddy. And his his tips were that you have to make it believable. So you
say that you're worth a million dollars and you make about 300,000 a year. You know, he goes,
that's believable. If you say you're a multimillionaire, it's harder to prove. He went and he researched
up names of what a rich person's name would be like. And he settled on the name Donovan Chase,
which sure, I guess it does sound like a rich person, but it sounds more like a rich person
from a romance novel. But he's saying it worked for him. And he goes on with this website. He's like,
you know, what I did was I created this Tinder profile and not Tinder, he went on seeking
arrangements, you know, went on that website and created a professional profile showing how much
money he had. And then he goes, I would see women in my area on Tinder and they wouldn't give me
the time of day. And then I would see them on seeking arrangement and they'd be all over me
because now they've perceived me as someone of value, someone who had money that can give them
something. And so he goes, you know, I used to have all of my stats and all of my phrases that
I used on seeking arrangements on this website. But what happened was this website got so popular
that all the women read it. So they knew exactly what to look for. So I put that in another article
called Salt Daddy 102. This article with Salt Daddy 101, like introduction to Salt Daddy.
So of course, at this point, I'm curious, I click on the link. It's not another website. He's selling
a book on how to be a salt daddy for $89. Now he's a sugar baby. Now he's ripping me off.
I'm gonna pay $89 for a book on how to be a salt daddy. Here, page one, chapter one, why?
In the book, just lie about stuff that you think people will believe. And the beauty of the internet
is, is that if the lies don't work, you shut down the profile, open up a new one with a new lie.
I don't have to pay $89 to know how to deceive people. Wait, no backup. I don't want to pay $89
simply to deceive people. And I'll bet you anything. If anyone buys that book, that book is full of
the most useless knowledge. And I bet you he's trying to sell other products around the way.
I hate it when people manipulate people and I hate it when people rip people off. I mean,
it's just predators versus predators versus predators. And prey gets caught up in the net
sometimes. Don't pay $89 for a book telling you how to lie. Ridiculous. Although I do think the
term salt daddy is still pretty, pretty funny. But I don't recommend becoming a salt daddy yourself.
I don't really recommend becoming a salt daddy. Oh, and there's weird, there's a war between the
sugar babies too. Some sugar babies are like, you need to have an allowance of $5,000 a week.
Like that has to be agreed to upfront. And other sugar babies are like, I don't need an allowance
as long as I'm taking care of like if I'm with a rich man, he's flying me around the world.
And he buys me stuff that I want. The fact that he's not giving me cash every Friday doesn't
matter. And there was like a war on the forum and they're like, you don't know how to be a sugar
baby. I'm just looking for comfort. And I mean, you can meet somebody and it get get a genuine
relationship out of it. That actually would be a really interesting romcom where it's like a salt
daddy tricks, I guess I'd probably just be called rape by deception. I don't think that would be a
good romcom. Never mind. Let's move on to the next story. So the next story is part of our
sex, spiracy week, our week of sexual conspiracies. This one's a little different,
because this one has absolutely no proof to back up any of the claims. It's all just people
saying stuff. And like all the other conspiracies on this show that are rigorously tested and
scientifically proven, the first story, first part of it is a little sad. But the second part is going
to make you chuckle. So I think it bounces out pretty well. There's this woman. She was a she
worked for the US Air Force, you know, generally give military personnel more credibility.
Maybe not this time. She works for the she worked for the US Air Force. And back when she was 25,
she was just going about life. She had a little kid. She was working as a radar technician officer,
radar tracking officer, I guess I should say the exact job she had details matter in these
types of stories. And then one day a reptile, a reptilian alien shows up,
kidnaps her, takes her to the moon because they need slave labor up there. And what better way
to get slave labor than to kidnap a 25 year old American woman. I mean, forget that there's people
all over the world and continents that have no tracking software when people go missing.
Can nap her, take her to the moon. She works all day moving boxes in this factory, they're building
this military installation on the dark side of the moon. And then at night, the alien bangs her
and invites his alien reptilian friends to bang her too. So there's like this gang bang going on.
And then the oddest, the oddest detail of that whole thing is there's a bunch of grays standing
on the corner watching them. So I imagine like the grays are just like cuckolds to the reptilians,
like the reptilians are like these strong, virile creatures. And the grays are just like these
emaciated creatures like smoking cigarettes in the corner being like, yeah, take it hard.
Yeah, give her that a, give her that big juicy egg. That might have gone a little too far. But
anyways, and she says this happened like eight to 10 times and she didn't remember any of it,
but she had some missing time in her life. And she got hypnotized and through hypnosis,
this was all revealed to her. Now, it goes without saying that didn't happen. There's
multiple things wrong with that story. One, I don't even have to go through them. The whole
thing is ridiculous. What's sad is the woman either did suffer some sort of sexual assault,
and this was her only way of coping with it, or she's just nuts. Like I think this story,
they couldn't find really any incident that mirrored this type of thing in her past. But the
whole thing is just weird. And I read that and I was like, okay, that woman's just a little nuts and
it's just kind of sad. We do cover a lot of people on this show that seem to have some sort of mental
illness, your host, most likely included. And from there, so that woman was like, oh man,
I can't believe it happened. I had sex with all those aliens. I feel so ashamed. Then I found a
group of women who are the opposite and they're like, sex with aliens is the best. Reptilian sex
is the most savage, primal, fierce sex you can ever have. And I feel bad for women who don't have it.
And I gave birth to a hybrid baby. There's a whole group of these women who believe that not
only have they had consensual sex with the reptilian species, they've actually gone through
pregnancy and delivered birth. These women actually do have proof, proof of this. They have pictures
of their children, hand drawn pictures of their children. They have all sketched out drawings
of what they believe their hybrid children look like. And they look like precious moments pictures.
They're just normal kids with like eyes that are really big. Some of them have like little
reptilian foreheads, but they're like women, you have to bang these aliens. It feels so good.
I'm reading this article and sometimes the women say they'll actually be brought up to the spaceship
for some hot, sexy, scaly sex. And they said, one woman says, one time she just saw a light come
through the sky and her ovaries began to ache. And she's like, that's it. They just beamed an egg out
of me and I have another hybrid baby. So you're going, oh, Jason, great. You're just picking on
people with mental disorders. No, not really. Well, kind of. But what I think is interesting about
this is there is a gen. It's not just these women, these two women featured in this article. Aside
from the woman who got taken to the moon, these two women are having hybrid children. It's not
just them. There is a forum. There is a website called hybrid children online. And this is a
website specifically for women who have hybrid children or who have hybrid children and don't
know it. See, you can take this workshop. You can take this workshop that this very slick,
admittedly slick website has where you can learn to connect with your hybrid child. You can remember
your galactic heritage and soul mission. You can rekindle your own inner child and you can cultivate
your extrasensory abilities. So basically pay me money and I'll teach you how to imagine stuff.
I'm looking through this and this website is creepy. So you have the hand drawn pictures,
which was weird enough because they're saying this is my own child. This is Bucky. And it's just a
drawing. This website goes the extra step. They've taken photos of normal children and photoshopped
their eyes to be huge. It's really disturbing and it gives it this kind of anti uncanny valley thing
where it makes them look less human. It's not that uncanny valley thing where they look too human.
So this package where you you can sign up for this thing and you'll get all these interactive videos
that'll help you telepathically communicate with your child. I mean at this point they're praying.
I may be making fun of them but they're praying on people who have mental illnesses. You can watch
these videos. They have you can access their Facebook group. You can be on these four these
group calls with each other. $444 for this program. So let's say that I have a mental illness and I
think that I have a hybrid child out there and this is a real mental illness I have and I'm
suffering with and I finally find people who agree with me. They will only agree with me and they
only help me out if I have $444 or to be fair two payments of $225. So you can save six bucks
if you just buy it in full but come on and they have that little trick where they go maybe you
have a hybrid child and don't even know it. So if you're lonely and you don't know why you don't
remember last Thursday night it's not because the wine it's because an alien abducted you had hot
passionate alien sex with you took out your baby and dropped you back off on earth. And people
believe this. People believe this. You know this the idea of humans breeding with aliens has been
around for a long time but I don't understand it with. I can't have sex with a dog but I can't
have a baby with a dog. A creature that evolved on another planet we wouldn't be able to breed with
and then you go okay maybe they came here first and were maybe they're there the progenitors of
our species. Again I think the most likely thing that aliens are from earth if the aliens exist
I don't think they're coming from the cosmos I think they're from either under the ocean or a
cave system or from another dimension which think about it they're based I just realized aliens are
salt daddies because think of this if and reptile shows up and the woman's like oh my god you're a
reptile and he's like yes I came from the star Cyrus or is it serious I can't even the aliens like
I'm serious Cyrus anyways I'm from a star a long way away and I came across this vast distance to
make hot animal passionate love to you and the woman's like oh my god she's all a flutter
and he takes her and he just ravishes her and then after that as he's putting back on his little
reptilian silver suit he's like see you later and he just walks into a cave by mount Adams like I
think they're probably telling these women that they're from the farthest reaches of space but
then it turns out like they're just like swimming underneath the Gulf of Mexico like they're basically
salt daddies because they can't be coming that from that far away doesn't make sense and if they did
why would they be banging these women these women are pretty hot actually if you look at the article
I wouldn't travel light years to have sex with them but aliens might actually be the ultimate salt
daddies the intergalactic salt daddies they're lying about it they don't have hyperdrives they have
like a submarine at tops a really fast submarine that might be able to hover outside the water
the women are like hey why aren't we on your UFO and he's like uh my thrusters in the shop I have
to borrow this RV from my butler so we're just gonna have sex in this and then they just slink
out the back and go into like some deep cave system and they're telling the graze all the
stories are like oh yeah dude she totally put out she let me get to the earth and the graze are
just jacking off in the corner listening to his amazing stories dead rabbit radio
dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
twitter is @jsonocarpenter you can hit us up there I'm sure you guys are going to be happy when this
experience week is over because I just can't get through any of these stories without going to
some sort of weird place but um we're just going to keep we we got a ton more stories for you sometimes
I'm worried about running out of content and then I both of these stories I came up with at the last
minute I had previous stuff to talk about I really didn't like it I recorded it hated it deleted it
and I really like this episode I think I think it I'm much happier with this episode so we will be
back tomorrow with another great episode with a couple more stories um dead rabbit radio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day
but I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys