Did a battle of the wits between two giants reshape the landscape of Ireland and Scotland?
And then we take a look at the conspiracy theory that the Black Plague wasn't a natural disease spread by fleas or rats.
It was actually a biological attack from aliens today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
I don't wanna sleep down, actually I'm a walkthrough down.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I am your host, Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We've got a lot of interesting stuff to cover. Do I have any notes?
I'm trying to think. If I have anything I need to talk about.
No, I think we're good.
So let's go ahead and get started with the first story here now.
So the first story we're gonna talk about, we're going back to the land of fables.
Now this is an interesting one. We covered Taley Poe and we covered Humpty Dumpty.
This one is a little more...it's kinda weird because it's...
Okay, so let's just go ahead and jump into it.
So in Ireland they had a character, a guy named Finn Mackool.
Finn Mackool. Now he was basically their version of Thor, their version of King Arthur.
He was this mythical hunter, warrior, leader type guy who was...
He was taken fairly seriously in their literature, in their myths.
And at some point someone thought, "Hmm, let's retcon this guy."
Like they took this dude, imagine if they took Thor throughout Norse mythology
and not only turned him into a comic book character, but turned him into a fat slob and a coward.
I don't know who came up with this version of the Finn Mackool story,
but I had never heard of the guy until I read this and then I thought that this was it.
Looked into it and he's like a national hero.
He is their icon in Ireland, or at least he used to be.
So someone really didn't like Finn when they came up with this story.
So in this version of the story, Finn Mackool is not a great warrior, or a great leader,
or a mythical hunter or anything like that.
He's a giant, so he has that going for him. He's much bigger, he's huge in this story.
So Finn Mackool one day is kind of messing around at this place called the Giants' Causeway.
So around Scotland and Ireland there's these hexagonal giant poles.
And it's because of Magama bubbling up. It looks really weird.
It looks man-made and it's one of the reasons why people think that trees don't exist,
because they don't look... they're hexagons.
Like people go, "How can you see hexagons in nature?" You know, honeycombs.
You do see them, but Scotland and Ireland both have these hexagons.
And so the story was there used to be a bridge leading from Ireland to Scotland.
It was called the Giants' Causeway. The Giants themselves
placed these stones so they can get back and forth.
Well anyways, so Finn Mackool's messing around and he decides to challenge a giant in Scotland.
The giant in Scotland, his name is Benadonnor, also known as the Red Man.
Now he may be a mythical hero to the Scottish people as well, but I didn't look into that.
So he's sitting there, this great hero of Ireland is a giant in this version,
and he starts yelling across the sea, "Hey Benadonnor! Benadonnor! Let's fight!
I'm tired of all this fight stuff that we've been arguing about that Jason didn't research.
Come and get me!"
So Benadonnor, he's just hanging out in Scotland, drinking a couple pints.
He's a giant, so he'd be drinking a couple gallons.
He's like, "Oh man, okay, let's rumble. Let's do this."
Finn Mackool is standing on the Irish side of the bridge, and he starts seeing Benadonnor walk towards him.
And first off, just how it normally is, he's so tiny in the distance that Finn Mackool's like,
"Oh, I can break this dude."
But as Benadonnor gets closer and closer and closer, he realizes that he picked a fight with the wrong giant.
I don't know if they've never met before, but he should have figured just the word giant in his name.
He's equal size, but this guy was a giant among giants.
So Finn Mackool gets super scared and runs home.
Again, national hero reduced to a loonatoon character in this legend.
He ran all the way back home, and his wife is there.
His wife's name is Unog.
And he's like, "Unog, Unog, this dude's coming. He's totally gonna stop me.
I picked a fight with the wrong guy. You have to help me."
And she's like, "Yes, dear. I will help you.
Um, go hide in the baby's room.
Uh, dress put on this baby uniform. Baby uniform. I just happened to have sitting around."
He should be creeped out. We should be creeped out that she has baby clothes that fit her husband.
But if you want to know if your marriage is in trouble, ask your wife to disguise you as a baby from a guy who's going to beat you up.
If she doesn't leave you on the spot, she's a keeper.
So anyways, Finn Mackool dresses up like a baby.
This mythical lawyer, great hero, dresses up as a baby in heights.
Benidonor does come into the house, and Unog realizes, "Mmm, he's all giant.
Maybe he could satisfy my, my wanting needs."
But she puts that aside because she has a duty to her husband.
She invites him in, and she goes, "Oh, yes. Okay, I'm just doing the voice, 'cause that's gonna get old."
She goes, "Yes." I'll do a little bit later. She goes, "Yes."
She goes, "My husband's gone, but may I show you around our humble abode, our giant house?"
Giant Benidonor's like, "Yeah, sure. I'm gonna have to duck to get in all these doors, 'cause I'm so much bigger."
"Hehehe, I bet you are!"
So she starts to play a battle of the wits with this dude.
She goes, "Hey, look. This is my husband's. I don't think they've met before, 'cause otherwise, both of them are total idiots."
But she goes, "Look, it's my husband's spear."
And she points to a massive redwood sitting in the corner of the house, and he's like, "Mmm, if he's throwing that around, he must be really, really strong."
And here is his shield, and it's just like, takes up half the house.
Again, why does she happen to have this stuff sitting around?
But anyways, the story, I guess I'm pointing out logic in the wrong parts. There's giants existing in this world.
He's like, "Hmm, I couldn't lift that shield."
And then she goes, "Hey, are you hungry? You look like a big strapping man. You look like you could hold a giant woman down and please her."
He's like, "What?" And she's like, "Nothing, nothing."
"Are you hungry?" He's like, "Yeah, I am a little hungry."
She goes, "Let me get you what Finn McCool normally eats."
Now, this is where it becomes, basically, Tom and Jerry.
She gets two slices of bread and puts a hot iron riddle in between the slices of bread and goes, "This is what my husband normally eats. He eats this all the time."
And when Benidotter bites into it, all his teeth fall out.
He's like, "Ah, only a true warrior could eat it."
I mean, come on, dude. At that point, if you ever bit into something and your teeth fell out, you're going to check it and be like, "Hey, why'd you put metal in this sandwich?"
Like, I mean, you can call their bluff, dude. You don't have to then go on with the rest of her trials.
But he does. Because then she goes, "Oh, that sandwich, that's probably not gonna fill you up. Let's give you this piece of steak."
And it was really a slice of steak with a board of wood with nail sticking out of it, nail to the bottom of the steak.
Really, Benidotter, you're gonna eat that. You can obviously see that there's wood attached to it, but he does, 'cause he's an idiot.
Breaks out the rest of any teeth he had remaining are broken out. Plus, now he's like, bleeding from the mouth.
He's still walking around the house, though. Then she goes, "I have to go feed the baby. You want to come see the baby?"
And he's like, "Yeah, now this is the ultimate bluff, because the baby is her husband."
And I'm assuming when she's gonna feed him, let's make it, you know, I'm gonna breastfeed him.
Okay, that might be a little gross, but anyways, they both go into the baby's room and there is Finn McCool, dressed up as a baby,
and Benidotter's like, "Oh, if the baby's this big, then Finn McCool must be a giant."
And no point does he realize that baby is too big to come out of that woman. Absolutely not. There is no way that is possible for a giant woman to give birth to a baby bigger than herself.
Never even considers the fact. However, he is in intense pain from having his teeth knocked out.
So, she then has one final test for him. She goes, "Want to play catch?" And after everything that's happened, he goes, "Yeah, yeah, let's go on and play catch."
Also, do you have any Vicodin? Because I'm in extreme pain right now. No, no, I don't have that. Let's go play catch.
And she goes out there and there are these massive boulders in their backyard and she goes, "That's what Finn plays catch with. Go ahead and pick one up and throw it to me. I'll catch it."
Benidotter's like, "Okay." He looked a little heavy. Are you sure you can catch it? She's like, "Oh, yeah, I play catch all the time."
He then picks the boulder up, holds it above his head to throw it and drops it on his skull and fractures his neck.
So, at this point, he's like, "There is no way I'm fighting a guy that's this big." And he starts to go back to Scotland.
Now, Finn McCool being the great hero that he is, as he sees Benidotter walk away, he lets him get a couple miles away and then he jumps out of the baby's crib and starts like trash talking him,
eventually pulling up pieces of the earth and throwing it at him. One of the big chunks he pulled out made a locknig,
which I actually think might be Loch Ness, but I'm not entirely for sure on that. And that piece of earth missed Benidotter, landed in the ocean, became the Isle of Man.
And then once Benidotter got across the giant causeway, Finn goes, "You know what? I'm never going to make that mistake again." He destroyed the rest of the bridge.
So that's the legend. I think it's interesting because, one, it would be the equivalent, I think the best equivalent is,
if you had the, we have the story of George Washington, who is a real person, but fairly mythical at this point.
He's a real person, but he's such a national hero, he's such a symbol. If someone wrote a story where he pretended to be a baby to hide from the King of England,
it's just such an emasculating legend. It's such a bizarre story to tell.
And in the end, the dude's a total punk because not only does he wait till the guy leaves to then challenge him to a fight again and start throwing stuff at him,
he then destroys the ability for that guy to ever come back. I think something else happened in this story. I think that as he was in the baby's crib,
Oonga, he heard from the other room, Oonga's like, "Ooh, my husband can always satisfy me. Here, let me spread my legs."
And then she really tricked him into wearing a blindfold and he's just humping a hallway and he's like, "You can't feel anything.
There's nothing here." And she's like, "Oh, are you in yet?" And he's like, "Uh, yeah, yeah, don't say that. That's very insulting."
I think that happened as well. I think, technically, Finn McCool got cucked by his own house.
You got a stranger over there, being in your house, thinking it's your wife, that has to gotta mess you up a little bit.
And then he's like, "I'm gonna destroy a bridge if that sequence of events happened to me as well."
Okay, so let's go ahead and move on to our next story. Now, our next story was actually a request. It was a requested story.
It's On the Conspiracy Iceberg. It's always the best of both worlds when those two things line up.
This is from Sage Says on YouTube. Sage says, "Requested this story."
So, on the Conspiracy Iceberg, the phrase is, "Aliens cause the black plague."
It's an interesting idea, and there's some interesting backing to it. But before we get into that, let's set the stage.
It's the mid-1300s. People are just milling about in Europe, doing villager stuff.
Walking around, cutting wheat, making bread, eating bread, sleeping. The normal life cycle of a peasant.
But the black plague didn't just affect peasants. It affected whole population centers. But you had these people going about their normal, dark ages day.
And they look up. Like they always do. They're bored. There's no television, so if you want to see something, you just look up.
Go, "Hey, birds." I wonder if that bird, Ross, is gonna get together with that bird, Rachel.
I don't know. I guess I'll have to tune in next week to find out.
But this day they look up. There is a long, cigar-shaped object in the sky.
What? What is that? Hey, peasant guy with a peasant name. Look.
What? Hey, run and tell the town crier! I can already see it. Oh my god, everyone's coming out of their houses and they're watching this object float in the sky.
What?
[SPLAT]
A white cloud begins to emit from the back of this cigar-shaped vehicle.
When no one starts coughing, it's not this immediate like, "Bleugh, bleugh, bleugh, oh look at my body, I have black plague!"
It's just a mist. Pssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss
That's just a mist. Pssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss
The plague came from Asia to Europe. People didn't have any real immunity to it. It came over either with rats or new evidence is saying it came over with fleas and lice.
But it decimated, more than decimated, the European population.
Generally, it's accepted that 30 to 60% of Europeans' population was killed off at this time, and it wasn't one particular thing.
And that's why some people lean towards the UFO thing. It wasn't like you had the plague and then it was over with.
You know, Ebola will pop up, it seems like, every year, but the plague would kill a bunch of people and then lay dormant for 5 to 10 years.
They'd have no problem with it and then it would pop up again and wipe out another 100, 200,000 people.
This went on for about 400 years. It was quite the sight to bleed, get it?
So, the point is, is that this wasn't like, it was a virus that would come and go.
What's interesting, some of the things they can't really figure out about the bubonic plague, so you have the bubonic plague, which is generally caused by the fleas and the lice and the rats.
You get that and you get the bulbous, you get the big black bumps on your body, and it's super painful, and it has a pretty high kill rate.
But it's not super transmissible between humans. You have to get bit by something and then something else bites you.
Pneumonic plague, which also was around the same time, was different. That would cause you to throw up blood and you could give it to other people.
And they say most people who died during that time period, technically, the black plague is a catch-all term.
The bubonic plague was one part, a different disease, but if you had the pneumatic plague, not pneumatic like pistons, but you know what I mean?
Like, pneumonia version of the plague. You were dead and everyone around you was dead as well.
This plague is still around, this version of the plague, the breathable one, but it tends to strike in cold weather
when people are trapped in houses together, or you know, small contained areas, and they're breathing it in.
What was weird about what was going on in the Middle Ages was that the pneumatic plague, I'm just going to use a catch-all term plague,
because I'm pretty sure I'm not pronouncing that word right, but the plague, instead of being passed around in cold weather in contained conditions,
the plagues were striking during warm periods, spring and summer, and you would have areas that were completely isolated,
for the most part, from other city centers, and they were getting it.
So you'd have places where they weren't interacting with nearby villages, and they were just getting wiped out during the summer.
And so scientists even now, they're like, "We don't know what the mechanism was for everything that was going on."
A lot of it was shoddy record keeping. The people keeping records were dying.
Plus, you know, they weren't writing anything down. Everything was wood carving.
You know how long it takes to carve wood as you're throwing up blood?
It didn't act like a normal disease.
And that's where the conspiracy theory started that aliens caused the black plague.
The scenario that I gave you with the cigar-shaped UFOs, that was put forth by an author named John Franco,
or Juan Franco--no, it's John. I don't know. It's spelled with a G.
So, John Franco, degli esposti.
Sorry, sorry, sir. I know that's--I didn't even come close, but--
He's a UFOologist and author. He's written several books about UFOs.
Now, that was his--he said that in--between 1347 and 1350, these cigar-shaped crafts were spotted over the skies in Europe,
and released a mist onto these people.
I haven't been able to find any verification of that outside of his work,
and that is a second-hand quote because someone else was quoting him.
But here's the thing. You can find stuff about aliens caused the black plague in Italian.
I couldn't find--I mean, I'm sure if I kept looking I could probably find English versions of this stuff.
But the top search results are going to be in Italian.
Very, very, very well documented, I guess, sourced materials, but it's all in Italian.
So, I was running through a translator, so there's a little bit of translation issue.
But I don't know if this is just an Italian conspiracy theory, if it hasn't really caught on in America.
But, John Franco--whatever he pronounced his name--he's written tons of books about this.
They're all in Italian, and I found multiple websites that are in Italian
focusing specifically on aliens in the black plague and aliens in the Middle Ages.
So, it was weird not to find that stuff in English, really,
but I guess it is a more obscure conspiracy theory.
That's why it's on the conspiracy theory iceberg.
So, these are the reasons why it may make sense.
The plague would pop up in areas that it shouldn't have, in times that it shouldn't have,
and it ended up abruptly.
So, you'd have a bunch of people get it and start dying, and then it would stop.
And then it would be another five, ten years, and then it would happen again.
Obviously, the big question is what would be the purpose of aliens doing this?
They had the ability to drop plagues on us from their ships.
Why would they just do it for, you know, a couple years, kill--oh, shit, it was 400 years,
and they did kill off, like, kill off, like, 40 million people.
But I mean, like, why wasn't it constant? Why was it just focused in Europe?
Why weren't they doing it worldwide if they were trying to do some sort of depopulation thing?
That would be the question. It could be a test.
It could be an accident where the ships don't mean to be leaking this exhaust, this chemical.
But those are questions that I think we can't answer right now.
Why? Why would they be doing it?
Let's assume for a second that they did do it.
And what's interesting is, again, going back to these Italian sources,
there are tons of sightings, recorded sightings of UFO objects in earlier, like, 600 AD forward.
And of course you go, "Well, Jason, yeah, there's that book in the Bible that talks about Ezekiel."
I'm talking about, like, UFO sightings that resulted in people getting just mashed.
'Cause, yeah, everyone can look up and see a UFO.
That's kind of lost its luster.
Let's look at the stories where it had pretty grim consequences for the people involved.
And again, this was, I was translating this from Italian, so I don't have some of the information got lost,
and that's my excuse. I did try verifying some of this even more.
In 1548, in a place called Thuringia, there was a globe of flame that appeared in the sky.
So you're thinking, "Oh, maybe it's a comet."
A lot of this stuff you'd think was like, comets or asteroids and stuff like that, or meteorites,
but the people in this area called Thuringia, a globe of flame goes, "Pfft!"
Meteorite, right? Just entering the orbit, blows up.
Coagulated blood shoots everywhere.
They said if they were covered in red goo that resembled coagulated blood,
which reminds, which makes me think of the Kentucky Meat Storm story.
Like, is it something coming from, is it some sort of event?
Either it is a natural event like a meteorite spraying blood everywhere, or it's a UFO type of thing.
And it's so funny because where I got that from, the article said,
"A globe of flame seemed to explode on Thuringia in 1548, dropping a substance similar to coagulated blood in the most total dismay of the people."
Well, no, duh, no one's gonna want to be like, "Oh, you know what I really need today? I need to be covered in blood."
"Pfft! Thank you!" Like, of course they're dismayed, their clothes are ruined, and they only had one set of clothes, they're peasants.
So, we have the coagulated blood falling on everybody.
Here's another event, and this was 8th Century Europe.
They couldn't get a specific place for this incident off of this website, but...
So, this story is 8th Century Europe, this next one we're gonna cover, and it's...
I couldn't get more specific than that, I think a lot of it was translation errors, but 8th Century...
And my incompetence, but 8th Century Europe.
People started reporting these creatures that control the skies in their ships.
They called them the "Silphie", and they saw them everywhere, so much that they gave them a name.
Like, it wasn't just like, "What's that?" They're like, "Oh, no, no, that's the Silphie, they're here every week, they're usually coming to town to buy milk."
But no, they would see these vehicles fly overhead.
Let me read you this quote.
[reads text]
[music]