Seven years ago a man who claimed he was abducted by aliens
Said that he knew the date that they would show themselves to all of humankind and that date was just passed into law
by the United States Congress and then we take a look at the theory of
Video games getting too smart for their own good. What happens when programmers are constantly crafting games?
24/7 all around the world
Is there a chance eventually one of them could become self-aware and make you their target today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a ton of stuff to cover first off
Let's bring in one of our supporters work give it up give it up to William Burdell's William Burdell's
Walking in he's drinking milk. I'm running out of stuff for you guys to do as you guys entered Dead Rabbit Central
He's drinking milk. Hopefully you're not lactose intolerant. William actually donated during my Thanksgiving live stream a very generous donation
So I appreciate that you're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode. You can't support the show financially
You know exactly what I'm gonna say. It's okay. Just help spread the word about the show that helps out tremendous
And it's fan art Friday. So take a look at this awesome fan art from Twitter
Twitter user named Slappy Sleepy Slappy Sleepy drew this I think actually I couldn't find this guy on Twitter
But I haven't my know it's Slappy Sleepy made this so awesome. Thank you so much Slappy Sleepy William
I'm gonna toss you a shovel in a bag of coal
Let's hop in the carpenter caboose
We're taking the train to our first story and our first story is actually something I touched on yesterday
So chica chica chica chica chica chica train is moving across the countryside yesterday
I told a story and I said I don't even know if it's true
I don't even know if my recollection of it was true because I couldn't find it anywhere online
Couldn't find any bookmarks for it
It was about a man who I said was in Malaysia who built a box to hide underneath in a woman's restroom
Well, I found it. I've actually found the story. So I wanted to go in a little more detail with this one
It's fairly short William go ahead. I see you are see you're already going to Malaysia. No, no, no turn left
We're headed to New York City. It was way off. I was just on the top of my head
I thought it took place in Malaysia chica chica chica chica. We're headed to New York City
It's February 13th 1992. It's one day before Valentine's Day. Everyone's looking for love
But Joseph Cornetta
31 year old resident of New York had something else in mind
He built a coffin sized box and took it into a woman's restroom at a place that he worked
He was the plumber so it kind of makes sense. That's a good cover story plumber's walking in the bathrooms
I mean they normally don't disappear
They normally don't walk in and then never walk out
but he built this coffin sized box wrapped it in brown wrapping paper and would go into the women's right it was there all
The time so now I have more information and kind of feel you and you're like Jason
I don't want you to fill me in the story was gross yesterday
He built this coffin sized box and it was there all the time and you have to step up on it to wash your hands
Or to look in the mirror every so often
He would go in when there is no one there and again that gets perfect cover as a plumber
It's almost like his whole life led up to this scheme. He builds this coffin sized box
He would go and he would hide in it and women would have to step on it to use the sink and he would look up their skirts
the way that his scheme
unraveled was that a woman saw a creepy guy go into the
Woman's restroom and she she reported it. She goes. That's weird. She sees this guy go in he never comes out
So she actually alerts security and a female security guard goes in there and she's looking around
She's like that is weird because this woman just saw this guy come in a while ago and he's never come out
It was a ghost to me who's a ghost plumber then she's like in the bathroom. She goes on might as well wash my hands
so she steps up on the platform and
She falls through it she falls on top of this guy now
It's coffin size so she didn't like plummet like 10 feet, but she fell on top of this guy
She jumps off of the platform and lifts it up apparently she she hulk
Apparently a wooden coffin can't hold her and she can also just pick it up
Yeah, and when she picked it up underneath it was Joseph Cornetta and he was charged with third-degree burglary
That's weird. I get maybe they didn't have voyeurism laws back then New York
They might not have them nowadays for all I know but that is a true story. I didn't dream it up
I did find it in a book of wacky news and I put something in the show notes
So you can look at it yourself if you're so inclined, but I wanted to go ahead and clear that one up William
I'm gonna toss you the keys to the dead rabbit durgible. We are headed out to I did not plan this story to fall on this date
It was supposed to be on yesterday's episode supposed to come out yesterday
We're touchy the keys of the dead rabbit durgible. We're headed to the United States Congress. This is not political
This is nothing to do with what happened recently at all, but we do have to go to Congress for this story
We're flying back to the United States Congress and after flying to the United States Congress
We have a little meeting set up like a table. That's all it's a folding table and a couple of chairs in the dead rabbit durgible
We're all sitting around it and I go okay guys. It's a bizarre story. That's going on
I got an email from Scott and he turned me on to the story. So I tip a little hat to Scott
I see him send to the table. Thank you very much for sending this my way
What's happened is?
Recently at the end of December Congress passed a 2.3 trillion dollar relief bill and in it this if you're not familiar with
American politics or American lawmaking
I don't know if other countries do this it's something that America does and every every stripe of the political divide
It hates this part, but you can have a bill that's for
Legislation a relief legislation, you know like helping businesses and things like that economy building and then you can just throw in a bill
You can be like oh, I have this bill that I wrote last summer that I know won't pass otherwise
So I'm gonna put it in this larger bill and you don't have time to read all 5,000 pages of the legislation
You just go oh my constituents want me to take care of this so hopefully there's nothing
Totally evil in this bill. They do it all the time
You'll see them pass a bill like a defense bill to fund the military and then there'll be like a bill to build a
fly fishing arena for 10 dudes in the middle of Alaska
It happens all the time this time though. It's pretty dope
All those other times it was a total scam and a ripoff shame on you politicians
But this time it's dope what happened was senator Marco Rubio from Florida
Drafted this bill called the Intelligence Authorization Act for fiscal year 2021 and this is what this says
This is groundbreaking stuff the Pentagon and the FBI have
180 days from the passage of the bill. This is this is not conspiracy theory
You can look at these links. These are all real. This is mainstream news
I'll have it in the show notes. You can Google it yourself and it'll pop up like CNN
C-Span military comm all this stuff the Pentagon and the FBI have
180 days from the passage of the bill and it's already passed it passed at the end of December to reveal what they know about
an identified aerial phenomenon a.k.a
anomalous aerial vehicles a.k.a
UFOs
From the passage of that bill
I think it was passed on like the 28th to the 29th of December the Pentagon and the FBI have to reveal
What they know now this bill requires a
Portion of it to be unclassified material and needs to be available to the public
However, because of the sensitive nature of the matter there is part of the bill also says you can't have a classified component that only like the armed services
Committees see in Congress, but the senators are here's the thing they go listen if something's going on
That's a threat to national security
Congress needs to know about it if it's something that's going on that's so beyond our capabilities
The elected representatives need to know about it. The military can't keep these secrets
Here's a couple portions of this bill
If you're like this in a this to hear you this isn't a policy wonk podcast
Let me read you this because this is the wording is very very important in this bill
Whether request this is one of the things they're requesting in this bill they want quote the identification of potential aerospace or
other threats posed by the unidentified aerial phenomenon to national security and an
Assessment of whether this unidentified aerial phenomenon activity may be attributed to one or more foreign adversaries
So it's not necessarily saying we want to know that a bunch of grays are invading
They're saying we want to know what you know
Does China have this technology does Russia have this technology does North Korea have this technology does?
Question mark have this technology another thing they're requesting is quote identification of any incidents or patterns
That indicate a potential adversary
May have achieved to break through aerospace capabilities that could put United States strategic or conventional forces at risk
unquote
So that goes back to that thing because all of the sightings of UFOs they all break the what we know is the laws of physics
so
Has an earthly adversary gained this technology and you're hiding it from us for whatever reason we need to know
That hundred and eighty days countdown started in December. It's going to put us somewhere in the beginning of July
When this report is due you know what's interesting about it like on the one hand I can see
Congress going we want to know about threats
To the nation we're elected representatives. We want to know what the threats are
Pentagon tell us what I find really odd about this is that the FBI is particularly called out
They do say other agencies that are adjacent to the Pentagon and
FBI need to comply to this as well, but those are the two that were named in the it's not even a request
This is law. They have to do this, but why the FBI?
You know obviously it makes you think of the X files, right because the FBI is
investigating aliens and ghosts and killbillies eating their own kids
Why like what are they doing doing with the UFO phenomenon?
Here's an interesting part of this bill what they're requesting from the FBI is quote
detailed analysis of the data of the FBI which was derived from investigations of
intrusions of unidentified aerial phenomenon data over restricted United States airspace
so apparently Mark Aruvio and other people in Congress know that the FBI as
Currently or in the recent past been looking into an identified aerial phenomenon
over the United States
Now we always know it's like the military right like that's a given the FBI is particularly called out
We want all the information you have about
Investigations because they know they're running them. We want that paperwork. We want to know what you know
So this had popped up in the news
About a week or two ago
I think it was towards the end of my break and I was gonna cover it
But Scott's email kind of made me ramp it up because Scott's email added another wrinkle to the case
Seven years ago. There was a reddit thread posted by a man with the account
Throw away alien now. He's not throwing away aliens
He's the accounts name that because he goes this is a first line of his post is throw away account
Because I'm afraid if you're not familiar with Reddit a throwaway account as you started up just for one thread
And then you get rid of it so no one can find out who you really are
He tells a story. He was first abducted when he was 12 years old back in 1987 and it's a really interesting read
It's odd because his account is very nonchalant even though at the beginning he states that he's afraid
It's very nonchalant the way he talks about it first off. He dispels a bunch of myths
He says there's no probing
That's everyone's first question right even if like if someone tells you that's why a lot of abductees don't come
Forward because a lot of people go as you get probed. We mean maybe they're not that blunt about it
But that's always the joke right he goes
I was abducting when I was 12 and I get abducted every couple years
Generally once they abduct you they keep abducting you and he goes even the word
Abduction's not the right thing. He goes you're invited onto the ship
And we've covered that a lot on this show where the aliens will be like
Do you want to come with us and people are like no in the aliens are like, okay, and they leave
And then you have the people who get abducted but they're like I lost time and you wonder at a certain point
Did they give permission and then they just got in too deep over their head?
He says you're not really abducted they ask you and then you go along but at that point then they just kind of keep showing up
Open that door once you're not gonna be able to close it
He says I've seen people cut open like put to sleep and cut open and they fiddle around with people
But then they sew him back up and the guy's fine
He goes the worst thing that he can recall really happening to him was them taking tissue samples
They take tissue samples off your lower back or your buttocks
Which would be interesting because that could be where the probing story comes from but he goes a lot of stuff
They do is very
Uninvasive is that a term not non-invasive? I think is the actual term
Fairly gentle. He says they would show him
Earth television shows and we're talking about great aliens what he's describing is great aliens and he also says this another thing
We've come across a lot on the show. He goes. They're not really gray
Like they are they're kind of a beige, but their skin that is a suit their bodies. That's a suit. They wear
It's a super tight
Space suit and we've come we've covered that a lot on this show. They're not little naked dudes walking around
It's a really really tight suit they're wearing he says they would show him television shows and they would just watch him
They would gauge his response to what he's watching Webster
He's like what this show sucks put back on different strokes for those shows even on in 1987
They're showing him go-bots. He's like what this sucks put back on transformers
He goes the aliens basically show no emotions
But two of them they would show sadness from time to time and then they would show irritation when you asked them questions
They hated it. They absolutely hated they had asked you questions non-stop as they're running these studies on you
But if you started asking them questions, they're totally done with them
They don't know one here at all. He also said that although they can beam and this is weird too because I've seen this so many times in
The stories we covered and I never even really questioned it. I didn't really think of it
There's so many times that a great aliens show up and they're beaming telepathic messages into some farmer's head
Do you want to eat some pancakes and the farmer says sure I'll eat some pancakes?
He says the great aliens can beam telepathic messages into your head, but they can't read your mind
You have to verbally answer them
That's weird because that happens all the time. I never thought of that before
So many times the people are talking and the aliens are using telepathy because the aliens can't read our minds
According to throw away alien he says there he goes you can never verbally talk to these guys
He goes there he described their languages sound and like
That's dummy song
It was like this weird
It's weird noise once there was a boy
He also compared it to like the sound of a trumpet
I'm not gonna do trumpet sound because I know some of you guys listen to this show while you're falling asleep
Interesting little tidbit to this he says that they actually love earth music two types of music in particular
I've always theorized do what aliens even be able to comprehend music if you went to an alien planet
Could you comprehend their music like would it make would you be able to tell it was a musical arrangement on another planet?
I've always been curious about that, but he goes aliens love
Bluegrass, bluegrass music.
Come on down and swamp, dam, dam, dam, dam, dam, dam, dam.
Actually don't know what bluegrass music sounds like,
but I assume it sounds like that.
Come on, I'm not gonna keep trying to do bluegrass music,
but imagine the word swamps in it a lot.
They also love the sound of this African instrument
called the Sheikir.
It's like a Gord, it's a percussion instrument.
So this Gord that has these like strings on it.
(makes a compression sound)
Come on down to the swamp right now.
I don't know what that instrument sounds like
either I gotta lift it up.
But I'm still busy reading about a man
hiding in a woman's restroom in a coffin.
Because I don't know, this is interesting
'cause he says their voices sound like a trumpet.
This would kind of make sense.
But he says their voices remind him of a trumpet
and it also sounds like (makes a compression sound)
like this hum thing.
So maybe a blend of the two.
As much as I talk trash about a gray aliens,
I will agree with him on this.
He said gray aliens hate jazz.
They despise jazz music.
But I can just imagine the aliens are like flipping through
earth television stations trying to find something
for this dude to watch and they come across like
PBS Jazz Hour.
(laughs)
They're like ships going out of control,
everyone's trying to hold their ears and pilot
an interstellar craft at the same time.
Hurry up, change it, change it.
They hate jazz, they hate jazz.
And they hate classical music.
I almost feel like I've had so much hate and anger
towards the grays and then this could bring us together.
'Cause I also despise classical music and jazz.
I feel like maybe they are my space brothers.
Maybe they can come on down and swamp with me
and listen to some bluegrass music.
He says they've been here for like 10, 20,000 years.
He says these monitors on this screen,
he said these monitors that they're looking at
would show him images of the past.
So he actually saw them.
This is really interesting note.
He said that I saw the aliens at the construction
of the pyramids.
He didn't say they were building them
because we have a lot of good theories
of how humans could build the pyramids.
So I think he could have easily just said
I saw the aliens build the pyramids.
And then you'd be like, oh,
you're chasing that support where you zone out
on the story, all these other claims.
Well, yeah, they hate jazz.
I hate jazz.
That makes sense.
He says that he saw them at the building of the pyramids,
not building them themselves.
So that was interesting detail.
Because again, he could have easily just said,
if he's making it up,
make up parts of the popular mythos.
He also said that he saw footage of this massive stone
building, like this giant stone tower,
somewhere in Europe 10,000 years ago.
And it would have been demolished in the meantime.
So the whole lost civilization thing,
that's a really cool visual story on that as well.
And it's interesting because he,
that's pretty much the end of it.
He kind of wraps it up with that.
And he's basically open to questions.
And then he has this original thread
and then at the bottom it says edit.
He's edited it at a certain point.
The edit was also seven years ago.
The last thing he wrote was no more questions.
They are not happy with me.
Sorry.
And the account has never been used since.
It's only been used on that one single thread.
It's never been used since.
He did answer someone's question and they were like,
what are the aliens think about nukes?
Do they want to stop war?
And he goes, no, they don't really care about nukes.
He goes, at least they never asked me about nukes.
He goes, at one point,
they did show me some footage of them abducting
some soldiers during World War I.
They did seem pretty curious about human wars.
They didn't really care about nukes.
A lot of times nuclear disarmament and environmental stuff.
Aliens are always trying to wanna clean up our environment
and stuff like that or disable our nukes.
Because they never even brought that up.
And this guy's been being abducted from 1987
to what, seven years ago, 2013.
That's a lot of time to be hanging out with gray aliens
and them never bringing up.
And he never mentioned the environmental thing as well.
So that was interesting.
So what does this have to do with Congress?
This Reddit thread that was set up seven years ago,
this account has not been used since,
he says in this post,
the gray aliens told me they were gonna make themselves
know into the world in July of 2021.
He goes, it's either,
he goes, it's kinda hard to understand them sometimes.
You know, with the constant humming in your ear.
He goes, they either said July 8th or July 18th, 2021.
But he says that's when the gray aliens
are gonna let everyone know they're here.
And so the reason why,
this thread has just been gathering dust
over the past seven years.
The reason why it's taking flight now, no pun intended.
The reason why it's in hyperspace now
is because July is six months after the passage of this bill.
Where the Pentagon and the FBI and any adjacent group
has to tell America and more secretive stuff
to the members of Congress,
but they have to reveal what they know about UFOs,
unidentified aerial vehicles.
So a bizarre coincidence?
Did this guy know this?
Are aliens such a master of reality
that they could see into the future and they go,
well, eventually, you know,
some dude in Florida is gonna write this bill
and he's gonna sneak it in during this relief package.
And we're just gonna tell this kid,
or is it possible that Marco Rubio is a gray alien?
No, I'm just joking.
Is it possible that there are aliens
behind this bill as well?
I guess that's just as ridiculous as saying Marco Rubio.
But you know what I mean?
Like maybe there are forces saying it's time.
Or actually maybe, there's a lot of maybes in this,
but maybe they know the aliens are coming in July
and this way it kind of gives everyone an out.
If the Congress announces,
hey, look it, we know that these things
are from out of this world.
And then a bunch of ships flow up and they're like,
hey, look it, we didn't lie to you.
We actually told you the truth.
It's the most likely scenario is
it's a super weird coincidence.
Like the rational scenario, super weird coincidence.
But a coincidence nonetheless.
And as Garrick once said, I believe in coincidences,
coincidences happen all the time.
I don't trust coincidences.
So we'll see what happens.
It will it be another date that just passes?
And that actually, this is interesting
'cause it won't be.
The Pentagon and the FBI have to reveal that information.
The information could be there is, it's all this.
It's all Chinese technology.
It used to be Soviet technology.
It could be that.
And that would answer a whole lot of questions.
Or it could be the Pentagon's straight up go.
We don't know what these things are.
They're not from around here.
So this isn't, Scott goes in his email, he goes,
I thought it was just one of those,
one of those many fake into the world things
that pops up every single month
in the conspiracy theory community.
And I go, no, this is real.
The bill is real.
So the date won't, something will happen in July.
The very least we're gonna get information
from armed services and the Federal Bureau
of Investigation involving UFOs.
At the very, very least and at the most.
Come on down and swamp me.
We're, we see a bunch of UFOs float.
I'm all like, my galactic brothers,
the first thing they do is they destroy every jazz bar.
Just doing that, I walk in with the bat.
I'm like, I'm with the aliens now,
smashing tubas.
We don't have time for the full gaming story
I wanted to tell,
but I wanted to wet your whistle.
Wanted to wet your whistle with this one.
William Bertels, I'm gonna touch the keys
to the carbon helicopter very quickly.
We are gonna fly on out to Sacramento, California.
(imitates car engine)
At this whole segment, we'll do it Monday
about how video games may be coming more self aware
than we think and not super advanced video games,
but like basic games being played so often
that they may actually start to turn on the players.
We've got some cool, cool stories for you
in involving that, but in the video game realm,
William Land the Carboner Cofter right here
by American River College,
where long time listeners of the show know that I went
to college, some of my happiest years,
I've had a lot of them, so it's tough competition,
but some of my happiest years were at American River College.
I'd always go to the jack in the box.
You can take this journey yourself
if you're in circle.
You know guys, I'd go to the jack in the box
and I'd get a chicken teriyaki rice bowl,
(makes chicken noises)
drink a Coke, I'd go back to school.
(laughs)
Jason, that's not how you're gonna wrap up this episode.
No, it's not just product placement.
One time though, I remember I was on a bus for some reason.
The jack in the box has nothing to do with this story.
I just really like chicken teriyaki rice bowls
and I'd also get a large order of jalapeno poppers,
but in the egg roll.
But one time I was on a bus driving through this area,
so there's like a little shopping center.
There used to be a military surplus store
with who I could only describe,
the guy who owned it as a domestic terrorist.
He was basically Otto from the Simpsons.
Every time you walked in there,
'cause I always wanted to buy pants,
buy like cool army pants.
You always thought that the Fed thrown away at any point.
He did not want customers in there.
I swear he was selling weapons in the back.
But one time I'm taking a bus through this area,
and I look out the window as the bus is driving,
I look out the side window,
and I see two men walking down the road.
There's a shorter overweight man and a taller skinny man.
They, this is, (laughs)
this is how I'm ending my Friday episode,
but this story's true.
Tall skinny man, short overweight man.
Both of them have mustaches.
The shorter man is wearing red.
He's like wearing a red shirt and blue pants.
And the tall skinny guy is wearing a green cap,
a green t-shirt and blue pants.
And I'm like, this guy's kind of look like Mario and Luigi.
Right?
(birds chirping)
(laughs)
Hold on, hold on, don't look up.
Don't look up yet.
Like this guy's kind of look like Mario and Luigi.
Now the bus is driving.
If I was in my car, I totally would have stopped
and asked them, "Hey, are you Mario and Luigi?"
But I didn't have that power.
The bus is driving by,
and I see them in some sort of animated argument.
Like it's overblown,
like you know how people argue in a silent film?
Like that, it's exaggerated argument
as they're walking down the street.
And then to make it even more like some bizarre scene,
Mario, he has a red baseball cap on,
he takes his cap off and hits Luigi over the head with it.
And Luigi covers up his head with both hands.
Like someone just hit him in the head with a baseball bat
and it's so animated.
I can't hear anything,
but he covers up his head with both his hands
and I see his mouth go, "Ow!"
Like super ridiculous.
And I remember the bus driving
and I am craning my neck now
and I see them just continuing to walk down the street.
I'm pretty sure that was actually Mario and Luigi.
Now again, it's probably not,
they're probably not eight bit characters
in the real world.
I found the whole thing so bizarre.
Everything was perfect about it.
The way they were dressed, the way they looked,
if anything was different.
And the thing that pushed it over the edge
was they're over the edge antics.
It's like watching a real life three Stooges.
Like if you took your hat off,
take your hat off right now,
go by hat and sit down next to someone
and hit him on the head with your hat.
They're gonna be like, "What?
"What'd you do that for, man?"
Maybe they're sleeping and they're like, "Ugh, what was that?"
They're at no point will they hold their head
with both their hands and go, "Ow!"
Unless they're a newborn baby.
Even in the Fontanella and don't do that.
If the person next to you is younger than a year,
don't do that.
Actually, don't do that to any child,
but there was something so,
it was like, it was so bizarre.
It wasn't the most bizarre thing I've ever seen.
It wasn't even in the top 1,000 bizarre things
I've ever seen, but it's a good way
to end the Friday's episode.
It's a good cliffhanger for Monday's episode.
Is it possible that you play a video game for so long
that it becomes self-aware?
And it knows you are a human player
trying to control its destiny.
We'll explore that story and more next week
on Dead Rabbit Radio.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is gonna be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Yes, I did, I did in Friday's episode on a story
about an overweight man and a skinny man
getting hit with a hat.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
Glad you guys listened to today.
I love you guys, have a great weekend, I'll see you Monday.
(upbeat music)
Thank you.