Are you looking at a cursed photograph?
Have I unleashed a horrible haunting on all of my listeners?
Could you kill a robot?
And then we travel to Nevada to uncover an interesting Indian story about giant cannibalistic
monster people.
However, when archeologists start digging up their remains, the story seems surprisingly
true.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You know, it's funny I had a different intro set up for today, but I'm sure you guys are
saying just explain this photo please.
Now again, I have two listenerships, people who listen to it on YouTube, who are now being
confronted with this image.
And then there's the rest of us who listen to the show on podcasts at work and things
like that.
This is just in your pocket.
You feel this little face pressed up against your skin, or maybe it's sitting in a corner
of your office, your phone as this is being streamed via bluetooth.
So you guys don't have to look at the photo as much.
But I ask you now to take that phone out of your pocket to look at the podcast art for
this episode because it's creepy.
It's super creepy.
So you guys are like, yes, yes, thanks for explaining that this photo is creepy.
And I know there's a couple of you out there being like, this is nothing.
I go to rotten.com.
That's not the point.
It's not a gory photo.
It's an unsettling photo.
A curse to photo, I believe.
Let's get into this.
The year is 1991.
We're one year away from Terminator 2, rocking into the box office.
It's June 5th.
That's nothing to do with this story.
Arnold Schwarzenegger is not in this photograph.
It's June 5th, 1991.
There's a little Super 8 Motel in Albuquerque, New Mexico.
Security guards walking along.
Hey, you got to open up your hotel room.
Open up.
Security.
No one's coming to the door.
Tries to open it.
Won't open.
Security guard has to unlock a deadbolt and then unlock the door.
Double bolted.
Opens up the hotel room.
The security guard walks into the hotel room and sees like a suitcase laying there.
You know stuff you would imagine in a hotel room.
That's not suspicious.
He's like, "Hazooka is in a hotel room.
Time to call the police."
Like, it's just stuff.
There's a couple bottles of alcohol, some cigarettes, things like that.
But there is a shape in the shower.
Recognizable shape.
It's body.
And then the security guard's like, "Well, that's suspicious.
I mean, yes, this is a Super 8 Motel in Albuquerque, New Mexico.
I've seen a couple of these, but I'm just going to leave and get the police in here."
Police come in here and what they find is a woman is hung.
She's dead.
Hanging from the shower head.
She was hung with a suitcase strap.
At this point, it's interesting because they said that they believed she'd been dead for
two days, but at this point she is so decomposed that she's unrecognizable.
They can't look at her face.
They can't tell anything about her.
Now, I'm wondering if the water was running the whole time.
Because in two days, I don't think that's enough time to really decompose the point
that you're unrecognizable.
I used to work in a mortuary.
And a morgue would be more specific than a mortuary.
But anyways, I mean, bodies can decompose pretty quickly, but to be unrecognizable.
But anyways, so I'm wondering if the water was just running the whole time.
That will wear you down very, very quickly.
Point is that she's dead.
They don't recognize her.
They can't tell from her face.
The only way that they can identify her in any sort of way is in this hotel room where
there is this woman hanging, no name, nothing to identify her with.
There is a photograph that she took at a-- you know those little parlor, those little
like things.
They have it in movie theaters or arcades or carnivals.
You know where you get into the giant box and it takes like five photos of you and it
comes out on that little strip.
It's like instant photos and you make funny-- do they still even have those?
Not everyone has a camera, but you'd crawl into this box with your friends or like whatever,
your mom and then it would take pictures of you.
You guys know what I'm talking about.
So anyways, that was the only thing they had on the table with all of her other stuff.
There was a little tiny photo of her making that face.
And there's a man sitting behind her, like she's sitting on some guy's lap.
They've never been able to identify the man.
They've never been able to identify her.
There's just that photo that they now circulate to see if anyone recognizes her.
There is a scale.
They found a digital scale in there that's at George Martinez.
They don't know who that is.
They don't know if that's the guy in the photo.
But that is all just a sad circumstance.
People do leave areas that they're in.
Did I say she had heroin in her system?
I don't think I said that yet.
They did find heroin in her system as well.
So it's possible that she was just doing heroin and goes, "This sucks," and then kills herself.
They don't think she was murdered.
I don't think most heroin users are like, "Dungeon of heroin.
Time to kill myself."
But the police don't think this was a murder.
They think it was a suicide because the door was locked from the inside.
But they've never been able to identify her.
This photo is circulating, trying to say, "The photo is haunting."
The photo is haunting.
Now, the photo could have been taken weeks or months before her death.
It could have been taken the day before her death.
But there's something about the look and face.
So what happened was I was on Reddit earlier yesterday and I was reading this thread and
it was like, "Most disturbing media you've come across regarding true crime."
Because I follow a lot of true crime reddits.
And someone says, "Oh, the Albuquerque Jane Doe photo."
And I was like, "Yeah, whatever.
I've seen it all."
And I clicked on it and I felt this face floating.
So my apartment, I've talked about it being haunted, right?
And this is what happened yesterday.
I had to get up to go to work.
So it's dark outside.
It's all spooky.
I looked at the photo and again, you guys are like, "Jason, you're a big baby.
I'm sitting.
This photo is not creepy at all.
I'm watching it on YouTube and I'm like in the dark.
I have all my lights shut off.
It's not creepy at all."
I don't think it's just me.
I bet you anything.
You're getting-- Look at it.
Look at the photo and tell me that's not a haunting photo.
What happened was I woke up before 30 yesterday morning.
I'm on my phone and I'm reading this stuff on Reddit and it's like, "Oh, this is spooky."
And a lot of these pictures I had seen before and they weren't gory.
They were just disturbing.
I'm going through my phone and I click on it and I was like, "Oh, that was creepy.
Creepy Albuquerque Jane Doe woman."
And then I remember being-- I usually shut off all my lights like a big boy, like an
adult.
I shut off all my lights and then I usually have to walk through a dark apartment because
the light switch to like by my door doesn't work.
It works.
I haven't replaced the light bulbs.
So generally, I have to shut the lights off on one side of my apartment and then walk.
What is it?
Like 10, 15 feet to the front door and then I open-- Now again, I do live in a haunted
apartment in a haunted apartment complex.
So it is spooky in general.
But then I walk to my front door.
I turn my back to my apartment as I undo my three locks.
I'm glad I'm giving all this information out to my stalkers.
And then I walk out of my apartment complex.
What I did this morning after looking at that photo.
And I looked at it and I go, "Oh, that's creepy."
Just something about it.
It's so terrifying.
I then, whenever my back was turned to-- I'm going to have a hard time recording this
episode whenever because I keep looking over my shoulder.
I've been doing that ever since I started recording.
And again, you guys can be like, "I'm not feeling it."
But just roll with me on this.
If you don't think it's creepy, just pretend it is.
Just pretend.
Just pretend for me.
Don't give me comments being like, "That's not creepy."
Be like, "That's really creepy, Jason.
Super spooky."
And I'll be like, "Yay.
They agree with me."
I look at the photo.
It totally creeps me out.
I can't stop looking at the photos.
And now I'm sharing that horror with you.
Then it's time for me to leave.
And I'm all suited up because I got all these lights and lanterns on my backpack so people
can see me while I'm walking on the road.
And I shut off my light.
It has these three light bulbs.
You're riveting, "Block, cast, you jayson, don't care."
I'm shutting off the light.
I have these three light bulb lamp thing.
I shut off the first two and then I can't shut off the last one.
I can't be in a dark room by myself because I know that face is right behind me.
And I remember not even wanting to turn my back on my bedroom, which is where I get a
lot of the haunting vibes.
I didn't want to turn my back on my bedroom.
So I kind of did this weird shuffle.
I did this side crab walk where I was walking sideways.
I had to walk towards the door, but I didn't want to turn my back completely to my bedroom.
So I'm doing this weird kind of shuffle.
And then I just want to, I have this feeling I need to get out of my apartment.
The face is right behind me.
So I get out of my apartment and I start walking and then I realize I left my walking stick
because it's snowing.
So I'm standing at the end of the hallway, my spooky, spooky apartment convalesce.
And I go, Jason, there may or may not be the face of a deceased woman in your apartment,
but you do need your walking stick.
So you're just going to have to face the problem head on.
And so I chuckle to myself as I made that pun and I turn and I walk in and I was just
panicked.
I was like, I'm doing the door and then I grabbed my walking stick and I ran out.
Not literally.
I bounced out.
You're like, Jason, you've heard me post a podcast about ghosts.
You seem to be awfully scared by a photograph, but I swear there's something to this photograph.
I really do.
I think that this is, a lot of times you'll see people talk about cursed photographs or
things like that.
I think this might actually be a cursed photograph.
It's not a gory photograph.
It's not a depressing photograph.
It's not a grisly photograph or anything like that.
It's not a photograph of someone's last moments or someone getting ripped apart by lions or
and it's a photo of a moment of fun.
A woman getting her photo taken at an InstaMax photo booth somewhere in 1991.
But it's the only image that we know of, of this human existing.
That alone makes it bizarre, but that's not the, I've seen photos like that before.
This photo, there's something about it that I believe is haunted, cursed maybe.
By gazing upon this photo, you are now inviting this horrifying image into your mind.
So you're welcome for putting it on the podcast.
I don't know the ramifications because I only just saw it, what, 24 hours ago, so it's possible
that seven days after viewing this photo, you actually see the face and you may be thinking,
Jason, that's pretty disrespectful because you're talking about like this woman who's
committed suicide and you're turning her story into a ghost story.
Well, that's probably true.
However, I will defend it like this as well.
If you recognize this person, you can follow the show notes and you'll see links to contact
someone.
So maybe some good will come out of it.
Maybe someone will go, that was my aunt.
I remember her.
So there's that too.
That's another reason why I'm putting the photo, not, I'm not just putting the photo
up to curse my listeners.
Maybe you recognize her, but I'm also putting it up because I think it's a creepy photo
and it's possibly cursed and I'm sorry.
And speaking of sorry, I should have said this earlier, but I've got tied up in that.
We have a new Patreon supporter and I'm sorry that this Patreon supporter is getting mentioned
in this episode.
Tressa, thank you very much for supporting the Patreon.
Really, really means a lot.
Tressa's like, yeah, next time don't mention my name after the horrifying photo segment.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too.
We have a merch store and if you can't do that, just get the word out about the show.
It really, really helps a lot.
Helps the show grow.
Reviewing the show wherever you listen to podcasts really, really helps a lot.
I appreciate anything.
Now I told you I was going to do the story about killing robots.
Could you kill a robot?
We're going to save that till tomorrow because I want to get into this next story here.
We'll save the killing robots for later.
People are like, I love killing robots.
You're all disappointed.
Like, oh yeah, to talk about that horrifying photo.
And get back to me.
Am I wrong that I just spent 15 minutes talking about a photo that only I and the Redditor
person finds horrifying?
I think there's something about the photo.
I think anyone who mocks the photo is only going to get more of the photo coming at you.
But anyways, anyways, we're done with the photo.
It's still going to appear though.
I'm not changing the podcast art so it's stuck there for the rest of the episode as
we go to this next one.
We're leaving behind Albuquerque, New Mexico.
We will let Tressa fly the carpenter copter and take us all the way to Love Lock, Nevada.
Flying away.
And we're sitting in the back.
We're discussing the story.
Tressa's flying the helicopter and I look and there's a little photograph.
You know how in those war movies they put little photographs on the dashboard of their
vehicle.
We look and we see Tressa put a little photograph on the dashboard of the carpenter copter and
we're like, "What is that?
What is that?"
It's the photo of the girl.
I don't know why he can't stop.
This podcast is now, this entire episode is just a photo.
And anyways, so make a long story short.
We're like, "Tressa, Tressa," and she turns around and she has the face of the girl.
We're like, "Ah, okay, that's the end of that segment."
That's the end of that segment.
Tressa became the girl.
She became, "Sorry."
Again, people are like, "I don't want to support your Patreon.
I'm going to get possessed by a photograph of a dead woman."
Sorry, Tressa.
Anyways, we land.
We regain control of the carpenter copter and we're like, "Tressa, Tressa, we have to
perform an exorcism."
We end up landing the helicopter in modern-day Love Lock Nevada.
Now back when we're going back in time to look at the story, it wasn't called Love
Lock back then, but if you're in the area, this place exists.
This is a really, really fascinating story.
Really interesting one.
It's 1913.
These dudes are hanging out in Nevada and they're like, "Ah, you know what we should do?
We should find, like, we should go in this cave."
And then everyone, all those buddies are super suspicious.
"Bill, every time we hang out with you, you just want to go in caves.
Like, what is your thing with caves?
I really like caves, man.
I just find them really neat and warm."
So anyways, they do what Bill says because they're global.
They walk in and it's a tiny little cave opening.
Usually like humans can't fit in that, but these guys, they go in there and they're like
ca-ching their eyes or like brrrrrrga, brrrrga.
Because they're in a cave full of bat guano.
Now I know you probably thought it was gold or diamonds, but these guys, they're like,
"Mmm, give me that sweet, sweet guano."
Guano is extremely valuable.
Extremely valuable.
You use it for a fertilizer.
You use it for gunpowder.
I don't know if they still use it for gunpowder.
It's 1913 though.
They're like, "Yes!"
They're like, "I got that guano money, baby."
They're like going to the club.
They're just throwing it.
It's all white and sticky.
But anyways, they start mining the cave.
And they have to make the opening bigger.
What happened was the opening was so small that only bats could really get in and out
of it.
So bats, it was totally peaceful for them.
They'd go in there, poop everywhere, and you had like centuries of bat poop.
They're mining this stuff.
They start mining.
They're a couple feet deep in this stuff, because it's all hard and sterilized.
It's not like dog poop.
It's not like you step in and they're like, "Oh!"
They're like to their knees and dog poop.
It's like fossilized.
So you're like, it's like a mineral.
So they dig down.
Over the years, they're digging, they're digging.
By 1924, they're starting to chop open with pickaxes.
They're starting to mine into these guano walls.
They're finding artifacts.
They're like, "That's weird.
Clay pot.
That's bizarre."
Hand?
Huh?
They find like skeleton bones and stuff like that.
They're like, "That's weird.
Who would have been in this cave if it was so small?"
But they just keep digging.
It's just too valuable to really get into it.
But archaeologists start to hear about all these artifacts they're finding in this mine.
The archaeologists show up and they're like, "Okay guys, the mining thing is good and all,
but let us try to dig around in here and see what we can find.
Some lost civilization maybe?"
Now when the archaeologists show up and they're digging around, it's not just that they're
finding pots and stuff like that.
That is interesting enough.
But these, and this is where I came across the story, these skeletons are referred to
as giants.
So now you're into this whole thing of giants being dug up and then the Smithsonian showing
up and smashing the bones and all this stuff.
We've done an episode on that before, but the idea is this is that there was a giant
race that preceded humanity and it's proof that the Bible's real and the Smithsonian
doesn't want people to believe in the Bible.
This is a legit conspiracy.
I'm no game.
It's not legit in the sense that I believe it, but there's a huge amount.
Whenever I talk about this on any episode, I get a lot of feedback about, "You're wrong.
Smithsonian actually does this."
But for new listeners or people who are sane, the idea is this.
Before humanity, there was a race of giants.
That possibly.
I'm not arguing that.
I don't know necessarily that they lived alongside humans, but anyways, the point is this.
There was a race of giants preceding humans, possible.
And their bones are everywhere.
If you look back at old-timey newspapers from the 1920s, 1930s, you would see all these
articles about giants being dug up and the Smithsonian would appear at the end of each
article.
Like all of these articles end and the bones are shipped into the Smithsonian and then
there's never any follow-up on these stories.
So they're basically this mustache-twerling villain and the reason why this Smithsonian...
So God...
And I gotta do...
So this is the reason why Christianity comes into this, is that in the book of Enoch, the
book of Genesis really, but the book of Enoch goes into detail and I did an episode on that
as well, angels came down and started banging human women and their babies were giants.
And then God created the flood to wipe out the half-human half-demons.
So the idea is this, is that you have these giants that pre-existed humanity or were alongside
humanity and they're proof that humans and demons had sex and created this race of giants.
The Smithsonian wants no proof of Christianity.
It hates Christianity.
So it is going around destroying these giants, otherwise it'll prove that Christianity is
real.
That's absolutely insane.
I have heard the conspiracy theory, which is a little more rational, that the Smithsonian
was headed up by a guy and I covered this in an earlier episode too.
Maybe I'll put this on one of my repeats, maybe I'll do this episode.
But anyways, there was a guy who was running the Smithsonian in the early days and he said,
"There is no race greater than humanity in any..."
I'm totally paraphrasing here.
No one was more advanced than where we're at right now, so any proof, any...
I shouldn't say any proof, any theories leading to that conclusion are obviously wrong because
we're the most advanced species.
So some people have taken that to mean we have proof they're a more advanced species,
go out and smash their bones.
And other people go, "No, he was just very..."
Not ethnocentric, but like civilization-centric.
He believed that this was the most highest form of civilization.
So any scientist who says Atlantis, Lemuria, advanced giant races, they're wrong and we
should prove them wrong.
So anyways, that is a more viable story that the Smithsonian goes, "No, we don't think
anyone was more advanced than us.
Let's secretly smash these giants."
That one, again I don't think it's true, but that one's more feasible than the Smithsonian
going like, "We hate God!
We hate God!"
Like it's a Marilyn Manson concert and just smashing bones.
That's completely ridiculous.
And I should say this too, the reason why, and every so often someone will address this,
the reason why there were a bunch of stories in the 1920s and the 1930s about giants is
because people were making them up.
It was yellow journalism, it was newspaper- I'm not saying they were all fake, but a lot
of them were.
So anyways, let's go on with this story.
These people said, "We found these giant skeletons."
Now the website Anomalien, which is actually a really good website, I'm not knocking them
for this, but you know people are going to get their information, weirdly from time to
time.
Anomalien.com is a really good website.
They say that the skeletons were 8.5 to 10 feet tall, which would definitely put them
almost outside the range of humanity.
I think that if there were giants, of course there's giants.
We know Andre, but I think it was, if you found Andre the Giant Skeleton, I don't think
you could then go, "There was tens of thousands of these people.
I think they're genetic anomalies."
But anyways, this race of giants, the reason why I want to address that, because these
guys are known as the Nevada Giants.
I'm not going to be demunking at all, because this actually gets really, really interesting.
I'm just kind of going over all this base stuff, because I want to get this out of the
way now.
When we looked back at the original literature where they found these bones, they did say
they were giant.
They were giant as in, they were 6 feet, 6 inches.
So language is really, really important.
Language is really, really important.
Because back in the 1920s, where you don't have basketball players, like massive basketball
players, someone who's 6 foot, you'd be, if I saw someone who's 6 foot 6 and someone goes,
"Hey, how would you describe him?"
I'd be like, "Oh, great personality.
Really nice dude.
He paid for my dinner.
He's actually kind of cool."
No, no, no, no, no, no, physically.
I was like, "Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He was a giant dude.
He was like 6 foot 6.
He was huge."
And then 100 years later, you would have the article, "Podcastos meets giants."
So they wrote in their book, the archaeologists would be like, "The skeletons we found were
that of a giant."
But then you go two sentences down and they go, "Yeah, he was 6 foot 6."
So that type of stuff gets distorted over time.
And they said, it appeared bigger because it was next to, I think, two or three female
skeletons that they found, which were much shorter.
So that's where these stories come from.
Here we go though.
Let's move past the giant stuff because I want to get to where is any of this true?
And it is.
We know who's in that cave.
And who's in that cave?
Giants, actually.
It was a very, very tall tribe.
So we're going back in time to Native American days.
We're going way back in this same region.
There was a tribe called C.T.
Ka.
C.T.