Paranormal events continue to swarm around the host of America's fastest growing paranormal
podcast.
That'd be me.
And then we travel to the United Kingdom to hang out with a couple friends who are smoking
some weed.
It was a beautiful night.
Everything was completely calm.
Until the phone rang.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're gonna get started right away.
First off, let's go ahead and give a shout out to one of our Christmas livestream contributors.
Everyone give it up for Alex.
Woo yeah!
Come on Alex, come on in to Dead Rabbit Command.
You're gonna be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon or can't support the show financially through
live streams, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That really, really helps out a lot.
I haven't really talked about this a lot.
I think I mentioned it at the end of the last season.
I have a vacation coming up.
I know I just got done with a two week break but I actually have, that was just me sitting
in a chair playing Minecraft.
I'm actually going down to visit some family in a couple weeks.
So I am going to start pre-recording a bunch of episodes and then we're gonna have some
new classic episodes.
I've been wanting to bring those back.
I got a lot of behind the scenes stuff I want to talk about.
We're bringing back the classics so you guys I think will only notice I'm gone for one
week.
We'll have one week where there's no nothing but we've got a bunch of episodes coming up
and then some behind the scenes classics, some drama that's happened behind the scenes.
All this stuff are gonna go through that and I can't wait to share that with you.
Anyways, Alex, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're gonna drive around the corner because we're gonna end up back at Dead Rabbit Command.
Because I wanted this, this is an interesting story I think and it involves me.
It involves me.
I want to start this off.
The other day people were talking about this on the Patreon Discord.
They were talking about the paranormal activity that I've gone through.
Specifically we're talking about the episode, I wasn't talking about it, they were talking
about it, but the episode where, I'll see if I can even find it in the show, I don't
even know if I put it in the show notes I was doing an episode and I saw what could
only be described as a dog's paws, like a little dog, not a little dog, a big dog, walking
by my recording studio door.
I just saw the silhouette of its paws outside the door and it totally freaked me out.
I left it in the recording, it completely freaked me out and I talked about it a bit
and then I went on with the episode.
And then when they were talking about that in the Patreon Discord, one of my mods and
a longtime supporter of the show Hot Diggity Dane wrote this.
I've always wondered what it is about Jason that draws so many paranormal experiences.
The amount of episodes where phenomenon happens while recording are much more common than
they ever should be.
I fully believe that the experiences Jason has are authentic, but why is it happening
so much to him?
At first I thought it was like the old, you look into the paranormal long enough, eventually
something will look back.
But I've lived, that's a famous quote, right, it's a famous quote.
Be careful if you search for monsters, you may become one, or if you stare into the abyss
too long the abyss dares back.
But he continues, "But I have listened to a lot of paranormal podcasts and have only
encountered one other host that has had a solid encounter in the last few years and
never while recording the podcast."
So it's interesting, I read that, I don't think I responded to that comment, because
I don't know.
I don't know the answer to that either.
It could be because the show's daily, here I'm going to be honest with you guys, it
happens more often than I talk about on the show.
I'm constantly editing out weird noises, constantly.
A lot of times I'm in the studio, which is in my closet, which was haunted long before
I started even doing the podcast, right?
There are so many times when I'm recording and I can hear something walking around.
Now I always think, "Maybe it's a neighbor, maybe it's a squirrel with size 11 shoes."
I don't know.
And then sometimes people are playing their television really loud and that kind of can
come through on the mic.
There's a lot of times while I'm editing it, sometimes I hear it when I'm recording and
I'll have to stop and let whatever it is pass.
And again, I'm always thinking it's something rational.
There's sometimes I'm editing and I hear a noise and I'm like, "I have no idea what
in the world made that noise."
None.
But I edit it out.
I think there might have been one or two episodes where I left it in and I don't remember if
I ever jumped into the editing process.
See that's the thing, usually I record the episode.
Then a couple days later I'm editing it and sometimes if I'm in a rush I'm editing it that
same day.
I'm recording and editing the same day and I just like chopping stuff up to get it out
there.
Now obviously if I picked up, someone's like, "Help me!" or something like that.
But I'm going to leave it in the editing process.
I'm going to come in on the mic and say, "Oh, I don't know what that was."
But usually I will just chop it out because I don't know what it is.
I can't control my environment around me as far as like making sure no one else is playing
loud music or anything like that.
You know, who knows, right?
I just chop it up.
And I also have edited out whole segments about paranormal activity that's happened
to me.
I actually did this whole segment a while back and I cut it for time.
You're like, "Jayson, what are you doing when I told you this story?"
When I was putting the episode together, generally I just have notes, right?
I'm going off the notes and I went into the segway.
I think it was even during a live episode.
So the Patreon Discord users heard me talk about this for like 10 minutes.
I'm not going to talk about it that long.
And then I edited it out when I was doing the episode to try to have them in underneath
40 minutes just for convenience to you guys, right?
You guys don't have all day long to be listening to stuff.
So I figured I would talk about it again at some point.
Going back to the paranormal dog story, I saw a, what looked like the paws of a dog.
Like if a dog walked by a door and you only had that little half an inch to inch gap underneath
between the door and the floor and you saw a dog walk by, that's what it looked like.
That's exactly what it looked like.
And it totally scared me.
There were probably about two, I might even be, I'm going to say two to three weeks, but
honestly it might have been four to five weeks.
When I was walking around town, right out of the corner of my, it happened so often,
it was driving me nuts.
I'd be having my headphones on, I'd be listening to my music out of the corner of my eye and
it would always be about maybe like 20, 30 yards away.
There would be a black dog.
And I'd turn and I'd look because I hate loose dogs.
You cannot understand how much I despise these things because I had to fight one once.
I had to fight in a quita.
Think I talked about it on the show before, but I had to fight in a quita and if I haven't,
then I'll do it in a later episode.
I had to fight in a quita.
I had to save this dude's life because he was being chewed up by this massive dog, bread
for war.
I hate loose dogs and I used to hate dogs.
I had to go to dog therapy to not hate all dogs after that event because it bit him so
hard and broke his wrist and he was just leaking, dude.
This dude was just bloody everywhere.
I think I've talked about it before on the show though.
So I hate loose dogs.
So whenever I see, and that's just one of my experiences of loose dogs, that's the
most, that's the one that really set me up.
Whenever I see a loose dog, it always draws my attention.
It always creeps me out.
I'm then looking for the owner while I'm reaching for my pepper gel.
Right?
It's this thing.
And after I saw the dog walk by the studio door for about, I'd say, for a period of time,
for a good period of time, I kept seeing the dog out of the corner of my eye.
Now because I'm so paranoid about loose dogs for the first dozen times, I just thought,
you're just jumpy.
You're just jumpy.
It was weird.
It almost always was on the left side that I'd see it.
But I thought, you're just jumpy.
But as it continued over the weeks, I started to make the connection that this could be
related to the ghost dog in the studio.
And I think the story I was, I think I can be able to find the episode.
I think the story I was talking about was about a ghost dog.
I started seeing this ghost dog walking around town.
It was driving me nuts.
And once I, again, at first I just thought I was actually seeing a real dog and then
I would turn and I wouldn't see anything.
May know connection that eventually I started thinking, what if it's related to what I saw
in the studio?
And I still continued to see this dog out of the corner of my eye, sometimes on the right
side, but mostly on the left side.
And then it totally stopped.
The phenomenon completely stopped.
And it was good because I was so jumpy.
I was so jumpy whenever I saw this thing.
And then one day, and I again edited this out of the episode, I'm sitting in the studio
recording episode.
I look and I see the pause walk back by the door.
And I freaked out again and I was like, okay, I'm not even doing this anymore.
I don't want this.
People think this is some ARG or something like that.
So I regained my, I opened the door.
I was like, okay, this is just something that's going to happen now.
And I was, I kept trying to figure out what it was.
I, I thought I had figured it out for a moment.
I thought it was my bathrobe, which would be a accurate thing.
My bathrobe arm thingy.
What's that thing on the, the bathrobe cloth.
You're just describing a bathroom, the belt, the belt.
I thought that was swinging, but it's simply not low enough.
But yeah, so I don't know.
And now it's all, now I don't, I started to see that a couple more times.
All I was recording, I was like, what, I was like thinking, am I doing, am I like gesticulating
so much in the closet that I'm causing this?
Like I was still trying to rationally think, and then it went away.
And that's the interesting thing is if it was a physical cause and nothing changed, I'm
doing the same gesticulations.
My bathrobe is the same way, all of that stuff from the time I started recording in the closet
really until that.
And then after it's gone now again, I don't see the dog footprints outside the closet
or the silhouette of the dog.
It was weird.
It was always walking from east to west.
It was always walking like from east to west.
I don't know how to explain any of it.
Because again, if it was something I was doing, I started, I remember there was a point where
I was going, I have to be doing that.
This has to be something that I'm physically making the silhouette appear.
But I don't know, man, it's super weird.
And the reason that reminded me to really talk about that was again, just the other
day Sabine, well actually months ago she made me this "Get Well" sign for Bigfoot because
I was sick, right?
I'm sure you guys, I'm sure a lot of you are listeners of this show now, I'm sick all
the time.
And it's always something either incredibly minor or incredibly rare.
I have all sorts of weird ailments, but usually I'm just a big, big old baby, right?
My tummy hurts, I'm sick.
I'm just kind of rolling around on the ground.
She made me this "Bigfoot, Get Well" sign and I hung it up and then a couple months later
I lost it.
It fell down behind something.
She got all butt hurt.
She goes, "I made you something."
Come on man, you know how heavy that bookshelf is?
I gotta move this wall, you know?
So anyways, you know, of course guys, I moved the bookshelf and I went to go find it.
And that bookshelf, when Jen came in to feng shui my apartment, we pretty much moved everything,
but we didn't move the bookshelf because that's where my television was.
I was like, you know, I don't watch television anymore.
The bookshelf has really not been moved for at least, I would say, 11 years.
Maybe 10.
Maybe I'll quibble by a year, but I'm pretty sure it's been there for a long period of time.
I moved it just a little bit and got my grabber.
That's the thing that all old men get.
So they don't have to bend over and pick stuff up.
I got a little grabber from Walgreens, reached in and there were three things behind this
bookshelf.
Three things.
Which is crazy considering how chaotic my bookshelf is.
I might take a picture of it for the image for this episode.
But three things.
An old receipt, which was close.
It was like just fell out of the garbage can like a week ago.
The big foot, get well picture.
And this letter.
And I picked it up and it says to Grandma McGee.
It was my great grandma McGee.
And basically the letter, so I'm not going to read it in full.
But the letter basically is me saying I'm afraid you're not going to get better soon.
And I'm more afraid that when you die I'm not going to see you in heaven.
Because I don't know if you're a born again Christian.
That's what this letter goes on to say and it's asking her to take Jesus Christ into
her heart.
All of that.
If you read this letter and believe then I will not have to be afraid of missing you.
Love you dearly Jason.
That's how the letter ends.
And I look at this.
I have no idea how this letter got behind my bookshelf.
None.
Zero.
It's a full page.
First off, okay so my great grandma died.
I guess I should have given you a little bit of context.
She died in August 2001.
See this letter, in August of 2001 I was an adult.
I could have sat down and had this conversation with another adult and say hey you know I
know things aren't going well let's talk about what I believe in.
Let's talk about the afterlife.
So I would have had to write this, if I wrote this letter I would have had to have been
probably under the age of 15, 16.
Because at that point I was confident enough in my, I'm Southern Baptist right.
I would have been confident enough.
My religion doctor, she was Catholic right.
It's not like she was from crazy culture or something like that.
Or you know like a full on atheist or anything like that.
So this letter at the very least though is 21 years old.
And again I don't think I wrote it then.
She was in a rest home.
But I think I wrote this letter closer probably to around the age when I was 12.
Which would put this around 30 years old.
More than that right?
33 years old.
That's a creepy number.
This piece of paper, this piece of paper could be up to 33 years old.
It looks like I wrote it, I don't know maybe a year or two ago.
And the reason why I say that is there's hardly any yellowing on it.
When I showed it to Sabine she goes, I don't know when you wrote it either.
I couldn't, it's been exactly the same since you were a kid.
But she goes I'll tell you this, this piece of paper does not look like it was behind
that shelf for 10 years.
And I said that.
I go minimum.
I go I will allow when I used to have a television set up there that maybe I moved it to one
side or another.
But for the past 10 years I've lived here for 11 years that thing has not moved.
There were three things behind it.
Bigfoot, not actual bigfoot but the bigfoot picture.
The dirty receipt that had just fallen out of the garbage can and then this piece of
paper.
Now this is one of those things that I don't necessarily classify as paranormal but I don't
know how to classify it.
I don't remember writing it but I'm sure that I did.
This is something I would have done when I was a child.
I just have no idea.
The only thing I can think of is I did write this as a child and my grandma when she passed
away she gave me a little box of her lighters.
She had collected, she was a lifelong smoker.
Smokers that she was 12.
She died at 92.
She had a collection of really cool lighters.
When I say really cool lighters there was like a Zippo in there and then there was like
an old lighter.
Then she also tossed in a 98 cent lighter from Albertsons.
It says Albertsons on it.
That was in there too.
My Albertsons lighter is up on my shelf.
It has a spot.
It has a location for that lighter.
The rest of the cooler lighters are actually locked away in a box.
The storage area with the Albertsons lighter which I also think is cool.
It's like up among all of my Chachkeets, all of my toys I've collected over the years.
That's how much I value that lighter.
I can't imagine a scenario where I got this letter and then just tossed it on my bookcase.
Now if I do take a photo of my bookcase you'll see a couple books by Joe McKinney, the famous
zombie author.
He's really good.
Then I got like a copy of Star Trek meets X-Men on there.
Then a few PlayStation games, some LEGO stuff.
It's not really a bookshelf.
I probably should stop calling it.
You'll see a bunch of other greeting cards up there that I've collected over the years.
But really I should say over the past two years.
But I wouldn't have put something this valuable just sitting on there.
So why am I talking about this?
Did this manifest?
This does not look like it.
I'll take a photo of it for the show notes.
It definitely does not look like it was sitting behind that shelf for ten years.
I don't know how I would have gotten back there.
And I don't know why I would have found it now.
Like Sabine's been complaining about that stupid Bigfoot picture for like nine, ten
months.
That's the only crafty thing I make.
I don't do any arts and crafts and I finally do something and you lose behind your bookshelf.
I don't know whatever.
So I finally go back there and I get it and then I find this.
I don't know what this means.
Now it's possible that it's just the letter.
Well it's not just a letter.
I wrote it to my great grandma.
I love my great grandma.
It's possible that I did write that letter and then it came in the little box that she
gave me the lighters in.
That's most likely how I got possession of it at some point.
And then I might have had it sitting up there.
If you look at my shelf you realize well he has some greeting cards from his mom and then
like X-Men comic books.
The things covered in filth.
I don't imagine myself putting it up there.
My question is why did I find it now?
And I'm going to wrap up this segment.
Again I don't know if it's paranormal.
I don't know if there's any meaning behind it.
It's just a weird thing.
I'm going to wrap this segment up by a weird Jason story.
When a close associate of mine dies like a family member or a close friend.
I don't have sex for like two weeks.
I don't have sex.
I don't masturbate.
I do nothing sexual for two weeks minimum.
Because I think their ghost might see me.
It's a totally real story.
Someone passes away that I know.
I figure.
Here's the reason why it's only two weeks.
Because after week three or four being a ghost you're probably like going to movies.
Probably haunting movie theaters.
I know when I die I want to hang out to the bottom of the ocean.
I want my ghost to check out all of those caves under water.
Like the deepest points of the ocean.
I think like maybe like my grandpa will be like oh yeah you know I didn't talk to my
grandson Jason enough.
Now that I'm dead maybe I'll go see what he's like.
Oh gross gross oh no and he's flown away.
So it's a it's not like there's no reason behind it.
No one's ever told me like that that's a thing.
Like it's a superstition or something.
I just don't.
I'm showering with all my clothes on.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me naked you ghost.
I don't.
And it's so weird because generally every time someone close to me dies within about a week
or two I dream of them.
They come in and now it's not anything dramatic.
It's not like I'm dreaming and they show up and they're like hey I'm just here to say
goodbye.
I really had fun knowing you and I was glad to be your friend.
Nothing like that right.
I'll have a dream and they'll be in the dream.
They're just in the dream and sometimes I will I won't remember the dream that they're
in.
I'll simply wake up and I'll have the feeling whoa.
Like that was the dream.
Like I won't it's it's hard to say like sometimes I'll have the dream and I'll know that they
are in it.
And then sometimes I'll just wake up and I won't remember my dream but I go oh I dreamt
about them last night.
Like I got the feeling that they had said in some way not dramatically again saying goodbye
is they're like fading away or anything like that.
I have the dream about a dead relative and it's it's it's weird right.
Again I just have the feeling like that was them appearing in the afterlife in some way.
It's usually within a week or two I get the feeling that they have moved on except for
one time.
This is so weird.
My grandma Miller great grandma McGee's daughter grandma Miller she died.
We talked about this on the show to the phone call story but this was such a weird paranormal
thing that happened to me.
When my grandma Miller died it was a huge thing because once she was like the matriarch
of the family and I remember knowing this right I lived with grandma Miller for a while
and I lived with grandma McGee for a while.
I spent almost every summer with grandma McGee and I lived one entire year when I was going
to elementary school with grandma McGee and when I was adult I lived with grandma Miller
and I remember knowing and saying when grandma Miller dies the family falls apart.
I go the only thing we all have in common is grandma Miller like all these different
groups all these different groups of people and unfortunately she did die.
It was completely avoidable.
It was 100% avoidable but there are this huge family drama going on at the time.
I'm not going to get into the specifics of it but family always had a lot of drama and
there is this huge family drama going on and she ended up passing away.
You could have been avoided had she had.
Anyways I did not have that dream for months months.
I remember when she first passed away I was with my mom and that was her mom and it was
one of the worst sounds I'd ever heard a human make when my mom got the phone call that her
mother had died.
I've been around all sorts of human suffering throughout my life but hearing a daughter cry
out for her mother it was I was sitting in the car where the Dairy Queen drive through
and she gets the phone call.
I couldn't eat.
I mean it was just it was gut wrenching and of course you know I'm my mom's son and I
had to kind of you know calm her down you know get her back home.
But grief right it was unexpected it was an unexpected death.
My grandma Miller was old but what she died of could have been prevented.
So anyways and I technically don't know the medical definition what she what killed her
but this was a couple years ago this would have been like five or six years ago.
But anyways the sound my mother made it was awful.
I gotta I gotta be the straight man right I gotta get up this episode.
I started going from ghost I did not plan on talking about this.
So I get my mom to calm down.
There will be two large blizzards please Oreo thank you.
We get to her house and again you know just trying to console my mom and then talking
to people on the phone because they're in Sacramento we're in Hood River and all this
stuff and then we make arrangements to go down for the funeral.
And I remember that it had been maybe three or four months after she had passed away.
I gave myself a couple weeks before I could grieve right because I was trying to help
my mom.
I spent a lot of time with my grandma like I lived with her for many many years and then
after a couple weeks I finally gave myself you know an hour or two to cry and then you
know you you move on.
And so anyways though it was probably like month three or four I had realized I haven't
dreamt about her yet and that scared me because I always figured that the joy of my life was
that the dream was them moving on to a better place obviously.
I didn't dream about I didn't dream about Grandma Miller.
Month four month five still no dreams not even that I didn't remember the dream but
I had the feeling nothing.
Grandma Miller made sure you are of this huge family and not only did we have the biological
family but tons of step uncles and step cousins and all of this stuff.
Huge family.
I don't think it is she trying to figure something out is she like staying behind to does she
have some business she needs to attend to like all of this classic ghost stuff because
my great grandma McGee I loved incredibly dearly.
I have very few regrets in my life very few and one of them is not stopping by more often
when she was in the rest home because she never hesitated to take care of me but I thought
she lived forever she was 92 years old 93 I think even thought she wouldn't live forever.
I drive by the rest home on my way to my house and be like hey Grandma I just kind of wave
she's like going from the window I just figured it doesn't matter if I go today or tomorrow
she's never gonna die.
It's one of the very very very few regrets I have in my life but I dreamt about her right
in that two week period I had a dream about her.
I did not have a single dream about Grandma Miller now we're on month five and I started
thinking maybe she's handling some unfinished business or maybe something bad has happened
other than her dying maybe something bad has happened to her soul.
And I remember on month six I had a dream I was at Grandma Miller's house and she was
there big smile on her face just being Grandma Miller just taking care of all of us.
Nothing spectacular about the dream there were no omens or signs or symbols there was no
kiss goodbye as she walked into the ether nothing it was just a normal dream but my
Grandma Miller was in it when I go okay Grandma I'm a little worried there for a while thought
something happened to you but you're in a better place.
I don't even know why I started telling that story in the first place honestly I know we
were talking about the letter but yeah I mean we're not gonna get to the phone story I hope
this was entertaining.
See the funny thing is like I edit stuff out when I talk about personal stuff because a
lot of times like I did the whole segment about seeing the ghost dog out on my field
of view and all that stuff and then I was listening to him I was like this isn't interesting
this is boring so I edited out I edited out for time and then I never brought it back
up I think I recorded that segment like three or four more than that because I just got
done with a two week break it was like a month or two ago I did that segment I was like ah
whatever it's boring it's boring then I'm getting haunted by this ghost dog when I was
doing a segment again I think it was about a ghost dog and then I kept seeing this dog
out of the field of view and no one would see it.
So I hope that this story was entertaining I hope this episode was entertaining and to
go back to hot diggity Danes thing we'll finish it up like this I find my life I'm not gonna
say that my life is completely normal but I don't think it is incredibly interesting
by any metric.
I was watching the Dave Chappelle special the other day he was at his old college or
high school and they were gonna put his name on the side of the building the side of the
art center right and he was talking about his life and how he got into comedy and I'm
sitting there and I was like oh my god this dude's life is so interesting I can't imagine
being interviewed by someone and them asking me about my life and I'd be like well I can
tell you a couple ghost stories I mean I can tell you a whole bunch of ghost stories I've
read about and I can tell you a couple ghost stories that I've been in but I don't find
my life particularly interesting.
Obviously there's a few standout things I can say stuff like I saw shadow people I fought
a witch I've seen demonically possessed people but see then I go well who hasn't you can
read all sorts of accounts online of people who have done similar and more exceptional
things so I don't think my life is super interesting and I don't think regarding hot diggity dogs
question I don't think there's anything incredibly special about me either I mean I don't think
I'm any more special than you I think we're all special in our own way but again if 8
billion people are special in their own way yeah sure but I don't I'll be honest I don't
think there's something about the show that's causing paranormal phenomenon to pop up I
think the only thing I can think of for hot diggity dogs question was why does Jason seem
to have this more I the only thing I can think of is one I'm recording in a place that's
no one haunted which is the closet we didn't have these see I've been recording these past
I don't know five six episodes and quite a few going forward in the living room where
I used to record my podcast first 500 episodes were recorded in the living room now that
it's so hot this is the coolest place to record in the audio quality takes a little bit of
a hit but and there's more background noise but I there's been I as far as I remember
there has been no paranormal activity I don't think I was talking about any of it when I
was recording in the living room and even in those early episodes I talked about my closet
being haunted I knew my closet was haunted within a week of moving in here and since
I removed the recording studio into the closet I would say the main reason I don't think
it's anything about me I that could be it right I was also thinking this is the only
as far as I know there's only two daily paranormal shows that are actively in production this
one and then the ghost hunters have one the taps guys do a if it I'm pretty sure it's
around a daily ghost podcast that's it so it could also be the fact that it's daily
right recording stuff all the time but I'd say anything it's more of the location than
anything I don't think it's anything about the show and I think it's anything about me
I don't know but you know that's the thing with paranormal activity I said this on really
yesterday's episode you doesn't always have a dramatic ending it doesn't always have this
big thing it's not like this letter is going to burst into flames and my great grandma
McGee's gonna appear to me tonight with three keys and she says one of these keys will unlock
your destiny I don't know probably not probably not she has a ghost dog she's like get him
boys the dogs maul me to death in my sleep my astral body is torn to shreds I hate loose
dogs and I hate reading stories about people being mauled by packs of dogs and yet I read
them all the time and I want to tell you guys this I am doing you a service by not covering
it every time I come across it they are grotesque grotesque I think people should be criminally
liable for whatever their dogs do they are like financially liable sure and sometimes
people catch charges like a manslaughter charge but if your dog your dog should be considered
an extension of you I should be able to reko act you which means if you are in a gang
and a member of a gang commits a crime the entire gang is charged with that crime if
you own if you own a dog that is mistreated you treat I'm not saying like a dog that goes
wild right but if you get multiple reports that your dogs are violent in the neighborhood
and that's what all of these stories are about every story goes yeah they got multiple reports
they got multiple reports over the years of these dogs chasing kids and then one day this
woman was walking down the street and they ate her colon these dogs ate her colon and
her esophagus and both of her arms and one of her legs that's horrific and her face that's
horrific that's the worst she's still alive right she's still alive they come on man I
think I think whoever owned those dogs should be charged for eating a woman's colon I think
you should be able to reko act them but I digress I digress in this sweet and I don't know
was this episode sweet was it entertaining hopefully it was but you guys have a great
weekend well save the phone call story for Monday it is absolutely humdinger will not
go off on any ransom I love dogs I do love dogs but loose dogs dead rabbit radio gmail.com
is gonna be your email address you can also it is up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
tick tock is at dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy
true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to
it today have a great one guys
[Music]
(upbeat music)