When archaeologists find a village built on the remains of another village, it may point
towards a cosmic catastrophe, and then we travel to the Grand Canyon to meet a young
man out on a Boy Scout trip.
He thought he was just going to earn some merit badges.
But he may have unlocked the mystery of why people just disappeared.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
Hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys enjoyed the end of yesterday's episode where I just said "Why cows?" for
three minutes straight and then the episode just kind of ended.
Hope you guys enjoyed that.
I'm still wondering why cows?
It's still very puzzling, but I'll continue to keep that puzzle in the back of my mind
and we'll talk about it for three minutes and then just kind of end.
Instead, I'll give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, Luis.
Everyone give a round of applause to Luis.
He's riding a cow.
I'm like, "Oh great.
Oh, it's back in my head."
Luis is doing cow tricks, if that's a thing.
Luis, you're going to be our captain, our pilot of this episode.
If you can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
Luis, go ahead and hop off that cow.
I'm going to toss you the keys too.
The dead rabbit dune buggy.
We are leaving behind dead rabbit command.
It's a new place.
We'll have a play set coming out in 2021.
It's really cool.
We are leaving behind dead rabbit command.
We are headed out to Syria.
Dead rabbit dune buggy is jumping over a bunch of sand dunes.
It's pretty dope.
Doing tricks.
Cow.
Going back?
Is it counting the back giving us a thumbs up?
Or like, "What?
We didn't know cows had thumbs.
This one does."
We are headed out to Syria and we're going back in time.
And I mean back in time.
So, I hit that time travel button, I suppose.
It's just regular back in time.
If you say differently, you go farther back.
We're headed back 12,800 years ago.
God, I don't know why I put the emphasis on the 800.
That's the least impressive part.
1,000 and 800 years ago.
Going through the time vortex.
Now, as Luis is navigating the time vortex, I turn at you and I say, "Hey, so I found
this article the other day.
You're like, "This isn't every episode of your show.
Why are you making such a big deal?"
It's all about you finding articles or people sending you articles.
True.
But it was interesting.
I came across these articles the other day and it talked about RR gods created by meteorites.
This is really, really interesting.
It's a series of articles I read.
25 or 30% of all meteorites have the same shape.
It's the shape of a cone.
It's the shape of a conical object.
They say that actually helps it maintain stability as it's through the atmosphere, less likely
to break up.
And they're specifically talking about iron meteorites.
But they've been able to track back in history, King Tut, one of his knives, was made of iron
from a meteorite, which is pretty dope.
And they know it wasn't just accidental.
Some guy was like, "Man, I really need to make a dagger for the emperor.
I'll do that."
They knew, they called it from the sky.
That was the type of iron it was.
So they knew it was from meteorite.
You can go back and you can look at, there's Bible verses.
There is a Bible verse in Acts where they talk about the statue of Diana that fell from
the sky.
And people are always like, "Is that like a turn of phrase or something like that?"
No.
Modern archeologists believe that the statue of Diana, the image of the goddess Diana
or Artemis in Greek mythology, that was in her temple at Ephesias, it was described as
a cone.
It was described as a cone-shaped rock.
So they think that it was a meteorite that came down.
And of course she would think that was divine back then.
Find this thing.
And they go, even modern depictions or later depictions of Diana, she had like a bunch
of boobs.
And they said that they think that was actually a modification from the--sometimes meteorites
will land and they'll have these like weird ridges on them, that if you try to emulate
them they could look like a bunch of boobs.
The idea was that some of the earliest worship, idol worship, was from meteorites.
Because you're in the middle of nowhere and then all of a sudden there's just this chunk
of iron.
And if you're lucky enough, you saw it fall.
But even if you were walking through a forest and there was a cone of iron just sitting on
the forest floor, you're going to think there's something divine about them.
But that's just a little taste for the story.
I just kind of thought that was fascinating to talk about.
Luis is taking us out of the time void we are now in Syria 12,800 years ago.
There's a village off in the distance and Luis is being getting us closer and I kind
of go, no, slow down buddy, slow down.
We don't want to get too close to this place.
So we're standing on a ridge and what we're looking at below us is the Syrian village
known as Abu Hurayah.
Now almost all of this information I got from an article on the Smithsonian website is
written by Javier Barbuzano.
So thank you Javier, really cool research you did on this.
12,800 years ago there was a village there known as Abu Hurayah.
Well, kind of.
That's kind of what it was known as.
Just a village is probably really unnamed at that time.
So we're sitting there and it's dawn and we start to see the hunters gather up their supplies
and they're going to go out and look for fresh meat.
It might take them a couple of days, that's not the easiest thing to go down and track
a wooly mammoth or a sea monster or whatever was in this region at the time.
We also see the gatherer contingent, they're getting their baskets ready, they heard in
the news, they heard from the papyrus, there's a cool new berry patch somewhere off in the
mountains, it'll probably take like an 8 hour trip to get out there, get some berries man.
But we know something's coming.
You could warn them but we don't want to interrupt the timeline.
We're just kind of sitting there, we're all eating our grilled cheese sandwiches.
First we see it.
We look up, even though it's a sunny day, you can see the flames in the sky.
Huge fiery chunks are entering the earth's atmosphere.
You look over at me and you go Jason are we safe distance from what I assume will be a
catastrophe?
I go probably.
It's so loud at this point.
You can't hear me running back to the Derev Dume buggy trying to start it.
I don't know far enough away from this thing.
What is going on is a comet had fragmented in space.
As it was passing through our solar system, fragments of this comet begin to enter the
earth's atmosphere.
Now most of them just burnt up.
But the theory is that one of them was large enough that survived the entrance into our
atmosphere and when it got to a certain point, it burst in the sky.
You might go that's cool, maybe like a nice little rain shower of hot iron.
A bunch of new gods were born that day.
No, when a comet air bursts in the sky, this is the theory.
Each one is as powerful as a nuclear bomb.
Let's fast forward to the year 1972.
They're going to build a dam at Lake Assad in Syria.
And archeologists know that this area is important.
They know that there used to be a really big settlement here called Abu Hurayah.
It was one of the biggest settlements in the area.
It was a huge center for trade, a huge agricultural center.
It was the place to be in ancient Syria.
But they're going to build a dam, it's going to be flooded, archeologists goes, "Okay,
just give us like a year."
They're like hurrying up their dust and stuff off as guys are like getting the bricks on
the dam.
The water's just kind of starting to get held back.
They're like, "Can you slow down a bit?"
And they're like, "No, no, we're not."
They think it's hilarious watching the archeologists brush stuff super fast.
They're breaking skulls.
They're like, "Oh, I'm so scared."
Archeologists had like a year or two to do as much as they could with this place before
it was all underwater after this dam was completed.
But as they were going through it and they knew the history of the region they knew as
an agricultural center, they realized something.
Abu Hurayah was built on top of another village.
Now that's not super unusual.
Places got razed generally due to war or someone just wanted to rearrange the furniture so
they knocked down all the thatched huts and built like clay adobe huts.
But they started to notice something.
The village underneath Abu Hurayah was Hunter Gatherer.
The one on top of it was an agricultural, again, not just an agricultural place, but
an agricultural powerhouse.
And they go, "Okay, that makes sense.
We do know that hunter gatherer societies just stopped because it got harder to find
food.
There was an ice age at a certain point that lasted like 1300 years.
The woolly mammoth died off.
It became more difficult.
So people moved to agricultural.
This isn't, again, super unusual, fascinating, but not so fascinating that I'm going to get
drowned.
We can't spend a lot of time.
But what they start to notice is that in the old settlement, there's a ton of glass, a
ton of minerals that should not be there.
Now when I say glass, it's not like they had a neat little stained glass window there.
As they were looking at it, they said, "The only thing that could burn something this
hot, not just the glass."
They said, "Whatever was here, the entire village was torched."
They said it would take 3000 degrees Fahrenheit to do this level of damage to the soil.
And no village at that time period, 12,800 years ago, would be able to generate that
kind of heat.
They said volcanoes don't generate that kind of heat.
Doing all the soil samples, looking at everything they have, they come to the conclusion there
is a theory that about 12,000 years ago a comet or some sort of cosmic disaster happened,
plunged us into an ice age for 1300 years.
They believe this village was ground zero.
The theory is that a comet air burst over the village and nuked the entire area, burnt
it to the ground.
Everything that was there was instantly vaporized.
But what they also noticed was Abu Hurayah, the town that they knew of from historical
texts, had the same tools, they had the same cultural markers as the hunter-gatherer tribe
beneath it.
So the theory is that the hunters went out and the gatherers went out their respective
ways.
And then the village you had, the elders, you had the children, you had the children's
caretakers.
And while those two groups were away, the city was incinerated.
When the hunters and the gatherers returned, which I'm sure they would have heard that,
didn't matter if you were three days away on foot, you heard a nuclear blast.
When they returned, there was nothing left of the village, which you would obviously
chalk up to some sort of religious act.
So the theory is because the culture seemed the same through the artifacts that the hunters,
the gatherers came back and they just rebuilt a new town on top of it and they immediately
dropped their hunter-gatherer lifestyle.
They probably did it for a little bit.
They probably weren't like, "Oh, I need to wait for this wheat to grow."
No, no, no, don't hunt, don't hunt.
We gotta sit there and look at this wheat.
They said it wasn't the first tribe in the area to do agriculture, but it was the best
at it.
Which I'm wondering if somehow this cosmic radiation, Jason you're like, yesterday you
talked about Batman comic books, the world isn't fantastic for.
What if the cosmic radiation from, you're like Jason you were doing so well, just telling
a good science story.
What if the cosmic radiation from the comet actually did help them grow wheat and stuff
there?
Who knows?
Again, that's non-scientific, but this is known as the only human population center
that's ever been destroyed by a meteor or a comet.
It's never happened before as far as we know.
And there are people who say, "No, there was no younger dry-ass period," and that's what's
called when that mini ice age happened.
Yeah, it happened, but it didn't have anything to do with the comet.
The science isn't fully there on that, but the archaeologists and scientists who looked
at this area go, "The soil, this can only be generated by an air burst of a comet."
So this could actually be proof of that theory that a comet got caught into Earth's atmosphere
and plunged humanity into a mini ice age.
Either way, a fascinating story, whether or not my version where Audrey II came down
and it was like, "Grow wheat."
They're like, "What?
Grow wheat!"
Or just that this is the only time we know of a human civilization being wiped out by
an air burst or really in a sort of comet or meteorite.
Either way, it's an interesting story of human endurance.
They're like, "Oh, well, that sucked.
My kids were there and they all got incinerated, but let's build another town."
And it's actually now that I think about it, it is a story of human survival and human
endurance, but at the end someone goes, "Well, let's just build a dam here and all got washed
away even though the fire of the universe couldn't destroy this town."
Eventually some guy was like, "I want fresh water in my area."
So they flooded the entire thing.
But either way, I find it very, very fascinating.
Louise, let's go ahead and give you the keys to the carbonar copter.
I have a little Audrey II in a pot.
She's taking a ride with us.
Let's leave behind Syria.
We are headed out to the Grand Canyon.
Louise is actually flying through the Grand Canyon.
It's super dope.
Like that movie, Blue Thunder or Airwolf or one of those helicopter things.
This story actually originated on, I believe the export.
I saw a green text of it online.
I didn't see the original thread.
But we don't have a year.
We don't have a name.
These are things that happen when stuff is posted anonymously on the web.
Those are details I like, at least like a date.
However, you got to play the hand your dealt.
I do find it a fascinating story.
So we're still going to explore it.
Louise, land the helicopter right here.
And we're just going to walk along the bottom of the Grand Canyon.
And currently also at the bottom of the Grand Canyon, there are a bunch of Boy Scouts.
They're also on a little nature hike.
And the scout master is like, "Everyone, look, the Grand Canyon, this is...
Look on both sides of you.
Isn't it grand?
There's a wall on this side.
There's a wall on that side."
There's a little creek beneath us.
There's a swell.
And the other Boy Scouts are like, "Do we get a merit badge for like looking at both
canyon walls?"
And he's like, "You get two merit badges."
They're like, "All right.
We're going to call the narrator of this story.
Let's call him Bobby."
Bobby's a 14-year-old boy.
So Bobby is walking with the rest of this group through the Grand Canyon.
Now he explains that there's basically two groups here.
Fast walkers are at the front.
Slower people are near the back.
And he goes, "Listen, I did cross country at the time, but I had a friend who wasn't
very fast.
I kind of hung back with him because you're not just fun walking through the Grand Canyon.
He also says he's a big rock nerd.
Really, really enjoys the sedimentary life.
So he's walking through the Grand Canyon with his buddy.
And farther up ahead are the rest of them.
You know, Boy Scouts are pretty self-sufficient.
The Scoutman, they're not a bunch of babies.
The Scoutmaster knows that the kids in back are going to be able to take care of themselves.
So he's walking up there with the fast kids.
Bobby's walking and he's kind of just taking in all the geological formations around him.
His buddy's talking about probably Pokemon or something like that.
As he's walking through the Grand Canyon with his buddy and taking in all the sights and
the not sounds, just rocks, so there's no sounds, they're just there.
He sees a vein of andesite.
He thinks to himself, "That's weird."
Andesite shouldn't be at this point in the Grand Canyon.
This part of it shouldn't have that.
In fact, check, I don't know.
The only thing I know about the Grand Canyon is that it's a big old cut in the earth.
And so he goes, "Hey, man, I'm going to go check out this andesite vein."
The buddy knew he was a big rock nerd, so he didn't really think anything about it.
So Bobby starts kind of climbing up little ridges in the Grand Canyon.
He's not at the top.
He's not spired, man.
He didn't crawl all the way to the top, but he's kind of like working his way around
the sides, the bottom sides of the Grand Canyon.
He's following this andesite trail.
And then he says he comes across the flower that's popping out of this andesite vein.
He goes, "I've never seen a flower like it before."
To be fair, he's not a flower nerd.
This flower may exist, but he's looking at this flower and he said, "It was unusual
because it had green petals.
I hadn't seen a flower like this before."
And as he's kind of looking at the flower, he goes, "Something in me made me want to
touch the flower itself."
He says that when he pressed on the flower, the leaves almost acted as some sort of Venus
flytrap mechanism.
They close shut and at the same time, pollen shoots out of the flower and gets in his face.
This is why I like rocks.
They never hurt you unless it's a landslide or a rockslide of rocks, rocks, help, help.
He's getting hit in the face with all this pollen and he says almost immediately his
body goes into a state of panic, which would make sense.
I got shot in the face with a fire extinguisher more than once actually.
It sucked every time.
But the first time it happened, you get panicked because you don't know what's going on.
It sucks all the oxygen out of your lungs.
It totally sucks, dude.
I got shot in the face with a couple fire extinguishers.
The first time was the worst because you just...
[GASPING]
Like, you can't...
You go into an instant panic thing.
Now that was fine compared to what's about to happen to this guy.
But I can understand the second you're hit with some sort of bizarre powder.
It does kind of freak you out.
He said with this powder from this flower and he immediately feels fear wash over his body.
Not shock where you're emotionless, but pure fear and he starts to run away from the flower.
He scrambles down the mountain and at this point even the slower groups a bit ahead of
him because he kind of peeled off.
He's heading down, not the mountain, he's headed down the side of the Grand Canyon and
he's running and he sees the slow group in front of him and he starts to slow down.
The danger has passed.
Whatever that flower was is gone.
He's gonna go home and destroy all the flowers in his house with the mighty rock.
He starts to slow down as he gets to the group and as he's slowing down the fear begins
to well up in him once again.
Inhuman fear.
This isn't like I don't want to walk by a sewer grate because I'm afraid Pennywise is
gonna get me.
It's...
Pennywise has me and he's about to eat my soul.
It's the most intense fear you can experience.
He's slowing down, he feels it begin to well up in him, he begins running again.
He's running not just from the flower at this point, he's running from the fear.
He runs past the slow group.
"Hey Bobby where you going?"
He's running.
And as he's running he's feeling his body want to slow back down.
But every time he slows down the fear gets worse.
The only thing that keeps the fear at bay is the speed.
He's running, he's running through the Grand Canyon.
Imagine like a road runner cartoon, there's like dust kicking up from behind him.
He's running.
He's running so fast that he's very quickly gaining on the fast group.
And they were much farther up the canyon.
He's running and he can see the fast group in front of him.
He can't stop though.
He knows he can't stop.
People see him just hauling down the Grand Canyon.
They see a coyote shaped silhouette at the top with a box of dynamite.
They're like, "Uh."
They see him running through the canyon.
The Scoutmaster obviously knows something wrong.
He's thinking that someone must have got injured in the slow group.
And this kid's trying to warn him.
But as Bobby's approaching the fast group they can tell he's not slowing down.
He runs right past them.
The Scoutmaster at this point is now pursuing Bobby through the Grand Canyon.
As well as other Scouts are now trying to chase him down as well.
They have no idea what's going on.
They just know this kid is running, blows past him and is running to who knows where.
Eventually the Scoutmaster catches up to Bobby.
Scoutmaster gets ahold of him.
Bobby needs to run.
He's trying to his feeder up in the air.
His feeder kicking up in the air as the Scoutmaster is holding him.
Beep beep.
The Scoutmaster supposedly, this is where the story gets a little weird, but in the
flower this is where he starts to go, maybe.
Scoutmaster gets the kid in a chokehold and other kids also have to hold Bobby down.
And then Bobby passes out, like in an 80's action movie.
You can pass out and wake up later.
But whatever.
Again, this is where the story is going.
Yeah, maybe, but Bobby passes out and then he comes to later and everyone's standing
around him and they're like, dude, what happened?
And he tells the story about the flower.
They're actually on their way to a Native American reservation.
And when he got there, he asked, hey, you guys know anything about this flower?
And they're like, no, we've never heard of anything like that.
Now, like I said, I saw this on Reddit.
So you had a bunch of people saying maybe it was Dutura, maybe it was some sort of loose
indigent flower and things like that.
And they're kind of picking the story apart from that angle.
Going back to the green text itself, Bobby ended the story by saying, I thought this
was an interesting point.
He goes, that happened when I was 14 years old.
Every time I hear in the news or when I'm looking at stuff like Missing 411 or things
like that, and you hear about people disappearing in one location and then they're found 30
miles away and people always go, there's no way they could have done that.
There's no way they could have made that journey.
He said he ran six miles in 30 minutes.
He goes, I'm a fit guy, like he said, he was doing cross country, but I was completely
wasted.
They actually, when they were trying to figure out a way to get him out of the Grand Canyon,
at a certain point they were like talking about they went and got a horse to help get
him out of there because he was so physically beat, but he was able to get back to his feet.
But six miles and 30 minutes, he shouldn't have been able to do that.
Around a five minute mile is doable, but to be able to keep that up for six miles is very,
very difficult.
So that is an endurance thing.
He goes, but I reminded of my own experience with that flower whenever I hear about people
who are missing in one location and are found 30 miles away up on a cliff or something like
that.
That's an interesting little clue to stories like missing 411, where you have someone,
a kid even, go missing in the bushes and then they're found on the edge of a mountain top,
dead, people go, there's no way this kid could get up there.
But if the kid was under the influence of some sort of adrenaline drug, you could take
someone who was six or seven and basically run until they died.
That's what Bobby said.
He goes, if I was there by myself, I truly feel I would have ran until I just died.
I would have kept running.
And when I fell down to the ground, I would run in the circles, run in the circle like
the three stuages, whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop
whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop
whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop whoop
[music]
Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio.
Twitter is @deadrabberradio.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, and I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[music]