When a young boy starts having horrible stomach pains, he thinks he's just sick.
Instead, he laid an egg. An egg came out of his butt.
Then we travel back to the year 1909 to meet a young hypnotist putting on an amazing performance.
Everything is going perfectly until the finale begins. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys are
having a ton of fun out there. First off, let's give a shout out to one of our legacy
patreons coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now. Give it up for Andrew Light.
Everyone give him a round of applause. He's coming in a pure beam of energy.
Andrew, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode. If you guys can't support the
patreon, I totally understand. Just help spread the word about the show. Tell your friends,
tell your family, talk about it online. That is how you can also help Dead Rabbit Radio.
Andrew, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the oars for the Dead Rabbit Robo. We are leaving
behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're going to take a nice little relaxing rowing trip. It's very,
very far. I hope you have been working your upper body. We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're headed out to Gawa, Indonesia. Splash. Splash. I was recommended this story by Sheen
Anagins on Twitter. So thank you very much for sending me this absolutely, absolutely disgusting
story. A lot of times I say, don't eat while you're listening to this podcast. Actually,
I don't say it enough. I don't say it enough. I should warn you guys more often. This episode,
do not eat. Do not eat. I don't care how much food you've just prepared to sit down and listen
to an episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. Don't. Don't do it. If you're a condemned prisoner and this
is your last meal, if you're sitting there and you're about to be taken to the gallows
and somehow you're listening to this podcast, skip the meal. But thanks, Sheen Anagins, for
sending this story over. We're in Gawa, Indonesia. It's February 2018. There's a young boy named
Aukmal walking through town. I wish I was someone who'd driven me. Why am I walking like this?
Aukmal gets to the hospital and the doctors are like, "Oh, not this character again. Not Aukmal."
He walks in. He goes into his normal room. He's like, "I know. Room 6. Room 6." He hops up on
the little gurney. The doctors are like, "Listen, we have a Hippocratic oath. We do have to take
care of you even though you're sick, but we don't really believe you. We don't really believe what's
going on is happening." And it's not like this guy's making up symptoms. It's not like he has,
what is it, Munchausen syndrome. It's not like this little 14-year-old boy is pretending his
stomach hurts. His stomach really hurts. The doctors are fully aware that his stomach hurts.
The doctors know why his stomach hurts. They just don't understand how it hurts. This is completely
shocking the doctors and they've seen it before with this young man. As he's laying there on the
little gurney, a little egg pops out of his butthole and rolls across the gurney. The doctors are like,
"Ockmole, that is impossible. What we just saw is impossible. Humans cannot lay eggs."
Now, Shananigan sent me this story. I go, "This is so gross. I don't really like eggs that much to
begin with. And here's a human laying an egg. How do I know the eggs again from the store are actually
from chickens?" And I was telling my friend Sabine about the story and she goes, "That's impossible.
Humans can't lay eggs." I look at her and I go, "Yes, in normal world, but in dead rabbit radio
world, it is possible." I just can't cover this story and go, "That's impossible. That's not fun."
And there's video footage of this. Sabine did not want to watch the video footage. And this is
where the story really gets interesting because there's two layers to this. One is a human laying
eggs. That's interesting enough, but we know that's impossible. But doctors are saying this is
happening. There's photographs. There's video footage. So the other interesting part is the
investigative side. Here's what we know. This kid, he'd been doing this since 2016. Between 2016
and 2018, he has laid 20 eggs. Sometimes he would lay more than one in a day. Eggs coming out of his
butt. The family's like, "It's delicious. Hey, Aukmaa. How's your stomach doing?" He's like,
"Aww, they're like perfect." Eggs for breakfast. They're taking these eggs and they're cracking
them open. And oddly enough, the eggs are either all yolk or all white. The doctors go, "This is
impossible. A human can't lay eggs." But when they take an x-ray of him, there's eggs in him. There's
some of their eggs in his body, just one at a time. But there is an egg up there in the x-ray.
And the doctors are thinking, "Aukmaa is either swallowing eggs whole," which is a feat. That's
bizarre enough, right? He's either swallowing eggs whole. They're working their way down his
digestive tract. Or, more likely, he's stuffing them up his butthole. And they hurt. Your butthole
is not supposed to hold a chicken egg or really any egg, an ostrich egg. And he's pooping them out.
But they can't prove it. They have a 14-year-old boy come in and complain of stomach cramps,
and his family say, "No, he's not sticking them up his butt. He's laying eggs." The doctors are like,
"That is impossible." And this is where we get to the video. Videos. This is really interesting.
Daily Mail. It's almost like lost media, because there is a full video out there somewhere of
Aukmaa laying an egg. But really what it is, it's a 14-year-old boy having an egg come out of his
butthole. So that video is not-- I don't think that video is legal. I'm sure the doctors-- I'm
sure the doctors didn't even want to see it. They're like, "Ugh." There is a blurred screenshot
on the Daily Mail. There's a screenshot of it, and you see the egg coming out, but it's super
blurry, and you really don't want to see what the blur is anyways. And there is a portion of the video.
They show Aukmaa laying in this hospital bed, like this hospital rolling gurney thing. And he's
obviously in pain. He's groaning. Oh, he's clocking. He's pulling feathers out. He's obviously in pain.
And then they cut to the egg on the gurney, and he's just kind of like slumped around. He's like,
"Ugh, finally." And for whatever embarrassing reason-- I don't know if the staff of hospitals in
Indonesia are 13-year-old girls, or they just let a bunch of 13-year-old girls in, but I swear,
like, the video ends with Aukmaa laying an egg. There's a bunch of really, really young girls
taking photos of the egg with their cell phones. How'd they get in there? That would be so embarrassing.
It's being embarrassing enough to lay an egg in front of your family. And then that would just
be weird. But then laying an egg in front of a doctor, at least maybe he can help you. But just
imagine a bunch of random girls walked in, and they're like, "Oh, this'll be on my TikTok." Sorry,
Aukmaa, but that appears to have happened. He's all passed out. He doesn't even know until he's trending.
If you go to the Daily Store, they have a longer version of the video, but they don't actually
show the egg coming out of the butthole. And that's fine. I mean, as far as I wanted to, research
on this, I'm totally fine in not actually seeing that. But the whole video is out there somewhere,
because the Daily Mail had a screenshot of the egg coming out of the butthole.
And the doctors are saying that it's impossible for humans to lay eggs. And when you go to the
debunking websites for this, that's their answer. Humans can't lay eggs. It's impossible. But that
is- UFOs are impossible. Bigfoot being undiscovered for as long as impossible. Like, you could just-
that's not really skepticism by just going, "That's impossible." I mean, that's like lazy skepticism.
So I needed an answer to this. We all know this is impossible, but we covered the impossible on this
show. Is this boy actually laying eggs? As time has progressed in the story of Aukmaa, and they're
able to- I don't know why they didn't- I do not know why they didn't test this on day one, but around
2018, 20 eggs later, they do test the eggs. They're chicken eggs. And now the skeptic community goes,
"A human cannot lay chicken eggs." Well, that's no different than what you're saying before.
We know a human can't lay chicken eggs, but here is a man, a boy, laying a chicken egg. Explain that
science. You saw the x-ray. Scientists leave in the room. I'm still yelling at him. You saw the x-rays.
How does the egg not break in his butthole? They don't explain it. All of- like, it was so hard.
I was- I go, "There has to be a rational explanation for this." That's- gives us more information.
Yes, it is an impossible for a human to lay a chicken egg. Yes, but he's doing it.
And there was just a lot of articles written around February 2018 when the story made it
mainstream. And then a couple websites tried debunking it, and then there was nothing.
And that's usually how we see these stories go. Like, some event will happen, everyone will cover
it, and then no one will ever give you a follow-up. We've run into that a lot on this show, and I
really have to dig through stuff. And whenever you try search terms, it brings you back to this
flurry of articles in February 2018, because that's when it was mostly talked about. You have to change
your Google search terms for anything after February 2018. And I found something. I found
something. If you look for the story of Aukmal, you will find everything I talked to about. But
if you change your search filters for anything after that big mainstream news flurry of articles,
you'll find an article written in April 2018 called "Hatching Hoaxes" by Kenneth Young
for the Indonesian expat. Kenneth verified the video. I don't- I don't know if he watched
him himself, but Kenneth said yes. There are videos that exist of a boy pooping out eggs, but
he was stuffing them up his own butthole. Without a doubt, he was stuffing them up his own butthole.
And it had nothing to do with the fact that boys can't lay eggs, or girls can't lay eggs, or any
human can't lay a chicken egg. It had to do with the fact that eventually the Child Protection Unit
of Gawa, the Child Protection Unit of Gawa began investigating this, and they discovered this boy
was suffering from emotional disturbances and was sticking eggs up his own butt. So they took him,
they're treating him for psychiatric problems. Everything is normal in the world, and we wish
the best for Aukmal. And that's the end of the egg story, right? Humans can't lay eggs, right?
Well, as I was researching this story, the one thing that got the Doctor Show flummox is humans
can lay egg-like objects. This is 100% true. I do not recommend looking this up. I do not recommend
looking at photos of this. There is a thing called peritoneal loose bodies. It's a piece of fat from
your abdominal cavity. It kind of breaks loose. Have you ever heard of diverticulitis?
You're like, "I've heard of it, Jason. I've never heard of it pronounced like that before."
It's where your intestines get inflamed, like a little seed gets stuck somewhere and it gets
inflamed and it's super painful. This is something similar to that, but a piece of your
abdominal cavity breaks off. I know I didn't pronounce it right, but we're just gonna keep
going with it. The snowman, the yeti, is in your stomach. It breaks off of your... this little
piece of fatty tissue breaks off of the wall and your body starts floating around. It begins to calcify.
It's just this piece of fat that begins to grab onto things passing by. It's like, "Oh, that looks
delicious. Little piece of a baguette." And it calcifies and it gets thick and hard and large.
Now, usually, it's very small and you poop it out and you have no idea it's in there. But...
But sometimes these things... so disgusting. Sometimes just flashing back to these pictures
I saw. Sometimes these things will grow bigger than a chicken egg, but it looks exactly like a
chicken egg. 100%. There's photos of them reaching into... they had to do surgery to get one out of
this guy. There's photo of them reaching into his guts. And there's just an egg, a perfectly white,
clean egg sitting in this dude's intestines. This one doctor was shocked. He had his old man come in.
He was complaining of this horrible stomach pain. They couldn't figure it out. He hadn't pooped in
four days. They're trying to flesh him out. He's like, "This isn't helping. This isn't helping."
So they had to go in. This is like an emergency thing. They go in and the doctor goes, "Is that an...
See that? Is that an egg in this dude?" And they pulled it out. It was like five inches around. It was
this massive, twice the size of a chicken egg, but it was white and that oval egg shaped. Then they
cut it open. And because it's a piece of fat and has all this calcium, all these calcium deposits
around it, when they slice it in half, in the middle of it is this squishy... I don't know if it's
squishy. It looks squishy. I didn't touch the picture. It was this squishy looking grayish, yellow circle.
And the rest of the egg shape was a hard white substance. It looked just like a hard boiled egg.
Exactly, exactly like a hard boiled egg. First off, can you imagine what that smelled like?
You're like, "Jason, Jason, why'd you even say that? I didn't think about that."
Can you imagine what it smelled like when they cut it in half too?
Humans can lay egg-like items. So we're going all the way back around. All those articles just saying
they can't lay eggs. They can't lay eggs. They can't lay eggs. And yes, they can't lay an egg. A human
can't lay an egg and it can't lay a chicken egg. But there is a chance that tonight you will be
sitting there and you're like, "Oh man, what a delicious meal. And as you're batting your tummy,
because that's what I do after eating a meal. I rub my tummy. A little piece of fat breaks loose
from your abdominal wall. It's floating around. You've had it a little too hard. And then pretty
soon, "Oh my stomach. You're Jason. Why are you making your listeners go through pain for science?
And then time will go on and you'll swear there's an egg inside of you and you're telling your
doctors, "I think there's an egg in me." And they'll be like, "That's impossible. That is impossible."
And then you look at the camera and you wink, "Ding!" Because you know the truth. You know the truth.
I don't know why you want to just tell them you had one of these peritoneal loose bodies.
You're like, "Yeah, yeah, I know what it is. I don't know why I'm winking at a non-existent
camera." This could happen to you, dude. You're not going to stick eggs up in your butt. We know
that is not going to happen. But you could lay an egg-shaped object soon. I mean, it doesn't happen
overnight. It takes a while. I can't say it'll happen tonight. See, don't believe them when they
just say that's impossible. It was. It technically wasn't possible. They didn't... It wasn't an egg.
But I just kept digging and because I kept digging, I was able to share the fact with you
that someday you may lay a giant egg-shaped object.
Andrew Light, I'm going to go ahead and touch you the keys of the carbonicopter. We're leaving behind
Jakarta. We're waving goodbye. I really hope Aakmal is doing better. We are headed out to
Somerville, New Jersey. You know what's funny? Both of these stories are really about the
discovery of things. I didn't know humans could lay egg-shaped things. I never imagined what they
could smell like if they did. But now I do. Now I know those things. This is the same thing. Whenever
I thought about hypnotism, I thought it was a parlor trick at best. And I don't want to say a scam,
but a joke at worst. It may be a scam because you know you'd see those commercials or there's
ads and magazines about hypnotize me to stop smoking or to stop eating, stop eating so many eggs,
stop eating so many of those eggs that your children are laying for you in that human farm out
back. And I always thought, you know, maybe there's something behind it. But I don't know. I remember
when I was a kid, we were at the county fair, the state fair, there was a hypnotist on stage.
And he was asking for volunteers. And I remember thinking, "I'm going to do that. I'm going to do
that." And my dad, I don't know how old I was. I probably was about, I don't know, nine or six
or 12 or 24. I don't remember. But I remember thinking, I remember saying, my dad's not a telepath
to say this out loud, I want to volunteer. My dad put his hand on my shoulder and he says,
"Never volunteer for a hypnotist." Very, very, very weird parental advice, right? Very specific.
And here's why. He goes, "Never, ever volunteer for a hypnotist because you don't know what they're
going to have you do on stage." They may embarrass you, Jason. I never thought about that. I never
thought about that because apparently I was nine or six or 12 or 24 and I'd never seen a hypnotist
before. This was the first time I'd ever run into a hypnotist. Because if you believe in hypnotism,
you could go up there and he goes, "Act like a gorilla." And that's kind of funny because that's
a mighty beast. You're banging on your chest. You're stealing bananas. You grab a hot blonde
and climb up the whirley wheel. He could say, "Be a donkey." That's not a fun, impressive creature.
And then come out being hypnotized. You're in the middle of Mexico. You've been carrying
pails of water for some dude for the past three months. But I always thought it was a parlor
trick. I thought a lot of it was persuasion, persuading people. Plus, I've heard this before,
too, when you go up to get hypnotized on stage. They're like, "You're sleepy. You're sleepy."
And then you pretend you're asleep and he goes, "Be a duck. You don't want to ruin the guy's show."
You just go along with it and be the duck. I've heard that before as well. I always thought
hypnotism was either quack science or just a joke or an act. But I did a bunch of research on
hypnotism and it's so funny. When I started researching this story, I thought, "I'm not going
to do a huge overview on hypnotism. Everyone knows what it is." But as I kept researching,
I thought, "I don't really even know what hypnotism is." Hypnotism? So I'm going to do this overview.
I'm going to do this overview. Hypnotism is thousands of years old. But that's like self-hypnotism.
That's meditation becoming one with the universe, eliminating all thought. Thousands of years old.
But the way we think of hypnotism with going, "You are getting sleepy. I'm going to give you
commands you're going to do." That is super recent. Late 1800s. That is very, very recent in human
history. And it used to be called mesmerism because it was named after Franz Mesmer. He was the guy
who believed this thing called animal magnetism that you could affect people simply by your presence.
He was kind of the forefather of hypnotism and that's why they originally called it mesmerism.
And that is a term that's used interchangeably. So hypnotism, two people sitting across from
each other and one going into the other person's thoughts and controlling them, super recent.
And this is what makes me think it's not a quack science. And a quack science would basically
be like a healing crystal. Your knee hurts. I'm going to put this crystal on your knee.
Your knee doesn't hurt anymore. The crystal did it. And you don't think of the fact that you
weren't trying to balance a crystal on your knee. So you kept it elevated for a long period of time.
You weren't putting weight on it. That's probably why your knee is better. That's quack science.
It doesn't really work. This stuff works apparently, like based on this research,
works so well. It's very, very dangerous. Extremely dangerous hypnotized people.
June 22nd, 1903 in Shenandoah, Pennsylvania, there was an amateur hypnotist. And this is very,
we're going to see a thread here through these stories. John Hilde, an amateur hypnotist,
is at a local bar. He sees a pretty girl named Jenny B. Berninsky. It's a parlor trick. He's
just trying to get the attention of a pretty girl. Hey, how would you like to be hypnotized?
She says, yeah, sure. And he puts her under. He does his little hypnosis thing and actually puts
her into a state of unconsciousness. But he can't bring her back out of it. She's stuck like that.
Until 2pm the next day. That happened on June 22nd, 1903. This article in the Clinton County Times
newspaper was published on June 26th, four days later. And in that article, it said she was still
in critical condition. And there was no follow-up to that. There was no Google search I could find
after that. She was catatonic for hours and hours and hours on end. And when they brought her out,
she was still in critical condition four days later. There's a website called the Brookside
Center for Counseling and Hypnotherapy. They say it's very, very important if you are going to do
hypnotism. I never even thought about this before. I just thought it was some goofy thing. Never,
ever use hypnotism to treat people for something that you don't know how to treat without hypnotism.
There's a thing called dental hypnosis, where the dentist will hypnotize you to help you remain
calm during the procedure. They'll still give you all the pain medication. They'll still do the
novocaine. But some people have tremendous anxiety with going to the dentist and some dentists use
dental hypnosis. And at the Brookside Center for Counseling and Hypnotherapy, they tell this story.
There was a dentist who did this and it was very, very successful. And his patient goes,
"You know what? I used to have such horrible issues with going to the dentist, but now I don't
and thank you for your hypnotherapy. Could you use your hypnotherapy to help me stop smoking?"
He says, "Yeah, sure. Totally." So he does. He uses the same hypnotherapy techniques to get
this woman to stop smoking. And she does stop smoking. But she's hit with crippling anxiety,
crippling depression. She can't go through the day without being overloaded by obsessive thoughts.
Eventually, she can't even complete normal everyday tasks. Never ever use hypnosis for something that
you can't treat without hypnosis. He doesn't know how to get someone to stop smoking. But he did it
anyways and he messed with her mind. It's fascinating because you're basically fiddling around with the
brain is what you're doing. And this makes me think it's real because if it was a hoax,
then there would be really no downside to it. You also, it's interesting, you have to be careful
what you say. This is bordering on like a wishmaster curse. According to the journal Clinical Hypnosis,
Principles and Applications, there's a story about a burn patient who was having difficulty
eating. They don't want to eat anymore. So they hypnotized them and put them under and said,
"It's okay. You can eat. Eat everything on your plate. You'll be fine. It's okay."
Well, one day this burn patient was eating and got sick and began to vomit, began to throw up
all the food they just eaten and the vomit was hitting the plate. And after they were done vomiting,
someone walked into the room and this burn patient was eating the vomit, not even thinking about it.
Clean your plate. Eat everything on your plate. It's rewiring of the human brain.
It's easy to mess stuff up with. But all of those stories really pale in comparison to where we're
going now. Andrew, land this carbonar copter in Summerville, New Jersey. It's November 8th,
1909. We're the Summerville Opera House. So hope you guys brought your tuxes. Hope you guys are
always dressed in your finest clothing before you listen to this podcast. There's a travel
lean magician/hypnotist, obviously. Otherwise, I would have done a whole overview on magic,
named Professor Arthur Everton. And he's on stage and he's like, "Do I have a volunteer?
Who wants to be part of my hypnotist show and my old time dad is holding old timey Jason?"
And he's like, "Let's leave now." People get nervous during hypnotist shows. People don't
always want to go up on stage. So there's a term for an assistant. They're called a horse
because they lead the audience on. It's very, very common for hypnotists to have this. When
you're calling for an audience member to sit up on stage, what if nobody does?
That's kind of a bum wreck to your hypnotist. There's not anything else you can do. So hypnotists
have these people called horses. And Arthur Everton's horse is his good buddy, Robert Simpson,
a 35 year old man. They both used to be piano movers. That was his job before he broke into the
hypnotist game. He was just a hard working dude, Arthur. And that's where he met Robert. He goes,
"Hey, I'm doing this hypnotist thing. Would you like to join me on tour?" And Robert's like,
"No, I don't think so." And then he gets hypnotized. The next thing he knows,
he's in like a showgirl outfit. He's like, "Oh, how did I get here?"
Robert Simpson is the horse. So he'll jump up. He'll get on stage. They do the thing. And then
other people go, "Oh, that looks fun. Betty, you go up there." And other people start doing it.
The hardest time to get people on stage is the beginning and the end. Because stuff gets more
and more ludicrous as the show goes on. So someone goes up, you realize it's not that bad.
A bunch of normal people go up. And then to finalize the show, you have someone else go up
if no one else volunteers. Now, in this particular situation, Robert Simpson was the final horse.
Because no one else was volunteering. Robert Simpson, it was his job to volunteer at last.
Oh, shucks. I guess I'll do it. He goes up on stage. When I'm saying these people are the horses,
they're accomplices is what they are. They are truly being hypnotized. They're not faking it.
They are truly being put under. It's just, I don't want to make it think that it's some scam.
They are actually hypnotizing them. But they're just, they know the process. They know the guy
they're totally comfortable with that they're fine with walking around pretending they're a
chicken, stuff like that. Or really thinking they're a chicken because they're actually hypnotized.
Arthur has other assistants. It's this full show. I mean, I say he's an amateur hypnotist.
I mean, he has a production company. He is on tour. So he has assistants,
and they're bringing out these two chairs and they send them about six feet apart.
He brings Robert up and he starts doing his pitch and he goes, I'm going to hypnotize you,
Robert, and you're going to become stiff as a board. That's pretty easy, right? Some guys
probably like, oh man, I should have volunteered for that. That sounds easy. And so he hypnotizes
Robert. Robert gets sleepy, sleepy, and then becomes as rigid as a board standing up.
Arthur's two assistants then grab Robert and place him across the chairs. So his head was on
the back of one of these chairs and his ankles were on the back of another one. That's impossible.
I mean, it may be a really good core workout. If you really nailed your planks, you could do that.
But to have the back of your head on one chair and then nothing supporting you and then your ankles
on the other chair, this man's truly hypnotized. That's not the whole trick. I mean, that's enough
of a feat that a man is perfectly still between these two chairs. This is the finale of the show.
Arthur jumps up on one of the chairs and walks across Robert. He's standing on Robert, who is
still stiff as a board, and Arthur begins to jump up and down. Arthur begins to jump up and down on
this dude and then walks off of him. I'm zooming in instead on his face. Takes a little bow.
Amazing act. Everyone's applauding. The two assistants take Robert off of the chairs,
stand him back up, and then Arthur goes, "Relax!"
Robert immediately goes limp and as he is crumpling down, the back of his head hits one of the chairs.
He's now just laying motionless on the ground. Some people are still clapping. They still think
this is all great, so I've never seen a man crumple like that. Woo! On core! Arthur realizes something
is wrong right away and the audience realizes as well when he begins calling for old timing 9-1-1.
In fact, then it was just one. Eventually, the doctors show up and Arthur is standing over Robert
going, "Wake up! Wake up! The hypnosis is over. Wake up!" And he's giving these commands to come
out of this trance and Robert's just laying there. The doctors looking at each other and they're like,
"What? Well..." They get close. Now, and nowadays, if this type of situation would happen, you'd take
you to the hospital, they'd start running brain scans on you. Back then, these doctors get there
and they go, "This man is clearly dead. He's dead." They really don't have any other way to test him
other than cutting him up to see if his heart's still beating. But his heart isn't beating. I mean,
at least have stethoscopes and stuff like that. There weren't caveman doctors. But nowadays, they
would still take you to the hospital just to figure it out. But the doctor's to clear him dead
of the scene and Arthur goes, "He's not dead. He's just hypnotized." Wake up! Wake up, Robert!
Robert, come out of the trance. He spends hours trying to revive Robert. Because again, the
doctors know that he's dead. It's not like, "They're like, 'Well, if you let us take him,
you know, 30 minutes ago, we would have saved him.' The doctors, by the time they get there,
he was dead. They don't know what killed him yet, but they can tell that he's dead."
Arthur is arrested for manslaughter and he is adamant. "You gotta give me another chance."
Like, "Wait, do we give you a couple hours of chances?" He goes, "Okay, you're right. But what
if I brought in another hypnotist, one of the greatest hypnotists that I have a phone number
two? There's a lot of great ones out, but I can contact this guy. His name is William Davenport.
He's actually a professor at Columbia University and an expert hypnotist."
Arthur explains what's going on and William goes, "Oh, man, it's clearly simply hypnotized. Did you
try waking him up for hours on end, of course?" William comes to the morgue. "This guy's been
dead for a while now." William comes to the morgue. The doctors are down there. The police are down
there. Arthur is down there. And we have this quote from this news article. William is standing over
Robert and saying, "Bob, your heart, Bob, your heart, your heart is beating. Bob, your heart
action is beginning. It is beginning. Oh, I say, Bob, look, your heart is beginning to beat."
He does this for four hours. And sometimes he's being very polite. Sometimes he's talking very
politely to Robert. Other times he's screaming in his ear, "Bob, your heart action is strong.
Bob, your heart begins to beat." But it doesn't work. At this point, since all of the hypnotism
tricks have been tried, they do an autopsy on Robert. He died of a ruptured aorta.
I didn't have anything to do with the blow on the back of his head. And the question is,
the fact that Arthur was jumping him down on his chest, did that have to do with the ruptured
aorta? And the coroner goes, "No." The coroner goes, "We can actually tell, based on everyone who
was in the audience and Arthur and all the assistants, when Robert died. He didn't die when
he was being jumped on. He would have crumpled there immediately. He would have totally ruined
the show. Arthur jumped up and down on his chest, walked off. They picked him up, held him up right
for a bit. And then Arthur said, "Relax." That is when he died. That is when his aorta ruptured.
It's possible that his aorta would have ruptured if he had simply sat in the audience a little bit
longer. We cannot say definitively. I mean, to be fair, if you're jumping him down on your chest,
probably didn't help things. But the coroner said this was an accidental death. Arthur stopped being
a hypnotist after that. I don't think he could probably get any more assistance. He stopped being
a hypnotist after that. He only shows up one other time in history. I got this from a mysterious
universe article, this cool little detail. I'll be in the show notes. He got busted for running
liquor during prohibition. And as he was being arrested, he told the officers, "You guys are
lucky. I could have hypnotized all of you. I could have hypnotized all of you and gotten away.
Scott, free. I have a bunch of chairs. I have a bunch of chairs I can lay to you on." They're like,
"Get in that car, you rumbum." So even then later, even though he was an hypnotist on stage,
he was still boasting of his hypnotic powers. Maybe he perfected them over time. Maybe it was
just a boast. It's a terrifying story to think about. It's either the story of a hypnotist who
had an unfortunate accident and lost his best friend, or the story of a hypnotist who got a
little too big for his britches and performed a feat of strength and mental mind control that
got his friend killed. But then there's another version of it. Let's put on our conspiracy
caps to wrap it up like this. What if Arthur and William were right? What if he was just hypnotized?
He was told to go as stiff as a board, basically inanimate. And Robert complied.
When he was told to relax, his body became loose, but he didn't awake. His mind was still in a body
that couldn't move, that couldn't speak. He was trapped from the outside world, and he hears
his friend standing over him, "Wake up, Bob. Wake up." And he can't. He's waiting for the right
combination of words, the right command, to pull him back into the world of the living, where his
senses are fully functional, and he can have a good laugh and a drink with his buddy afterwards.
But he's trapped there for hours, he can hear his buddy calling his name, and he can't wake up.
He feels himself being lifted up by strange hands, throwing onto a gurney,
throwing in the back of an ambulance, taking to the county morgue.
He loses track of time, how long he's in that solid black room. There's no sound,
there's no light, there's no warmth, until he feels motion, and the morgue door is slit open,
and his little cart is dragged out of this small hole in the wall, where he can once again see light.
And for four more hours, he sees Arthur out of his peripheral vision,
worried, surrounded by police officers. He sees a man he's never met, commanding him
to come back to life, commanding his heart to start beating again. Robert wants nothing more,
but the right combination of words hasn't been said yet, he is still asleep.
Eventually he is put back into his small cubby hole in the morgue, for another
indeterminal amount of darkness and fear, until one more time that door is slit open,
he is brought out as men wearing masks stand around him, prepared to do an autopsy.
He is still alive when they cut into his skin. The coroners don't understand how no one realized
this until just now, but Robert was still alive, and they knew this would be the end of their careers
if this news got out. So one of them takes a small scalpel and simply nicks Robert's aorta.
Robert never woke up from his hypnotically induced coma, but as he bled out in that morgue,
Robert was finally released from the prison of his own body.
DeadRabberRadio.com is going to be your email address. You can also
search us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great night guys.
[Music]