When a drowning man is resuscitated and brought back to the world of the living, he has to wonder
What world is he now living in?
And then we take a look at the story of Marcus who when he was only nine months old his father died in a tragic accident
So how is it possible that 20 years later when Marcus was out on a camping trip?
He stared off into the forest
And saw his father
staring back today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys are having so much fun
We only got two episodes left until the end of season 18. After that, I'm gonna take a two-week break, but I will be back
After those two weeks, I will also be doing my YouTube shorts, TikToks, the whole time
So if you want more Dead Rabbit Radio, just tune into the YouTube or the TikTok or the Instagram
I post this stuff everywhere, but daily one-minute true crime videos
They take me like five minutes to do so I'm not taking a break off of those
But someone who I never take a break off. Maybe I'll take a bite out of walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now
I'm so hungry. Give it up for Strand. Woohoo. Yeah
Licking our lips. We're gonna eat you up Strand. Strand. Strand of spaghetti, hopefully. Strand
You're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon
I totally understand. Just help spread the word about this show that really really helps me a lot
I won't make any promises that I won't eat you, but I'll try not to. Strand, let's go ahead and break out the hair
Hovercraft. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're gonna glide all the way out to Tyler, Texas
Is that the sound of hovercraft makes? I really only know it from the GI Joe toys and as we're going out there too
I want to say check out the newest episode of the asylum case studies
The asylum case studies is a podcast that I've been lucky enough to be a part of a couple times and on this news episode
Me and the host Tressa we review the movie Megaparana. It was terrible
It was a fun experience the movies awful so as strand is using this hovercraft watch over those megaparana's - I should have warned
I should have warned strand before he took it out. I realized his head is gone
He's getting eaten a lot in this episode. He's now officially dead strand. We'll put your head back on take us out to Tyler, Texas
And let's take a look at this story here
This story takes place. We don't really have a time for this, but I'd say probably in the past ten years in Tyler, Texas
There is a man
Being pulled out of the water. Come on. Help me get him up
They're like his friends are straining to get him out and they throw him on the ground that he's all
He's like dying and stuff and they're like hurry up dude hurry up guys do that thing
We saw do the thing we saw and people like what do we watch a lot of stuff or adults?
We've seen tons and you know the thing like you push on his tummy and you breathe in his mouth
So they're like okay, so they're doing that. They're giving him CPR and then all of a sudden
He spits up a bunch of water. Do you like that sound effect? It sounded like I was actually coughing and
He sits up and he's like whoa
Where what what where am I guys? What wait who are you? Who are you guys? What's going on?
What happened his friends are like dude you won't believe it like you drowned
He's like who are you guys and
This is the journey of this young man. We're gonna call him. We don't have a name for this. We're gonna call him Terrence
Terrence has no idea where he is
Terrence has no idea
who he is
Because he's looking at this group of people. He goes. I don't know any of you. I don't know why I'm at what's going on
The last thing I remember I was hanging out with one friend one one friend. I remember being inside
I don't remember being in Tyler, Texas
What is going on and his friends have to convince him?
I don't know how wondering how much oxygen your brain was deprived of but you are Terrence and
We're your friends and we're down here at this body of water and you almost drowned and he goes no
None of that is true
none of it
So of course if your friend was doing this of course you're gonna call an ambulance right you're gonna take him down to the
Hospital you're gonna do something so that's what they do they take one hospital because they go we were really concerned about you like
You would have to have some serious level brain damage to have this level of amnesia
To just not know anything and they're like would be the trauma queen you're only in the water for ten minutes
Your lips are only half blue so he goes to the hospital and they run a bunch of tests on him. He's totally fine
He didn't have massive amounts of oxygen deprivation
He didn't suffer any sort of brain damage that they can tell and they're like, okay, you can go ahead and take your friend home
He's okay, and it's like what are you talking about? What home? I'm not from around here. I'm not Terrence. I
Don't know what's going on and they're like great the doctor at that point already locked him out of the hospital your problem
He's your problem now. We already ran all the tests so they take him home
And he walks in the house. He's like this is exactly what I figured. I don't know this house
But the thing is as much as he's saying he doesn't know any of this stuff everyone knows him
And he walks in the house. It's not like familiar to him at all
But it's his house. He starts to go through like old yearbooks because at this point you would start to be convinced maybe I
Am Terrence
Well when he starts finding physical evidence right when he's going through old yearbooks and it's like pictures of him
He's like
Opens it up. Nobody signed it except for his mom signed it. You're my superstar
He's like oh man super depressing. I wake up in someone else's life, and he's a tweed
He goes through old yearbooks
He's in him
What is he going to do right? So he's like obviously I must have just forgotten this stuff, but maybe not
He's at this war with himself, but while he's in this life
He has a job
Right, he doesn't do it. It's a totally different job than he remembers when he's like I should just do this job
I guess he's walking into the police station because I guess I'm a detective
Is he's interrogating murder suspects? They're like I didn't do it. He's like yeah, probably I don't know
I don't remember any of my training. You're free to go bloody hobo. He's walking out
He's like man that's got that bloody hobo sure was honest with me
He has a totally different job than he remembers totally different life than he remembers and
four years go by and
for four years he is slowly
Complimating to what he thinks is a new life, but everyone around him goes no Terrence. This is you
So for four years he goes in he's doing all of his stuff
And he goes you know I've been holding on to this past for so long
And maybe it was
Maybe it was just maybe it was just a dramatic brain injury. I
Think I need to stop focusing on the past and be Terrence
And what happens is as he starts to make that change things
Get better and over the next four years
Right the first four years he was fighting it now the next four years
He actually got a promotion at work
His social life is doing well. He's
Frigging him out by going who are you who are you?
He was like I may not remember exactly who they are or who they were but they you know
I should hang out with these people they are calling me constantly going are you okay Terrence?
Or we're still really worried about you so he gets a promotion at work
He's making new connections with his friends his social life's working out and the next four years of his life
Are some of the best four years of his life or at least the best four years he can remember
And then one day
He wakes up face down in a puddle of his own piss
In a dirty room in his best friend's house
He's feels this
Warm urine on his cheek and he's looking at the carpet. He rolls over and he goes
Dammit, I'm back in my real life
That's the story of a man who used salvia one day
Salvia is a it's it's such an interesting drug. It's legal a lot of places
Do it I hope that was a story that didn't make you go
I should try that so it's a super hardcore mind-altering drug and I know there's a lot of
Psychonauts out there and to be like well technically doesn't alter your mind it messes with your brain whatever chemical
Reaction that has it's not good and this the story this man's story is one day
His buddy goes hey you want to smoke some salvia and he said sure and he took a hit and
The next thing you know he woke up in Tyler, Texas being pulled out of the water
while his friends are trying to bring him back to life and he lived eight years in
Tyler, Texas as this new person and in reality he was probably high for maybe
Like a couple minutes
Right, so he wasn't in the puddle of his for eight years his friends are like
Ah, he'll pick himself up eventually the whole trip like generally when you do salvia it lasts for about five minutes
And then you figured give him extra two minutes to be on himself
So he's probably down there for a list in ten minutes, but in his brain
It was an eight-year journey in another man's life
Salvia salvia is I've never done salvia. I've been offered it many a times
I've never done it, but I've known really close friends of mine who have done salvia
And it's it's a trippy drug not not because it literally takes you on a trip
It does that but the way it works one of my cousins a very very good friend of mine named Billy
he was into all sorts of drugs and
He tried salvia and I'll always ask people to do it. So who was like well like what was your trip because it's always crazy
He goes I smoked so I've sent him on my porch, right? This is orange veal. So you could do this. He was sitting on his porch
And he was smoking salvia and he goes all the I might have told the story before in the podcast
So excuse me if I'm repeating myself. I find it so fascinating my buddy Billy cousin Billy is smoking
Salvia on the porch. He goes I took a hit and the next thing I know I was a brick. I
Was a brick I go what he goes. I was a brick
Like a brick in a building. I turned into a brick
He goes specifically it was like just my head like I still had my body
but my head was a brick and
The brick was in he goes I could look both ways and I could look up and down
He goes it was a brick wall that went on for infinity
in
Every direction he goes I looked and I looked to my right and I looked to my left and I just see
Nothing but billions of bricks in both directions and up and down he goes and it scared me so bad
I was trying to get out of the brick wall
And I put on a little pink Floyd and everything was okay. You know, he goes I jumped up
I because I knew my body was still humid and I begin running as fast as I could
Down green back which is a main thoroughfare in Orangeville. He's running down green back
He's over by the youth center right a past
Telling you guys exactly where this is that if you ever want to visit it. It's past
Cable Park you keep going
There's like a youth center on the right hand side if you're headed towards Roosevelt
Anyways, he's running down the street. He's giving people directions. He's like no keep go and turn make a lefty cable park
He's running down the street as fast as he can. He goes where the wall was moving with me
And no matter how fast I ran I
Could just feel the wall there was no escaping
the wall
And it lasted like for five minutes and then he turned back
to cousin Billy
Now when he told me that story I laughed I laughed so hard because I could just imagine him running down the street just sweating
afraid that he was a brick wall, but
My cousin Billy is now doing 17 to life in prison
Because he killed the dude
stabbed him
And so you think is that story
What was he seeing a future now he was into some stuff, right?
He was into some stuff and I remember once we were talking and he goes Jason. I hope I never kill anybody. I
Hope I never kill anybody, but he lived a life where that was possible
Right that was something that could happen
So the question is is like did the salvia show him the future?
I mean, I hope he gets out right. I hope he gets out. I really need to write him
It drives me nuts that I don't write him, but you have to think was it showing him in the future
Did he already feel like he had nothing he was just a brick in an endless wall just another rat in the rat race?
Or is it actually showing like this is your future now? He could have changed it, right?
I don't think the future is predetermined
But it's so fascinating salvia so fascinating then you have a story like this and what I find interesting about this is we talk so much on
This show and we'll actually kind of mention it on tomorrow's episode last episode quantum immortality, right?
We talk about it a lot on this show and I find it endlessly intriguing
That's kind of what this is quantum immortality is where you dying you slot into another body
No, I'm not saying this guy died because he did salvia, but what if it triggered the same thing?
What if he actually did go into the body of someone in Tyler, Texas who had died and then it popped up with his new personality in it and
Then he's going around like was it totally hallucination
Or did he actually in another timeline spend eight years in this body and if he hadn't jumped into that body that body would have just been dead
They would have mourned their friend who drowned that day and that would have been the end of it
But because this dude teleported into the body of Terrence they got another eight years with him
I don't know fascinating fascinating story
And I let me source this too because some of you guys may be familiar with this story
I found this on the X board
Someone was talking about salvia and they said they heard it on a podcast now because the exports completely anonymous
I don't know what podcasts it's from some of the details may because we're playing a game of telephone at this point
They heard it on a podcast. I'm hearing it from this anonymous poster, but they had a really interesting thread on
The export about salvia experiences and the poster who told that story said his question was like what in the world is salvia
He tells that story
I just told you about in Terrence was a fake name right well. He was a fake person
Right. He was who knows who that person was or if he even existed Terrence from Tyler, Texas
He also shares this story. It's very short
He says I also heard a story about a guy who was doing salvia once and he hit it and the next thing he knew
He was a coat of paint on the side of a barn and
He was that coat of paint on the side of a barn for 20 years
and
He felt every minute of just being pasted on that barn every minute of every day for
20 years and
Then he's back with us
So what is salvia do you actually teleport to another reality?
Did he go to another body or did he just imagine all of this and then you'd wonder when you'd wake up out?
I remember once I read a story a long time ago these two dudes the very
hilarious the very first time the very first time these two guys were smoking some salvia it was September 11th 2001 and
They smoked it and then who's interrupted and they're like a plane just crashing to the World Trade Center and
I remember hearing this story like in 2005 and they go we don't know what's real like as we still can't
Figure out if this is real where where we are. They're currently deployed into Iraq. They're like guys wake up. Wake up
We're in Fallujah. They're like, I don't know. I don't know this all be a dream
Yeah, they smoked it and the news turned on right whatever they were watching the view or whatever and it the news got interrupted with a plane
Crescent of World Trade Center and they sat there. They were like all these years later. We don't know what's real
We don't know if we smoked ourselves
Into the war on terror which to them that's what it would feel like they took it some salvia and then as their trip was starting
Everything changed in America fascinating fascinating. I again. I'm not saying you guys should do it
I think it's probably highly dangerous, but and it doesn't seem to be super recreational
I'm surprised more people don't do it
Turning what coat of paint on the side of a barn for 20 years. Do people abuse cough syrup?
Strand let's go ahead and touch the keys of the carbon or cofter. We are leaving behind Tyler, Texas or are we?
We're headed all the way out to
the Pacific Northwest
1982-ish around that time is when this story starts off and we're in the Pacific Northwest
And there we're gonna meet a little boy named Marcus. It's not his actual name. That's the name we're gonna be going
We don't know the person's actual name
Marcus was a little nine-month-old baby. So what do you do at nine months?
You just kind of gurgle and roll around on your tummy. He's doing that
He can't he's not even smart enough to do it at the same time. He has to roll then girl and
While Marcus was just being bounced on somebody's knee
His father and his father's friends were down at the river and they had a canoe and it got stuck. Oh
Come on man. They're trying to move the canoe off
Trying to get off these rocks and they go hey Marcus is dead
That's the only name they know by the only reason he's cool because he has a cool baby
Hey Marcus his dad can you come over here and help us get it unstuck and Marcus's dad was like sure and they're
fighting with the canoe trying to get it off the rocks and
The undertoe snags up Marcus's dad
pulls him under a
Few days later and a couple miles down the river
Marcus's dad turns back up. He's dead. He had drowned
That wasn't a theme. I wasn't trying to do a drowned theme episode
I didn't even think about it when I put these two stories together
But Marcus's father passed away when he was only nine months old
Never gonna flash forward 20 years were around the year 2002 and
Marcus finds himself camping in
The same area where his father passed away like after 20 years, right?
He didn't really even get to know the dad like I don't know if a friend of mine got killed on a certain city block
If I would feel comfortable going back there
I'm like, oh no, he died in the only Chipotle in town. No
You know what I mean like life goes on
Life goes on my uncle Jeff got shot in that gang shooting at a jack-in-the-box
In orange veil and I still went to that jack-in-the-box
I mean like it happened when I was a little kid, but I'll admit when I went to the jack-in-the-box
I was always like, uh
Like I was never happy because you'd have to sit in that drive-through and you'd be like oh
This is where uncle Jeff got shot right. I did a whole episode on on that. I'll put that in the show notes
Well, I was like, yeah, we you'd end up going to the jack-in-the-box
The only jack-in-the-box within like 20 miles or whatever, but it's like oh man
So I get it like you would go back. He didn't even really get to know his dad, right?
I knew uncle Jeff on the other side. He survived the shotgun blast to the head, but it really messed them up
anyways
What's it talking about? Oh, yeah, I was talking about this story. It was talking about this story
I'm supposed to be talking about so he goes to hang out of the river because it had been such a long amount of time
And what else are you gonna do? It's the place where you hang out
So there 20 years later Marcus is on a camping trip with his girlfriend
His best friend and his best friend's girlfriend
So it's a little quartet a little group of four people
Headed up camping and you know what? It seems like Marcus kind of needs a camping trip when you look at not only
Marcus's story when he wrote this out when you look at other posts that he made he struggles a lot with depression
struggles a lot with depression and he even states that he has had
Run-ins
with suicide
I don't know if that means suicidal ideation or if he's attempted suicide
But he does say that you know suicide has played a factor in his personal life. He's posting on the depression subreddits
And he mentions suicidality in this story as well
So it's 9 30 p.m. And him and his best friend they kind of walk away from the camp
The girls are being attacked by badgers. They're like, oh you guys can handle it
They walk away from the camp and there's like this rocky outcropping and both of them are just sitting there smoking cigarettes
And Marcus is looking out over the river
The same river
that his father drowned in
And not the exact same location
But the same general area
He's smoking a cigarette and he's sitting on this rock
He looks across the river and he sees someone standing there
Someone's standing there and this person is staring at Marcus
Now, you know what? It's a public area
You're allowed to stand and stare where you want to stare, but it's a little late to just be standing in the forest
Right? It doesn't look like he has a camp set up
What's this guy doing there and as Marcus is looking at this guy it dawns on him. This just isn't some random dude
That's his dad
Now he was nine months old when his father died. He never really got to see him or he did see him, but he didn't really remember it
But over the years
You know, he'd seen photographs people talked about his father
He can kind of put a mental picture together and he goes that's clearly
Who was standing on the other side of this river?
Somehow through the distance somehow through the darkness he knew this was his dad and he turned to his friend
He goes do you see that guy over there?
And the friend looks over and goes what?
No, I don't see that at all. What are you looking at? Is there like a deer or something?
And as Marcus is staring at this figure all of a sudden a spotlight appears
Suddenly the area around his father is lit up. He can clearly see now
This is his father
The man turns and starts walking about 20 feet to his left
And then moves a little bit back into the tree line
But Marcus still can clearly see his dad
turn around
And pick up a bag and start kind of rustling through a bag
Marcus is shaking at this point
He's watching his father prepare something
His best friend goes dude, what what are you looking at? What's wrong?
But Marcus can't even speak he knows that from the best friend's point of view
He's just staring out into the darkness. He's just looking at nothing
But he sees this entire area clearly illuminated by some sort of spotlight that is shining on his father
And the dad turns around now
And he's holding a noose
He throws one into the rope up over a tree branch
Ties it down
Puts the noose around his neck
Stares directly into Marcus's eyes
And then hangs himself
And even while hanging there as he slowly sways back and forth
The entire time he's staring
directly at
Marcus
You have to imagine right that this would open up a whole lot of questions
First off first off did I bring enough pants because I pooped in these like that would be a terrifying thing to see
But once a little bit of time and a little bit of distance is between this horrific vision
Or haunting or whatever you want to call it
Marcus starts to
This is so this is where Marcus goes with this and I totally think this is a valid way to look into this Marcus went into this whole thing thinking
Was I lied to
Was I lied to because people do do this this does happen
He goes what I started to think was that my father did not die by accident
My father killed himself
And he was showing me that he killed himself
And that took him on such a journey that he began questioning
Members of his family was like hey, what happened to my dad and they'd be like well
He's trying to get that canoe loose and he drowned be like well, you know, I think I'm old enough now
I think you can tell me the truth and be like what are you talking about? He drowned
He took this journey so far. He's questioning his family
He goes and he gets a copy of the death certificate of his father
accidental
So
That's one way to look at it, right? You're at the place where your father died and families do often cover up suicides
Suicide tends to run in families
Right if you have a close relative who committed suicide the chances of you committing suicide go up
Father committed suicide. I can imagine it doesn't guarantee it. It doesn't guarantee it at all
But we do see those patterns. So if his dad we know that Marcus is dealing with suicide as an issue
If his dad committed suicide that would track
Right that would make sense
So then he started thinking okay, so maybe my dad really did die in a
Accidental way. He was trying to get this boat loose and he drowned
Was my dad trying to warn me of something
Because I do struggle with suicide the the wording he used I want to read this exactly what he said when he talked about suicide
he said quote
I had numerous close calls with suicide as a young adult
So I don't know if that means he would mentally was like he had the suicidal ideation. He's like, oh my god
I'm gonna kill myself. I'm gonna kill myself and he gets someone
To like talk him down or if he actually attempted suicide. There's a big difference between the two
Right, there's suicidal ideation where you just think about it all the time
There's the stuff where you you can't stop thinking about swallowing the pills
And then there's the one where you've swallowed the pills and you're calling 911
Like it's the same thing between wanting to be like, oh, I swear to god
I'm gonna beat my brother up with a baseball bat versus
grabbing the pad versus grabbing the bat and taking a swing at him because he
Wants to keep watching his favorite show and you know it sucks
Big difference. So I don't know but he goes was my father warning me
He does talk about the close calls with suicide. He goes but none of them involved hanging
So it wasn't like he ever attempted to hang himself for really even thought about hanging. So why was this?
Vision of his dad hanging himself. He he didn't really understand that
And then he thought and this is kind of where I was kind of going with it
Originally when I was reading the narrative, it did seem like maybe his dad was trying to
Tell the truth right showing up. This is the real way I died
but
When you kept reading it and he started talking about his investigation you go, okay
I believe that I mean the family can lie but the coroner generally won't right
So the other one was that maybe it wasn't my father at all
Which is the creepiest one right that it was some sort of demon
Some sort of wraith
Taunting this young man
Man who already struggles with suicidal tendencies
This demon this dark spirit
Is taunting him is showing him his biological father killing himself
in the woods
Staring at marcus directly while it hangs
And it's like this entity was trying to
Goed marcus on
Even lie right even lie say your father really died this way come join him
Come join me. I meant to say I'm your dad
I you I said it in the third person, but I'm not really a demon disguised join me son
Join me
A malevolent force trying to trick him into committing suicide
You know what's interesting is we don't know which one it was
Right the thing with the paranormal is you very rarely get a concrete answer
So was this his father showing him this horrible vision for some reason
To warn him
Like was it a at least a good reason
Or was it a darker force trying to manipulate marcus into committing suicide?
We don't know and one of the issues is is that the person who posted this goes by the username
plasmo des maniac
And this I looked through this person's posting history. They generally
posted in a subreddit for depression
Talking about how things you know they can get better
But a lot of times they're bad and just kind of you know trying to help other people out with depression
They haven't posted in 10 months
This story was posted 11 months ago and they have not posted again for the last 10 months
And and I should add too that marcus is now 40
This story just didn't happen a while ago
This this story happened 20 years ago this marcus character again. It's a fake name. He's 41 now
He says his age i'm 41 years old and so he's been dealing with this story for 20 years
Why does he bring it up?
11 months ago and then one month later stops posting for good
As far as we know right maybe he does maybe he will start posting
In in you know still be posting but kind of the implication the unfortunate implication is that something's happened
And then just to put another weird twist on this. I don't know why this happened
He posted this story 11 months ago
And then one month later he was posting in the in a depression subreddit
And in the thread they were posting in was how do you cope with suicidal thoughts?
The last thing he wrote was when talking about suicidal thoughts he
How he struggles with them or how he copes with them he goes
I go shopping maybe at a grocery store and just make a point to talk to people that work there
I don't want to take out my issues on them. So it kind of tricks me into being nice and happy for a minute
Eventually I don't feel like dying
It's an odd story it's a it's a it's a fascinating ghost story and then the real life story is absolutely tragic
Like we this guy's been struggling with this vision for 20 years
He saw it when he was in his early 20s now. He's 41 and he was never able to make sense of this all that time two decades. He's not able to
Figure out why his dad did this
Was it his dad?
Why did he get this message? Why did his dad kill himself?
Or was it even his dad he can't figure that out we can't figure it out and it's possible that we will never figure it out
I
I'm hoping
He just left reddit reddit is such a cesspool reddit's one of the worst websites on the surface of the internet hands down
So if someone stops using reddit, I'm totally fine with that. I think it's probably a good thing
But it's also possible the reason why he hasn't posted in 10 months is because the struggle became too great
Keeping up the illusion that he was happy
was too great
And I hope not I hope not right. I don't wish suicide on anybody
death really on anybody as well
We're left with nothing but questions. What did he see on the other side of this river? Was it taunting him?
Was it trying to warn him?
It's the warning thing seems so weird because do you think the dad would just be like you got a lot to live for bro?
I'm a ghost
I'm a ghost with the most I'm beatlejuice. I didn't know your dad was beatlejuice, bro
and
Don't kill yourself dude because although it's cool to be a ghost. Look at me. I'm dancing with these cockroaches and stuff like that
Hanging out with christini richie or wanona rider. Whoever was in that movie
Don't be a ghost yet
That's what you would think a warning would be right
You don't I mean like if someone just give you guys a heads up if you die and then you want to warn me of some calamity
Don't show up and just stare at me
I'm not gonna get what you're saying
And especially don't do something gross, right?
so
You know, there's other ways to do it even if you couldn't talk even if you want beatlejuice and you could
Go on a cartoon slide even if you weren't beatlejuice. You have to figure out another way
I lean more towards this was something malignant in the woods showing him
something
So grotesque something so grotesque that it stuck with him for 20 years
Something that was so awful that even 20 years later
He's still seeking answers and not in the kind of way like is my apartment haunted in the kind of way is why would my dad do that to me?
Like I already grew up without a dad and then the next time I see him
He's hanging himself in the middle of the woods and he has to know that I struggle with suicidal thoughts
It has to be something darker. It has to be something more malevolent
And if that's the case
This may have been marcus's vision
And marcus may have gone on the next 20 years dealing with that
But this thing wouldn't be limited to marcus. This thing may still be out there in the woods
Waiting watching
Hunting
It stands in the darkness ready to take the shape of a person's greatest fear
What will it show to you?
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also put us up at facebook.com/deadrabberradio. Tiktok is @deadrabberradio
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]