How easy is it to haunt your own life?
What would you do if your dream girl turned out to be a real nightmare?
Now I take a look at the story of a young man who was sleeping on a couch one night
when a shadow man walked down the hallway.
And this time, the shadow man brought some friends.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a good day.
I hope you guys are having a good day too and I hope you guys have some cool Halloween
plans.
Someone who I can always count on having cool Halloween plans.
Coming into Dead Rabbit Command dressed up as Baby Yoda in the Squid Games, it's Alexander
Ribbaum, everyone give a round of applause to Alexander walking in in the two most popular
Halloween costumes this year.
Alexander, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show.
That really means a lot.
That is how shows like this grow.
So please let your friends and your family know how much fun you have listening to Dead
Rabbit Radio.
Speaking of fun, look at this fan art for Fan Art Friday made by Lord Cute Things.
Look at that.
Look at that little, you're like, "Dude, I'm driving a car."
Quit telling me to look at my podcast.
If you can't see it right now, it's a picture of a little bunny with a radio in him.
And now people are pulling over their cars, they're like, "Okay, I gotta find out.
Is this a drawing or is this like some maniac took a photo of this?"
It's a picture of a, it's a drawing of a radio in a bunny and although the bunny looks
sad and although the bunny looks sad, that is deceiving.
He's happy because he's part of the fluffle because he also listens to Dead Rabbit Radio.
Alexander, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We got this little bunny with us.
We are headed all the way out to Poland.
And while we're headed out to Poland, I wanted to share this with you.
I have been having, for the first time in like 10, 15 years maybe, I have been having
some legitimate paranormal phenomenon happen to me.
And you go, "Jason, you did a live stream recently where you said you thought you saw
shadow people running around a house you were house sitting."
So how does it, well, that's true.
I'll put that episode in the show notes.
That was a live stream when we did, but.
I'm not saying that I haven't seen things here and there.
I did that episode where I saw a cryptid when I was walking through town here.
Twice.
I saw it twice.
I didn't know it was a cryptid at the time.
I have no idea what it was, but I found out later it was called a crawler.
So that popped up and I saw those shadow people and I had my haunted apartment for a while
where I see the old man in my closet.
The closet that I'm currently sitting in the dark recording this episode.
Creepy.
And then the bloated dead man on my couch.
I remember looking over at him.
I'll put all these episodes in the show notes, but those were all singular events.
What's been happening this past week, I woke up.
This is, this actually has never happened to me.
And you read about this all the time in spooky things.
I woke up in the middle of the night for whatever reason.
And when I got up out of bed, I heard music playing in the other room.
But I went into the other room and my cell phone, which I normally listen to Pandora
with was playing just started.
Like I had not interacted with it at all for hours, right?
I go to bed, it's not playing.
There's no alarms set on it because that phone is only for my music.
That's all that.
It's like a phone that I don't pay monthly service for.
So I have one cell phone for music and then one cell phone for an actual phone.
And I thought that's weird, but as a singular event, nothing huge, right?
And then a couple odd things happened.
Yesterday, the day before I was a half hour late getting home because a dog was just running
around my house.
It was like running across the street.
That's not paranormal, right?
That's just more irritating because I'm not going to let the dog get as I'm standing in
the middle of the road.
I don't like nervous dogs.
I do not like nervous dogs.
One story I have not told on this podcast is that time I had to fight in a keto.
It's not fun and I don't like nervous dogs and I don't like big dogs walking down the
street, but I don't want to see it get hurt.
And so I'm like, oh great, I'm standing in the road.
I'm calling the police.
I have a little bat I carry with me.
I had that out.
And luckily it looks like a flashlight so I don't look like a bobby from the 1800s.
But anyways, that's not paranormal.
That was just annoying.
But then last night, I was over at my friend's house and we were watching Squid Game.
Now her house is the house that I live streamed from and it, she says, yeah, I didn't want
to tell you this because I know you're a big old spook baby, but my house is hot.
She told me this after I did the episode about seeing the shadowman there.
She goes, she kind of kept your mouth shut.
And then later she goes, yeah, my house is haunted.
It's totally haunted.
Yeah, it's been haunted for years.
And she goes, when I'm alone, she can hear people walk in the front door and walk through
the kitchen.
She goes, I hear it constant.
Sometimes it's noisier than other times, but it's constant.
And that house that she lives in used to be a church.
And she said once when they were doing work under the house, under where the altar area
is, which is where the bedroom is now, they found a cat skull and a wand.
So I mean, if you just found a cat skull under the bed, you know, that's Jerry finally won.
But the fact that they found the cat skull and a homemade wand made them think something
else was going on and that was under where the Christian altar was.
So she told me that and I was like, yeah, you know, I figured I saw this weird shadowman.
But that livestream was a couple of months ago.
Well, I was watching Squid Game with her the other day and you curious about my review
of Squid Game, right?
I brought it up a couple of times.
The ending was awful.
What a waste of time.
I was so disappointed.
I was so disappointed that I'm glad this ghost story happened.
Otherwise, I would have been a total waste of my time to even go over there.
We're sitting there watching that awful ending awful.
We're sitting there watching Squid Game.
And without really comprehending it, this is so weird.
This was so weird because I've seen shadowmen full on.
I've seen these shadow dogs full on.
I've had things mimic my voice.
I've had all these weird experiences.
I'm sitting there with this girl and I hear the front door open.
Someone walk in.
Someone walk in behind them.
And a set of keys thrown onto the kitchen counter.
And I turned not in fear because I knew no one was coming over.
I turned as if I expected to see some long lost friends.
Like so many times when I've been at parties in the past or friends houses in the past
and you're sitting there and you're having a good time and you're waiting for
more of your friends to show up, you hear the door open.
I heard distinct.
I couldn't tell you what they were saying, but it sounded like two people talking.
One coming in a couple steps behind.
You can hear that it was fascinating.
You could hear the distance in their voices because one's a little bit more around the
corner.
And as one of them is walking into the kitchen, they throw their keys on the counter and makes
that unmistakable sound.
When I said that sound, you guys all knew what that sounded like.
Keys on a kitchen counter.
We've all done it our entire adult life.
And we've heard other people do it.
And it was such an instinctual sound that I turned and expected to see Josh Moore,
Meyer and Jason Campbell walking into the kitchen or Steve Daimwood and Jacob Camp.
It was fascinating.
And when I turned and I looked, I halfway was wondering if the girl was going to turn
and look too.
It was clearly that we both heard it and it's clear that we were both awaiting more friends.
But I turned and looked and no one was there.
And as I was turning my head back to watch Squid Game, I realized that was that was a
ghost walking in.
That was that.
Listen, it could have been a bunch of different things.
There could have been a bunch of mice running in.
It could have been Tom's revenge over his fallen ancestor.
It could have been my imagination.
It could have been the thrilling, gripping conclusion of Squid Game being so disappointing
my mind manufactured this to have something interesting to talk about.
But it's I think it was a ghost.
And I think that's what she was hearing.
And she might be hearing something inner in that's more of her experience.
And to me, all the times I've been at parties and all the times I've been over at Friends
House and friends have been over at my house.
That unmistakable sound of people walking in and throwing their keys on the counter.
That is clearly what I heard.
And it made me feel like home.
Made me feel like fun times in the past.
Fascinating haunting.
I go over there quite a lot.
So I don't know, will this just be a one off thing?
I don't know.
But in the past week, I have had some, all of that's happened in a week.
You can remove the dog thing if you want.
And there was just weird that again, again with the dog thing, you don't want to go
too much into coincidences.
But I show up and there's probably four other people following the stalk.
Some people are going to restaurants.
Some people are no one else had a cell phone on them.
I go, have you called the police yet?
They're, I don't have my cell phone.
I left it in the car.
Oh, yeah, no.
So I had to stay there.
I'm on the phone with the cops and blocking traffic.
And okay, maybe that's not fair.
Normal.
Maybe I just want to complain about people letting their dog loose because he wasn't
like a stray dog.
But anyways, that's my other podcast.
I forgot live dog radio.
Keep those dogs alive, but take better care of them.
Alexander, I'm going to go ahead and toss you.
We're driving the dead rabbit, dirgeable to Poland.
I'm actually going to skip the Poland story right now.
We're going to move on.
We'll save that for later.
He's like, damn it.
I've wanted to go to Poland.
Well, look down there.
You see that?
That's Poland.
That should be good enough for your Patreon money.
Thank you.
Alexander, I'm going to go ahead.
We're going to skydive out of the dead rabbit, dirgeable.
We're not even landing this bad boy.
We're going to skydive right into the carpenter copter and I'm going to throw you those keys.
We are leaving behind Poland.
We are headed all the way out to North Carolina.
Squid games was so disappointing.
It was bad.
It was a waste of my time.
The second episode was probably my favorite episode.
I think episodes one and two, they alone told a great story.
But dude, boo, episode whatever that was, nine.
You know what else I'm watching though is I'm watching Chucky.
I'm watching the Chucky TV series.
You're like, Jason, hold on.
Are you about to tell me that the Chucky TV series is better than Squid Game?
It is, dude.
Alexander is flying us all the way out to North Carolina.
It's November 1982.
There's a young man, let's call him Steve.
It's nighttime.
The lights are off.
The raccoons are out.
There's probably a pigeon taking a nap.
But in Steve's girlfriend's house, he is as snug as a bug in a rug.
It was nice and warm here because his girlfriend's stove was still emanating heat.
One was on Warp Corps for Star Trek, but it's keeping him warm.
You know, one of those heater stoves, one of those stoves where it's heating the room.
It's one of those.
And in the middle of the night though, he wakes up.
His eyes are kind of adjusting to the pitch black room.
He's looking around and everything seems normal, but his eyes are drawn to a long hallway.
And when he's looking down this pitch black hallway, he sees something.
Against all logic, he sees something.
Because while there is no light to make out any definition of what's going on down that
hallway, he sees a man standing there.
A shadow man.
A shadow so black.
So impossibly black.
It stands out in the darkness.
The shadow man that I've seen have that same detail.
You shouldn't be able to see pitch black in pitch black.
Which makes you realize that this is something outside of our physics, outside of our reality.
And you're looking at this thing and your brain triggers something.
This is real, but this is impossible.
The shadow man that Steve is looking at in the hallway is so tall.
He has to bend his head forward to fit.
Steve's looking at this thing and this thing is looking at Steve.
And Steve's mind is going wild.
He can't comprehend what he's looking at.
He tries to speak.
Nothing comes out.
And the panic rises and he starts to scream, barely a whisper.
The room grows colder, almost freezing.
And he watches this shadow man begin to glide down the hallway.
He said once it got into the room and made a curious path, it walked along the wall.
It didn't make a beeline straight towards the couch.
It seemed to move around the room and it passed through solid objects.
The physics of our world do not apply to the shadow men.
As the shadow man is standing over Steve, Steve comes to the conclusion that this thing
is pure, unredeemable evil.
It's not a guardian spirit.
It's not a wandering soul.
It is something that redefines the word demonic.
It is nothing but the horrors of the universe.
Personified.
In the presence of such raw negative energy, Steve feels his mind go numb.
He can't even comprehend what's standing there.
And that's when he hears, faintly, like it's miles away somewhere.
Laughter.
Evil laughter.
And he hears the sound grow.
He hears it getting closer.
And he hears this laughter and it's laughter, not of this world.
It's something that doesn't belong here, but he recognizes it as laughter and it grows.
And he hears the conversations of several people, groups of people, like he's at a party.
And then he hears a high-pitched woman's voice say, "Peerce above all the other noise of
this ethereal celebration."
We scared him to death.
He begins to pray in his mind.
It's the only thing he can think of. Whatever is going on is about to win.
And as he's praying in his mind, he's finally able to yell out, "God help me!"
And the coldness of the room is instantly replaced with the heat emanating from the
stove.
It's funny, fascinating story.
I didn't think of that.
This is one of the things that's true.
I had just decided today to tell the story about the ghost thing that happened last night.
And oh, I was thinking about saving it for another episode and I just know this is super
intriguing.
Who knows what else is going to happen.
And that was not my intended first story.
It was the one about the dream girl.
And then I'm doing this story and there's the party.
And I didn't even think about that.
I heard people coming into the room as if almost there was a celebration going on and
this dude, this dude did not want to be at that party.
So now I'm a little more sus about what was going on in that house to be honest.
But looking at this story, looking at this story alone, it's very so creepy, right?
Shadowmen have just a tendency to be probably one of the creepiest figures you can run into.
Mostly it's the demon, like the actual horned or snake or like three headed one heads a
dog, one heads a frog, one heads Tom.
You know, you have this stuff.
That type of stuff is creepy.
But Shadowmen, because it's like something that imitates a human.
It does have that uncanny valley thing.
You're looking at someone, when you see a Shadowman, you're looking at someone and it's
the outline of a human.
It's the mimicry of a human.
This is a ghost, which is we know what a ghost is.
It's like there was a French maid who got her head chopped off during the French Revolution
and now her sexy ghost is walking around somehow in Vermont for some reason.
They took a cursed comb or something like that.
We get that, right?
It's like, oh, if I end up a ghost, I want to be like a cool ghost, right?
I want to be haunting someplace cool.
I don't want to be.
That's why I only work in cool places.
You know, in case I get to the capitated at work, I want to like haunt a Chuck E. Cheese.
That would be dope.
I don't think, could you imagine haunting a department store?
You're walking through Macy's.
You happen to take a shortcut.
You're going through the lingerie department.
Wait a second.
I'd love to be a ghost in the lingerie department.
But let's say I was in the hardware department.
Right?
Because I hate hardware.
And I'm walking through and a saw falls on my head and chops me in half.
It was a very, very poorly maintained store and a very, very sharp saw.
And he goes, "Ew!"
And cuts me in half.
And now for the rest of eternity, I'm walking around the Lowe's.
I'm hanging out at a home depot.
That is hell for me.
That would honestly doubt it.
The only worst place I could die would be like a stadium.
Well, I actually know that would be actually pretty dope too.
Because I'd constantly be like, flowing around like kicking balls.
You know, if you're in with all the games, you're like, we can no longer come to this
arena.
Apparently, apparently the ghost hates sports.
And he messes everything up.
I'm a ghost in a NASCAR track while driving cars late at night.
Like, ah, you used all of our gas in the races tomorrow.
What are we going to do?
But you'd want to be a ghost in a cool place.
So that, whatever.
I don't know how I got on that.
But anyways, the other thing I want to talk about, this poor sap, right?
And this guy sleeping on his couch.
We don't know how he ended up on his girlfriend's couch.
I'm assuming, I'm assuming that wasn't by choice.
I'm assuming they got in a fight and she's dating the shadow man he found out.
He's like, oh, if you keep cheating on me with that shadow man, she's like, what are
you going to do?
It's a shadow man.
Like, what, what really are you going to do?
You going to beat him up?
We don't know why I was sleeping on the couch.
We probably didn't have the best night anyways.
And then, okay, that's a bad relationship thing.
The other thing is this horrible monster coming at him down the hallway.
That's a spooky image.
Nobody likes looking down hallways.
I'm sure hallway architects hate their job.
And then you got like something floating at you from it.
It's pure evil.
But the way, all of that stuff alone is a really cool.
That's a dead rabbit radio story.
Spooky and it allows me to go off in a long tangent of where I want to hunt.
But the party, that's, that's the, that's the thing that sets it apart from an average
like spooky shadow man story.
And I read it and I thought that, okay, with shadow man, I do believe that is some sort
of interdimensional thing.
And the idea of that, there's like a gathering, there's a party of these spirits of these
demons of these shadow people, whatever you want to call them.
And it's like, I imagine it like a real fancy party with like champagne glasses clinking.
You hear a butler going, more champagne.
Would you like some?
I phrased that weird.
Would you like some more champagne?
The butler just became, he just got hired.
So don't, don't take it out on him.
I imagine like a fancy dress party like squid game with all those fancy guys.
That was so dumb.
But anyways, you know, like a fancy party, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink,
clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink,
clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink,
clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink
clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink,
clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink,
clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink
clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink,
clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink, clink,