Could a simple question have a paranormal answer?
And then we travel to Chrisfield, Maryland, where a man is at war with a witch.
Is it possible that an old, timey remedy could end the witch forever? Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys have a great weekend.
First off, let's give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, Cyan River.
Cyan, thank you so much for supporting the show. Great name as well. Very beautiful, very evocative.
If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. Just help get the word out about the show. That really, really helps out a lot.
Now Cyan, I'm going to toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy, but we're not going to go anywhere just yet.
I want to have a little comment about yesterday's episode, okay?
So yesterday's episode just kind of ended, and it seemed to depress a lot of people.
A couple of you reached out to me and was like, "Hey man, is everything okay? Is everything okay? Misty, I appreciate it."
A lot of people did that actually, but everything's okay. It's funny because that's not the way I intended on ending that episode.
Can't think of a good name also. I was talking to them on YouTube as well about this.
That wasn't the original ending of the episode. It was very emotional.
If you haven't listened to it, it was an episode about committing suicide while you were asleep,
and I was relating a story of a friend of mine who had killed himself.
And it's funny because even in the episode I go, I didn't intend the episode to be this dark.
I just was talking about the subject, and it was obviously hard for me to talk about.
Hope is what I was trying to get across. I was supposed to have a more uplifting ending.
Life is about hope. That's one of the biggest factors in, I believe, your quality of life, is how much hope you have.
And it was supposed to be basically like, "What? My friend who killed himself, maybe he killed himself, maybe it was an accident.
I don't know. I don't know all the specifics." But I have hope that it was something different.
And that maybe misplaced hope, that maybe, like I used the analogy of the life raft,
it may be something that I'm clinging onto that doesn't have any rationale.
But I hope for a better answer than the one reality has presented to me.
It was supposed to have a hopeful ending. It was supposed to be like,
"We move forward and we try to find truths in things that don't mean to make sense,
but we have hope that in the end they will make sense." All of that got lost,
because I basically just kind of trailed out at the ending, and then the episode just ended.
So I wanted to let you guys know that, one, I'm 100% fine. I'm not super depressed or anything about it, too.
I've always seen this show. We talk about dark topics. We talk about paranormal,
conspiracy, true crime, stuff like that. And I think a lot of you guys have picked up on this.
I like to-- I don't mind telling a scary story. I don't even mind creeping you guys out,
or maybe even sometimes bumming you guys out. But I hope for a better future.
And I look at all of these stories. I try not to focus on ones that leave you with super-negative emotions.
Sometimes it can make you question things like the justice system, or just justice in general.
It can make you question things about what is reality and things like that.
I'm not trying to sugarcoat stuff, but at the end of the day, I always try to be more hopeful.
I'm a very hopeful person, and I think that comes across on the show.
Yesterday's episode-- I'm not really apologizing for it. I think it was a good story,
but I think that I didn't really get to the ending of it, which is,
I have hope that things will make sense in the end. I hope you guys feel the same way.
I don't want to be about scaring people.
There's a lot of conspiracy theorists who do that, and that's their bread and butter,
is they say, "Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow, the world's going to end,
and the globalists are going to come in, and they're going to do all this horrible stuff."
You buy my merchandise now, because tomorrow, you may not have a chance.
That was a pretty good impression of a particular conspiracy theorist,
but I'm not just putting it all on him. There's a lot of people who do that.
I don't want to be the person who sells fear like that.
I'll make you scared of the boogie man or the faceless man in your kitchen,
or Chester Cheetah in the bathroom, or the dog eating the cereal.
I like to make you scared, but I don't ever want to make you guys feel hopeless.
I see a lot of entertainment value in what we're talking about.
I feel like at this point, I might be rambling, but I just wanted to clear that up.
Yesterday's episode was supposed to end on a hopeful note,
that sometimes we hold on to things that may not actually be true,
but we hope they are, because it's a more satisfactory answer
than the one that reality leaves with us.
And sometimes hope is all you have to cling to.
That was how I originally wanted that to go across,
instead I just kind of got quiet and edited out honestly about
a minute and a half of me just sitting there quietly,
trying to think of how to recover that ending,
and then I just go, "There's no way I can do that."
So, I wanted to clear that up. Everything's going great on my end.
I hope everything's going great for you guys.
Hope is one of the most underrated, yet powerful things in our life.
It is the one thing that no matter how bad things are,
hope for a better tomorrow can really make a big difference.
So that is my... I hope that made sense. I hope that made sense.
Here we go.
Saiyan, you got the keys to the Jason Jalopy?
I'm getting a nod.
We are leaving behind hope. Hope floats.
Where did that movie take place?
Nowhere. Hope floats USA.
We're leaving behind the blockbuster video store that was playing
Hope floats because it's 1998.
We are driving out to Stockton, California.
So you know where this store is taking place?
If you know anything about Stockton, California, yes.
It's the meth capital of the world.
So when Stockton were going to be in a man,
he goes by the user name Thoughtbot100.
Now this is actually a pretty quick story.
I said I was going to do uplifting stories this episode,
and this story definitely uplifts my spirits because
poses a very serious question to us.
We walk into Thoughtbot's house. It's half dismantled.
It only has two walls.
The other walls he removed because he's building another house somewhere else.
We walk into his house. There's two walls, half a ceiling,
one third of a floor.
And we go, "Hey Thoughtbot,
we heard that you have a challenge for us skeptics,
us meth skeptics. We don't believe that...
Well, we believe meth exists.
We're not skeptical of the existence of meth,
you know, I'm always talking trash about meth on my podcast and stuff like that.
And he turns around, he does actually have a great question for us, though.
He turns around, this is the question he posted on Reddit.
The question that made me go, "Hmm, checkmate, methhead.
I think you finally, I think you finally, uh,
I think you finally made me a meth believer."
The conceit is this, he says, as he takes a puff of his pipe.
It's a Sherlock Holmes pipe, but it's full of meth.
The conceit is this, young people.
This is his question he posted on Reddit.
You think that the voices in my head are just a hallucination, right?
That is what your scientific people have told you,
also known as scientists?
They've told you this, right?
But I posit that the, this guy actually
pronounces words better than I do.
I posit this theory that may become a conundrum for you.
Takes another hit of his pipe.
If the voices in my head are not psychic,
then how do they know what I'm thinking?
Hmm?
His question really is, how do the voices in my head know what to say
if they're not psychic, if they're not from some sort of external force?
Now, us meth skeptics understand that a hallucinating person,
he actually refers to himself, I've never heard this term,
I don't know if this is a politically correct term,
but he refers to himself as a voice experiencing individual.
Oh, no, no, no, I'm not delusional.
I'm a shadow man-seeing American.
So apparently that might be the correct way to talk about people
who are in the midst of meth psychosis.
So anyways, how do the voices know what to say to him if they're not psychic?
Now, we would go, well, because they're your voices, dude.
Like, that'd be like me going like, hey, that's weird
whenever I imagine something I see in my head,
but how does my head know to project what I'm imagining?
Well, it's because you're doing it.
And that would be in any other forum, people would go, well, that.
But we're not on any other forum, we're on the subreddit for meth.
Here is a quote from the esteemed philosopher Lil Suicide Note.
Lil Suicide Note had this to say, "As soon as I start hearing stuff,
I just pop a zan and they shut the f up."
So yes, yes, as soon as the voice is in your head up here,
just take more drugs, take a zan,
which is, I'm assuming not zantac, I'm assuming it's not for their heartburn.
Xanax, theological thing, it would be awesome though
if you were a voice experiencing individual, you could just go and take some zantac.
Not only would it quell the shadow man shouting at you to get a facial tattoo,
it would also cure that Taco Bell you ate earlier.
So Lil Suicide Note says that and also came up with this great tip.
The voice is in your head, right? The voice is in your head.
Lil Suicide Note, Lil Suicide Note Esquire said this,
"By the way, many voices can be people outside."
So basically, sometimes you might think you're hearing voices in your head going like,
"Hey Billy, throw the ball!"
"Oh dude, that was such an awesome hit with that baseball bat."
"Oh yeah, home run."
And you're like, "Oh, my voice is in my head, why are they doing this little league game?"
It's actually, you might not have known this,
but sometimes when you hear stuff, it's not in your head.
It's not in your head, it comes from outside, it comes from stimulus,
it comes from sound waves vibrating against your eardrums.
Who would have thought? Who would have thought that?
Thank you, Lil Suicide Note.
"By the way, many voices can be people outside that your brain thinks come from your imagination."
So if you hear voices, just go asleep.
That's a good tip from Lil Suicide Note.
However, if somebody, I've never heard voices in my head, right?
If you've never heard that, I'm not a voice experiencing individual.
But I would imagine, we've done stories about people hearing voices in their head,
and they always say they could tell it was in their head.
I would imagine if I did hear voices in my head,
I wouldn't get it confused with any other, like,
I would assume if I was hearing voices in my head,
that I wouldn't get it confused with just normal conversations going on outside.
I don't know if voice experiencing Americans have to deal with them going like,
"Why do I keep hearing this really loud Carnival Barker telling people to step on up?"
And they're like walking by the state fair, and they're like,
"Oh, my hallucinations, it sounds like 10,000 people in my head at once."
I think you can tell the difference, but again, I'm not a voice experiencing individual.
Secondly, that's not a good tip either.
If you hear voices, just go to sleep.
Don't go to sleep because the voices may be going,
"Dude, dude, your house is on fire."
Oh, no, and you're like, "Oh, hallucinations.
No, you're not going to fool me this time.
I'm just going to pop this Xanax and go to sleep."
So, voices on outside head may be good, unless you're telling you to like, you know,
like, "Stick them up because you're in the 1920s gangster movie.
Stick them up, wise guy.
Maybe listen to those guys, probably should,
because they're going to like shoot you with a Tommy gun if you don't."
If voices in your head probably don't listen to those,
then we have this guy named Miro Man.
He said, this is very, very clever,
"I don't hear anything," is what he said.
"I see writing and images on textured surfaces and faces and clouds."
And he shows a bunch of photos.
There are a bunch of pictures you can go online to look at pictures of gnomes.
You remember David the Gnome?
Or just a gnome in general, a little pointy hat and little face.
Did you know that sometimes a cloud can look like a dude with a beard?
It's like, "Clouds are the most beard-like things in existence anyways,
outside of actual beards."
Anyways, you can find photos.
This guy's posting them.
Hundreds of them, he says.
I only looked at one of them, but gnomes in clouds.
You know, it looks like a gnome.
I'm not going to lie, it looks like a face with a beard.
But anyways, he says, "He doesn't hear voices.
He sees writings and images on textured surfaces and faces and clouds."
And then he goes on to explain,
"It seems like a guardian spirit writing to me."
These messages aren't just random, it's a guardian spirit reaching out to him.
He says, "It feels like a guardian spirit writing to me.
It's telling me to quit meth."
That would actually be quite the conundrum, right?
Because what if you need meth to communicate with your guardian angel,
but your guardian angel is telling you to stop doing meth?
Like, that actually would be an issue.
And I've said, yes, I've said the word conundrum twice in one episode.
That's a good idea for all you writers out there.
A man who can contact the supernatural and use that information for good.
Or bad.
It's up to you. I'm not going to write your book for you. That's your job.
But he has to do meth to do it.
Like, every time he tokes on meth, his guardian angel shows up,
and he's like, "Dude, dude, dude, stop taking meth also.
Here's the winning lottery numbers."
So he would have to make a decision,
"Does he keep smoking meth? Does he keep smoking meth?"
And win the lottery, or does he not smoke meth and not win the lottery?
There you go. That's the dilemma.
Do you call that the hero's journey?
That's-- there you go. I've just written your book for you.
They actually-- that actually used to be the thing with spawn.
It used to be, every time spawn used his superpowers,
he got weaker, and eventually he'd use so many of his superpowers
he'd get dragged into hell.
You're like, "Jason, what the hell are you talking about?"
What? That was a weird segue.
I always thought that was an interesting thing,
and then eventually they just go, "Oh, no, that's not going to happen."
And then you could use his powers all the time.
Same thing in Star Trek Voyager.
Originally, they were like, "Voyager,
you only have 70 torpedoes this whole mission."
And then half-- it wasn't like everything in the first episode.
They're like, "Oh, we found more. Here you go.
Here's unlimited torpedoes.
I think the idea of limitations is good."
But, Cyan, let's go ahead and we're leaving behind Stockton, California.
Let's hop in that carbon helicopter.
We are headed out to Crisfield, Maryland.
[imitates helicopter flying away]
Helicopter's flying away.
Half of it's missing.
It's being pawned off at some shop.
Hey, look at this. I found an official part of the Dead Rabbit copter.
Whatever it's called. I don't-- I don't--
They're selling off parts, but we don't care, right?
We can rebuild it.
I hope that's the fuel-- they took our fuel line.
So, Cyan, we now have the carbon helicopter on the back of a tow truck.
Tow truck is driving us.
We're leaving behind halfway between Stockton and Crisfield, Maryland.
We're going to get to Crisfield, Maryland.
We've got to have some repairs done on the carbon helicopter.
And while we're here, we're going to sit.
We're going to watch a baseball game of the Crisfield Crabbers.
[cluck]
[whoosh]
That's the sound of a bat hitting the ball.
It's not just me saying the word "cluck."
We're watching a game of the Crisfield Crabbers,
eating some hot dogs, popcorn, what have you.
And also sitting on the stands is Kent Allard.
Kent actually sent me the story.
And if you'll remember, Kent Allard sent me--
The last time we went to Crisfield was the story about the man and the cabin.
It was a really good episode.
So thank you, Kent, for this submission.
Tips is a little baseball cap to us.
Crisfield Crabbers, go home team.
We're sitting here, and now everything's sepia-toned.
We're going back to the year 1923.
It's March 3rd.
And this was reported in the Crisfield Times, which was a newspaper back then.
So this story was reported in the Crisfield Times in 1923.
I don't have a time for when this story actually took place,
what year this actually took place.
But it was reported in 1923.
But we're imagining like old timey Crisfield.
It was a simpler time back then.
People just went about their business as opposed to day.
Everyone's a busybody.
Everyone's looking in each other's windows.
So we're walking through the sepia-toned city.
And in the city, we're going to meet a man named Webb White.
He's the local weirdo, right?
He's the guy that everyone in town goes, "Oh, great.
Here comes Webb White."
He's local weirdo.
He lives with his wife on the outskirts of town.
Now, he's a weirdo.
He probably comes off as a conspiracy theorist believer of the paranormal.
What would be a conspiracy theorist in 1923?
They're like, "You know the Mayflower really didn't land in Plymouth.
It landed in the Florida Everglades."
Like, how would you be a conspiracy theorist when...
Like, what would you...
King George still runs the United States.
Like, I wonder...
There had to be conspiracy theorists.
Like, that's not a new thing.
But I wonder how they...what they were.
And it's funny because they really want to get disseminated.
If you were a conspiracy theorist in your town,
it's not like you were printing up leaflets.
You would just tell everyone in town,
you're like, "Well, you know that Roanoke wasn't inside job."
People are like, "What?"
And then once you died out, it would be gone.
You wouldn't be able to leave any record of your crazy conspiracy theories.
Unlike today, because of Angel Fire,
everyone's conspiracy theory lasts forever.
But he was a local weirdo,
and he believed in the paranormal and stuff like that.
And again, in America, we had a big spiritualism revival.
America's always been a fairly paranormal believing country.
Actually, I should do an episode on that,
because Americans in general tend to really believe in the paranormal.
In Europe and stuff, they believed in witches and devils and stuff like that.
You had a lot of Catholic influence and pagan influence and stuff like that.
Sure, but eventually they're like,
"Well, we don't believe in that anymore."
But Americans would really get into the spiritualism like turn of the century.
But even for that place in that period of time,
people thought this dude was a weirdo.
And some guy, against all of judgment, thinks,
"You know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna pull a prank.
I'm gonna pull a prank on the one guy in town
who's crazy enough to actually do something about it."
So basically, old-timey Jake Paul walks up to Web White and goes,
"Hey, dude, come here, come here.
Come here. He has his pilgrim clothes on."
The caller's all popped and the shirt's too tight.
And he's like, "Hey, Web, come here, come here.
I got this hilarious thing to-- I mean, not hilarious.
I have this totally true thing to tell you, Web.
Come here, come here, come here.
You know your neighbor? He's like, "Yeah, well, you don't let me finish.
You don't let me finish."
Did you know your neighbor's wife is actually a witch?
Now, that is dangerous to say to someone who's mentally imbalanced.
Even today, right, that could obviously cause some problems.
I don't know if this old-timey Jake Paul realized what he was doing.
Maybe he did and he's just a psychopath.
But Web White actually believes that witches exist and stuff like that.
He totally would have been a fan of this show.
And he runs home and he's like, "Oh, my neighbor's wife is a witch.
I have to kill her."
See, that's not the funny part of the prank, right?
That's where the priest says that as he's leaving.
He's running away from Jake Paul.
He's like, "Oh, I got to go do something."
Jake Paul's laughing and he hears him as he's running off.
He's like, "I got to do something.
I got to load my gun up and I got to kill."
And Jake Paul's like, "Uh-oh.
Maybe the joke went too far."
"Ah, that's okay. I got to go lift weights."
So he goes, "Lift old-timey weights."
They're just hay bales.
Web White goes home and he knows an old-timey way to kill a witch.
I'd actually never heard of this before.
This might work.
I'm not recommending it.
But apparently, if you take a picture of a witch and you shoot it with silver,
wherever the witch is hit, the witch will suffer a wound.
So, I mean, I don't have to break it down for you.
Obviously, if it gets shot in the hand,
"Oh, my hand hurts."
It gets writer's cramp using that feather to write letters.
"Oh, my hand cramp."
Shooting on the heart of the head, it will kill the witch.
Shoot the picture in the heart of the head, it will kill the witch.
Sounds legit.
That might actually be...
I don't know if this guy's just super crazy
or that might actually be an old-world way of getting rid of a witch.
But there's one problem with this, right?
You need a picture of the witch.
You can't whip out your cell phone and take a picture of her gardening, right?
You can't even have a Polaroid and take it and you're shaking it.
You just draw a picture of this woman.
So now we're getting all sorts of complicated stuff, right?
Because unless your artist skills are on point,
because you could draw a picture of this woman
and then shoot it, and then nothing happens.
And then, like, 50 miles away, there's a woman who looks exactly like the drawing.
She's like a two-dimensional, her hair's all scraggly.
She wears a dress that looks like a triangle
and all of a sudden she just blows up in her kitchen.
Like, it's really hard to draw a picture of someone that is so representative of them.
And if you shot it, they'd die.
Pablo Picasso's like shooting in his drawings.
Aliens are blowing up on some weird planet.
He draws a picture of the switch.
So I don't know if it was like a sketch.
I don't know if it was this super detailed Bob Ross-style painting.
It's all like watercolors and layers, stuff like that.
But he draws a picture of the switch, because what else is he going to do?
He then takes 10 silver dimes and sticks them in a musket.
This guy, at the very least, is ingenious.
Insane! Totally insane.
But he takes 10 silver dimes, he puts them in a musket.
He hangs the picture up on the outside of his woodhouse,
which is exactly what you think it is.
It's a house full of wood.
He puts it up on his outside of his woodhouse,
and he takes his musket, and he aims it at the picture,
and goes...
So he shoots it, and the 10 dimes shoot out,
and it peppers the picture.
And then he hears...
[Screaming]
Screaming. Screaming if you didn't know what that was.
The picture wasn't having an orgasm.
He hears the sound of a woman screaming,
and he goes, "Gadzooks! I got her!"
And runs off into his neighbor's house.
He wants to see what he's actually done to this witch.
She's not a woman, she's a witch.
She did nothing wrong to a woman.
Remember, someone just came up and said,
"I think she's a witch."
And then he decided to murder her via picture.
He breaks into their house,
and what he finds is a woman in the kitchen screaming,
and nothing else.
She's totally fine. She's not obliterated.
She has all of her extremities.
Her face is totally fine, except for the very loud noises
coming out of her mouth.
And the neighbor jumps up, the husband of the screaming woman,
and was like, "Web, what are you doing in my house?
What are you doing?"
And now, remember, here's the thing.
These two people were just sitting there,
having a nice quiet evening,
casting spells against the non-believers.
No, they're just doing normal stuff.
They're just doing normal stuff.
So they just leaned their head out the window and went, "Cops! Cops!"
And then the cop showed up.
So he's being a lead away in handcuffs.
He's like, "Oh, no, but I swear, I shot the picture and I heard a scream.
That could have never happened if it wasn't a witch."
And that is when we find out how this whole mystery unfolded.
So let's go back in time.
We rewind this.
He has the picture lined up and he's taking the shot.
He doesn't know it, but his own wife is in the woodhouse,
collecting wood.
She has no idea what's going on outside of her shed.
But then she hears a gunshot, super close to her,
and she swears someone's shooting at her.
We've talked a lot about hearing voices this episode.
Man with a gun.
There's a picture on a wall.
On the other side of the wall is a woman.
So when he shoots the picture and doesn't know there's anyone in the room
and hears the woman scream, he thinks it's the witch.
He thinks he's killed the witch.
But it turns out that it was really just his way.
He really just shot at his poor wife.
For the most part, he got arrested for breach of peace,
is kind of what it was charged for.
He didn't get arrested for attempted murder of a witch.
He didn't get arrested for shooting a drawing after 6 p.m.,
which is against the law in Christfield, Maryland.
He didn't get -- it's just basically like breach of peace.
But they said in this article that when he broke into the house
and he saw that the woman was okay, he flipped out.
Imagine being disappointed that someone didn't --
someone didn't disintegrate from your magic spell.
You think he heard that it.
He ran inside the room, kicks in the door,
and sees that a woman is not a puddle of goo
full of, you know, silver dimes and stuff.
Like, "That's just a woman holding a turkey."
She just pulled out of the oven.
Did they have ovens back then?
"Holding a turkey." She just pulled off the fireplace.
So part of the breach of peace, one,
I don't think it was against a lot of fire muskets.
Kicking in someone else's door, screaming that they're not disintegrated.
You probably get to charge for that, right?
We don't know what happened to any of these characters.
We don't know what happened to Time Traveling and Jake Paul.
What we do, now he's in our era, causing chaos.
That's why the feds arrested him the other day.
He had drawings of all these witches around.
He's like, "If it worked back then..."
Wait, it didn't work back then.
He totally failed.
He takes them all down, and the feds just arrest him anyways.
Allegedly.
But anyways, we don't know what happened to Webb White.
We don't know what happened to his wife.
His wife probably got said, "No more shooting at me.
Webb, I know you're crazy, but you crossed the line
when you opened fire and that shed I was in."
He's like, "Oh."
We don't know what happened.
He probably went...
This would really solidify his...
If he was trying to get rid of that town weirdo vibe he was giving,
this wouldn't help.
But a small town story featuring
a Jake Paul, I bet you didn't expect that.
A crazy man and a woman accused of witchcraft.
Out of all this stuff, I think the most compelling thing
is that idea of if you shoot a picture of a witch
with silver, it'll damage them.
So let that be a warning to all of you out there
who practice the dark arts.
And look like a cartoon character that's easily drawn.
You may think you're getting away with casting spells
and eating frogs or whatever you do.
Dark, evil witches of the world.
You may think you're getting away with it.
But someday, some kid at school may be drawing a picture.
He's drawing a picture and it's just a picture of a witch.
But it looks like you.
And then he goes, "Hey, Bobby, can I borrow that silver-colored crown?"
And the guy's like, "You mean a crayon?"
He's like, "Whatever, just give me your silver-colored crown."
So he takes out the silver-colored crown
and he's like, "Drawn on the witch stuff?"
He's like, "Drawn more on the witch."
And you, you're in Albuquerque, New Mexico,
you're washing your dishes that you just used.
This was your nice china you used when you summoned the dark lord
and you're like, "Oh, that was such a nice visit from him.
Now it's time to do my dishes."
And you feel your arms start to itch.
And you're like, "What? Oh, that's weird."
But you don't really think anything of it.
You don't know about this old world remedy for witchcraft.
And so then this kid is like, "Oh, okay, I'm done drawing the arm.
Hey, Tony, do you still have that silver marker that actually has silver in it?
It's like, "You can cost your dad a thousand dollars?
Can I borrow that?"
And they're like, "Yeah."
It actually has silver flakes in it.
And he's drawing on the drawing,
but it's like on the face.
And now you're back in Albuquerque and you're trying to watch an episode.
What show do witches watch?
You're trying to watch episode of Gilmore Girls,
because I swear to God, the only reason that show last time on the air
was some sort of black magic.
That show was insufferable.
This witch is watching Gilmore Girls.
She's like casting a spell.
She's like, "Stay on the air. Have a reunion show."
And then her face starts itching.
"Oh, what? What?
This is the worst thing that's happened to me.
My arm itches and now my face itches.
Ugh.
Oh, it's where my face is itching."
And then we flash back to Lil' Boy and he's like,
"Hmm, I've used a silver..."
I have a silver finish apparently.
I've used silver crayon and I've used a silver marker.
But this is boring.
I've decided to draw like a rocket ship or something else.
So he crumbles the paper up and then he like was walking down the street.
He used the paper the whole time.
He has this thing.
He can't let go of things.
And then he sees like,
"There's a river.
There's a river of molten silver.
He's in Silver Town, Nevada."
And he throws the paper into the silver river.
And then we go back to Albuquerque, New Mexico.
And her spell was successful.
Gilmore Girls was renewed for another 40 seasons.
The plague is upon us.
The fourth seal has been opened.
But while she's laying in bed,
she starts itching again.
Which again isn't the worst thing.
Just pop a Benadryl.
And she starts itching again.
She's like, "Ugh!"
And then her bed catches on fire.
And she dies.
Obviously, right?
That's more than an itch.
"Witches of the world beware.
We know the only reason Gilmore Girls exist is because of you.
And we now know your weakness.
A drawing, a simple drawing of a witch.
Infused with silver.
Can stop your evil deeds."
So, "Witches of the world beware."
If you continue to practice your dark arts and curse this land.
Some people look up at the clouds and they see gnomes floating around.
Some people look up at the clouds and they see...
They don't see gnomes.
They just see normal clouds.
But witches, I want you to look up and look at those clouds.
And you see, "Hmm, that's weird.
That cloud's awfully gray.
And it's coming right at me.
It's coming right at me."
And you know why it's coming...
You know why it's coming right at you?
Because that cloud has a silver lining.
So it's gonna get him?
'Cause the silver thing?
And hope!
It plays in the whole thing.
Every cloud has a silver lining.
Except for witches.
They don't count.
They become drawings in melt and silver.
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is gonna be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio.
Twitter is @deadrabberadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listen to it today.
Have a great weekend, guys.
I love you and I will see you Monday.
[Music]