Today we meet a group of people who believe the more rotten the meat the sweeter the treat
Then we take a look at some bizarre statistics that show what people really think about conspiracy theories
Now we travel to Australia to take a look at a bizarre UFO story when Amy Rylance is abducted in front of a witness and
Beamed aboard a UFO. She's only gone for three hours
But how did her hair grow so long in such a short time?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now trapped in a haunted mayor
Trapped in a prison not of his own making. Let me out
People don't
They're damned to hell. It's Dean Ryan everyone give a applause to Dean Ryan
There's like a janitor wheeling in this giant giant mirror. It's like family on it. Let me out. Let me out
Someone smash that mirror. I'm not gonna do it. I can't afford the bad luck
Someone smashes it Dean Ryan. You've now been released to join us with the rest of the world
Dean Ryan
You're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon
Or if your soul is not doomed to an eternal two-dimensional existence. That's fine too. Just helps read the word about the show
Really really helps out a lot Dean. I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit robo
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command. We're gonna head out to a
Tropical little paradise no one as the middle of nowhere
splash
Splash rowing all the way over there's a dude you guys may have seen this this is popped up on the news recently
if you guys
Have seen it. I apologize for bringing it back up. I apologize for these bad memories
There's a guy who got his name on YouTube. He goes by severage
Severage is a man and he has a unique idea
Severage is what's known as an
Anti-vegan now it's different than a non-vegan. I'm non-vegan. I don't eat vegan food if you eat vegan food fine
I don't care right as long as you're not trying to eat my food. We're square
Non-vegan is people who aren't vegan and anti-vegan is
Someone who is against veganism who thinks that it's wrong and you you eat funny cuz you may go well Jason
I actually think veganism is unhealthy or I think it's kind of highfalutin. I think it's pretentious whatever
You're still not an anti-vegan in the way that severages
Because you still eat I'm assuming you still eat vegetables
You may not agree with the vegan lifestyle again. I really don't care
I used to be vegetarian for moral reasons and then it got too expensive and morals went out the window
I was like, I'll eat a cow you may not like the vegan lifestyle
You may think it's pretentious or it's not super healthy, but you're not still not anti-vegan anti-vegan is someone who consumes no vegetables
at all
Not even the carnivore diet is considered anti-vegan because see anti-vegan
They're like what you cook your food you disgusting man
Anti-vegan is the consumption of raw meat
Surprisingly, there's more than one person who does this they consume raw meat
Now as I'm telling this story, I'm gonna keep having visuals of this video. I watched of
Severage he had a jar. Okay, hold on a second. I can't be gagging the whole story. There's this video. It's on YouTube
He has a jar of meat that he has let sit in this jar for a year
Never cooked it
Not like it would matter if it was cooked first and then he left over a year
He sticks his fork and he pulls out what looks like hard
clam chowder
It's dripping white goo
Sorry, my apologies if you're eating clam chatter tuna casserole my apologies if you're eating anything right now
It's basically like a giant meatball of rotten meat and he goes I'm gonna eat the whole thing right now like that's supposed
to be in the impressive part
And he begins to he begins to devour this piece of rotten meat
It's funny because I've never eaten rotten meat. I've eaten undercooked meat
I've never eaten rotten meat. I assume most of you guys have never
Severage turns out to be a
Severage is Dean Ryan. This is the episode he's supporting. He's like, oh no trapped in a mirror and he's making fun of me
We've never eaten rotten meat, but just you there's an instinctual thing
That kicks in when you talk about it and you look at it
It's not like I can even like if someone was eating poop
I've never eaten poop, but because I spend a lot of time around poop myself
I'm not like a poop connoisseur that I know like the smell and the texture. I don't want anything to do with it
So when Cece I can't watch people eat poop
I don't feel bad about that. I'm not like oh man, I really should I really should start doing that
But watching someone eat rotten meat
I've never really been around rotten meat more than once or twice especially not year old meat watching him do it
It makes you physically ill. I could barely watch it and he's eating this raw meat this year old raw meat
And they do it for a couple reasons one because they're anti-vegan and this is all they can consume. They're so hungry
They're like, oh when will dinner be ready? Oh three more months. Oh, no
They're eating I'm sure they have to eat other meat in the meantime, but
They're they're anti-vegans. They eat this raw meat and it also gets them high
That's what I found out about it
There was recently some news articles in the Sun and Newsweek
Where they were like this new trend some people on the internet quote-unquote some people on internet
Which is usually like three or four weirdos and then all of a sudden eight people tweet about it
And then some lazy journalists will write an entire story about it
And then some lazy podcaster will cover it the difference is is I know the game
I know the game when Newsweek or Huffington Post or God forbid the New York Times runs a whole article about three tweets
It blows my mind have my degree in journalism. It absolutely rattles my cage when
Anyways, I'm part of the problem because I reported on a podcast this podcast is goofy and it covers weird stuff
It's not the gray lady. Anyways, some people on the internet a couple people are eating raw meat
It's become this viral storm viral because of the worms in their stomachs
apparently if you eat it it gets you high and
The articles they're like well, I really don't know the articles like IFL science commas like we really don't know the mechanism
Of why it would make you high it could be that the bacteria
Hit your stomach it could be that you're definitely ill it could be the side effects of these diseases
I watched this video a severage and as he was eating it like before the video was like five six minutes long after he gets
Then eating and he goes yep
I already feel high already feel high and I thought oh
That's how he gets high they make it up
It's all in their head
There's very few drugs that you can ingest that you get high immediately
Like within five minutes of taking the drug so it's it has to be just psychosomatic
IFL science. There's your answer. I almost feel like it's just a way to attract people to their disgusting lifestyle
If you eat rotten meat, you'll get high you may get some sort of rush from the fact that you're doing something
That's been forbidden by nature
But I don't think you could actually classify it as a high if you're saying it was a high after two or three minutes of eating it
I think it's in your head or
It's similar to that high that endorphin rush which again
Is it really a high when you eat salsa when you eat really really hot salsa?
It makes you feel high
But it's not like you're sitting next to the stoner and the guy's dropping acid and be like dude
I can see the elves too. You're just faking it
You're trying to get just eating bell peppers the whole time
But you want to get in with the cool kids
But if you want to get illegal high and you want to be the most disgusting person in your neighborhood
Try raw meat so the very least you can pretend like it does something so bizarre
Subculture internet fad whatever it is the media could be hyping this up right now
I did watch a man eat rotten meat
I did watch a man eat meat that was a year old and if you look at a couple of his other videos
This guy might be moving into Hans territory. He has a video where he's eating a lump of meat
That's a year old Hans never did that Hans never did that
He also has a whole video about how time doesn't exist and he uses as an example
Proving time does not exist
The movie back to the future
So
I'm gonna be following this guy for a bit. He basically says there is no past. There is no future
We are hanging out with Jesus right now
Maybe he is getting high off that meat
He believes the grass is the seed the blade and the decayed remains all at the same time interesting quantum philosophy
You kind of lost me when you started talking about back to the future
I have a lot of bad memories of conspiracy theories connected to back to the future and the fact that while you're explaining this conspiracy theory to me
Your breath smells like Salmonella
I'm gonna take a pass on this one, but I will continue to look into them. We might have a new Hans on our hands
Dean Ryan, let's go ahead and tashi the keys to the Jason Jalopy. We are leaving behind the anti-vegan movement
We are headed out to
Canada
Cars driving underwater because we are on an island, but eventually we reach America's North Cousin Canada
We pull up to a research laboratory. We all got on our lab coats
We walk in in Canada. I found this so fascinating when I saw this the other day in Canada. They recently did this survey
It was done by Insight's West polling company and I can't remember a survey done recently
That's given us this kind of breadth of information
This poll was done very recently between March 31st and April 5th. These questions were all conspiracy questions
Do UFOs exist?
53% of Canadians and we're actually gonna I think these would match up pretty much to most places in the Western world
Do UFOs exist 53% of the population says yes
18% of them absolutely believe they exist. That's kind of what I expected that one didn't surprise me that much
But then we look at this
COVID-19 created in a lab. It's actually been so long since I've even thought about the COVID-19
Origin conspiracy theories remember like the official story. It was bat soup when's the last time you even heard the term bat soup
That was the official story. So I was I totally forgot about this stuff COVID-19 created in a lab
37% of Canadians believe that's possible
They believe somewhat and 11% totally believe that it was created in a lab and I go that that's interesting 10% of the population
Believes that any of the JFK conspiracy theories
33% believe somewhat in the conspiracy theories 9% totally believe them
So we start to see this the really the biggest conspiracy theory that people believe in is
UFOs exist
I think most people when they think about the scope of the universe they go there has to be aliens out there somewhere
So I think that that's why that has such a high percentage any JFK conspiracy theory whatever it is
33% but then we start to get into some conspiracy theories
That are fairly popular that I didn't think would be
Scientists have found a cure for cancer
31% of people believe that scientists have found a cure for cancer, but they're not revealing it to make money
Dude, that is a conspiracy theory
I have not heard of in a long time that used to be really popular in the 80s and the 90s and
I also heard it about AIDS that they had a cure for AIDS, but they weren't revealing it
But Magic Johnson got it. That was the conspiracy theory
Also, there was a conspiracy theory that he didn't get AIDS in the first place or HIV
He didn't have HIV in the first place that it was some like
Way for him they basically some bookie or someone says you owe money say they it was a weird conspiracy theory
But there was one conspiracy theory that Magic Johnson didn't have HIV in the first place
The other one was that he got the cure because he's still around. He's doing great HIV is not the death sentence
It was when I was growing up, which is good
But that scientists have found a cure for cancer that one is actually they took this poll in 2014 and then they did another one in
2021 that's dropped 17 points that has almost been cut in half
Since the last time it was pulled so very very fascinating
There's a couple other conspiracy theories that took total tanks in the past couple years, but that's one of them
29% of people somewhat believe
That humans have been cloned
That at least one and it's so funny because I joke about like when we talk about all the Hillary Clinton weird stories and
Obama's a clone Hillary Clinton's a clone Nancy Pelosi's clone doppelganger, whatever I make fun of that
I 100% believe that a human has been cloned. I don't think it's cloned and then growing to look exactly like
68 or 78 hour old Hillary Clinton is I don't think we're anywhere near that
Nor do we want to be why would you want to clone you?
Make you super old
But I do believe there's at least one person walking around today who by definition would be a cloned person. I
100% believe that that technology is there. I would be in that 29%
I just don't think they're like lifelike
lookalikes I
Think that you they have probably taken genetic samples from people and cloned them
But they would be little little baby Barack Obama little baby Hillary Clinton eating herself
I think that she's taking a bite out of her arm to like Hillary. We have to grow you a new arm again
Bigfoot exists
20% I don't know if that's higher or lower than I thought honestly one in five
Canadians again this is the poll you have to extrapolate everything and I'm extrapolating this to a lot of the Western world is where well
But one in five adults believe bigfoot exists
I live in an area where a lot of people believe bigfoot exists because I live up in kind of the home of bigfoot
I live up in the Pacific Northwest, but in California. No, I wasn't even interested in bigfoot
I thought it was kind of lame you wouldn't run into a lot of people who believed in bigfoot
So overall see that's the thing like I'm around more people now who believe bigfoot exists
But growing up it was just something goofy it was on the level of the Loch Ness monster and
They don't ask specifically if Loch Ness monster exists in this poll they ask if oh go go go
Exists which is the Canadian Loch Ness monster only nine percent of people exist
And I think you could extrapolate that to say maybe a little bit more maybe
10% 11% believe Loch Ness monster exists 20% one in five people believe bigfoot exists
This is what I found bizarre because I had not really heard this conspiracy theory
I didn't know was a conspiracy theory
Out of all my years of research. I've my great-grandma. I think believed it to a certain extent
But I just figured it was my great-grandma being a sore loser
I and I know people would believe this but I didn't think it was this high or that this was considered a conspiracy theory
20% of people
Somewhat and five percent of those absolutely believe the lottery is rigged
Fascinating I honestly didn't know there was that high of a percentage of people who believed that I
Know there have been
Lotteries state lotteries things like that that have been rigged
I know that crimes have been committed where it's been rigged, but to think one in five of
Adult Canadians believe that the lottery is rigged. It's the same amount of people who believe in bigfoot
That's weird to me. I that kind of threw me for a loop. That's actually bigger than
Stuff like global warming as a hoax the pharmaceutical industry has something to do with cova 19 that it was engineered
It's twice as big as the cova 19 vaccine has a microchip
Like that's a huge level conspiracy theory and what I think is so interesting about that is conspiracy theories so often
You can use to make money. There are whole industries that popped up
Relatively overnight off of people's fears about cova 19 and the vaccine
There's whole YouTube channels podcast
There's stuff you can buy to help suck up the stuff that the vaccine people are shedding all this stuff all this nonsense
Who's making money off the lottery thing that almost seems like if you guys if you guys have some money and you're looking for
Something to spend it on I bet you you could honestly get a pretty good following if you started a
Podcast or YouTube channel that focus specifically on the lottery is rigged
Because I think that is an empty lane
I don't think anyone else is doing that all these other
Conspiracy theories we talked about are very very well populated UFO people. I got a tweet today on my phone
Did you know UFO disclosures happening tomorrow? I mean it's non-stop. It's non-stop
But the lottery thing I don't think anyone is pushing that conspiracy theory
9/11 the 9/11 was a conspiracy set in fourth by the United States government
And this is in Canada that they're doing this it may be a little higher in the United States
17% that's a still a huge amount that is almost one in five Canadians believe that 9/11 was an inside job
But that actually dropped 12% from 2014 so that's also taken a sizable hit in
The last six seven years people have gone. Maybe that's not accurate. So that's another one that's on its way out
That one in the scientists the cure for cancer those ones are going to be much smaller
Conspiracy theories cross the political boundary. It does not matter what side of the political spectrum is on it
Honestly does not matter what your education level is it doesn't matter what your religious background is a lot of people think it's a bunch of yokels a
Bunch of like fundamentalist yokels up in the woods who believe this stuff about 5g and COVID it cuts across all barriers
It's just different conspiracy theories different groups believe in different conspiracy theories
And the general consensus is that more men believe in conspiracy theories than women that can be correct
That can be correct what this poll realized was that does happen for
Specific conspiracy theories there are two conspiracies in this list that more women believe in than men
One that the Princess Diana car accident
Was not an accident. It was either an assassination or there was something else going on
It wasn't an accident more women believe that than men and
The lottery is red
By a wide margin of 23% of women believe that versus 16% of men
So fascinating we I hope you guys enjoyed this. I hope I didn't bore you with these numbers. I find this stuff absolutely
Fun to talk about because it's these raw numbers. We don't really get to see this much stuff
We live in a realm of paranormal. I'm all it's so funny because I'm
Whenever I meet someone and they're like, I don't believe in ghosts or any of that stuff
It always takes me a back because I spend so much time in this sphere
I'm just spending time in this pair of dimensional sphere. I'm rolling through the city
It's been so much time in this world and I know that people don't believe in UFOs. I know people don't believe in ghosts
I guess when I'm saying when I meet people who don't believe in anything
Any of it because some people don't believe in ghosts, but they're like, oh, yeah, UFOs are real or they don't believe in ghosts
You're your foes, but they'll be like, oh, no, I swear I saw bigfoot ones
But I'll run into people who don't believe in anything and it's always odd to me
It's always weird to me. So it's nice to look at these numbers and see
How how they break down how they break down and to see that some of the conspiracy theories like the coven 19 5g internet connection
That is only 6% of people believe that we have nothing to compare it against in 2014 because it didn't exist
But oh 6% of people believe in that which is still a sizable amount when you're talking about, you know
Nations of millions and millions of people but like the UFOs I could see it being a 50/50 split
So I hope you guys enjoyed that. I really had a lot of fun reading that to you
It's nice to see the total picture of
Paranormal belief, but we've done enough number crunching with these nerds and then now we're all ripping up their notes
I'm like, sir, we need that for the next day. We're like get out of our way retired being nerds are messing all this stuff up
We retired of learning stuff. It's time to go investigate a real life
UFO abduction. We don't need no numbers for this Dean Ryan
I'm gonna toss you the keys of that carbonicopter you go ahead and signal that bad boy to land we're leaving behind egghead central
We're headed out to
Australia
I
Got most of this information from a website called howan wise.com. We've actually been to this website a lot
And I wanted to give him a shout out. They actually did a really good write up on this story
I had some other sources as well, but that's a great website. You guys should check it out Dean Ryan
We're headed to Australia specifically. We're headed to gun dia. That's in Queensland, Australia. It's 9 30 p.m
October 4th
2001 longtime listeners of the show know that is my birthday
Not 2001 that would make me 20 years old. I was 25 when this story took place
I was 25 years old we're in gun dia
we're actually at a
Construction site a site where they're about to build a winery known as whispering winds
Now there's a little house a little structure there where we have Keith Rylance 39
Amy Rylance his 22 year old wife and their business partner Petra Heller who's 35
And what's great about this story is they have gone on video talking about this. We have names
We have specific dates. We have faces. This is a very very verifiable story at least from their point of view a lot of times
On this show and just paranormal stuff in general like yesterday's episode all the alleged hauntings at the university
It's nice to actually have names and faces and proof that people are coming forward and telling these stories
But this night October 4th
Keith has already called it a night. He's already gone to bed pretty early Petra is in her room and
Amy is in the living room. She's up watching television. The rooms are fairly connected
So it's not like this sprawling house something happens in one room. You're gonna be able to hear it in the next a
Huge storm rolls into the area
Amy's still just watching television. She's watching the storm channel. She's like whoa surround sound. It's amazing
But by 1115 she is also dozed off so everyone in the house is asleep
The storm is gliding over the Australian landscape and then all of a sudden it's something wakes Petra up
It's 1115 she's the only one awake now
She's walking through the house and she gets into the living room and that's when she sees a
rectangular beam of light shining in from outside the house
In the middle of this beam of light is Amy. It's like the light is aimed directly at her and
It takes Petra a second to realize what's going on here. Amy is in the beam of light, but she's no longer laying on the couch
She's hovering off of it
Petra is terrified. She's speechless as Amy is floating through the rectangle of light
she then
Flies out the window and as she's going out the window the window was opened at this point
But the window screen was still there. She actually pushed through the window screen and tore open as she flew through it
Petra faints at this site. She can't even really get anything out. She faints and almost immediately comes to and
Begins screaming
This is when Keith wakes up and he runs out in the living room and Petra is screaming
She can't get a word out. She can't even comprehend what she just saw
All Keith knows is there's woman. It's on the ground screaming. There's a rainstorm outside
His wife is gone and the window has a huge tear in it
So he goes to run outside to see what had happened your first instinct would be kidnapping
Second instinct wild boar you're in the house back after all kangaroo mob. Who knows?
As he goes to run outside Petra starts saying don't go out there. Don't go out there
They got her they got her which of course is going to make him even more want to go out there
She tries to convince him of what happened that she got sucked up in this beam of light Keith does not believe her
He runs out. He begins running through the wilderness around the house calling out for his wife's name. No answer
He goes back in and Petra again is pleading with him what I saw you got to believe me what I saw
She was abducted at this bright light came in she floated out the window Keith still can't believe it
But in the back of his mind, he's trying to figure out like what could it have been? Where could she have gone?
They call the authorities
They call the police at 1140 so it's about 25 minutes later. They make the phone call now because it's Australia
It takes them until 1 a.m. To get there because there's a police station down the road
There's a police station maybe in the nearest town might even be the town past that
Keith is still out looking for her and as time goes on he starts to believe that maybe Petra is telling the truth
Because what else could it have been? The police show up and they you have to imagine they were extremely suspicious of what's going on
Young woman goes missing man with his female business partner are there
Female business partner is saying she was abducted by aliens the man kind of seems to be going along with it
The cops are probably thinking like did they murder her is this some sort of weird cover story? Is this the worst alibi ever?
Police are kind of searching the area around the house as well
Ring ring
Their phone starts ringing Keith answers it and there's a woman on the phone
And she goes
Is this the home of Amy Rylance?
Keith is like yeah
The woman goes she's safe
She's safe. She's here
Where's here?
Where's here Keith asks?
So this is what the second side of this story is
500 miles away. It's an eight-hour drive. There's a town called Mackay
It's it's around 1 a.m. And a young woman comes stumbling out of the wilderness headed towards a gas station
She's disheveled
She's dehydrated. She's barely coherent. She stumbles into the gas station
She's not really making any sense. They can tell that she's in distress. They give her some water. They charge you for it
They're like you have money on you right? She's like oh
They give her some water and there's a woman there who was gasping her car up. She actually says
I think this woman needs to go to the hospital
So her and her friend who was traveling with her they put the young woman in the car
They can't figure out who it is. She can't really say what her name is
They drive her to a local hospital and at that point when they get to the hospital, she's getting more fluid in her
She's becoming a little more lucid and apparently the woman who took her down there was going through her personal items
found her
Certification was able to get the phone number of her husband so on and so forth and that is how she's placed in this phone call
McKay is
500 miles away from where she was abducted. It's an eight-hour drive
But remember she was abducted at 1115 and now we're sitting a little bit past 1 a.m
How did she get so far away?
Now if you believe in UFOs we know how she got so far away
But the detectives are trying to figure this out the detectives
Don't really believe the story and if we've talked about this before on the show
There is a totally different view of aliens today than there was when I was growing up from the 60s until the early
2000s really it was a huge joke if you watch and I'll be in the show notes. There's
The news segment about this story in Australia and when they're interviewing one of the detectives when they're interviewing
Detective senior sergeant leaf Lindsey. He's laughing on camera at these people
He's laughing at them
Because it was a big joke for the longest time. It was a big joke now people take it a little bit seriously
But it's he doesn't seem to believe this story and that's fine, but he's like oh my god
I'm so sorry. I'm giggling and he's like trying to keep a straight face and he starts laughing again
He's like oh my goodness is this on is the camera on and it's super disrespectful
But he's openly mocking these people in their story
So the cops don't believe it, but they can't really figure it out. They actually are investigating
When they start looking at the story they go with the idea that this was staged and they begin asking people
In the town of McKay if she was seen before this happened if she was actually waiting there for the signal
But if you believe in UFOs
This is the story she tells she's on the couch. She's watching television. She doesn't fall asleep
She's just sitting there on the couch
Watching TV and then all of a sudden she's standing on a metal bench in a room full of lights
She immediately knows she is someplace other than where she should be and
The fear sets in
That's when she hears a male voice say don't be afraid
We're not gonna hurt you. Please be calm and
Then a door
Opens up a six foot tall man
Wearing a suit that covers him literally head to toe
There are some drawings with the story
It almost seemed like a full biohazard suit and the person wore a black mask underneath it to cover like their mouth and nose
So definitely humanoid, but they were covered in in a giant suit
She could see his eyes, but she couldn't see his mouth or his nose. He comes out and
Some sort of procedure was done
She doesn't remember what was done when they did pick her up from the hospital and they do show this in the video as well
She has these small triangle marks on her thighs and on her
Heels on the bottom of her feet and the reporter asks what happened and she goes I don't remember
I think they were just taking some sort of skin samples
But she says she was standing on the bench the guy entered something happened
She doesn't recall and then she said that the man said he was going to drop her off
Not far from where they picked her up
and
The next thing she knows she's walking through the bushes in the middle of nowhere and she sees the lights of a gas station off in the distance
And she finally gets there and basically collapses and is brought to the hospital
They do end up calling some local UFO researchers
They come out start interviewing them and then the trio of them Petra Keith and Amy disappear not mysteriously disappeared
They just stopped returning phone calls. They couldn't be they didn't want to go back to that house
They told the UFO researchers that they believed a car tried running them off the road
They believed that possibly the men in black were after them. They didn't feel comfortable telling their story anymore an
Interesting detail to note as well
When she is reunited with the people who know her they noticed a couple things one she recently dyed her hair
But her roots were showing much more than they should be in that amount of time that had passed
She dyed her hair a week ago her roots shouldn't be showing that early
And that could just be a bad job right though. She might need to get her money back
But it was also her legs. She normally shaved her legs
Her legs had several days worth of hair growth on them
So that's another outside factor now to the cops
They just go well, she's just not shaving her legs
It's a
Interesting hoax that they're trying to pull off and that was kind of the way the cops are going with it
But was she
This is what I find absolutely fascinating
We talk about lost time, but technically should be able to work both ways if you have vegan
You have to have anti-vegan if you can exist in our timeline if you can disappear
For an hour and then be dropped back off into you. It seems like a minute, but really an hour has passed
It could work in reverse where you are gone for three hours. You are measurably gone for three hours
But where you're at four eight ten days go by and
I think we'll wrap it up like this. I think the story is an interesting clue
to
other phenomenon
Stuff like missing people even stuff like missing 411
Because you have people being abducted and then dropped off quote-unquote nearby
To a starship
500 miles is nothing right something that's built to cross the galaxy
500 miles is nothing
To us five feet is nothing, but to an aunt that's its whole day. It's like damn it
You gotta get the sugars way over there
So to the alien who picked her up and dropped her off that could have simply been nothing
500 miles it's eight-hour trip
Just get on your eye on teleporter and you'll be fine
It'd be interesting to think like these people who mysteriously go missing they walk into the backyard they disappear
They're walking through the woods. They walk me on a shrub. They disappear. Maybe they aren't missing forever. They're just deposited in a place
So far away
No one thinks to look for them there and even then they didn't drop her off the gas station
They dropped her off in the wilderness near the gas station if it had been a young child or someone who was drunk
Someone who was frail
They would have just died in the wilderness
She could have ended up going the wrong direction and in her dehydrated confused state instead of walking towards the well-lit
Gas station. What if she had walked in the opposite direction? She'd be bleached bones in the Australian wilderness
And Petra and Keith would probably be on trial for murder
It could even happen to you tonight
As you're falling to sleep hoping to find some peace some comfort in your dreams
You close your eyes
And then you open them
You're no longer in your bedroom
You don't remember how you got here
Your limbs are trembling you can barely stand up
Your thoughts are racing your throat is dry
Your skin feels singed and sore a
Memory comes back a
Kindly alien telling you to just be calm everything will be okay
And you did what they said
You work home
You didn't panic is the laser scalpel singed to your skin
You did what they said you did everything that they said
But you can't understand why you're here now
You're crawling on all fours across the mossy forest floor
it seems
Devoid of all wildlife almost as if the beasts of the forest were scared away by whatever deposited you here
As you crawl across the forest floor
You hope you're crawling in the right direction
You hope you will find civilization
But you won't
You will just be another missing person
Seriously vanished from their own home
Did they run away?
Were they kidnapped where they murdered these are questions people always ask when your name is brought up
But they won't ever think to look a thousand miles away at that soft lump of vegetation
Underneath that oak tree that vaguely makes out the shape of
you
You
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be in your email address
You can also do stuff at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day and I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]