Get your dancing shoes on because we're doing the cabbage patch and we visit a small town in Utah
Or at least we would if it still existed
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I hope you're having a great day
I'm having a great day. It's a little hot. You know what's funny?
How are these intros gonna go when I'm freezing cold and I just gonna keep going. It's so cold. It's so cold
I'm one of those guys that I I'm kind of the minority because I'd rather be hot than cold
I feel like I am still a little more energetic when it's hot when I get when it gets cold and just miserable
You know, I can just take my clothes off or drink a bunch of water and I can cool down
But when you're cold when your bones get cold
That's the worst I came across the word. Let's start off with our food-based conspiracies
This is our week of food-based conspiracies
So honestly, I found what I would consider one of the dumbest conspiracies and I know what you're thinking of flat earth is stupid
The moon landing being faked stupid all that stuff like there's a lot of stuff
There's a lot of competition the reason why this is so dumb because it's so easily disproven
And yet a ton of people believe in it
A ton of people believe in it. So this conspiracy theory is
that China is
Making cabbage out of plastic and selling it to people to fool them
so you go to the store and you buy a head of cabbage and
When you pick it up, you don't immediately feel like you go. Oh, that feels waxy and weird
I'll put it in my shopping cart and then you take it home and you're cooking it and you're like that's weird
It's not really cooking right but I mean who am I who am I to guess how cabbage is supposed to be cooked
And then you eat it and you go wait a minute. This is wax
Like that's one of the dumbest conspiracy theories, but people believe it in the big group of people like it's it's a conspiracy theory
It's not so much in the West but people in Indonesia were having a big problem with it and how it started was that
They were making this Chinese
Business was making wax
Copies of food for restaurants. So when you walk into the restaurant you could look at a bowl of
I don't know wontons or dim sum or whatever because it was a lot of Japanese food on Lena
So you could go in you could see like
Some orange chicken and it looks perfect. You see each little piece of rice and
You see chunks of orange and the sauce and that little gross piece of orange peel that they leave in there for some weird reason
You're not supposed to eat and from that people then begin to suspect that China was making
Wax cabbage and selling it now they were making it and there's a YouTube video showing how to make wax cabbage and we'll include that
But that's a pretty big leap to go from here's a YouTube video showing how we manufacture this stuff to
They're selling us wax cabbage and people were complaining about this people in Indonesia were like you check your cabbage man because it's made of wax
They're tricking us. They're tricking us because very she's stupid because one like I said it's easily
Let's say even if they were doing that what would be the end result you would pick up a head of cabbage immediately
Realize it doesn't feel like a head of cabbage that it's a lot heavier
And it's feels waxy and then you would put it down
You're not going to and people are like oh no people are getting sick from this stuff
if you eat a ball of wax
You deserve to get sick if you're over the age of six and you eat a wax apple and you're not stoned
You deserve to get a little sick don't deserve to die, but you deserve the tummy ache you get from eating that
So you pick up some cabbage you go home you prepare it and then you eat it and you get sick
And so people were complaining about this and there's a couple
You know they've been trying to dispute this conspiracy theory, but it's like I said
It's done because it's easily disproven and it's also
vaguely racist it's a vaguely racist conspiracy
When we were talking about how to build a can how to tell make up a good conspiracy theory when you do it
I've always used examples of we don't trust governments and we don't trust the military or the media
This conspiracy theory is don't trust the Chinese
Don't trust anyone from China and people who believe in the conspiracy theory would go. Oh, yeah, man. Those Chinese. They're pretty shady
Like you have to take that leap of logic
So anyways that is just kind of a I mean that's all there is the conspiracy theory
But again people believe in it it would you know
We obviously know that if I watched they showed a YouTube video on how to make a wax apple people aren't going to say that
The government's making us eat wax apples, but now that I say that I'm sure I'm sure that's a conspiracy
I'm sure people believe that one out of every 85 apples is fake
But yeah, so fake cabbage now you may be a little more
Discerning when you go shopping for cabbage. I've actually never bought cabbage. I'll eat cabbage every once in a while like
With what do you eat cabbage with?
When have I eaten cabbage? I think the only time I've really eaten cabbage was with Mongolian barbecue. I love
Mongolian barbecue
The second story is
An interesting story so we got the cabbage taste out of our mouth second story
I find very interesting. It's on the conspiracy list on the iceberg list that we talk about all the time
And it's one of those stories that there's so little information for it. It is hard to disprove you
You know when you have the more information you have the easier it is to disprove
This is one of those stories that started off with just the phrase and
Then people begin digging into it and seeing what they could find and
Then I'll present that to you and then we'll kind of go through it. So this one is called
The Bel Ray Surge now the conspiracy goes like this in the city of Ogden or near the city of Ogden, Utah
There was a neighborhood called Bel Ray Estates. This happened relatively recently
1993 so again, it's far enough back that we can't confirm a lot of the stuff
But more recent than you would feel comfortable if this is a true story. So the story starts off
That first there was a sheep herder herding sheep out in the area and
there was a
lightning storm just appeared
Reno relatively out of nowhere
It
Came for it was like static in the sky. So you imagine this farmers out there with a sheep and there's like
Static in the sky it hits the ground and then moves across the ground crawls across the ground and begins just
electrocuting the sheep kills 12
Just shocks them to death here
And it's a weird people in town were like that's weird there was no storms in the area and the
The sheep herder who apparently survived
Said you know, I don't know what happened. I was just sitting out there
And I felt the electrical discharge and the next thing I know it was crawling across the ground and it
Killed my sheep
No one paid it in much mind, you know, there's freaks of nature these things happen
In the little neighborhood nearby of Bel Ray estates people just kind of went about their business went about their lives chalked it up
to a freak event and went on and
Then one day the town was empty completely empty
Not a person not an animal nothing
Wasn't a city wasn't a town there weren't a ton of people there
but enough
That people in the city of Ogden noticed that they were missing and
When they went out there
All they found was buildings
Empty buildings the wind cutting through the streets
The government bulldozed the town
Wiped it off the map
And it was lost to history that is the initial mystery of the Bel Ray surge
To get that much of the story first I started off on I have to find a source here a source there a source here little bits of information
Eventually I stumbled across somebody linked a YouTube video explaining it in more detail. It's pretty similar to the story
I just told you
So a couple things they left out of the YouTube video
They do say that they believe that this was caused by the accidental discharge of a weapon
It was basically a neutron bomb style weapon that was meant to destroy
Biological life but leave the buildings intact with low levels of radiation
So an invading force could take out a city and they just march right into it and that's similar to the neutron bomb
That's what they were going for with the neutron bomb. So they would leave infrastructure
Standing but eliminate the enemy. I
Did some more so that was their hypothesis. I found a few other ones. I
Actually found that the name of the technology supposedly is called the ghost circle
Now I ran across that and when I tried to find that info again
It took me a while which you know can be weird or it could just be that I didn't should have bookmarked my links
So we'll chalk it up to should have bookmarked my links. But anyways ghost circle technology is the name that's been given to this weapon
Basically just clears out an area
What's interesting about it is that it doesn't a
Neutron bomb will disintegrate human matter or biological matter what the ghost circle is supposedly does is it turns
living
biological entities into energy so it's not only a weapon
But it's an energy source you could then destroy the entire city
Destroy and like you're going into Moscow you drop the ghost circle into Moscow and then you use the excess energy and
Store it so you're basically both removing an obstacle and creating an energy source
How likely is that it makes a good story
Makes a good story. Let's assume for right now that this incident happened of the Bell Ray estates was wiped off the map
That story is interesting. I don't really know how the science would work. You would discharge that energy so quickly after evaporating people
I don't know how you would be able to then harness it. You bring a big giant Duracell along with you on a flatbed. I don't know
So I think that this tape you can start off with the story of
The estates and say that's true the weapon testing
May be true and then the people being turned into usable energy. That's that's where you're starting to lose me
That's where you're starting to lose me
Then I came across a couple others there or one other theory
Well, there there was two other theories
But one of them even the person who was stating it said this came from my uncle my uncle makes stuff up and it was that the Bell Ray surge
Wasn't a weapon testing. It was a UFO
And I don't want to say like invasion, but it was multiple UFOs
Over the over the neighborhood of Bell Ray and they were shooting lights down into the city and things like that
And that's I will completely dismiss that because even the person posting it says this comes from an unreliable source
however, the third one was was that
This gentleman talked to someone in Ogden because he lived in the area and the man says oh, no
I know exactly what you're talking about Bell Ray surge. What happened was they were having a massive
They're doing a mining operations in the area and when they were blowing the rock apart
What happened was there was a chain reaction underneath the earth and what made it?
odd
Was that the chain reaction when they detonated this bomb when they detonated this dynamite?
It didn't break in the way that they thought it would it traveled through tunnels almost like something was propelling the
Force through the tunnels in multiple directions and it caused this release of this gas
That caused a lot of people to get poisoned and they had to leave the area and then to cover that up
It was an industrial conspiracy basically the mining company said, you know what? We're just going to cover this up
Here's some hush money. Everyone leave town. We don't want to get fined and they just shut everything down. I
Actually think that as unlikely as that is that's probably more likely than the ghost circle
And here's why something like the ghost circle technology if it was real
It would be in more widespread use even if you couldn't control it even if you had trouble controlling it
You would still we would still see it pop up in
Across the planet like you can cover up one event maybe
And also if they lost control of it, then why didn't they just keep creeping through this, you know
To the farther cities of Ogden and stuff like that
But if it was successful then they're go, okay, let's go stage two. Let's we can use this to clear out a room
We can make just people disappear
No one will ever know what happened to them. There's no evidence that they even disappeared and we're not seeing that
So those are the three three theories that we have we have that it was in a accidental or maybe even purposeful
Could have been an accident
It could be in a purposeful test of the weapon because it was such a small community
It could have been UFOs it could have been a mining accident that got out of control
If this story is true, I
Don't think it's any of those three one and we'll go backwards. There's no record. There's no name of the mining company
There's no record of any sort of industrial accidents in that area
even the person who told the story couldn't name the mining company and
Conveniently the mining company pays all the money to keep everyone hushed up
So, you know never reached court. So there's no records for that the UFO story is
You know again came from an unreliable source the ghost circle technology
As intriguing as that is that we've built a weapon that can do that again
We already have a weapon that can do that. It's a neutron bomb. You're just trying to eliminate people and
Keep the infrastructure up
and if we're going to test a weapon like that
There's a thousand other communities that we could have done it in one thing that the people
You know I've run into this a lot of with conspiracy theories and stories like this that you notice that
Like harp when they're talking about the weather control system
It's tested in the United States like they think that because the US government is testing the weapon
They test it on their own population. We have tested, you know acid and aerosol weapons on Americans sure
But in a global on a global scale if you wanted to test this ghost circle technology
Why would you do it to a city?
In America in 1993 so this wasn't like back in pine, you know pioneer days or even like in the 50s
You would put it on a plane and take it to Venezuela and find a village to use it on
Or you'd go to the farthest outskirts of Siberia and use it over there
You you do it you could just use it to see how it affects animals. Why would you do it on a town?
It's about 30 miles
South of Ogden, Utah
It's this isn't some desolate area where no one's ever been this was a nice neighborhood supposedly if it existed
So I don't buy any of those explanations. It's possible that the city next so we'll go back to the original story
It's possible that the story is completely made up
It's possible that the neighborhood existed at some point and people just moved out of it. That's not likely
Generally especially again, this is fairly recent 1993. It's probably in most of my listeners lifetime. It's definitely in mine
So that leaves us with the story not being true
There's two caveats to that one is that supposedly there's satellite footage of before and after
So we see satellite footage of the town satellite footage of nothing and they talk about that in the YouTube video
And they actually show some photos. Here's the problem. I can't find the photos
And if you're testing a weapon if you're that level of the government where you're testing weaponry on the US population
And then completely covering it up. I think you have access to the photos of the satellites
I think they could easily call up the 1993 equivalent of Google and
Say hey remove those because we know that they do that now
We know they draw black boxes over secure area. So again, that doesn't wash
But this was something interesting I came across and all of my research going back and forth and watching YouTube videos and things like that
We'll take this with a grain of salt. I thought this was interesting and I'm gonna read portions of his post there
This is back in 2016 when he wrote this I've decided that after collecting all of the images
I will attach that the bell ray bell ray bells ray or bell rays surge
Those are all the different spellings of it is simply a myth
I think the original person who mentioned it was inventing the name then and there
There is no local history to the area and although things like this are really easily covered up nothing matches and logic prevails
logic prevails
Pickle party, okay
Then he goes on to say there is literally no coordinates maps
No towns people made maps or sketches of the hill range nearby and no local authority to that section of land south of Wildcat Road
Which makes it hard to go back in history and find what was originally there before 1993
so
We just have this empty area and he's saying we don't have any maps people haven't got any maps
Which again leads the credence to is always empty because why would you need maps and structures?
There was nothing there. Why would you need maps showing structures or even people going out there and doing detailed maps if there is no reason to be out there?
So again, he's debunking it, but this was what I thought was interesting
He goes but I did make some success and I admit some of the things I found were a bit strange like the abandoned landlines
These things I found in the road that I think are movement
Detectors and the fact that if you compare my satellite images of the area between February 2nd 1992
And April 1993 there is a massive change in nature and landscape
The waterholes appear
Property lines disappear phone lines go up. Yes, that's right in 1992
There is no telephone poles by the side of the road and in 1993 onwards
There is all connected and leading to one unconnected pole by the edge of another watering hole
WTF
And then he includes a link to a
zip file
with all of these photos
So
Let's take him at his word that he's done this research
He can come across and I think the most suspicious thing
I think the fact that the telephone poles went up after 1992
Isn't necessarily that suspicious because of the areas. I mean the area is still getting civilized at that area putting that up
I do think it's weird that they all kind of connect to an unconnected pole and
The fact that there's what he considers massive change in the nature in the landscape of the area
Interesting I applaud this guy for going out and doing his research and really digging into it
It's also suspicious that that zip file that is on the mega upload site. It's gone now
Does all of that mean that the Bell Ray surge story is true
Just on the facts no I think it's a story that feels good and it's creepy and
It could be true and I think it's kind of like the Dublin, Wisconsin story where it's a
Scary to think that an entire group of people can go missing
But the interesting thing about the Bell Ray surge if you were making up this conspiracy
I think one one place they tripped up is they provided too much detail
It's a weapon called the ghost circle
That can eliminate biological matter and leave building standing and it may or may not convert them to energy
And it was a weapons test and Dublin was just people disappeared
So your brain gets to feel it fill in the blanks was it demons was it interdimensional?
Did the town never exist was it a ghost town was it a military test?
Was there some sort of madness in the area did people just up and leave was there like a zombie attack?
Your brain fills in the area fills it in so you get to pick and choose what conspiracy you works best for you
If you believe in interdimensional aliens invading that's what happened
If you believe that ghost the Indians of Native Americans ran through the town shopping people's heads off and dragging them off to some horrible
Hell that happened
Do you believe UFOs abducted people that happened it left it so open-ended?
And it was far enough back that there were like yeah, there's no maps
None of this stuff is just a few
Or Mandela effect that was an actually another one that could have worked with Dublin, Wisconsin this one the the conspiracy is so specific
That you can go well, you know like I can dispute the weapon testing
They're not going to use an energy-based weapon in 1993 on American soil
They're going to do that anywhere else in the world
And I know what you're thinking Jason they still crack an LA they don't still crack in Venezuela and if fair enough
I'm not saying the American government has been amazing to its people a hundred percent of the time
There's a lot. There's a big difference between the CIA moving crack from South America moving cocaine from South America
Turning it into crack and having the bloods and the crypts sell it on the streets
Versus running a weapons test that eliminates
3000 people from the city of Compton
One's plausible and been proven honestly and the other one is you know fantasy science fiction
I will say this though. I'll give the story this
If it's true
The best thing that they could have done is to make up a crazy story like this
You can make it this ridiculous and people would just automatically poo poo it and that was kind of the idea with the is Simpsons real life
You take a real event that is completely tragic and turn people to mutants you cover it up in so many ridiculous theories and
Then if anyone ever exposes the truth you go no no, that's ridiculous
My personal feeling is that I
Think that this the Bell Ray surge story is
As intriguing of as Dublin, Wisconsin
But I don't think it holds up to the scrutiny of Dublin, Wisconsin
I think that whoever created this I don't think it's true and I think whoever created this story
should try to rein it in and
Turn it back into something completely vague and
That may have honestly been the intention
It may have honestly just been the phrase and over time this myth is grown first
It was like the Bell Ray surge and someone goes well, what's that and someone goes?
Town disappeared and left it vague
But once you started once it started to gain a bit of traction. This is a very very
This is this conspiracy theory is not very well known at all
I'm going to assume that 80% of the people listening to this have never heard of this conspiracy theory
So it may have started off to be suit a super big conspiracy theory
And it's just gotten too much information. It sags the story down a town in a town 30 miles away from Ogden, Utah
Disappearing off the map and the maps being changed. You have a perfect follow-up to a devil in Wisconsin
And people can fill in the blanks which always makes it more terrifying saying that it was this that and the other thing
None of that
It takes away from the this type of myth. It makes it less scary
I was watching a horror movie the other day called the autopsy of Jane Doe and it was absolutely terrifying
I was on the edge of my seat
So well done
Super tense
great acting
Creepy the stakes were high for the people involved
And I remember just being like oh my god. Oh my god. I getting so tense and then they
Revealed spoiler alert
They revealed that this body they were doing an autopsy on was a witch and I immediately felt all the tension leave my body
Wasn't the movie's fault the movie was still really good and had a had a good ending
But I don't find witches scary at all. I think I know just that's not a
That's not a creature type that I find scary. I don't find vampires scary. I don't find mummies scary
So
Right when they revealed that piece of information. I just complied all the tension
Dropped left my body and I was like oh they're fine a witch and I don't find that particular creature scary
So and I think it's the same thing like this when I was doing the research
It took me a while to find all this stuff too
This is all spread apart in these bits and pieces and when you look at these links
You'll see that it's just like huge posts that I had to go through
But as I was reading and I'm like oh, that's really creepy this town disappeared and then they're like yeah
It's a weapon and the US military was testing it. I'm like
It's just not a scary. It's not as fascinating
So I'm gonna call I don't I don't believe that the Bell Ray surge is anything real
But I hope it's stoked your imagination. Maybe you have more information than me
It's funny
This is also one of those ones that people are like oh my god
I was just investigating this and two cops just showed up at my door at midnight
And they're like do you know anyone in Utah and other people are like oh my god, please stay safe and that's you know
They're just playing around. I don't I don't know if the people saying please stay safe or joining in on the joke
But I mean I I've seen whole YouTube videos about this and that guy's not arrested and you know
Even though I'm getting these little pieces of information. It's not because it's being covered up. It's just because it's not well known
so if you have more information if you lived in the Ogden area or
You know I
Go nuts if you believe that it's absolutely true and you have some evidence or proof for me or anybody post it out there
But if you don't and you want to be part of this legend this though
I you know could be you know, this is one of those growing myths
Go at that too. I
Think that's just as fascinating sometimes the story for me
Finding this information for me was more fascinating than the story itself. I'm putting together this puzzle
It's funny because at the very end I found the YouTube video and that kind of just summed everything up
But in the beginning I'm finding this post and this post and this post and this post and to me assembling the puzzle was the best part
Whether or not it was true
became irrelevant I
Was happy that the term was actually a quote-unquote real term because sometimes I'm looking up sexual assault missiles
That's on that list. I can't find anything
I think someone just put it in there as a joke and the jokes on me because I spent a half hour
Trying to look up sexual assault missiles
And that's just part of the job
But this may be something you know if you know more information or if you think you can make this story better go nuts
it's still super unknown and
It's malleable enough malleable enough to really just kind of get in there and put your own personal imprint on it
I'm not saying go out and make up your own conspiracy theories
but again sometimes this stuff moves out of the realm of a true conspiracy theory and
becomes a thought exercise becomes a
shared narrative among fans of this stuff
So that's gonna be it for tonight's episode I hope you had I hope you had fun
I hope you had a good time listening to that. I like I said, I really like that Bell Ray story
I do like the story the Bell Ray search and I do like I
Did like the journey to get to the answers that I wanted and again that doesn't make it if somebody
Disproves ghosts to me. It doesn't make me not like hearing ghost stories even skeptics
Will love to hear a good scary ghost story. I
Do want to say that I want to give a shout out to a listener of mine
Ash black
Ash black if you've noticed on your podcast stream or on the website, we have a brand new logo
Ash black made that it's amazing and that was just something that he put together
He put together and like an evening if that
Sent it to me sent me a bunch of different variations of the artwork
It looks amazing and what I love most about it is that I think it sums up the show
It has a real kind of punk rock vibe. I like the color choice. I love that third eye
Hanging off of in the middle of the dead rabbit. It's just all of these great elements
So hats off to you ash black and truly is amazing truly is amazing artwork. I'm stoked that you did it
I'm stoked that it's just a great-looking piece of art. It's now my desktop wallpaper. It's my phone wallpaper
I'm just flattered and humbled that you took your talent and your time to make that for me. So I mean legitimately I'm
I'm speechless even though I said all that stuff dead rabbit radio at gmail.com as our email address
We're on Twitter at Jason O. Carpenter
We have a YouTube channel is dead rabbit radio where we take out little clips of these episodes and put them on there
Am I missing something Facebook? We're on Facebook comm slash dead rabbit radio on there as well
So feel free to contact me through any of those join them up subscribe to the podcast if you haven't already
It's great seeing the downloads. We have a daily episodes coming out. So I hope we're keeping you entertained
That's gonna be all of it for tonight. This episode looks like it's running very long
So if I'm able to get it into the 30 minute range, I
Stayed up quite late. I don't know why it went so long
I think I just talked a lot about Bell Research because I had a lot of fun research in that story
And I hope you had a lot of fun listening to it. I'm Jason Carpenter and I will see you tomorrow
You
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]