One of the one possibly one of the funniest true crime stories have come across recently we're gonna talk about that
We're gonna take a look at a time that American frontiersmen
politician
Shooter of animals Davey Crockett had a run-in with the creature. He couldn't kill and
Then we take a look at a bizarre
Theory that goes back
thousands of years
Is it possible that diseases are?
Actually supernatural today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day, too
Let's go ahead and get started because we got a lot of stuff to cover here
First off I want to give a shout out to our newest supporter of the show John from Scar
John from the Scar group. Thank you so much. He's the one who's he's done a couple pieces of artwork for the show
He's done the colored in Dead Rabbit logo, which you'll see appear a lot
He also did the custom artwork for the
final episode of the Korea week North Korea week
So I wanted to give John from Scar a shout out longtime supporter of the show
So you are going to be our carboner copter pilot for today
You're gonna be our chauffeur. You're gonna take us wherever we want to go
Doesn't matter if you want to go there. You are the one driving us around now
Let's go ahead and first off. Let's hop in the Jason Jalopy John. Let's go ahead. Let we're leaving behind Hood River
We're headed out to Natick, Massachusetts never heard of this town before never
I've never even knew it existed right and today I wake up. I've literally just got done reading this story
I'm recording this episode extremely early because the story is so hilarious
I just got to tell this story for driving out. We're leaving behind Hood River
We're going to Natick, Massachusetts. It's August
2019 now
They do a little bit of a meta here before actually getting the story. Let me tell you what was going on
It just woke up probably about two hours ago. I'm doing my reading
I do all reading all my articles in the morning stuff like that and I'm
drinking my Diet Pepsi
half awake
And I see this headline this couple is suing this this married couple suing some eBay executives
For harassment or something like that and I remember looking at being like, ah, you know some lunatic, right couple couple
Loona I guess I'm some sort of bootlicking corporate shill because I saw the headline and I was like a couple lunatics
Accusing this company of something they probably didn't commit
I'm kind of reading through the article and I'm reading it
I'm like, oh these guys probably just looking for a quick payday and then I get about halfway through the article
I'm barely awake. Okay, I get half through the article and I start seeing words pop up like prosecutors
federal charges
Felony and I go whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a second. This isn't some lunatic lawsuit
This isn't some like civil civil lawsuit because this story is absolutely insane
So when I was reading and I was like, this can't be true, right? This has to be some people looking for a quick payday
Let's rewind back in time and go to August of 2019
There's this married couple right they live in a Natick, Massachusetts and they've provoked the ire of eBay
The online auction site really the only online auction site and the only one that matters
Six former eBay executives have been charged federal crimes
Now this is all alleged, right? But one of the guys is on the run right now. They can't find them authorities can't find them
They're charged with high-level eBay executives. Okay
they're charged with conspiracy to commit cyber stalking and
Conspiracy to tamper with witnesses and you're like what?
The two main people involved was James. This is all alleged again James Bogg
He's the former senior director of safety and security for eBay and then you have David Harville
eBay's former director of global security and resiliency again
This wasn't a couple people working at the warehouse who were having a crummy day
These are people who ran their security teams
They also had the you also had the former senior manager of global intelligence and a former senior manager of special operations for eBay's
global security team
Okay, all alleged and that's the lesson I'm gonna say that
So you have these high-level people who are threatening emails and texts are threatening to crush this lady
I'm gonna put her down. They're gonna show her what's what
So listen the reason why they're all former and executives is because eBay is already running internal investigation
And fired all of these people and said we had nothing to do with this
We have nothing to do with this other people say it may go a little bit higher against the CEO of eBay actually
Recently over this over what we're about to get into if these former eBay executives, right?
high-level
These people are pulling in hundreds of thousands of dollars a year and they want to strike back at this couple
They want to quote crush this lady
So this is what they this is what you're paying all this money for for your senior manager of global intelligence
These are the plans they come up with to harass this couple. They send threatening messages emails text messages
That's pretty standard, right? They send pizzas. Okay. This should have been an obvious setup, right?
The pizza parlor is is should have
They should be responsible for this one at 4 30 in the morning
Tom and those pizza like obviously that's fake
No, I don't even know pizza parlors are open at 4 30 in the morning
But apparently if you have eBay on your side, you can make them open they add this is pretty funny
They put a ad online
That said if we're having a yard sale, but if no one is outside force said yard sale just knock on her door
That's pretty harmless, right? I mean it'd be annoying
And again the people who I mean who walks up to an empty yard and be like yuck yuck
I wonder this with this location the yard sale, right?
Well, better go knock on the door
Yard sales at 4 30 in the morning. They also this is where it starts to get a little more iffy. They put a craigslist ad
Inviting singles couples and swingers to their house to party after 10 p.m. Every night now
That's like trolling 101 and it's quite hilarious to think that you imagine like a boardroom and all these people are sitting there in their
Suits and their ties and stuff like that. They actually have like a PowerPoint
They're like, what are we going to do to this couple today?
And they're like, I don't know how's the Swinger initiative going and they're like go to the next slide
They're like according to this five percent of all swingers in Nantik have been to this house
You see now why I thought this was just somebody I was like there's no way that eBay executives that actually be doing this
I'm reading the article and I'm just kind of glancing over and I'm thinking there's no way that
There's no way this would be happening, right?
But then I get further down and the federal government is involved these guys are actually being charged one guy is on the run
But that's not all that's not all because remember who you're messing with bro. You're messing with eBay and
eBay known for
Having access to every single thing on the planet
So I mean I could call up and have a bunch of swingers show up at your house, right? I could not gonna but I could
But eBay has the villain
Basically has access to every prank in the world
So this is they started sending this couple stuff
They get a bloody Halloween pig mask like the mask the saw pig woman thing
It's like a head, you know, you guys know what a pig woman looks like
I don't know. Maybe you don't maybe you don't watch horror movies
I mean sure it wouldn't be fun to get in the mail, but whatever
Then now you have a holy costume. Thanks eBay. They sent this is cruel
Married couple sitting there one day you get a book how to survive the death of a spouse
That's dark but then the line thinks up
They send them a box of maggots
You're like already reading this book. They're like, oh, this is kind of creep. They're sending us some threats
But next to the big mask
Next day you get a box the box is moving across your table
Box of maggots box of live spiders. I mean it come on these guys
This is genius trolling at this point
This is when some executive at eBay overheard and goes what you're having a bunch of swir show up at your house
Why don't we send them all the gross stuff we sell on eBay box of maggots box of live spiders?
Which you know both of those you have to open right to find the maggots in the spiders
It's not like you just saw a box on it
It's from spiders or us with a sticker on it caution live spiders inside they open the box up the spiders poured out
I know that probably triggered some of you guys and I meant to do that
I meant to do that open a box up bunch of maggots pop out
One giant maggots rule them all
This was funny. This is another funny one. I mean they're all kind of funny except for the book they sent a
They sent them a bunch of porn
But see that that's one thing you're like, all right. I just got my free porn magazines first time if you'd go
They still make porn magazines. This is quite quaint. I'm gonna show this to my hipster friends
They sent porn, but they sent it to their neighbors with their name on it
Basically it looks like they were ordering the couple was ordering the porn, but it was getting delivered to the wrong address
That's a nice spin eBay
Give a plot for that's funny
That's that porn to the neighbors with their name on it. That's pretty funny. I'm not doing to me, right?
But still pretty funny and then they sent them a pig
I just had to record this story like when I got the reading they sent him a pig fetus
They sent this couple a pig fetus, but
But the shipper of the pig fetus something sparked in their brain and was like, hmm
They actually called up the family first. They probably realized it was going to a residential address
It was probably like for is this the place my uncle lives in that town
He's got a bunch of porn that he didn't order and it had his neighbors name on it
They called up the family go did you order a pig fetus?
No, we did not order a pig fetus so they didn't get that so you're asking yourself what in the world could have
Prompted six there. I don't know if I said this earlier. It's six different eBay executives
Who have been fired and are currently facing charges one is arrested the other ones on the run and for the people born arrested
But they're facing these charges
What could have made these eBay executives again last time allegedly?
Start a campaign of terror
sending swingers sending a sex perverts to their house
pizzas maggots
Live spiders. They're still running around look behind you. There's one ten yards away from you at any given time. They're everywhere
All this stuff attempted attempted pig fetus delivering what could this couple have possibly done to get this
They wrote a newsletter
They wrote a newsletter about e-commerce and in the newsletter they talked about eBay
said eBay sucked and
Then in the anonymous comments people to be like you're right eBay sucks
That was it that was it
That's terrifying right I
100% thought because I read the article obviously backwards the lead was these this couple writes this newsletter and eBay is harassing them
And I'm thinking that's
Impossible I remember reading go they're probably just suing them in court because they got a bloody pig mask and it could have you know
Someone could have been messing with them or whatever. I thought that's
Impossible and I kept reading the article and I'm thinking I'm half awake and I'm thinking they're firing civil charges against six eBay executives
Saying that they were speaking truth to power and they were getting harassed because a bloody pig mask got sent to their house and
Then I was that uh-uh
nope
They these people are being charged they're facing jail sentence prison sentences
They've been fired from their job at eBay after an internal investigation
That's
Terrifying and and the couple went to the local police and they were like telling the cops that the cops at first were kind of like
What I was doing like that sounds impossible
And then finally the detectives really started looking into it
They pushed it really really hard and then they got all the eBay and eBay started investigating and canned all these people that's terrifying, right?
like I
It sounds made up, but no and the the police are saying we're not gonna reveal the name of the couple or their blog
We're not even gonna reveal it was a blog. It was a blog dude
Like you know what I mean think about that would be the quick think about how much people crap on Michael Bay online all the time
Right and the fact that Michael Bay would even take one one minute out of his time to post a craigslist ad to send
Swingers to your house sounds ridiculous
But these guys had a targeted campaign against this couple and that's it who had a blog talking about e-commerce and they're like eBay sucks
Now and here's the thing we don't know because I don't have access to the blog
I don't know exactly what they said, but I can't admit the most scathing review of eBay the most
Expose a review of eBay on this blog
Would not justify that activity right eBay couldn't I
It's boggles my mind because obviously this wasn't a executive having a bad day and goes you stink leaves like a fake phone call
This was like targeted harassment over time period, right? It takes a while to arrange a big thing to get sent to somebody's house
Absolutely bizarre terrifying really
You think I like I'm always coming across gang stalking stuff, and I'm like a gang stalking any gang stalking me
This is usually a bunch of bunch of weirdos, right? And that was my knee-jerk reaction to this one. It's like there's no way
This is true absolutely creepy, and then I think as I'm reading the article people that I piss off all the time
Like yeah, so anyways that is a bizarre true crime story. It's funny
It's good that the people are getting justice and it probably make me pause a little bit more
When I wake up in the morning and I'm reading an article like this or even in the midday because I completely brushed it off
I was thinking out this can't be true, but they're being dragged in front of federal court
Really the couple now they may be making the blog still we don't know but the couple now definitely
Can sue eBay later on get a ton of money?
I'm sure lawyers are already salivating over that lawsuit and they got a free free box
It's out of it, right and they made some new friends. It turns out that the real harassment was the swing or friends
They made along the way
I think that is the real lesson to learn from this whole thing. So shame on you
former executives of eBay and possibly other members of the eBay community allegedly
But who knows
Scary though, isn't it dude like all the stuff that's put out there on a daily basis all those negative opinions out there on a daily basis
I can understand if you're making fun of like a local restaurant and they like get uppity and they're like no you take that down
And so I mean it's still still despicable like people are allowed to have their opinions and things like that
But then the restaurant should just be like ah, whatever we have enough good customers
Or maybe that review is valid or whatever
But that's like a local thing to have eBay actually care what some blog whether or not the blog had 10 readers or 100,000 readers or whatever
It wouldn't affect their overall business for whatever reason what this person was saying in this blog
Was really digging into eBay's skin
But still
Live maggots was a bridge too far eBay. I mean again, I got a free bloody pig mask out of it. That's awesome
But everything else is pretty gross. Let's go ahead that story took a long time
I'm editing nothing that story took a little bit longer than I thought so we're gonna save the davi crocket story for tomorrow
It's quite short, but it's not short enough to really do justice now
John let's hop in the carpenter copter. We're leaving behind natik
Massachusetts and I yes. Yes, you do notice I have a
Safeway plastic bag in my hand and john's like you're not really that's not what I think it is
It's all wiggling
It's a little of both you'll never know when you need
A handful of maggot spiders we might in the rest of this story who knows so i'm gonna carry this bag around for the rest
They have us in we're flying the helicopter
We're flying it out
We're leaving behind the united states and we are headed out to
Thailand
We're flying over the villages. It's january 2013. We're going to tamban ta seawang in thailand
so we're walking through this village
and
Everything's going normal. It's just normal village life. There's a bunch of dudes singing about stuff some chick wants to read books
And then this young healthy man falls over dead
People are like oh what happened that kind of ruined the big chorus we were building up to
A couple days later another young healthy man in the village dies
Over the course of a couple days four men in total die of some respiratory illness
So they contact a medium doctors can't figure it out
So they contact a medium
And she says you have to hang a red shirt outside of your house if you have a young man in your house
You have to hang a red shirt outside your house that'll keep the ghost from getting them
I actually mentioned this on yesterday's episode
Disease goes away young men stop dying five years later in 141 kilometers away. What is that like 200 miles in nakton
Ratchezma's femi district
Young man dies respiratory illness. No one can figure it out a couple days later another young man dies
respiratory illness
This is in 2018
Word gets out of what the cure could be
Put a red shirt hanging outside your house
People stop dying now in in the area
They attribute this to a a widow's curse a widow's ghost. It's basically a
What it what it sounds like a a woman whose husband died when she passes away her spirit is floating around and it's striking down young men
Is some sort of brutal revenge thing
And the red shirt or red towel was to wave it away
But you know, it's probably just is a skeptic. It's probably just
Coincidence, right? You have a disease that strikes. You have an unknown respiratory illness that strikes and it's already run its course
The red shirts don't actually change anything
The disease would have stopped anyways. Let's leave behind tylen. Let's head out to india. This is in 2020
We meet a man. We meet the swami
chakrapani
He's the national president of the all india hindu
maha shabaha
And he's making this statement. We're standing in this crowd and he's making this statement in india
the corona virus
Is an avatar
sent to get revenge for eating animals and everyone in the
Crowd is clapping everyone in the crowd is clapping and he's like yes
Yes, it has come down
to destroy
the meat eaters
And it's ravaging the planet. We've gotten out of control. We've lost our way
We've lost balance with nature. He knows the cure for it
The president of china must create an idol of the corona
And seek forgiveness
All non vegetarian chinese people must pledge to not hurt any innocent creatures
And doing this will make the corona return to its own plane of existence
We're standing in this crowd and you go well
The last i checked the could not only chinese people were eating meat
And last i checked not only chinese people had corona virus and i was i'm like yes
Yes, but india and china don't really like each other. I want to use these two stories really as a jumping off point
Do diseases have a super natural origin?
We talk about demonic possession where a demon can
Inhabit a human being and cause it to cause chaos destruction work for ebay starts sending out pig fetuses all this stuff
A demon can possess a body. Why couldn't a demon?
possess a germ
Why couldn't a demon possess something smaller than a human body?
And if the and i'm not disregarding corona virus or any disease whatsoever. I'm not saying i'm not saying anything like that
This is a thought experiment
But if a demon can possess a human and biblically a demon can possess a pig
That happened when the dude was possessed and jesus was like you get out of that dude and the demons are like uh, uh, uh
And that's where that famous quote comes from when jesus has how many demons are in you the demon goes
We are legion for we are many
And the demons like no that was a cool line
But get out get out and the demons are like aw and they he
God puts them in the bodies of pigs like possesses a bunch of pigs with them
It's like get in there and then the pigs drown themselves
the demons cause the pigs to drown themselves so
Biblically demons can possess non-human creatures in fiction and impossible
stories that you see
Demons may be able to possess inanimate objects
Onto dolls and stuff like that, but you could debate whether or not one those stories are correct at all
But you though you could have human ghosts inhabit those as well
I don't know if a human ghost could technically possess a human
But I should look into that considering that is kind of my job. But can a demon
possess
a germ
It's an interesting question because what that would mean
What it would mean is that the germ is vulnerable to the same thing that the demon is vulnerable to
So again in demon lore you can perform an exorcism on a human
You can put holy water on a human who's possessed by demon and it would drive these things out
If you are now again, this is gonna sound completely ridiculous, but if you add a a germ
On a slide like a micro microscope slide and you have a dropper of holy water when squirt squirt
Would the germ react to it now if you have a microscope
Please do that. Please go get some water and then start getting people to cough on slides
Maybe you can find ones that are demonically possessed, but wouldn't that be interesting?
I think it's an interesting thought experiment. Could a demon infect a germ and if it did
Would when humans are possessed again according to demon lore when humans are possessed they become incredibly strong
They become super smart. They can speak languages. They basically have
All the intelligence of a demon. So they've been around for tens of thousands of years of centuries tens of thousands of centuries
They have all the intelligence of the demon. They're physically strong. They can pick people up. They're in the classroom
Maybe some mild telekinetic powers now that I think about it is actually interesting because
Demons don't have a lot of powers once they're in a human body
They can mildly make stuff levitate, but like dematerialization things like that bending spoons
It doesn't really work that way. They're pretty limited
But they definitely do have increased strength and they have the vast intelligence of a demon
If you put that into a germ you lose it. I mean, I don't not say the germs are going to be able to bench press 10 other germs
But it may be able to become a more hearty creature
a creature more immune to
cures
So if we accept that demons can possess people
Why couldn't demons possess germs and if demons possess germs?
or a virus
What's to stop it from being a virus that is close to being incurable?
You could have it so that the demon virus that I can't believe
I'm actually even saying this out loud. You can have it when the demon demon virus when it splits and replicates
Does it have the full strength of the demon in each little atom?
Or does the demon get weaker and weaker?
And the reason why I think it's interesting is because
We talk so much about healing the body healing the body when it comes to medicine, but even
Western medicine is coming around with the idea that you also have to heal the mind
That visualization plays a huge part in healing
They do say that having visualization when you're sick imagining the cancer cells slowly dying off turning into nothingness
helps so much
So when even western medicine and eastern medicine has always been about the spirit the mind as well
It's not just like here take this you also have to
Work on your mind your meditation your onefulness to help defeat the disease
So what if diseases aren't just a biological enemy?
What if on just a basic level it's not just attacking the body but attacking the mind attacking the soul?
So to cure them you have to fight them on both levels
And if we accept that then we can push it one step further and say that not only is a life-threatening disease
Something that attacks the mind and the body but also something that attacks the spirit the soul
That's the demonic angle to it
By no means saying stop taking your medicine. I'm by no means at all saying don't go to the doctor when you're sick
But you can always supplement
Your healing with healing you can do yourself do what the doctors tell you to do
But at the same time being mindful
Meditating visualizing can help a lot as well
If the world of the supernatural is inhabiting the world of microbes
The battle to find cures for these diseases that have plagued mankind for centuries and new ones that are popping up today
Can go on even longer
Because we're not fighting just one enemy. We're not just fighting a biological enemy. We're not simply fighting an enemy of flesh and blood
But of spirit
It's not one that just creeps in our bedroom at night or follows us down a dark road when we're alone, but it inhabits
amoebas
turns sniffles
into respiratory illnesses
And we could labor for years and years and years in laboratories
trying to find a cure
And when we find a cure we find out it only works or barely works or doesn't work
But maybe the component that is missing isn't
Another amino acid
Maybe the cure that's missing is the right medicine
and a red flag
hanging outside your house
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio
Twitter is @dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but i'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]