When a young man gets stood up on a date, he hops on his motorcycle and sadly heads back home.
Little does he know he's not going to reach home, he's going to become a soldier on an intergalactic battlefield.
And then we take a look at a true story, we take a look at a story that actually happened and isn't made up by some lunatic.
It's the story of a young man fighting in a very real war, the war in Afghanistan.
A young man and his squad is on patrol in Afghanistan when they fall prey to a Taliban ambush.
When the bullets start firing and the explosives start going off, an unknown ally will show up.
An ally that may lie inside all of us. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had a fun weekend, we got a lot of stuff to cover today.
So let's go ahead and invite in today's show supporter walking into Dead Rabbit Command,
doing a little march like a little nutcracker soldier.
It's Saint James.
Woo yeah, come on in dude, Saint James is walking around.
You're not going to have to stop walking like a nutcracker.
Saint James, he was one of our live stream contributors for our Christmas episode last year
and he asked specifically, can I be in a military themed episode?
And here we go.
I hope you guys brought your flak jackets and your little helmets.
And I hope you guys are fully armed and ready for war.
We are leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command, we're jumping right in.
Do we have a tank?
We're jumping right inside the...
Whatever, what's jumping inside the chase in Jalopy?
There's no armor on it or whatever, you're like, ah, it's super scary.
Saint James, take us out of Dead Rabbit Command, there's bullets coming from every direction.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command, we're headed all the way out to England.
(imitates gunfire)
I figured for Memorial Day, people always want themed episodes.
I don't know why you ask so much of me.
I don't know why you guys asked me to do a particular content on a given day.
And usually I forget, usually it's like Santa Claus has already given me my gifts
and I was like, oh, I supposed to do a Christmas episode.
But Memorial Day, I remembered ten minutes ago.
So I quickly found some stories that I had floating around in my to-do folder.
These are really good ones, these aren't like leftovers or anything like that.
I really wanted to do these, but we get them to do them.
On Memorial Day, that makes them extra awesome.
And the first veteran we're going to meet is a man who was introduced to me
by one of our regular contributors to Dead Rabbit Radio,
a long time listener of the show, Alexandra Watts.
She recently sent me the saga of a man, no, a hero, known as Russ Kellett.
Nowadays, he's 58 years old and he's living in the town of Philly in North Yorks.
But he wasn't always 58 years old.
Did you know that? Did you know people's age changes every year?
This is the saga of Russ Kellett.
Thirty years ago, he's 28 years old and he's at a bar or a public house.
He said he was at a public house.
I'm assuming that's like a British term for a bar or maybe he was at a house that everyone lived in.
I don't know. Didn't research that. What, didn't sound spooky?
So I didn't bother researching that.
He's at a public house and he's supposed to meet somebody and they stand him up.
They never show up.
So he's sitting there either drinking a drink at a pub or at a pub,
or he's lounging at someone's house and they're like, "This isn't one of the public houses, dude.
This is a private house and they're chasing him off with a broom."
Either way, Russ Kellett is sad.
He's sad this person he was supposed to meet to either do breaking and interings or have a drink with didn't show up.
So he gets on his motorcycle, revs it all, saddling stuff.
He's driving his motorcycle home, tear drop streaming down his face.
He has his motorcycle helmet on so no one can see how sad he is.
And also to protect his brain from serious injury,
when he sees a tunnel up ahead and he's like, "Blimey, mate. I've never seen such a tunnel before.
In fact, there should be no tunnel on this road."
But he goes through it anyways because if you're ever driving home and you find a mysterious portal,
just go through it.
He goes through the tunnel and instead of the other side being more of England,
so he could drive home, he drives into a room he can only describe as like a dentist's office.
So, "Ahhhhh."
He comes to a stop on his motorcycle.
He's like, "Whoa."
And there's like a chair there and there's a bunch of like medical tools and stuff like that.
And he's like, "Oh man, that's not supposed to be through the tunnel."
And then he sees what- I'm gonna put my cards on the table right now if you guys haven't been able to tell.
I think he's making all of this up.
This guy has been in the game for 30 years.
Russ Kellett, if you're listening to this and you're excited to hear your story, you're like,
"Oh, it's gonna be awesome."
I think he's making all of it up.
I think he's totally making all of it up.
And I'll go through why, but here's a good starting point because
probably shut off the podcast if I said this sincerely.
Jason, this guy's clearly making it up and you're falling for it.
He drives his motorcycle into a dentist's office and then sees what he describes as, quote,
"15 foot tall alien men that look very much like Dracula."
And you go, "Jason, maybe aliens are..."
That wouldn't make sense, right?
There's stories of aliens sucking loose shot of people or aliens being some sort of parasitic bean.
Maybe aliens do look like Dracula.
Let me ask you this.
If I told you I walked into a room, forget the 15 foot tall.
If I told you I walked into a room and there was someone who looked like Dracula,
what do you imagine?
Like, what's the first thing you would think of when you would think of Dracula?
Or just a vampire in general, right?
He...let me finish this quote now.
It's in your head.
He drives into this dentist's office and he's surrounded by 15 foot tall alien men
that look very much like Dracula without the sharp teeth.
What?
That's the number one thing I associate with Dracula.
That'd be like saying, "Oh, he's running through the woods and I got abducted by this guy
who looked just like Bigfoot but he wasn't big, he wasn't hairy at normal size feet
and he was wearing an outfit of a park ranger."
But it was Bigfoot!
I don't...did he pull...I'm imagining then was it aliens wearing like really bad Dracula costumes
from like Party City with like the plastic medallion and the red cape.
But even then as I'm describing it, I'm still thinking of their fake teeth.
They don't have sharp teeth.
It's just 15 foot tall guys in there, I guess they're wearing capes with little medallions?
Anyways, so they grab him and they pump a liquid, a thick liquid down his throat
and he's like, "No, no, uh, uh, uh, uh."
And then he's a super soldier.
This is truly a Memorial Day episode.
What would a Memorial Day episode be without a super soldier story?
These 15 foot tall Dracula rejects with no teeth, give him this liquid and he becomes a super soldier
and then they're like, they don't give him any instructions.
Well, as far as he "remembers," he conveniently keeps forgetting stuff.
People are always...this guy's a master of publicity.
Whenever he says something, there's like 10 different articles about this
because when I tried looking more into this guy, I had to put like Google filters
to only search specific time ranges.
If you type in "Ruskelet Aliens," you'll get 10 articles that were just published like two weeks ago.
So I had to like, I had to go and really figure out who this guy was.
I was sure that this guy was really a super soldier.
Imagine my disappointment that this story turned out to most likely be not true.
He says they pumped me full of liquid and the next thing I know, I was in like this hangar area
and there was like these spaceships there and we're like walking onto the spaceship
and I turn around and I'm like, where am I? Where am I?
That's what you do, right? When you're being forced onto a spaceship,
the first thing you want to do is see what's behind you.
There's a spaceship in front of you.
He's walking up the spaceship. He's like, "God's name."
He turns around and standing behind him, or depending on the story,
he's told multiple versions of the story. I guess sometimes he's behind him.
Sometimes he sees this guy from like the next ship over or whatever.
He's looking through a porthole and he sees the other ship play by.
He turns around and he sees Robbie Williams standing there.
Not Robin Williams, which would have been far more entertaining.
Robbie Williams. He is a British.
He's basically like the 90s equivalent of Harry Styles.
He was like in a British boy band called Take That or Take Two or something like that.
And then he became his own dude.
He broke off from the mold. They were all conjoined quintriplets.
He sawed his way away from them one night and became Robbie Williams.
And he had a couple hits in America. I think he's still a real big deal in Britain.
And he goes, "I know you. You're that boy bander guy."
And the aliens are like, "Eyes ahead, eyes ahead."
And he's like, "Okay, I'll look ahead at this massive starship that I've never seen before."
I've seen Robbie Williams before. I've seen him on the telly.
I've never seen his spaceship before, but for some reason I find this dude way more interesting.
And then he spent the next 30 years on and off fighting an intergalactic war versus the dragoes.
These are reptilian creatures.
Now, I know what you're asking. Why would a 15-foot-tall alien race need to get a bunch of 5'8'' people to fight giant lizards?
He doesn't answer that question either.
But he goes and he fights these wars.
Now, these wars aren't just in other star systems, although he does say that.
And if you ask him, "Whoa, where did you fight?"
And he goes, "I don't remember that. He has no details about anything that you'd really want to know."
But he does remember, apparently, he fought in Europe and the UK and South America.
"Boring. I mean, real people do that. Real people fight there. Tell us about the space wars."
He doesn't remember those, though.
He says that time is different when you're in a spaceship, which is probably true, right?
Einstein's theory of relativity.
If you're ever abducted by 15-foot-tall Dracula knockoffs, time will be different.
That was Einstein's theory.
He said that when you're fighting these dragos, when you're in space or whatever,
four hours on Earth is four years up there.
Okay, I'll actually accept that as possible.
We've talked about lost time and how that works and just the way time works in general is weird.
Fine. I'll accept that.
He then, though, uses...
He actually says that he does this.
He's at work. He does have a day job.
I don't know why he would hire this guy. His resume must be hilarious.
He has representatives like 15-foot-tall alien.
Like, can I call him? He's like, "I don't remember the guy's number."
But he exists.
He says that, I guess, a lot of times his boss and coworkers would be like,
"Hey, Russ, why are you so tired all the time? How come you're always just like, uh,
falling asleep on the machinery and stuff like that?"
And he'd be like, "Well, this might sound unbelievable."
Because it is, because I've clearly made this up.
But in space, four years go by, but on Earth only four hours go by,
so that's why I'm tired all the time, because I'm constantly fighting space wars.
Which begs the question that we do.
There's obviously a bunch of questions about this.
Why would you even bother having an Earth job?
How come they're not paying him space money?
Anyways, his whole thing is that's why I'm tired at work all the time,
because I spent the last four years fighting.
It's only been four hours to you, but, well, first off,
this dude would look like he was the oldest man alive.
Secondly, I would say I'm sure, okay, let me assume that I'm an idiot.
I believe your story.
Are you telling me in those four years you never slept, either?
Like, you would get a good night's sleep over the course of four years.
Right? You get to sleep. You get to rest.
It's not like he's awake for four years, I'm assuming.
That's not an excuse I would take as your boss.
I'm just saying rest, if you ever try to get a job with me,
I will not accept that as an excuse, that you were fighting a space war.
He has...he's actually written two books that I could find.
One is a classic, a UFO classic, called "Russell Kellett Is E.T. Rider."
And it's the story I just told you.
They simply just saved you 20 bucks.
He gets on a motorcycle, he drives, he starts fighting a space war.
I was looking through the table of contents, and it did seem like it was a pretty intense book.
I might...I reluctantly put it on my Amazon wish list,
because of these...the story...that story itself is pretty super soldier by the book, nonsense.
But I am curious about these particular chapters.
And I have to be honest, there's a couple of people who might be scratching their head right now
and say, "I think we've heard this guy before."
I have a vague inkling that I've covered this guy before.
We might have mentioned him in passing, because he wrote this book in these chapters.
These chapter titles definitely sound familiar.
One of them is "The Monster in the Cemetery."
That's not alien, right? I'd like to hear about...watch this.
Some stupid alien monster in cemetery.
"The Three Nuns" is the name of a chapter.
That sounds interesting, right?
And then...let me...let me back up.
More interesting than this.
I want to see what happens with the three nuns.
Are they alien nuns? Are they sexy nuns? Are they nun ghosts? Who knows?
Maybe the three nuns are the people who stood them up at the bar.
He's still writing about that in this book, "An Intergalactic Conquest."
He's like, "Why didn't they go? Why didn't they show up?"
And then the ninja.
Like, that does sound evocative, right?
A super soldier fighting a ninja.
Now, it would only be a cool chapter if it was a real super soldier,
which we know Russell...Russell Kellett isn't.
Versus a real ninja.
I'd also be willing, though, to watch someone who thought they were a super soldier,
versus a real ninja. I'm either/or on that.
Real super soldier, versus real ninja, or fake super soldier, versus real ninja.
I'm totally down.
You guys are thinking, Jason, how can you be saying that this stuff's fake?
You're constantly just pulling weird stuff off the internet.
And you're right, right?
Like, I pulled something off the internet and someone said they saw a phantom hand
peeking around the corner and you don't go as hard on that.
That's true. That's true.
And I gotta give Ruskellet...
He does have a little bit of proof.
Because if you read The Daily Star, which I highly suggest you don't,
it's a tabloid, it's entertaining, but nothing is ever true in there.
And considering this is the first place I saw Ruskellet, that should say something,
they do show that Ruskellet has proof.
This is actually a quote from The Daily Star article.
'Cause you want proof, right? I want proof.
Here's a quote from The Daily Star.
'The author' meaning Ruskellet, 'the author has produced drawings to support his claims.'
Unquote.
It just sketches, right?
If that was the way we did things, everyone would...
The first class you would take in school would be art.
And people would just be drawn pictures of themselves as presidents
and they would just be going, like, walking away as well,
giving them, like, 'Sir, sir, you can't come in here.
You hold up a drawing of yourself, a little stick figure in the White House.'
And they're like, 'Sorry, sir, we did not know. We did not know you, the president.'
And there's another reason why I wanted to highlight this guy.
And Alexander, I had a lot of fun reading about this guy.
Thanks for sending this over.
It made me make a connection.
I think we'll touch on this in a future episode as well,
but I'd like to throw my theory out to you.
It's not even a theory, it's a question.
Why is the conspiracy theory community obsessed with celebrities?
It's...we...it's super bizarre.
The conspiracy theory community...
I watched and read more about the masonic meaning behind Will Smith's "Smap of Chris Rock"
than I was of legit conspiracy content over the past, like, month.
Month or two.
Conspiracy theorists love celebrities.
They are obsessed with them.
And I don't know what it is.
I don't know.
There's whole websites like Vigilant Citizen that is based on,
'Look at this photo of the...'
I'm gonna write a thousand words about this photo of someone covering up their eyeball in a photo.
It's weird.
And Russ Kellett is a huge reminder of that.
During COVID lockdowns, he got on the media.
He's really good at getting his name out in the newspaper.
He sent out a bunch of press releases.
I think 'cause he's such a goofball.
And he probably does interviews all the time,
and they're so wacky, like, ten other newspapers pick it up.
He was trying to get celebrities to visit him so they could look at UFOs.
And every time a celebrity, like, in the news would be like,
"Oh, you know, when I was a kid, I saw a light in the sky.
Couldn't explain it."
'Cause, you know, a lot of times celebrities do an interview,
and they answer the same hundred questions all the time in a good interviewer.
We'll toss an oddball question at everyone some while.
You ask Ariana Grande, "Do you believe in ghosts?"
She'll tell you some insane story.
We did an episode on that. I'll put it in the show notes.
So a good interviewer will look for those weird questions, right?
And so every so often, some British actor, actress, or singer, whatever,
be like, "Oh, yeah, I do kind of believe in aliens."
When I was a kid, once this alien walked through my bedroom
and pumped me full of his liquid, and I was a super soldier.
And I was standing in line, and I saw this guy in front of me,
and I swear it was Russ Kellett.
Whenever someone in the media would say, or a famous person,
not one of us normals, right?
A famous person would say they saw an alien, he would contact them.
Well, he would try, let me phrase that, he would try to contact them.
All of his intergalactic powers don't help him to get past bodyguards.
He would try to contact them and invite them.
And during the COVID lockdowns, you know, when everyone was afraid,
because they didn't want to run anyone else, he said,
"Come and hang out with me, this total stranger."
"We can hang out for a couple of nights and make contact."
Not between you and me, but hey, if love, if sparks start flying, sparks start flying.
What I find so just so disingenuous about that, right?
There are other people of your, in your interest group,
and they want to hang out with you, Russ,
but you don't want to hang out with them because they're not famous.
It's so, he specifically was only inviting celebrities to hang out with him.
That type of stuff, it's lame.
I don't get that. I don't understand that.
I don't understand it because there's a lot.
Imagine that if I said only celebrities could listen to this podcast.
It'd be like, what? It'd be insane.
And then imagine if I said, "Oh, you want to do a meetup? You want to meet me in real life?
How famous are you?" Just invite them out.
There's a bunch of people who share your passion, Russ.
You might run into some old veterans of the Super Soldier War.
Conspiracy theorists, and this guy would classify that.
He's more of the paranormal conspiracy theorist,
but they're obsessed with celebrity.
And I don't know if it's because they're obsessed with fame themselves.
I've always had a theory that a lot of hardcore conspiracy theorists are failed artists themselves.
I know when I was really trying to make it as a writer,
when I was writing screenplays and books and stuff like that,
that was the height of me 100% believing in conspiracy theories.
And I remember a long time ago, I was listening to Mark Marin, his WTF podcast,
and he is, I've talked about this several times on the show,
but one more time, he's one of the biggest podcasters, if not the second biggest.
You know, Joe Rogan would be the first.
But his career, he was gotten to drugs and alcohol.
He was a sanded comedian through the 80s.
His career never took off before his podcast.
And I remember on one episode of his podcast, he goes,
"At my lowest point, when my career wasn't going anywhere,
I started to think, is the Illuminati real?
Is this a real group? Like, why aren't I making it?
I have the talent, I have even some of the connections.
How come I can't get my break?"
And I wonder if there's a connection between trying to be an artist
and failing and going, well, it's surely not me.
It must be this group that controls the world.
I wonder if that's part of it.
I wonder if it's an obsession with being famous yourself.
And so you want to latch on to other people.
I find it fascinating.
And conspiracy theory, there was so much about that Will Smith slap.
I was on break when that happened.
That's why you didn't get bombarded with that stuff.
But yeah, obsessed with fame.
And that's where I put Russ Kellogg.
So I love this story.
I was able to talk about my own weird conspiracy theory.
That conspiracy theorist are more obsessed with fame than your aunt,
who buys National Enquirer magazine every single day.
They're more obsessed with that.
We got Super Soldier in here for Memorial Day.
We got a soldier, a real-life soldier.
I love this story.
So Alexandra, thanks for sending it over.
I don't think any of it's true, but it was definitely fascinating
to talk about it.
Nonetheless, it's a perfect mirror for this story that we're going to talk about now.
It's funny because this story also only has one source.
It was posted anonymously online.
So why do I believe this story more than Russ Kellogg's story?
It's funny.
Sometimes I read a lot about Russ Kellogg,
and the more I read, the more unbelievable his story became.
If Russ Kellogg's story was boiled down to maybe 500 words,
and I found it by an anonymous poster,
I probably still wanted to believe it because I don't really believe in the Super Soldier phenomenon,
as is, as it's presented to us,
but it probably would have carried a little more weight.
Right? Maybe.
Maybe.
I don't think I would have full-on believed it.
This next story, though, sometimes less is more.
But St. James...
St. James, I want to be in a military episode, not with that buffoon.
St. James, go ahead and let's call down that carpenter copter.
We're going into a real war zone.
Calling that carpenter copter.
We're leaving behind England.
We're headed all the way out to Afghanistan.
[imitates gunfire]
The year is 2010,
and war in Afghanistan were with a group of soldiers, U.S. soldiers,
currently deployed in the Horn.
That's what they call it.
I looked it up. It's the Horn of Panjwai in Afghanistan.
This is the birthplace of the Taliban.
This was a place of some of the most brutal fighting,
the most brutal continuous fighting from the beginning of the war,
all the way up until July 10th, 2021,
when the Taliban totally took control of the region.
But in 2010, the fight was still on,
and no one knew which way the war was going to go.
And we're here to join a soldier.
This young man didn't give his name.
We're going to name him Peter.
And Peter was six months into his first tour of duty,
and they're on dismounted patrol.
So they're just kind of walking through this area.
They have vehicles like riding X-Tomb.
I think it's a way so it doesn't look...
It doesn't look like a bunch of mechanized vehicles
who are just kind of riding roughshod through villages.
They get out of their vehicles.
They kind of walk around to give a human face to the occupation.
They want to try to win the hearts and minds.
And while they're doing that,
I mean, you match that's super dangerous, right?
As I understand the meaning behind it.
Super dangerous.
You're exposed, and you're walking with your guns, right?
They're not wearing khaki shorts.
They don't have all their body armor off,
but they're walking.
They're fully armed.
But just to give a little bit of a human presence to what's going on.
They're walking alongside their vehicles,
walking through this town,
and then all of a sudden,
right over Peter's head, he sees...
I'm assuming he heard it first.
I don't think he has eagle-eye vision,
but all of a sudden over his head,
an RPG flies past.
Sheeeeeeeeeep!
Go! No!
Something blew up!
Something blew up, Peter says,
and his commanding officer is like,
"Go that way!
Go away from the explosions and stuff!"
So Peter's like running,
and all of a sudden they're just under attack, right?
The Taliban launch this RPG,
they're shooting at him with rifles,
and Peter's like,
"Good, 10-6, 10-6!
I got people shooting at me!"
And he's like talking to them on his radio and stuff.
And all these other guys are doing the same thing.
It's super chaotic.
Everyone's talking to the radio at the same time.
The commander's like,
"Uh, one at a time, guys!"
Peter takes a position,
takes a firing position.
He has a saw.
He has that big machine gun
that you often see in movies,
and/or in your job if you're in the military.
And he gets behind his saw,
machine gun,
and starts going,
(imitates gun shooting)
Not just making the sound effect,
he was shooting bullets out of it,
and the Taliban's like,
"Ah, ah!"
And they're like running and stuff.
But this isn't the end of the battle.
I mean, people are just shooting at each other,
people are running,
everyone's talking at once.
It's total chaos.
And then all of a sudden,
Peter is blinded.
He says that this bright flash of light
washes over him.
And not only is he instantly blinded,
he's deaf as well.
He's laying on his back.
He can't see.
He can't hear.
Now, if that happened to you,
like just walking to the store today,
you'd be pretty alarmed, right?
If you're walking into Walmart,
and the next thing you know,
you're on your back,
and you can't see or hear anything,
you'd be alarmed.
And you would think,
"Oh, no, something must have happened,
like maybe something medical,
or maybe I was blinded
by the great deals at Walmart."
But in a war zone,
Walmart, the worst thing that's going to happen to you
is maybe someone will hit you
with their shopping cart
as you're on the ground.
In a war zone,
you're pretty much toast.
If all of a sudden you're blind and deaf
and on your back,
you're not going to make it.
And that's probably going through
this dude's head as well.
And what had happened was an RPG
exploded right in front of him.
A rocket-propelled grenade.
(sneezes)
Blew him back,
rendered him senseless,
and he's laying there,
and he's bleeding out.
And he said,
"It was so painful.
The sensation of what was going on
was so incredibly painful.
All I wanted to do was to fall asleep.
I figured if I fall asleep,
I won't be in pain anymore."
And all of a sudden,
as his vision is starting to return,
he sees a soldier running up to him.
"Peter! Peter, are you okay?
Come on. Come on.
I got you, buddy."
And he is like checking him.
He's like checking his wounds.
The soldier's like looking at all the wounds.
He's like, "I got you, buddy.
Get up. Come on. Get up."
And Peter gets picked up by this soldier.
And gunfire is still raging from all sides.
And he gets his--
Like you see in the Army movies.
And/or, again, you might do this in real life
if you're in the Army.
You do that Army carrier,
where the guy has his arm over your shoulder
and you're kind of dragging him
or carrying him as much as you can.
And he's like, "We've got to get you to the--
over here.
We've got to get you to this place
where they're not shooting.
I mean, that would be preferable, right?"
There's a medical vehicle.
It's called, like, a MRAP,
a mine-resistant ambush-protected vehicle.
They left the V off of the acronym.
They get under this,
and this is like a place to be safe.
This guy drags him to the ramp
and drops him and then rejoins the firefight.
The next thing that Peter remembers
is he wakes up in a field hospital.
He's like, "Oh, man, what in the world happened?"
He's like all bandaged up and stuff.
And the doctor is--
the doctor was just standing there the whole time.
That's his job to dramatically stand there.
So when you wake up, they can tell you everything that happened.
They go, "Well, Peter, you got shot at,
and then this RPG went off next to you
and you got a bunch of shrapnel in you
and you were bleeding out.
But we took all the shrapnel out."
Well, let me rephrase that.
We took most of the shrapnel out.
You might have trouble going through
metal detectors for a while.
But you're gonna be okay.
It's like, "Oh, yeah, thanks, Doc."
And then the command team comes in
and they're talking to him.
And they go, "Hey, it's so--
we won the battle, by the way.
If the Taliban aren't ready to overrun this hospital,
we won the battle."
But they go, "Yeah, it's really weird.
From what we understand, you were sitting there.
Like, there was a bunch of witnesses to this, right?
That RPG went off in front of you
and you fell on your back
and then you just stood up."
Like, everyone was shocked, right?
They thought you were toast.
You're covered in blood.
And you stood up and you held your arm out.
You just held your arm out in this weird position.
They kind of looked like a zombie
and you staggered back to the M-Rap.
And Peter goes, "No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
And then they said the actual quote, "I got you, buddy."
They're trying to make use of another room
or just kind of get everything kind of cleaned up.
And Peter's going through boxes of old photos.
And he's looking through these pictures
and he sees these old family photos
and he looks at one and he goes,
"That's the guy.
That's the guy who saved my life in Afghanistan."
He's looking at this old photo and he can't figure it out.
That is clearly the man who saved him in Afghanistan
and he talks to his grandpa, Mike, about it
and he goes, "Hey, who is this? Who's this photo of?"
And grandpa, Mike goes, "Oh, that's Donnie.
He was your great uncle."
I'm not answering any of my questions.
He's in this old photograph, but he saved me in Afghanistan.
He saved my life.
And grandpa, Mike, explained, he goes, "Donnie is dead."
Donnie has passed away. He passed away a long time ago.
But he passed away a war hero.
He was awarded the Bronze Star with Valor back in World War II.
So Peter has told the story that his great uncle Donnie
served in the 32nd Infantry Division in Papua New Guinea.
It's 1942 and him and his fellow soldiers are under heavy enemy fire
and one of Donnie's comrades gets shot.
And Donnie, while he's being shot at, grabs this man
and drags him out of harm's way.
Gets him situated where he is safe.
Donnie then stands up, takes a step to walk back towards the battlefield.
And the bullet slams into his chest, killing him.
July 27, 1942, he passed away.
And Peter, sitting there, looking at this picture,
he's heard this story and he couldn't help but truly believe
that his great uncle Donnie had fought in a war
long after he had already died to save a young man he never knew.
So in the last interesting story, we talk a lot about guardian angels on this show.
And this is fascinating to me.
I think this is actually beyond the guardian angel phenomenon.
To me, this is ancestral spirits.
This is like what so many religions and cultures can be based on
this idea that we are all connected. Your bloodline is so important
that it carries through generations, it carries past time.
Absolutely fascinating because we have that idea of it.
We have that idea of ancestral strength, that who you are is who you came from.
We have a guy who died saving someone's life and then in reality,
he saved someone else's life and both times it ends the same way.
He turns around and leaves.
Now the first time he turned around and left permanently, he was killed.
He was killed on the spot, but the second time, Peter never saw where this soldier went.
He did say that the soldier who saved him thought he thought it was weird
because he was wearing an older style helmet.
That was something he did observe when he was being helped by the soldier,
but you're not going to criticize his fashion choices.
Your life is being saved, but I thought that was interesting.
The circumstances was the same.
So was it...we talk a lot about ghosts and them being recordings of them reenacting events.
Was this so much a thing of Donnie being this ancestral guardian of Peter
coming to this time when Peter needed him the most?
Was it also simply a recording?
Because the event was the same.
It was played out the same, but it was spread across what, 60, 70 years?
So it's an interesting ghost story as well.
It's a guardian angel story with the ancestral spirit to it.
This one, the words "I got you buddy"
he could have said that in 1942 to this other young man
and hoisted him up and dragged him back and dropped him off
and then took a step and got shot.
And then in the future it plays out exactly the same.
"I got you buddy" he takes from the vehicle, he turns around and then no one saw him.
No one saw him at all except for Peter.
Fascinating is a ghost story, fascinating as a story of an ancestral lineage.
I also want to say this and we'll wrap it up like this.
I find it so fascinating that as a species maybe, definitely as governments,
we're constantly trying to find the newest weapons of war to fight with.
We're like, okay, planes were cool and all.
Let's make it jets.
There we go, jets are cool and all.
Let's make a drone.
Well, drones are cool and all, but what if drones flew themselves?
What if they didn't have a human controller that could hesitate?
We're always looking for the newest weapon.
Maybe we should go backwards.
Hear me out.
What if instead of now, which people are like,
"I'm just going to shut up for five minutes about some ridiculous thing,"
that you're going to keep adjusting because you realize how dumb it is once you say it.
Hold on, before you hit the button, before you shut it up.
What if we're always trying to make the newest weapons?
What if we use the old techniques?
I'm not saying that we have to start running around with sticks and clubs,
but what if we got our soldiers and said,
"Saint James has already left.
He's like, I don't want to be here for this nonsense."
You get soldiers and you go, "Have any of you had anyone close to you die
in a really, really action-packed way?"
Soldiers are like, "What?"
And the arm is like, because what we're looking for is we're going to put together a secret team
of soldiers who have ancestors who died in battle.
And then, because see that way, let's think about it this way.
Right now, if you put in a bunch of US Army troopers versus a bunch of Russian dudes, right,
we're fighting over Alaska.
It would be us like shooting at each other, but if we have a special group of soldiers
who like maybe you happen to be related with Viking,
and he got his head chopped off when he was trying to beat up a British king.
So in the middle of your battle with the Russians, you like fall down,
and then all of a sudden a goat shows up of a Viking guy,
and he's like heads up and he throws his head at the Russian right before he shoots you.
The other examples anyone else know is anyone else have a relative who's died
in a horrific and/or action packed away? Anyone blow up?
Like that could be his special ability, right?
He like sneaks into the enemy's camp at night, and he's like,
"Uh, he doesn't have a one liner. He just explodes violently."
Everyone's like, "Ugh!" Even if he did have a one liner, we wouldn't know,
because he would just blow everyone up.
Yeah, what if instead of spending money to do science, to build vehicles that we know work,
what if we didn't do that? What if we didn't do that?
What if we just started like practicing like ancestral spirit magic on our soldiers
and have them call forth all of the dead people in their lives?
They're like, "Mom, no, not you! Mom's running in. Mom's running in."
She's throwing poisonous cookies at the enemy troops.
They're like, "Oh, their cookies are so delicious. I can't help but eat them."
You obviously would have to have some requirements, right?
You wouldn't want to have just regular old ghosts,
just like Casper Goats floating through walls.
They're like, "Dude, I'm a ghost. I can float through the wall.
I can tell you what the general's saying there. Like, "Oh, that's too boring."
Do you happen to have a guy who got stabbed to death,
and now he has like swords come out of his hands,
and he's like, "Heads up!"
And he just jumps the heads off people. I don't know.
The point is that I don't see why we don't do that.
We know that might work, right?
People have been calling on their ancestors to help them out through battle for ages.
Drones have only been around for like 50, 60 years.
So that is what I'm-- I will have to do this episode.
I will write a letter to Congress asking for $1 billion to study my theory.
But until then...
DeadRabberRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also put us up at facebook.com/DeadRabberRadio.
Now, TikTok is @DeadRabberRadio.
DeadRabberRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
And I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]