So, I'll Black Panther the other day.
I know I'm a little behind the curve.
I'm not going to give a full review of it, but I do have to say that it's probably the
manliest movie I've seen since 300.
I just wanted to wrestle people after watching Black Panther.
And what we're going to talk about today is meatless chickens, Britain's calorie restrictions,
which is kind of tied into that.
Why people don't see UFOs anymore?
And a few other subjects.
I'm Jason Carpenter and this is the 14th Family.
Okay, so we have two related stories starting off today.
It's pretty interesting.
So, KFC has decided to try to create a...
The headline of the article on CBS Money...
I'm going to provide the links.
CBS's Money Watch website, they have an article called KFC Creating Vegetarian Version of
Its Fried Chicken in the UK.
So, where they're going to start doing is they're going to create some sort of soy-based
or plant-based chicken flavored.
I'm sure it'll still look like a chicken leg.
I wonder if it'll have a bone in it.
Because it's kind of...
I don't like bone chicken, but I guess that's kind of the part of the chicken, fried chicken.
I guess...
I don't know, maybe the bone will be edible.
But anyways, so it's interesting because I'm reading this article and the article starts
off like this is some sort of revolutionary thing on behalf of KFC.
But it actually turns out that a lot of restaurants, a lot of American restaurants are making soy-based
versions of their products for Europe because they're starting to have a crackdown on how
many calories...
They're having recommendations on how many calories you should eat per meal.
And we'll get into that in a second.
So anyways, KFC...
So, KFC is making their soy chicken, their vegetable-based chicken.
And then McDonald's currently has a soybean-based McVegan burger.
That's probably okay.
And then Pizza Hut is selling vegan pies.
Which I think the terminology is a little weird because when I think of the term pie,
I'm thinking of an actual pie.
But I guess they mean like pizza pie.
I'm looking at a picture of it here.
It looks completely unappetizing.
I don't...
Isn't most...
Isn't any pizza kind of vegetarian unless you put meat on it?
Like couldn't you just order vegetable pizza?
Like why does it have to be special?
It's a vegan.
100% vegan.
Our gluten-free flatbread crust.
None of that sounds...
Oh, interesting.
Bacon bits, 100% vegan.
Okay, I'm on the Pizza Hut website.
I have enough horror stories about Pizza Hut to fill its own podcast.
Pizza Hut is the grossest pizza parlor.
And I've eaten it a lot of them.
I've eaten it like the Little Mom and Pop shops.
And I had a Pizza Hut in my neighborhood that was just discussing you at order.
I had always ordered Marinette.
Well, I didn't always because I learned my lesson, but I would order marinara sauce for
my pizza and they would basically give me like red soup.
It was basically like all water with like a single chunk of tomato floating.
Floating in it.
And the pizza was disgusting.
I think once I ordered pasta and they gave me like two pounds, it was just like in this
huge like cafeteria style tray.
The whole thing was completely unappetizing.
And it's I hate that I'm bad mouthing all the Pizza Hut because of the local Pizza Hut
in Sacramento, California, but it was absolutely disgusting.
I have nothing but bad memories of it.
So having a vegan pizza coupled on top of that disgusting marinara sauce I had just isn't
doing it for me.
A lot of this is coming out because apparently the UK is trying to and I think I lost my...
Where did it go?
Okay, so while I'm looking for that link about the UK thing, I'll talk a little bit more
about Black Panther.
I know a lot of people have seen it already and it, you know, I always heard really good
reviews about it.
And you know, generally when movies get good reviews, I think people have kind of picked
up on this by now when talking to me is that I'm always very, very cautious when people
are like, oh yeah, you know, this movie is the best because normally it isn't like very
rarely have I seen a movie that people unanimously said was good and it was...
Okay, let me say this.
It's good, but the hype's not there.
Let's see British Calorie Restrictions.
But no, this one actually stood out and yeah, it was super manly.
Like I was surprised.
It was just all about like dudes fighting each other and like wrestling for control, like
politically and physically.
It was like, I just wanted to go out and like wrestle people after watching it.
And I still want to wrestle people and it's been a couple of days since I've seen it just
really kind of amped you up.
So I think I'm going to end up watching it again.
Here is an article.
Okay.
Okay, so I found it.
So what it is is there is a British plan that's called the 400, 600, 600 and it's basically,
it's a recommendation.
It's a recommendation.
They're telling people that this is what the government recommends you do, but this
is it.
You need 400 calories for, for, for breath fix and you need 600 calories for lunch and
600 calories for dinner.
That's 1600 calories altogether.
I know I double checked my math several times.
As interesting, I, I mean, I'm on a diet and I eat, I'm 285 pounds now and I eat probably
about 1800 calories on my diet.
I'm supposed to like to maintain that weight.
I have to eat like 2500 calories.
So that's a good 700 calorie deficit.
1600 calories is a huge deficit for a lot of people.
The average deficit, the average amount of calories that a man should have is 2000.
I think it's kind of similar for women.
So they're, they want everyone to eat basically under their deficit.
The reason why is two.
I mean, you could say, well, there's only one reason.
Well, there's multiple reasons, but we have it.
The world has issues with obesity.
They're trying to curb that as far as early deaths and medical costs, big part of its medical
costs.
The government probably wouldn't care if it wasn't costing so much money to treat people
who are obese.
Of course, people are going to say that it's part of like, you know, like government control,
government encroaching on your life.
And that is part of it.
I'm not going to just, I'm not going to say that's not true.
I think that stuff like this, this calorie recommendation comes into stuff like soda
taxes and candy taxes and things like that.
The government is trying to get you to curb your behavior.
They're not necessarily doing it to control you, but that is the end result.
They do end up controlling a portion of your life that you would think would be up to you.
The reason again, why they want to control it is because health costs are skyrocketing
and they want to bring those down.
Now, conspiracy theorists would say that this is just a way for the government to, if the
government, if you get used to the government controlling the little things in your life,
you're more likely to let it handle the big things in your life without question.
But we'll see how this goes.
So this is why they're introducing that meatless chicken.
It seems weird.
I don't have a problem with the meatless chicken.
I don't even have a problem with the calorie restrictions.
My concern always is that it's going to become mandatory.
Not mandatory.
Well, maybe.
I mean, I don't, I mean, they're going to be guards coming into your house and like,
like punching you or like throwing over your food stores if you have too much money.
Maybe I mean too much food.
Maybe it'll come to a thing like if you see a fat person walking down the street, the government's
like, "Oi, what do you, what do you do when mate?
Those are two different countries, but you're fat.
Like you cannot be that fat if you were following our recommended guidelines.
Maybe, maybe 1984 is not about the year with the amount of calories that, what was that
guy's name?
Willis Wallace Watson?
Anyways, yes.
Maybe we have finally cracked that, that ingenious code because 1984 came and when and nothing
happened.
So it's about the calories.
Next story we're going to talk about is UFOs are getting harder to spot a researcher claim
or research claims.
This is on Fox News.
Now, I know a lot of people poo poo Fox News, but it's, they have a great weird news section.
That's where I found, I found a lot of these weird articles.
So anyways, the headline, the article starts off with the best way to start off a UFO article,
but just by like being a dick.
First line of the article is, "Perhaps it should be close encounters of the blurred kind."
That's pretty funny.
I'm sure this reporter stayed up quite late to get this.
A new research suggests that UFO sightings in the US, which tend to move in six or seven
year fluctuating cycles, are in a permanent downtrend and researchers are puzzled.
So it's interesting.
So apparently in the past, like we'll have peaks and valleys of UFO sightings and the
article goes on to say that one of the big peaks was 2012 and we'll get into that in
a second.
But I think it's interesting if, if you, if there is a natural phenomenon, if there's
a phenomenon actually happening, it shouldn't peak or valley in that sense.
I mean, I guess like volcanoes come and go, but mountains don't disappear.
Like if there's, if you can actually say, yeah, every six years people see more UFOs
than they do and like there's like a six year high and then nobody sees a lot of UFOs for
a while and there's another six year high.
That seems to me more like a social factor.
I think that would make me lean more towards UFO sightings are more of a social thing than
a, than a scientific thing.
If we can see these peaks and valleys like that, I don't know, maybe I'm wrong.
But it's interesting because right now, yearly UFO sightings are there's 7,837 on average,
which is a drop of 41% from the three year peak average years.
So from where it was at where it peaked, it's 41, it's a big job, 41%.
The article goes on to say between 2012 and 2014, the US had a peak average of 13,500
yearly UFO sightings.
And then however, in 2015 sightings fell 11% to 11,975 and 2016 saw an even more dramatic
drop falling 21% to 10,602.
Then the next line is where stuff.
So you here we go with that.
So those are just raw numbers that research has come up with.
And so generally when you have these scientific scientific, when you have these scientific
studies going, you have the raw numbers and then you start postulating, you shouldn't,
but they do.
And that's when things start to go sideways.
Okay, I'll take those numbers more people, less people are seeing UFOs than before.
Okay, fine.
I'll take those raw numbers.
You have them.
I'm not going to question those next line cost to the researcher, Costa.
Costa has not yet found a solid reason for the significant drop in sightings, but speculated
that it had to do with broadband internet access.
Here's a quote.
We see relatively flat sighting reports from 2001 to 2006, Costa wrote.
This flatness is considered an artifice of reporting as broadband internet access was
still growing in most areas.
Access to broadband is a major driver in people having routine use of web reporting services
such as new fork and move on.
Okay.
If they're kind to see where they're going at, they can say we didn't get a lot of sightings
between 2001 and 2006, fair enough.
But now everybody has it, not everybody, but you know what I mean, most people have it.
And this is my main problem with the UFO sightings in general.
I was always big into UFOs growing up.
I think everyone when they're a kid falls in love with something paranormal because
the world just still seems incredibly magical and open to them and things like that.
So I was big into UFOs and I was a kid and I read the book.
I was big into everything, ghosts and UFOs and demonology and spontaneous human combustion
and all that stuff.
But anyways, I'd read these books and you have these pictures of these UFOs and I remember
a read, one book I was reading said to carry a camera with you at all times in case you
see a UFO.
And so if you see a UFO, we can take a picture.
And if only people carried cameras, we'd have more UFOs.
And I thought about that at the time.
I was probably like 12 or 13 cameras are still relatively expensive.
We didn't have digital cameras back then.
But I thought what a great idea.
Yeah, I should totally like carry a camera around with me all the time now that that
would just make me get beat up all the time by bullies.
So I didn't.
I couldn't afford a camera anyways, but now everyone has a camera.
Everyone has a camera.
We used to get you could look back and we'd get maybe 10 to 15 good UFO photos.
A year.
And you just had people with like actual camera cameras like film plate cameras, Kodak cameras.
Now everyone has a camera.
We get like 10 to 15 good photos a year of UFOs.
That's what doesn't make sense to these 7000 sightings.
We should have 10 let's say let's 10% 10% people take pictures.
We should have 700 photos a year minimum coming back of these things.
Now I understand that when I look up at the sky and I see something that I can't identify
that as a UFO and I understand that that is what is in this report.
The 7000 sightings are both large visible aircraft with windows and you see little aliens walking
around through the windows.
That's part of the 7000 and me looking up and going whoa, something just flew by like
a dart in the sky like a little light bulb that I was also in that sighting.
And so when part of the problems with the UFOs is that it's such a vague term.
Part of the problems with UFOs is that the numbers that they're throwing at us for the
amount of sightings we're not getting anywhere near that amount of photos or video or anything.
Where are the photos?
I'm not a total skeptic on this thing.
I can be convinced and I'm not saying that I just need photos to convince me.
It's going to go a long way.
You can tell me that this is going on and you can tell me oh no no no there's more UFOs.
We just don't have enough broadband internet to report them.
There's more UFOs but people just aren't looking up as much which is actually what they say
earlier in the article they say the spike that was seen in 2012 can be attributed to
the mine calendar media Bollyhoo causing more people to look up, Costa said.
So in 2012 more people were looking in the sky and that's why.
No more people were thinking about UFOs in the end of the world and all of this metaphysical
stuff so people were seeing more stuff, more things like that.
That's a more obvious answer.
If you're going to be on the fringe of science, you do have to start to be honest at a certain
point and go maybe most ghost stories are made up.
Maybe some of them are true, maybe a minority are true but we have to assume you just can't
accept everything.
And so these 12,000 when someone's interviewing this person and go why did we see more UFOs
in 2012?
I can just imagine the reporter going uhhhh people looked up more.
Because that's their grasp in its troughs.
That's really the only thing they could pull up.
I think it would be awesome if UFOs were flying around and we had footage of them and like
you know I could wrestle them, I could show them clips of a black panther and then communicate
via wrestling.
That would be awesome.
But you know, you know, we need a little more, we need a little more.
And you need to start, you have to be enthusiastic, you guys need to start putting your best feet
forward because, yeah come on.
You know, come on.
The reason why people, there's less UFO sightings is because broadband internet access, that
just doesn't wash.
You could see, I would have accepted a made up answer like there's less sightings because
the solar system's heating up and we've seen in the past that UFOs don't like being around
heat.
Okay I'll take that.
Or the global temperature is going up and UFOs are trying to send us a message by not
visiting us.
I'll accept that.
You're going to postulate something, postulate something.
If you're going to postulate something about something fantastical, postulate a fantastical
explanation.
Don't then say it's because we don't have broadband internet.
It's just bizarre to me.
Just bizarre.
But speaking of aliens, Elon Musk, everyone's favorite, well except for reporters.
Reporters don't like the guy anymore, but Elon Musk, everyone's favorite tech genius.
He's like a James Bond bad guy but good.
Or at least like maybe this is his origin story.
He tweeted the other day, "There are no aliens officially at least."
And of course all the conspiracy sites and the fringe sign sites go crazy.
It'll be interesting to see.
I think a lot of times.
I think everyone wants something to be out there.
And I think when somebody who's obviously very rich and very powerful and has access
to halls of government and access to science and research that the common man doesn't when
they post something like this, it may be tongue in cheek, but it definitely gets everyone
excited because we want there to be aliens.
I think that that would be exciting to know that there are other things out there in their
visiting us and stuff like that.
So we have articles where we're talking about UFO sightings, but then we always get thrown
this little bone and people go, "Oh yeah, maybe it's it."
It would be awesome.
I'm not going to lie.
If there were aliens though, I don't know if Elon Musk would know about it even despite
his tons and tons of money and the fact that he probably hangs out with scientists and
stuff like that.
And you know again, the question always becomes, what do we care about?
Do we care about aliens or do we care about aliens visiting us?
Because to me it's two totally different issues.
If someone goes, "Yeah, there's aliens.
We have proof of alien life."
And I'm like, "Really?"
And they're like, "Yeah, it's a thousand light years away and we can just tell from gas from
a radio spectrometer."
I'm like, "Ah."
And if they say, "Dude, we have proof of aliens."
And I'm like, "Really?"
And they're like, "Look out your window."
That's what we want.
I want to look out my window and see like a mothership or like any type of ship.
And be like, "Whoa, look at there's an alien."
And hopefully they don't like kill us before we kill them because we will have to shoot
them out of the sky.
That's obvious, but that's what we want.
So yes, there probably are aliens and Elon Musk technically is right there.
Wait, no, no, no.
Elon, yeah.
Elon Musk said there are no aliens officially at least.
Like, yeah, we just want aliens.
And so when people give us the smallest bit of hope that there are aliens out there, I
don't know.
It would be awesome.
I'm not going to like poo poo on the whole...
I'm going to poo poo on the whole UFO thing because I think it's kind of lame overall,
but I'm not going to poo poo on the existence of aliens altogether because I think it'd
be awesome.
I think it'd be awesome.
So that's all the stories we're going to do today.
There's a lot of bad news today.
There's a lot of like crummy like dark stuff.
I'm still trying to figure out how to work that into this podcast.
So I'm not going to touch it right now.
We're going to figure it out because again, I want it to be relatively lighthearted, but
when you're dealing with conspiracy stuff and like dark, dark topics, they're going to
come up.
So we'll figure that out.
I still haven't come up with a catchphrase to say goodbye, but I did figure out how to
fade my music in and out.
So that is going to be beneficial.
So we're going to go ahead and close out from here.
I am Jason Carpenter and thanks for joining the 14 family.
[MUSIC]