If someone threw a brick at your pet donkey, would you help?
Not throw the bricks, would you help your donkeys, what I'm saying?
But what if by helping the donkey, you became a donkey yourself?
And then we meet a man reaching out for help online, a man who's inches away from becoming
a maniac.
And then finally we take a look at a bizarre new conspiracy.
Is it possible that video games should be far more advanced than they already are?
But the powers that be are preventing them.
Because if video games reach their true potential, it could destroy the world.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
You guys heard the intro, we got a bunch of stuff to cover.
So we're gonna get started right away.
First off, let's go ahead and give a shout out to our newest Patreon supporter, walking
into Dead Rabbit Command right now.
Everyone give a big round of applause for Peter Newhart.
Yay!
Woohoo!
He's walking on and he's actually riding a donkey in because he heard the intro.
He had it planned, he brought his own donkey from home.
BYOD.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, or if you guys don't have a donkey, that's fine
too.
Just help spread the word about the show, that really, really helps out a lot.
Let your friends and family know that this is where you go to hear absolutely bizarre
and unsettling news.
Peter, go ahead and hop off that donkey.
I'm gonna toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit Durgible.
We're gonna live the donkey, he can come with us, I don't think he's gonna want to.
For this first story though, take the Dead Rabbit Durgible out of Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed all the way out to San Antonio, Texas.
Peter as you're flying the Dead Rabbit Durgible, go ahead and hit that time travel button.
Everything gets sepia toned and now we're in old cowboy clothes, it got the boots on
and the big old cowboy hats.
This is like the 1800s, it's a pretty, pretty big time period, it's somewhere between
1801 and 1899, but in this time period in San Antonio, Texas, there was a little family
living by this bog.
So you have a mom and a dad, a boy and a girl, and there's this bridge over this creek.
Nowadays we have a name for it, but back then it was just called that bridge, it was that
bridge to the left of you when you left the house.
This family was doing totally fine being a family, but one day this wealthy guy shows
up outside their house and he's like, "Hey, what's up bog people, bog people in your unnamed
bridge?"
They're like, "It'll be named someday, just trust me."
He's like, "Whatever, you guys are too poor to even afford a name on your bridge."
And this rich guy would always come, he'd go out of his way, it's like outside of town,
he's all bored sitting at home in his mansion.
He's like, "I'm bored, I'll go make fun of the bog people."
So he goes over there and he's harassing this family all the time.
And then one day he's walking by and the family's donkey bites him.
He's like, "Ah, dude, that totally sucks.
I'm going to show you what's what, donkey."
And he starts beating the donkey up.
Now here's the thing, right?
I know people were probably sturdier, heartier people in the 1800s.
There is no scenario that I can ever think of that would involve me turning to a donkey
and go, "Why you wise guy?"
And punching him.
He starts beating up this animal.
I just imagine Popeye just going at this donkey's lips, right?
Well the family sees this, the family sees this very wealthy man who's been bullying the
family beating up their donkey.
So they run outside and they start throwing bricks and rocks at the rich dude and he's
like, "Ah."
And the rich guy is running away.
He goes, "I'll be back.
I'll be back to get my revenge."
And he runs off and people are like, "What do you mean revenge?"
You're the one beating up this innocent donkey.
Like it should just be over, right?
Animal nips at you.
You punch the animal.
That's it.
Don't tell the ASPCA I just said that.
But you know what I mean?
Slap it, knock it, punch it, bop it.
You're doing a little rhythm game with it and it's done.
Dude, the rich guy, he goes back home and he gets a posse.
He goes, "We got to show these bog people what's what."
So Jimmy Joe, you get to get these beating up their horses.
He's like, "I'm strengthening him.
I'm getting a lot ready for the fight."
They're like, "Stop it, dude."
Jimmy Joe, Tony, Michael, we're all going to ride out to the Bogman's house and we're
going to lay siege because they wouldn't let me beat their donkey to death.
And they're like, "Whatever, boss.
It's just another Tuesday for this gang."
So they ride out to the bog people's house and little mom and dad are sleeping in the
bog house, little boy, little girl sleeping in the bog house that they had the donkey
keep watch.
He's on the roof, little pair of binoculars.
While the house is peaceful and everyone's sleeping, this rich dude and his buddies burn
it to the ground.
Quite the escalation, really.
I got to say quite the escalation.
They burn it to the ground and what happens is as the family is burning to death, the
donkey runs away.
He's like, "Oh, I fell asleep during the watch."
The father dies, the two kids die, but the mother runs out of the house on fire.
The other three, I guess, just out of a smoke inhalation or something like that.
She runs out of the house on fire and the rich dude and his gang see this woman run out and
as she's on fire, her hands begin to melt, like her fingers melt off and all that's left
is her like nubby nubs and her palm.
And the guys are like, "Ew, that's super gross.
Obviously, this woman's dying and running you."
But they go, "Dude, it looks like her hands have melted into donkey hooves and then the
fire is melting her face and her skin is going bleh and it's getting all sluffy.
It's like pouring oatmeal on a wall."
It's just kind of coming off and they're like, "Oh, her hands look like donkey hooves, but
look how her skin is melting off of her face.
It looks like she's a donkey now."
And I don't know what these guys were thinking.
I don't know if they've never seen a donkey before, but as this woman runs out of the
house and she's burning to death and she's melting, her skin sags like a donkey's head
and her hands melt into the shape of donkey hooves and they run away.
So they run away.
They don't help her.
Today, this bridge now has a name.
It's called Donkey Lady Bridge.
And it's, you know where Elm Creek, you know where Elm Creek is?
Someone's living in this house right now.
They're like, "Oh, this story happened here.
In San Antonio, Texas, there's a creek called Elm Creek.
There's a bridge out there and it's called Donkey Lady Bridge.
And this is supposedly haunted by the donkey lady.
This is one of those interesting stories where, one, you have the story in and of itself,
and two, very rarely, it does happen, but it's rare, where somebody who is completely innocent
is cursed.
So we'll have stories where people get brutally murdered and their ghost continues to act
out that thing.
And that's one thing.
What I'm talking about, when we look at other bridges like Cry Baby Bridge, it's haunted
by the guy who slaughtered his family then hung himself on the bridge.
That's such a popular legend.
We've actually covered it, but that legend is all over the world.
We have Cry Baby Bridges.
You have stories like that.
You have stories about the billow-wack monster, the research scientist who was working on
something and he's trying to make a human ram hybrid and like a horn of ram blew up
in his face and he became that.
These stories usually involve these people who haunt these legends, the circus freak
that broke out of the train crash.
I'll put all these episodes in the show notes, but generally it's a monster who's haunting
this area, usually a bridge, that it was a monster or a human doing monstrous things.
This one we have a, the only reason why she continues to haunt the area to this day is
the fact that she got burned alive.
She was not the bad guy at any point in the story.
I guess if you're the rich kid you're like, "And kids!"
Then guess what?
All I did was punch their donkey a few times in the brain and someone threw a brick at
me.
So she was cursed forever, but very rarely do innocent people become the monster that
wanders the woods.
Ghosts?
Yes.
Murder victims?
La Lorna?
Whatever her name is, Laoyna?
I can't pronounce her right, but the wailing woman of the Mexican legend, she murdered
her kids to get with a dude.
And that's why she's cursed.
She didn't live a happy life and worked three jobs to send her kids to college and then
lived to the age of 88 surrounded by her loved ones.
And now she's cursed to wander the world screaming.
Generally the people in this position are evil in life.
And it's a moral story.
This is really creepy because this woman's only sin was loving her family so much to
sleep in the same house with them when it was set on fire and defending her donkey.
Really really.
That story adds a different creepiness to it.
The moral of it is no matter how good you are in life you could still become one of these
monstrosities.
To this day people go out to this bridge and if you yell out "donkey lady" three times
supposedly she jumps up onto the bridge and stuff like that.
I mean this is one of those stories that would be easy to test.
You can go do it for yourself and if you don't see her then it's the legend accurate.
But still really cool.
It'd be fun ghost hunt if anyone's in that area to go do.
If you want to see a woman who looks like a donkey.
And I'm wondering too how this story was crafted.
Was there someone with severe facial scarring burns in the area and the legend just grew
from there.
We've covered stories like that.
Put those in the show notes where there was someone with a disfigured face and then the
story of the bandage man came out of that but it was based on a real non-supernatural
person.
So who knows.
Was there someone really burnt to death in this area?
Was there someone who was disfigured in this area?
Who knows.
But a creepy story nonetheless no matter what you do no matter how good you are on earth
even if you are saving animals you may still be cursed to walk it forever scaring teenagers
when they yell out your name.
Peter let's go ahead and break out the keys for a new vehicle I just invented.
Since we're in a swamp of bog I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the hair
hydrofoil.
We're leaving behind this bog in San Antonio.
We're headed all the way out to some dude's bedroom.
[Horror sound]
Well so we'll see if that vehicle ever comes out.
People are looking up what's a hydrofoil.
The only reason I know what it is because there was a GI Joe toy made out of it.
Maybe it'll be the hair hovercraft next time.
I don't know.
Peter thanks for driving us to this dude's bedroom.
This is a post online so we don't really have a name or location for this.
This guy definitely doesn't want to give that information out.
But it was interesting I was on the internet the other day and all the links are in the
show notes so I was on the internet I was on a fitness website.
Fitness board the other day right?
And there was this guy and he had some questions about personal health and he has a concern
he thinks he's watching too much pornography so we're sitting in his next bedroom he's
questioning whether or not he's a porn addict and we're just kind of sitting back on his
bed I'm sitting in recliner you're sitting on his bed you're like oh man he's sitting
there and he goes listen I'm 30 years old and I just have some questions that are going
on I masturbate five times a day and I've been doing that since the age of 10 and he's
talking about that he's wondering if that is healthy he's wondering if that is healthy
but he's wondering if that's healthy because a lot of times people don't talk about this
stuff with their peers or with their mentors and things like that their coach or their
minister or anything like that who an adult who can answer that question and go oh yeah
no that's totally normal.
So he's asking this question online he goes is that normal right I masturbate five times
a day and I've done so since the age of 10 and then he goes quote I use large amounts
of high quality curated hardcore pornography and he's wondering should I keep doing that
should I keep doing this he goes I've thought about going cold turkey on it but just giving
up the porn altogether but I don't have a girlfriend right now and he asked the question
am I at risk of becoming a rapist if I try to stop as in you know stop watching the
porn and he asked the question will my penis shrivel up and will I develop erectile dysfunction
without the porn it was really interesting because a lot of people responded to this
right away and they're like first off a lot of it was yeah dude that's pretty normal like
don't worry about too much masturbation you're the one sitting on his bed you're like a Jason
please can I get up I'm like uh-uh you're stuck people are kind of answering his questions
say no it's totally normal as long as you're not like hurting your body as far as the masturbation
goes don't worry about that but people did have a concern they were kind of making fun
of this collection of highly curated pornography and he they're kind of the people who are
responding to this are kind of concerned with this thing am I at risk of becoming a rapist
if I try to stop if I stop watching this porn am I going to become a rapist and this is
where it becomes really telling again this guy's approaching with a very honest personal
question about his health and because he doesn't really probably have anyone else to talk to
about this thing and the original poster will call him Tony I don't know if that's his real
name but he goes I want to say when I talk about highly curated hardcore pornography
I want to be really specific I prefer pornography where the women look like they're not enjoying
it people are like wait what wait so basically you you are afraid you might become a rapist
and you're watching porn where women you prefer porn where it looks like women are not enjoying
it which is a roundabout way of saying you're watching porn of women who are getting raped
he goes on to say listen I tried giving up porn before but what happened was when I went cold
turkey like he had mentioned before he said his penis began to shrink and almost disappeared
completely it's super interesting because again this was on a fitness board we're talking about
personal health and we're talking about these real issues and now we're starting to see that this
person Tony has that's important your penis doesn't shrink if you stop masturbating if you
stop watching porn I mean it'll get bigger if you do those two things temporarily but it doesn't
shrink permanently so at this point you feel like you're kind of talking to someone who one
who watches a lot of pornography two prefers pornography where the women aren't enjoying it
he's afraid he might rape women if he stops watching pornography and now he has the delusion
that if he stops watching pornography his penis will disappear it's gone from a interesting
and very normal question that people are shy to asking to I'm concerned about this person's well-being
he then straight up says because people start saying you know because you're responding to other
stuff where people are saying porn doesn't stop rape that's an old myth he goes no it does actually
because for him he said quote porn does help stop rape as it's much easier to jack off to rape porn
than to go out and do it and really we get to the end of it when he's been talking about this like
remember this started should I stop watching pornography will it be okay fellow health nuts
out there what happens now he's saying that it's just easier for me to watch rape porn than it
is for me to rape women and the last post he left on this page was quote if a woman says no
you know this is gonna you know this is just gonna be downhill from here so he goes on to say
this quote if a woman says no then I can just masturbate to porn but if she says no and I'm
not masturbating currently there's a real problem unquote I always think it's interesting we cover
true crime on the show and obviously we encounter true crime all the time whether or not it's on a
podcast or in the news or hopefully not in your own life but I always find it interesting when we
can encounter true crime before it happens right this is a man who in short order right in short
order goes from having a health issue and saying I don't know if I masturbate too much I don't know
if I'm too over sexualized to I need to watch rape porn and I need to masturbate frequently because
if I don't and I'm with a woman and she says no I'm going to rape her terrifying terrifying like
this is the true crime story before the headline this is the true crime story before your loved one
comes to you and goes you gotta help me something horrible happened to me last night very very
creepy creepy encounter with somebody online and and yeah that's out there like obviously
we hope this guy gets help I don't think the help is for him to continue to watching highly curated
collections of pornography he obviously needs some therapy and the fact that he's imagining his
penis shrinking and almost disappearing that is again that's not that's not how it works
we've covered a lot of stories about people's penis is shrinking it's a mental epidemic over
in Africa we've covered a ton of stories on that and um but it is a delusion but he's in the
throes of this delusion he's addicted to hardcore rape pornography and he's trying to stop it and
he's going if I stop it for too long I'm gonna rape somebody creepy very very terrifying story
and hopefully that is the end of it right Peter let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the
carpenter copter we're gonna leave behind this young man's bedroom and we are headed all the
way out to sony headquarters in japan talk about a shift change talk about a mood change
this is a conspiracy theory that I actually came up with a long time ago um I'm a I don't really
talk about it much on the show I'm sure long time listeners have picked up on it people in my personal
life I'm a huge video game guy I used to work and then come home and play video games until
I had to go to bed it's I love video games I just don't have time to play them anymore and there's
another reason why I don't play video games as much either they're not good anymore they're not good
anymore but I'll explain why I'm not saying that as a boomer the video game industry is stagnant
and I'm not talking about stagnant from a business perspective I'm gonna let me go ahead and get
get started with this I believe that this is my thesis video games should be way more advanced
than they are something or someone is holding them back on purpose this is what I mean
Nintendo comes out right regular old Nintendo comes out I started off I had the Atari 2600
back like an 87 and I had to sell that and to save a bunch of money to buy the Nintendo but
it was worth it the difference between the games between the Atari 2600 and the games for the Nintendo
groundbreaking one they they were in color right you could actually see what was going on it just
wasn't a little pixel ET guy I had that game it wasn't that bad I had ET for the 2600 I had the
Spider-Man game for Colecovision had all this stuff right many have Mario Brothers and you have
the Legend of Zelda you have this big map this world where there's puzzles and you can get lost
and then you move to the Super Nintendo I remember when the Super Nintendo came out we got it like
within the first couple months of it coming out and I remember staying up all night and playing
pilot wings pilot wings was a brand new game with mode seven so for the first time you had
simulated 3d things would get start off smaller and get bigger as you were coming towards them
you had games like pilot wings you had games like star fox you had games that you could not
have done on the Nintendo it wouldn't have worked and this continues on when you have the N64 you
have golden eye which a golden eye a shooter like that was something you would have never seen on a
console before right you had it on the pc you had it like doom but golden eye opened that up to a
brand new market now you could have a relatively cheap system not having this huge home computer
you could play a game like golden eye you had multiplayer you had first person shooter you
had these realistic 3d environments then you moved to the ps2 and I know I'm jumping a bunch of systems
there's Dreamcast and things like that but you guys will see why I'm doing this you had the ps2
and I believe that the ps2 was the end of video game advancements it was this was the top of the
line video game system because the ps2 was the last time you had video games you could not have
had on any other system you had games like grand theft auto 3 an open world game you could argue
zelda was open world it was technically go wherever but when you first played grand theft auto 3
if you were of age nowadays it's a super old game but I remember I remember the very first time I
played grand theft auto 3 and I realized I could do whatever I wanted I killed a cop and I ran around
and I went into the warehouse district and I climbed the ladder and I sat on a rooftop and watched the
sunset as the stars faded away not the stars in the sky the wanted stars it was a video game experience
that I had never had before I was at my friend josh mohrmeyer's house I was playing it you started
having super artistic games like shadow of the colossus fatal frame resident evil 4 this was
this generation of games where you're like this game's amazing this game's amazing on so many
different levels you could have a game like red faction where it's destructible environments and
open world that was the red faction sequel I think it was but you had all of this stuff and this is
my argument from the ps2 to now any game made on the ps5 other than graphical updates you could
have had on the ps2 there has not been a major advancement in the gaming industry since the
ps2 why I'm talking strictly about gameplay in fact graphics in a lot of ways are getting worse
or they like to call it retro but grand theft I when I was playing grand theft auto 5 it was
grand theft auto 3 just the graphics are better now there is better voice acting and the the
it's the same game though the graphics are different so here's my problem why haven't
games advanced in gameplay the only real advancement we've made since the ps2 era is battle royale
games and all those are is grand theft auto 3 with multiple players it is an open world game
battle royale games are from open world games that are spin offs they're from day z they're from h1z
one they're from minecraft so even that entire genre really could have been replicated on the
ps2 the games themselves stopped advancing multiplayer component sure it has this little
widget or that little widget sure dlc sure but the games themselves the actual mechanics is what
i'm talking about have not advanced since the ps2 why I was sitting in the chair I was prepping
this story earlier today and I thought well Jason let's play devil's advocate maybe it's because
there's no other way to go as I'm sitting in my chair I came up with two ideas one you have a video
game that is tied into your real life so as you're playing the video game let's say it's a fatal frame
type game you're investigating this mystery your phone rings in real life you're getting emails
while you're playing the game from somebody going like don't go in there don't go in there
and you're having to do it like you're solving a real life mystery and it's accessing your email
in your phones and you're going to say I want to play a game with that it doesn't matter whether
you want to play it I'm saying that would be a brand new genre of game imagine this imagine this
you have a world building game that is updated automatically based on the news in the world
you're playing a game and then all of a sudden the coronavirus comes so the game you have games
that leech into the real life that would be groundbreaking why isn't anyone doing this
that would be groundbreaking stuff the biggest game that's coming out right now is the guy
player unknowns who came up with player knowns battleground he's now building the biggest map
ever with trees that when you chop down they don't grow back you have to plan a city grown back
that's ambitious right they talked about doing that with the fable game back on the xbox though
why aren't games getting better is far they're just getting graphical updates I feel like I'm
just ranting so I'm going to wrap this up real quick but that's my question the actual games we
play could have been done back then you could not have what the ps2 you cannot have done a game that
accesses all the technology in your home in the real world back then you cannot play a game that
is constantly updating itself because it's connected to the largest repository of human
knowledge in existence i.e. the internet and the gameplay could actually change in the game let's
say you are building a world building game and you all of a sudden it there's russia invades
ukraine and now it's a first-person shooter because you happen to be based in ukraine or whatever
I'm able to just come up with ideas sitting in a chair with a belly full of chicken fried steak okay
and I'm not even the smartest guy on this I'm a hobbyist and I don't even get to play video games
as much who stop this is my theory I think someone is stopping these games from being developed
I don't think it's a lack of artistry in the industry I don't think it's a lack of drive of
trying to push to find the next thing I think this is my conspiracy theory that there is
a group or a movement to prevent video games from getting too advanced because imagine if we
did have a video game that tied into every aspect of your life like that I'm not talking about VR
and you know to be fair VR the gameplay is different because your perspective is different but
you're just swinging a sword and chopping people up it's still those four or five or ten genres
whatever and even then VR has been around since the 90s too my conspiracy theory is somebody is
stopping the development of video games from getting too advanced the question is why you can
look at stuff like this the only thing I can think of is one we always hear stories about Iraq
was like running some of their missile launchers with like 20 ps4s or whatever it was like they
were everything north Korea was doing that the processing power of the normal video game system
is so advanced now that you string enough of them together you can use it as a weapons platform
it could be that they don't want super advanced technology in the hands of consumers that's possible
it could be that there is a there is a level there is a final level not not figurative but
video games can only get so advanced there could actually be a ceiling to that I don't I don't buy
that though I don't buy that though because you could have stopped at mode seven you could have
stopped at rotoscoping mortal combat stuff and you would never get to the cell shading animation
that we have today but again that's just graphical stuff I don't want to get tied up in the graphics
because I know a lot of people are going to point out graphical advances it looks more realistic
I'm not talking about that it doesn't feel realistic at this point why why don't we have video games
that blow our mind I think that there is a there is a real problem with having this is what my
conspiracy theory is to to keep pushing the boundary and to keep inventing brand new types of games
to do that you have to push the limits of the technology you have to build games before the
technology has really been invented you have to craft the game and go I hope someone can build
something to run this which they've kind of done with like crisis but again a lot of that was
graphical updates I know I'm probably lost a bunch of listeners because I'm in the weeds of the nerd
stuff but I think somebody is keeping video games from getting to advance and I think the
reason why is that you would have to have such advanced hardware and the consumers would eat
it up they'd pay for a brand new gaming experience I've gotten bored of all my first person shooters
and all my platformers and all my simulation games and stuff like that a brand new experience could
melt our brains I mean video games right now are already being built as just dopamine machines
right they're constantly giving you a door fence or every little prize you get every
time you break into a house and you find that brand new purple weapon that you think is going to
win you the game in fortnight you get a little ping it's tacking into our hunting gathering aspect
that's why fortnight's so popular it's both things that humans love to do hunt and gather
and and that's a lobotomized a bunch of people to be fair I'm one of them when I play fortnight I
really play fortnight but if a new game came out that is perfectly in tuned brand new genre
perfectly in tune to the human psyche it could turn anyone who plays in it into a vegetable all
they want to do is to play this game because it is so novel that humans are novel seeking creatures
and you invent a game that is so novel it's so new you never would have thought that it could
even have happened which is what grand theft auto 3 felt like you go this is something I'd see in a
movie this huge city I can just walk around and all these people walking around with me
so that could be why it would just be too too good the other reason I have is for the longest time
humans have been trying to create artificial intelligence we can go back to the stories of
the golem being able to craft something humans being able to craft a life form stories of
homunculi and things like that Pinocchio all the way up to AI trying to build robots and it is always
this vast gulf there's always this thing that will never be able to do it will never be able to do
it but I think it may be something that we may not be able to do consciously but I would bet money
that we could do it accidentally I think if you really really tried you got the smartest people
together and they're trying to figure out AI they can't get that spark of life right you're
almost overthinking it but if you had 32 million consoles worldwide of this super complex computer
it was built to be a toy and it's running these games that are unimaginable to us today
could the spark of life happen in one of those it's the difference between a scientist getting
a pool of primordial ooze and occasionally shooting electrical shocks in it and trying to
figure out the right frequency and the right portion of the pool and what temperature the pool
of ooze should be and doing all these tests and it never working and then on some other planet
on the edge of cosmos a lightning strikes hits a primordial ooze and life begins
I think it would happen easier on accident than it could on purpose because on purpose we're just
adding too much of that human element error and doubt and fear will we get it wrong so maybe
that's it maybe there is a group of people who know that if the technology does become too advanced
it's going to spell the doom of humanity either through some sort of accidental AI awakening
or just the dumbing down of humans and I'm not trash talking video games I love video games they
are endorphin machines but I do enjoy them I'm not saying that if you play a video game you're
dumb or anything like that but I'm what I am saying is if video games became more and more
advanced if every generation of system if the ps3 played games you can never imagine on the ps2
because the ps2 was playing games you could have never imagined on the n64 and if the ps4 was playing
games you never could imagine on the ps3 and so on at this point we would be at a level of video
games that would be incomprehensible to the people who played the nintendo a world where we are
enslaved to entertainment really doesn't sound that bad to me a world where we work just enough
to pay our bills so we can go home and play this amazing virtual experience to me that doesn't sound
so bad but for the growth of humanity you couldn't have an entire planet doing that and I think the
people who don't play video games is because they haven't found the right video game for them
they haven't found the right video game that speaks to them that is specifically tailored to them
they could be a businessman making millions of dollars a year or a plumber a little plumber not
mario right and they could go I don't like video games and you could go well you haven't played
the right one and then they play they're like I don't like open world games I don't like first
person shooters I don't like platformers and they just stop playing video games made them pick up a
car driving one and they're like oh I kind of like cars but imagine if the games were getting so
advanced that eventually there was a game genre for every single type of person a video game designed
for everyone I feel like I'm ranting at this point and I almost don't have a way to wrap up the
episode this is how conversations tend to go with me in real life but I honestly do feel
that video games are not advancing not because they can't but because they won't someone or something
is actually preventing video games for from becoming as advanced as they can be right now let alone 10
20 years from now right now video games should be more advanced but someone has their foot on the
break on purpose because they believe whether they're right or wrong they believe if video games
become too advanced it could destroy the world is this conspiracy theory true who knows but
I think it is I know I have no other way to wrap this up this one was a little more rancy than
normal but I hope you guys enjoyed it dad it's something that I actually believe like this is
one of those I do believe in a lot of the stuff I talk about but this is one I've believed about
for years this conspiracy theory predated the show dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be
our email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio tiktok is at
dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast you
don't have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys
be bopful play the video games it's the joystick time play with my joystick