Would you be willing to play a video game that if you died, you die?
And then we end season 19 with a terrifying look at our possible future.
We always hear stories about the great reset, an idea that eventually we will be forced
to eat bugs and be happy about it.
Well, what if things are actually worse than that?
What if it's not bugs that we'll be forced to eat?
You knew this would end the season.
What if it's not bugs that we will be forced to eat?
What if we have to eat poop today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
We got a ton of stuff to cover.
We got a bunch of announcements too.
So let's get started right away for the last episode of season 19.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now was our newest Patreon supporter.
He's carrying a spear and a shield.
I don't know, maybe he's just carrying a 32 on sprite.
Walking into Dead Rabbit Command, everyone give it up for Harun Shaik.
Yeah, everyone's like, "Dude, learn how to pronounce people's names.
I'm trying.
Harun, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand that I do.
Just help spread the word about Dead Rabbit Radio.
That helps out so much.
If you get any value from this show, please help the show grow."
This is also the last episode of season 19.
I'm going to be taking a break until December 1st.
So I hope you guys stick around until the break's over.
I'm hoping you play some Dying Light.
I just got that game on a steam sale not too long ago.
I'm a huge fan of Dead Island, so I think it's like Dead Island, but faster and spookier.
We'll find out.
But even though I'm not coming out with brand new episodes until December 1st, on November
24th at 12 p.m. Pacific Standard Time, we will be doing our annual Thanksgiving livestream
special.
I hope you guys are able to join us for that.
Listen, I get it if you can't.
It's a huge holiday.
You guys are out doing stuff as well.
But if you do have some free time, stop on by November 24th, 12 p.m. Pacific Standard
Time.
It's always been fun.
We've done a lot of these.
We'll for them.
Or this will be the fourth one.
Over the years, that's a lot of fun.
And lastly, before we get the episode started, there's a billion cars driving by today.
I don't know why it's so busy and I'm recording in my living room again.
But before we get started, one more thing.
Let's take a look at this submission for Fanart Friday.
Look at this little bunny.
This little bunny man.
It's technically a dead wrap radio logo.
It's not a man.
But this was sent to me by Lyssa on the Patreon Discord.
I love it.
I love these little sketches.
It never stops humbling me when I see people take time out of their day to do a little
sketch.
That's really cool.
Or just even to listen.
People constantly sending me emails that they listen to the show during their work or during
their commute or while they're washing the dishes.
That's really cool.
That's honestly really cool because that's how I enjoy podcasts.
And it's cool that I'm part of that day for you.
I really, really enjoy it.
And that's why I keep doing this show.
Haroon.
Let's go ahead and get this episode started.
This episode I'm really excited about.
This is some cool stuff here.
Haroon.
I'm going to touch the keys to the Jason Jalopy.
We're leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command.
Take us all the way out to an eSports arena.
Haroon pulls up outside of this arena and he's like, "Is this the place?"
And I'm like, "No, this is an actual sport being played.
There's football going on in there.
Keep driving.
We need to find an eSports arena."
So he's driving.
He gets to a college campus and there's like a little room off to the side and we see people
walking in with their laptops and they're like, "This LAN party is going to be great.
Doom emulators for all."
And I'm like, "Nope.
Nope.
We're not going here either."
And you're like, "Where are we going?"
And I mean, those guys definitely were the definition of an eSport.
In 1999, Jason, who's still having LAN parties.
How old are you?
Okay.
Come on.
Get back in the car.
Haroon.
This isn't the right eSports arena.
Keep driving.
So he's driving through the city and we pass like all these other arenas.
And finally, he pulls up to this auto mechanics garage.
I was like, "Here's the place."
Apparently, I turned into a prospect.
They're all of a sudden, "Here's the place.
This is where the gold be."
So we walk into this mechanics shop and there seems to be no one around.
And I was like, "It's pretty clever.
It's pretty clever hiding spot, isn't this?
I saw this on an episode of Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles and I hit a button and all
of a sudden the lift that lifts the car up, it lifts up and now you see there's like a
staircase descending under the ground, which seemed great on an episode of Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles.
But now that I think about it, it's kind of a different story.
I think it's a bit of a dead giveaway because people would be like, "Hey, can you work on
my car?"
And they're like, "No."
You're like, "There's a lift right there.
Just lift it up.
Use my car.
Fix it."
And they're like, "No."
Because there's a hidden passageway down there built by Baxter Stockman.
We go down this staircase and we hear this, "Oh yeah.
Woo, go yeah.
Woo."
We're like, "What in the world was that?"
We keep walking down the stairs and we keep hearing like, "Yeah, yeah.
Place your bets.
Who's going to win this time?"
Yeah, yeah.
And we walk into this massive underground eSports arena.
We see two teams.
They're both maybe 32 people in each team.
Pretty standard for first person shooter, player versus player.
Hold on.
I got to move my studio back into the closet.
Yeah, I moved it out last night.
I was hoping to record it out here.
But apparently, Autobots and Decepticons are fighting in the front yard.
It's so loud here.
Give me a second.
Okay, sorry about that.
That was super annoying.
It's like every car in the neighborhood decided to test out their snow tires on dry roads
today.
That's why everything is so loud out there in the living room.
We're in this underground eSports arena.
We see on opposite sides of the room two different teams.
And there's about 32 players on each team and they're playing a first person shooter.
But seated all around them.
This really is like a sports arena.
We see the rich and powerful and the dark and mysterious as well.
Not Darth Vader, not Darth Vader, although he fits both of those descriptions.
Well this isn't just any old eSports.
I'm sure you could have guessed that the fact that we had to walk through an underground
tunnel in a hidden passageway in a mechanics shop.
This isn't any old regular old League of Legends nonsense.
This is truly a one of a kind event.
It is a gaming competition where if your character dies in the game, your head blows up.
Can you go chase him?
Yes, I'm sure this is possible like in science fiction.
I've seen tons of stuff with this in it.
From the lawnmower man to the lawnmower man too.
The idea of dying in the video game makes you die in real life.
Well it was a work of fiction until just recently.
Well to be fair, it still is a work of fiction.
The situation I laid out has not happened yet.
But recently Shananigans, a long time supporter of the show, Shananigans on Twitter sent me
this article about this man named Palmer Lucky.
Palmer Lucky.
If anyone sounds like a character from a Philip K Dick novel, it's this guy.
Palmer Lucky, apparently he's the co-founder of the Oculus, the VR headset.
He also has defense contracts.
And he has created a VR headset that has three bombs in it.
Right now he says this is kind of a piece of art sitting around the office, but he's
constructed this.
He goes, the idea is it's a VR headset that if you die in the game, you die in real life.
And you go, why would anyone invent this?
Why would anyone invent this?
Well apparently he's a big fan of an anime called Sword Art Online.
And the premise of that show is people put on VR headsets and then get teleported to
this completely realistic VR world.
Well it's not realistic, I guess there's dragons and stuff, little talking mushrooms.
But you think that you're actually in this world, but in the real world, you're hooked
up to this VR system and if you die in the video game, you die in real life.
He's a big fan of that and he goes, you know what, I used to be a big fan of Godzilla.
I irradiated a bunch of Agones that didn't do anything.
Maybe I'll be a big fan of this cartoon.
Maybe I should invent something that will kill you if you die in the game.
And you're going, why would anyone, even if someone's a big fan of something.
I mean, there's two elements to it.
One, you die in the game.
Two, the game is awesome enough to want to take the risk of dying.
The Sword Art Online world is so vivid that it's worth that risk.
If you're hooked up to this headset, you're playing Medal of Honor for the PS2.
I mean that's not worth it, right?
But imagine if you could go to a virtual world that was so beautiful and everything was amazing
and it was everything that the real world isn't.
Would you risk your head blowing up?
You might be shaking your head no, but remember talking mushrooms, talking mushrooms.
You have those guys as well.
He's invented this and he goes, listen, there are a few things I need to work out.
There are a few glitches I need to work out with this bomb you strapped to your head.
He goes, first off, we'd have to make it so the charges don't accidentally go off, which
is yes, that's a pretty big problem when you're dealing with bombs.
He goes, the way I envision it is that the bombs will detonate when a specific frequency
of red flashing lights appears in the game.
That'll cause the bomb to go off.
So that way you could have it for different video games.
The developer of the video game would know the frequency that would be game over, not
just the frequency of somebody flashing a flashlight in your face.
You're just floating around Neopets and some dudes like click, click, click, click, click
and your head blows up.
You could trigger it to be a specific frequency of red lights.
That's the first thing he has to get that thing done.
He goes, secondly, the game world and then the kind of what I was saying, he goes, you
would have to have a game world that was so vivid and so amazing that yes, it would be
risky, it would be worth the rest to get your head blown off.
Like otherwise when you put the goggles on, if you are playing like Chester Cheetah's
jail breakout that you got free when you ordered a Pizza Hut Pizza, obviously, that would be
the most stressful platformer you'd ever played, but you would know when that prickly
cactus was shooting its thorns at you that you're not really in danger.
I mean, you are, you do have a bomb strap to your head, but in the game world you would
just be like, oh, that's just a guy shooting sprites at me.
Now, that would be the last thought you had as your head disintegrates into a pile of blood,
brain matter, skull and half chewed pizza.
He goes, the game would have to be indistinguishable from reality to make it all fit.
That is something that I think game designers are working towards and what's funny is that
I, I would love a system like this.
Not necessarily my brain blowing up, but when I play Minecraft, I play in hardcore mode
and that's where when you die, your whole world gets erased and I'll drop like 30, 40
hours into a one world and I like find a village and I build a wall around it and I do all
this stuff and then I make up missions for myself.
I'd be like, oh, I must go find a treasure chest.
So I'm walking around and I basically playing this Minecraft game, which is okay to be
fair for me, making fun of League of Legends multiple times.
I get it, Minecraft's for babies, but I love Minecraft.
I play in the hardcore mode and then I put 30, 40 hours and it was single world and then
Creeper blows me up and it makes the impact so monumental.
So I get like the need for it.
He has a quote.
He goes, quote, pumped up graphics may make a game look more real.
But only the threat of serious consequences can make a game feel real to you and every
other person in the game.
And I do agree with that.
I've, I would love the idea of a game that if you died in it, the game's deleted.
Like you have to buy another copy of the game.
I think that would be great.
I think it'd be great if you had a first person shooter and if you die in the game, there's
then like a five to 10 minute unskippable cutscene of the army going to your wife's
house and knocking on the door and you see her sobbing and then they cut to a scene of
a mom.
It's actually your mom before you can play the game.
You have to get digital photos of everyone you know.
And your mom's like, no, not my son.
No.
And then there's like a full, there's a full length funeral and it would really make the
dying in the game be more consequential.
Imagine GTA, but you get a car accident and the cops arrest you.
They're like, that's it.
We're going to find you $1,000.
We take all your weapons and you can't play this game for the next 10 days.
Palmer Lucky says, as far as he knows, this has never been done before, but the genie's
out of the bottle.
And this would be awesome for the Illuminati that we talk about.
We recently did an episode on this guy named Donald Marshall who talked about underground
gladiator combats and they use clones and he fought Mick Jagger and Brendan Fraser stabbed
him in the intestines and all this stuff.
They were clones by the way if you're a huge Brendan Fraser fan, don't give up on them.
It was his clone, but he believes that celebrities from around the world have killed him and
the gladiator and this cloned gladiator arena.
And as foolish as that is, what you're really doing in essence is you're taking two people,
you're giving them weapons and then you're like, fight, fight to the death.
And then you as a businessman are standing about 20 feet from them or sitting in some
arena as these two people you've kidnapped are hacking at each other with swords.
Now we've all watched enough movies where you have the two people being like, you know
what, we're the ones with the swords.
They're just some rich guy in a suit.
Let's team up and we can hack our way out of here and all of a sudden the guy's like,
no, no, don't kill me, I'm from Wall Street.
And the two guys start a slave revolution.
Just them, it's a revolution of two, but it works.
You would think that, right?
But you'd basically be getting these trained fighters and locking them up and being like,
you will fight to the death until you become too weak to fight anymore and then you will
die.
And then the prisoners like, or, or you just start beating you up now.
And I'm assuming they'd also have goons with guns.
The Illuminati people would have goons with guns in around.
But my point is, is that you can do it like that.
You can have people place wagers.
But when you look at something like the Squid Game, that Squid Game show, they had to build
these massive sets.
Massive sets.
And even when you had like, I think it started off with like 460 people, they did have guards
with guns.
But you could easily have these uprisings.
But imagine if the Squid Games were just people with bombs on their heads playing, playing
Squid Game mods on Roblox and they're like, all the controls totally suck.
What are you talking about?
Oh man, my keyboard stuck and their heads are just blowing up.
I totally could see that happening.
I could totally see some sort of underground group forcing people to fight to the death,
but instead of giving them weapons.
And you figured this would even the battlefield.
Like imagine if a super buff dude got kidnapped and then next to him got kidnapped to scientists.
And he's like, oh man, never worked out my muscles except for my brain.
Obviously, I mean, is a, when you're betting, you're going to be like, is this a joke?
I'm going to bet on the buff dude.
And if everyone was in a VR world and they died, it would be more even playing field.
I mean, obviously the nerd would have an advantage there.
But a fascinating thing, he says that this is the first time as far as he knows they've
been invented.
I'm sure there have been other versions of this.
Okay, I guess I can't say I'm sure it is pretty science fiction even.
Now that the cat's out of the bag, I can see people going, make us 64 of these.
We're going to hold a tournament and whoever sucks at this first person shooter, their
brains blow up.
Although now that I think about it, you would imagine the Illuminati would have better things
to do than hosting these types of summits.
And actually that's a great segue into our next story.
Harun, let's go ahead and tashi the keys to the Carbindercopter.
We're taking it out one more time this season.
Rise away from this gladiator arena, there's only one dude left with his brains intact.
He's the winner!
I mean, he's covered in brains.
Did you imagine playing a first person video game with a VR headset on and you know it's
to the death and when another player, like the guy sitting at the computer next to you,
when he died, you're playing a game, right?
You have a perfect sniper position and then all of a sudden two feet away you hear a BAM!
And you're just covered in brain matter.
Like it would totally freak you out.
That would be the worst possible thing.
Well I guess the worst possible thing would be the guy sitting next to you with no head.
That would be the worst, but the second worst possible thing is you're trying to not die
and all of a sudden you're just getting covered in that loud explosion, you're getting covered
in brains and guts and gore.
I don't know why I just had to leave you with that last horrible image.
Harun, take this Carbindercopter away from this arena, we're flying all the way out.
To a weightlifting gym.
*imitates a drum roll*
There's a company called Fit Biomics.
They're probably just pronouncing that.
It's probably Fit Bi...
Oh I don't know, is there another way to pronounce it anyways?
Fit Biomics is closer to probably what it is.
There's a company called Fit Biomics and at Fit Biomics they have this new product invented
by Dr. Jonathan Scheiman.
It's called Nella.
That's not a bad name right?
Reminds you of Nutella.
Well be prepared to not eat anymore Nutella.
Dr. Scheiman, he has invented this thing called Nella.
He goes, "Here's the thing, I've discovered through my research that to be a super athlete
it's more than just your training, it's more than just your diet, it's even more than just
your genetics.
A large part of it is also your gut biome."
So then we're standing there in this weightlifting gym and we see this muscle bound dude like
doing all these reps.
He's like, "Oh yeah, look at me, look at me."
He definitely has some issues.
He's like, "Life doesn't matter unless people look at me."
He's lifting all these weights.
He's like, "Look at me."
And Dr. Scheiman goes, "Have you guys ever wanted to be as thick and muscular as this
dude?"
Here, take this pill I've invented, it's called Nella.
He's holding this pill out to us.
On the one hand, yeah, sure would be awesome to be this total buff dude who has issues
with people paying attention to one, but on the other hand, hey doc, didn't you just
say something about gut biome?
Trying to figure out how athletes and what's inside their guts is actually helping them
out.
As you were asking that question, I put my hand up over my mouth.
I'm like, "Hmmm."
As you're asking that question, he flicks the pill in your throat and you're like,
"Ugh, ugh."
If you take the Nella, you can actually become an elite athlete.
Now Nella, before you get too excited before you run to the store, you're like, "Oh, I've
got a marathon coming up.
Can I get one box of Nella?
Let me tell you what's in it, what he does."
And this is what he discovered.
He said, "He drove around Boston for two weeks, eight hours a day.
He's driving around Boston.
He's collecting stool samples from elite runners."
And what he realized was if you look at elite runners, they have this thing called, well,
I guess most people have it, it's called bacterium vellanella atypica.
And he goes, "When you look at elite runners, they have very, very high, consistently high
levels of this bacterium."
He said, "In a normal person, this spikes during exertion and this is one of the reasons
why your muscles get sore.
But if I took the stool samples from these elite athletes, he didn't tell me to snuck
into their house late at night.
He's all hiding in the closet, waiting until they go to bed."
And then he crawls out in the darkness with a little spoon, with a little wooden spoon,
a taster spoon from Baskin Robbins, go up in their butthole.
He realized that they have this in them.
They have a lot of this bacterium vellanella atypica.
And this is part of being an elite athlete.
He injected this bacterium into mice.
And what could only be described as the funniest and cruelest experiment?
He injected this bacterium into mice and they were able to run 13% longer than normal.
So I mean, that's something you get the intern to do, right?
I'm sure Dr. Shyam is like, "No, no, I want to inject them.
I did all the work.
I get to have all the fun."
He's injecting it into the mice.
But then you make your intern just watch two mice run, two mice run around on these wheels.
So like, tell me how long the one with the gut biome stuff, tell me how much more he runs.
And then he goes out on another fecal gathering mission.
So if you take a mice who's injected with this, he could run 13 times longer.
Now others go, "Uh, you know, sure, the science might be there.
We do know that your gut biome is a huge part of who you are."
They say 90% of the body serotonin gets produced by your gut bacteria.
I think it's really interesting when people go, "I have a craving for sugar.
I have a craving for that."
That's all your gut bacteria.
If you've ever gone a couple days without sugar, because I very rarely have sugar, but it's
weird when I do have sugar, then the next three days I'm craving it.
It's because all the flora in your stomach is there.
It pops up when you eat sugar and it's sending signals to your brain going, "Eat more sugar.
Eat more sugar."
Because if it doesn't get sugar, it dies off the whole life form in your stomach.
It's almost like a parasite in there and it's controlling you.
That's why when you start overeating, it's hard to stop and you'll have food addicts.
It's different where you're like a gambling addict.
That's like a serotonin thing in your brain or your heroin addict.
That's the heroin interacting with the dopamine receptors in your brain.
Food addiction, sugar addiction is actually a new life form in your stomach developing
and then releasing chemicals into the bloodstream saying, "Feed us.
Feed us."
You're building up this new life form in your stomach and when you stop eating sugar, it
takes three days for this life form to completely die out.
Then it will stop sending the signals because it's dead.
It can no longer talk to you.
It's totally different.
It's super weird.
The addiction to food is different.
There's a new life form in you trying to get you to eat more of what it needs.
Fascinating stuff.
We know that gut biome is super important, but he's saying you can take this Nella and
you now have the gut biome or you take it regularly, of course.
There's a monthly subscription for $59 a box, which you can either go, "Wow, that's really
low to be an elite athlete," or, "Wow, that's really high to eat someone else's poop."
You can get a monthly subscription of Nella and they're saying that if you take this,
you will be able to run longer than normal.
I'm sure that's not the only thing on the box because otherwise you're like, "Oh, no,
I'm good.
I don't run that much anyways."
I saw that and I go, "Okay, the VR brain thing, that's something that I could see in a sci-fi
movie and then I could see someone building it in real life.
If you wanted to have real life gladiator combat, this would be the way to do it.
It would be the safest way, I mean, not for the participants, but for you or it could
just be a novelty."
This one, this is really being produced and it is a performance enhancing supplement.
Imagine a world where if you want to compete in sports, you have to eat human poop because
everyone else has eaten human poop.
Now, to be very clear, to be very clear, 20, 30 minutes into talking about this, he is
not selling, I guess I should clear this up for the lawsuit, for the inevitable lawsuit,
he is not selling pills of human poop.
I keep human poop.
I also accuse this guy of hiding in people's closets with tiny wooden spoons and taking
their poop out without their knowledge.
That's just hearsay, your honor.
That's just hearsay, I heard it in my own head and then I said it.
He's not selling pills of human poop, but he's selling pills of this bacterium cocktail.
But in essence, I mean tomato, tomato, right?
You're taking a pill that at one point, this bacteria was in some dude's butthole.
Now maybe, and once I said that, okay, maybe it's not that, maybe he cultured this bacteria,
right?
He could then breed more of it in his laboratory, but I would still argue in this upcoming defamation
case that if you, this is a philosopher's question, right?
If you took a piece of poop out of a man's butthole and then isolated a small piece of
that poop and then used that small piece of poop to create a chemical, are you still not
eating a man's poop?
Are you still not, that was the origin point.
Are you still not eating something that came out of some other dude's butt?
Now I'm not a runner, I don't run for nothing.
But if I was a runner, I would be thinking, well everyone else in the race is eating human
poop, why aren't I?
There's some guy just scooping it up, he's like what?
Oh you're supposed to think this is in a form of a pill?
This is a supplement that you could see almost you having to take if you are doing any sorts
of sports at all, you're going up against people who are eating human poop and you're
not.
There's a lot of stuff that we would never do if we were forced to, no one, no one would
want to live in a society where people go you gotta eat this poop, it'll make you work
harder.
Dude I work at Best Spy, I already have to work, I'd have to eat human poop.
But if it's voluntary, right, it's voluntary, this is something that you could see athletes
going if I want to compete at an elite level, I gotta eat the poop.
I almost feel like this isn't a social issue or a science issue, it feels, I know I tossed
a word around demonic, I know I tossed a word demonic around a lot on this show but
it sounds like something that is so anti-human to eat something that came from fecal matter.
Now, I have to be very very clear, I am going to go and check and see, cause now I'm thinking
about not being accused of this guy, not being accused of Dr. Scheinman of hiding people's
closets, taking stool samples without their permission, getting enjoyment out of injecting
fecal matter into mice, I'm starting to think, I'm starting to think of something here,
there's gonna be two things, one, I either in the episode going, is it possible we'll
live in a world where people aren't taking fecal matter, fecal matter, to win sports
but really they're enacting some sort of ancient right to an old pagan god, like really this
is what it sounds like, devouring fecal matter, that's like belphagore, there's a demon who
loves poop and every time you use the toilet, I believe his name is belphagore, I'll double
check that but every time you go poop you're basically worshiping him and this sounds almost
like a demonic plot and people having like, this is really what it comes down with deals
with the devil right, you can train hard and you can do your best but eventually everyone
else in your sport is taking human poop, now you have to make a deal with the devil, are
you going to stick up for yourself and say, you know what, I run for the enjoyment, I don't
run to win so I don't want to eat human poop, that's what a deal or you know I am gonna
eat poop, I am gonna eat poop to win, that's really what a deal with the devil is, you're
making, you're compromising your own idea of what it means to be human and somewhat argue
what it means to be fair in sports, you're eating human fecal matter to become a better
athlete and that sounds like a demonic pact, you're giving away a bit of your humanity
for a simple contest, something that's meaningless on the grand scale of things but you're eating
poop to do it and all the while this great demon is watching all of this with glee, while
the world became more sanitized as we cleaned up the streets from just logs of poop rolling
down the open sewers of London to a world that's so sanitized that kids get peanut allergies
because they're not getting exposed to germs and bacterium that they normally are in childhood,
we've come a long way in a very short period of time, any sort of demonic entity that fed
off of filth and disease would be losing power but now in the guise of a pill that makes
you a better athlete, people are willingly ingesting fecal matter, this demon who had
been slowly but steadily losing influence over the world is now in its own way being worshiped,
when people are taking the Nella pill they're not like this is for you grand demon of fecal
matter, but in a way they're doing that sacrament, it's more than that, it's more than that throughout
all of human history people hated waste products but now they're willingly eating it and so
is this the return of this belphagore type character, this demon who lives in the waste
waters, a demon that lives in the filth, you're taking the sacrament just like you were taking
the Lord's Supper, taking the consecrated wafer and a little bit of wine, could this
be his way back to power?
If you want to win, you have to ingest the poop, if you want to win, you have to worship
the demon of the toilet.
That's one way I can end the episode but I am going to say this, I'm recording this for
a little bit of safety, there's a possibility, I thought about this as I was recording it,
that he's not actually giving people pooped, I thought about this, like wait a second I
never heard of me until I was reading over my notes and I'm recording the last episode
of season 19, maybe he wasn't feeding people poop, maybe, I'm sure there was a bunch of
you shaking your heads this whole time and you were like, does Jason actually think that
these Nell-a-bills are like brown, there's a little piece of corn, there's a little
piece of corn in some of them, no I don't think that, but I'm thinking now that the
stool samples were just for the experiments, in the sense that he goes, I wonder if there's
something different in an elite runner's stool, so he went, he didn't do it the creepy way,
he didn't do the creepy way like I said, he asked people, hey can I have some of your
stool please, which that's actually super creepy as well, but he gets this stool of
elite runners and he gets stool of regular people and then he matches it and goes, wow,
if you're an elite runner your stool has more of this bacterium, this vellanella atypica,
interesting, so then no stool involved in the production process, I didn't even think
about this, I totally didn't even think about this, then he throws away all of the poop
and he is able to produce vellanella atypica in some other sort of way, like he puts out
like a piece of bread, like he's doing some sort of science project for fifth grade, he
leaves a piece of bread out for a couple of days and it grows mold and he's able to isolate
the vellanella atypica, maybe he was able to produce this sans butthole and that's what
the pill is, the pill, just like probiotics when you go and buy him at the store, it's
possible just to be clear, I'm gonna double check before I release this episode, he's
gonna be like, clearly you're all, this man has no idea what he's talking about, he disparaged
me for three minutes, he called me a freak, a freak who's hiding in the shadows of people's
closets, so maybe he didn't, I will record this part just in case, maybe he didn't, maybe
he wasn't hiding people's closets, maybe this has nothing to do with human poop in its final
form, that might have just been the experiment, or maybe tonight when you're getting ready
to go to bed, you go, you know what man, season 19 that sure was a wild ride, dead rabbit
who talks a lot about poop, the whole season, it wasn't just last episode, some weird stuff
this season, you're like, you know, it's time for me to go to bed, but I do have that big
marathon tomorrow, well I'll figure it out later, you fall asleep, then your closet
door opens in the middle of the night, and you see a doctor shyman shaped silhouette
start to creep out and you're like, oh no, oh no, you know exactly what the silhouette
looks like, it's doctor shyman, it's doctor shyman, and you see him pull up a little wooden
spoon and you go to get up, then you realize there's four super strong men surrounding
your bed, they've had all the fecal matter they want, which is oddly a lot, there's some
weird fetish cult, they're holding you down with their fecal empowered muscles, you're
like no, no, and doctor shyman's walking closer and closer with his little taster spoon, he's
like, ah yes, for $59 a month, requires a lot of poop, it's like that old, what was
it, the outer limits, or the twilight zone tells from the dark side about the box, you
got the box, and if you pressed the button, someone you didn't know would die and you
would get a million dollars, but if you don't press the button, then you don't get a million
dollars, and you have like an hour to decide, and the woman presses the button, I mean she
gets a million dollars, and then the guy at the ending goes, ah yes, everyone presses
the button, I will give this box to someone else now, someone you don't know, that's this,
if you order, if you order Nella, what you really do is give in your address to FitBioMix,
and now they're also gonna make you part of the food chain, if you order this you're like
alright my Nattella, I mean my Nella, it's finally here, ohm, and then your address went
into a database, they're going to drive up to your house and start harvesting your butt
hole, because how else are they gonna produce enough of this, probably, probably without
butt holes, he's probably culturing it in some other way, but in the world of conspiracy
theory, who knows what is possible, who knows what, who knows what defamation is, can you
really define slander or libel when you're talking about the world of paranormal, can
you, can you, your honor I rest my case, dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is gonna be your
email address, you can also set us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio, tiktok is @dead rabbit radio,
dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast, you don't have to
listen to it everyday, I'm glad you listened to it today, have a great one guys.
[Music]
[MUSIC]