A beautiful bandit, a mysterious family, and a UFO story so bizarre even veteran UFOologists
have a hard time believing it. What happened in 1955 in a sleepy little town in California?
Were they invaded by aliens only children could see today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. It's actually only about two hours
since I finished the last podcast. Most of you guys know I work three jobs every so often.
Someone has to take a vacation at one of the jobs and I cover form. It's once in a blue moon,
but starting this week into next week and a little bit of the week after that,
I'm working all three jobs every single day. So try to get these episodes out when I can get them
out. And that's one of the good things about doing a solo podcast. I just want to get them out once a
day for you guys. So if anything absolutely earth-shattering has happened from the time I'm
recording this to the time you hear it, it's not because I ignored it, didn't know what happened
yet. I'm recording this at 11 o'clock at night. But let's go ahead and jump right into this one.
I'll keep my energy level up for you. I'm drinking my diet mountain dew, choice of a generation.
So hop on board. Let's use the Jason Jalopy. So throw your bags in the back. This is going to be a
long journey. We're going to have, bring a sleeping bag, some popcorn. I don't know why popcorn.
Bring food. That was what I'm saying. Bring yourself some food or some delicious beverages from
PepsiCo only because they sponsor the show. No Coke. No Mr. Pib. No Dr. Pepper either. That's
just disgusting. Prune juice flavored soda. Get in the car. And also they don't sponsor us for
legal reasons. That was a joke. We're driving down the road. Beep, beep. Keep your hand off the horn.
Only I can press the horn. Drive another road. And we're pulling up to Sugarland, Texas.
This just happened August 23rd, 2019. So this happened on Friday, last Friday. It's 825.
The darkest time of night when all the spooky stuff happens. 825 is quite early for this type of
activity. We're parked across the street in our Jason Jalopy eating. You brought snacks. I'm eating
them too. You're like Jason. I'm like, I thought you were on keto. I'm like, I'm trying to break.
Doritos. So as I'm swelling up and some gaining 10 pounds of water weight from just eating one
Dorito, we're looking across the street and there's a place. There's like a parking lot.
And we see this hot woman hops out of the car. And you're like Jason, you have to objectify her.
Yes, I do because that's the point of the story. Now give me some more Doritos.
You see this hot woman hop out of the car. Blonde hair, pink blouse, yoga pants. You're
taking a look. Hold on. This is important for the story. This is important for the story.
And also it's not just my fantasy. This is on surveillance video. Hot blonde hops out of the
car. Hair blowing in the wind. Beat of sweat moving down her chest. No, so anyways, we see on
surveillance video this blonde woman gets out of her Mercedes SUV, walks over to a building,
tries opening the door, goes back to her SUV, gets a portable power saw and begins cutting through
the window because she's breaking into the Botox RN MD Spa. It's a place where they injected
Botox into people's faces. Makes your face all tight, gets rid of the wrinkles. She cut her way
in and stole a bunch of Botox and then gets in her Mercedes SUV, just drives away. They don't know
who it is. They have no suspects. She's not wearing a mask. She's just walking up in her pink blouse.
She looks like she just got done picking up the kids or, hey, I'm not going to be sexist. Maybe
she just got done buying a business. Maybe she's a CEO. I don't know. Maybe she's president of
the United States, Jason. Don't be sexist. So nobody knows who this woman is, but anyways,
she gets in her car and she drives away. Now I will say this though, police of Sugarland, Texas.
My personal, if I was a cop, I would just look for women who look permanently surprised. Their
eyebrows are all lifted. No wrinkles. They'd be like, where were you Friday night? She's like,
no emotion on her face. Actually, she'd be really good in interrogation room because you wouldn't
be able to read her face. It would be full of a deadly disease and she shows no emotions. Just
constantly looks like she's in shock. I'm arrested versus hello. I guess your voice doesn't change.
Anyways, so be on the lookout, residents of Sugarland, Texas. An attractive woman
may actually have a face like her entire body at this point. It's just 90% Botox and she's coming
for you. Let's go ahead and move on to our next story. Hop back in the Jason Jalopy. We are driving
to a place that was recommended to me by Andrew. Andrew via Gmail sent me this recommendation.
We are going to Yucca, Ipa, Yucca, Yucca, Ipa, California. So we're going there. We're going
to, we're just call it the Big U. We're going to the Big U out in California. I'm driving up. Now
actually, it's perfect. We're in the Jason Jalopy for this story because this story requires you
to be in a car. So we stopped at that gas station. You bought some beef jerky, right? Okay, awesome.
You're like, Jason, you have a Patreon now. You can afford your own food. I was like,
I'm putting the gas in, man. So anyways, we drive up to outside of this house. There's a specific
house in the Big U, Yucca Paya, and it's an urban legend come true, video proof of this house. And
what happened was it started off in the area and then it spread to the internet and then things
got really bad. If you pull up to this particular house in Yucca Paya, you're driving your car,
you park in front of it, and a bunch of people come out of the house. Now you're thinking that's
not unusual. And so it's funny because it's so mundane, but at the same time,
it's very, very bizarre when you kind of step back and think about it. People will drive up to this
house and park outside the house. And then a bunch of people come outside the house. That's the story.
That's the story. That's the story of Yucca Paya. They're technically called the Yucca Paya
Watchers. So that makes it sound like really sinister, but that's it. You drive in front of a house
and people come out. And what's okay? So if someone just said, "Hey dude, did you know that if you drive
down this spooky street during the day in the middle of the day and park in someone else's parking
spot, someone's gonna come out of the house?" You'd be like, "That's the dumbest urban legend I've
ever heard." But the reason why Andrew sent this to me, it's because these guys don't just come out
of their house. They come out like four or five deep and begin screaming at people in their cars.
So there's tons of YouTube videos of people, you know, just dumb kids driving in front of this house
and they just park. And then like four dudes come barreling out of the house. They're all like
donkey kong. They're like, "Get out of the house!" So they've made themselves into a target for people
to just park the car any time of the day. And that's why they call the watchers. They don't just
watch, but they know when you're there. People are like, "We think they have cameras." Probably,
probably. But it's one of those, I mean, again, it's they've made themselves a target for people
parking in their front yard, which seems so not even in the front yard. They're not driving up on
the grass. They're like, "Oh, my petunias!" It's like they just park the car. The problem is,
is it's gotten to the point where people in the neighborhood are like, "Hey, look at these local
weirdos." Like in Bay Area, I've talked about him before. We have that guy named Joe Trombone,
who's this crazy schizophrenic hobo who just rapped all the time. Local legend. But in Yucapaya,
you have people going, "Hey, man, those guys, they run out of their house when you're parked."
And then people started doing it on YouTube and then people started coming from all over California
to videotape themselves. I'm surprised Jake Paul hasn't done a video with these guys yet.
It's become this thing. And they call the cops all the time. So now you run the risk of being
arrested for parking your car. And this was a total flashback for me. I read this short story.
I watched a couple videos about the Yucapaya Watchers and then I read this story.
I'll try to make it shorter. It's kind of, let's see how long this goes.
"I don't know how many of you heard of the Yucapaya Watchers. But don't ever go there."
They were pretty famous on YouTube. Here's the legend. That's their word. Legend has it.
"If you go by there any time day or night, the people who live there will come out of the house
and confront you and talk." Beep. Beep that up. People listen to the show at work.
"Me and my friends went there and just like they say, they immediately misspelled.
Immediately come outside. It was two in the morning. So the beep started walking to the vehicle
with a full, flesh sasch light." I really shouldn't make fun of people spelling because of my
pronunciations but a flesh sasch light shone on us and started talking. Beep.
"He took down our plate and called the cops." I guess. I probably could have read that more
smooth. "He took down our plate and called the cops I guess and we got pulled over on our way back
to the freeway. The officer said she knew we were at the Watchers and knew we filmed it and blah
blah so they checked us." This is my favorite part. This reminded me of me being in my 20s.
I loved it. It just had this like, this put a smile on my face when I read this last sentence.
"So they checked us all and looked for any excuse to arrest us since driving by a house isn't really
illegal. Long story short, my friend had one Tylenol 3 on him that he doesn't have a prescription for
so they arrested him. Don't ever effing go there." Now I'm not happy that the kid got arrested
obviously but I remember being such a stupid knucklehead kid and just doing dumb stuff and
you'd be driving with your buddies and the one kid has a single pill. I don't know why I find that
so funny. It's just such a flashback to what people do as kids that are idiots. So yes,
I don't think the moral of the story is don't go to the Ucopie Watchers. Don't have prescriptions,
even a single pill on you if you're going to do something semi-legal. But so the legend is this,
is that the Ucopie Watchers are like satanic cult or they're meth dealers like they have something
to protect. I just think they're weirdos who have attracted more weirdness to them because
of the way they react stuff. So thank you Andrew for the recommendation but looking into it I don't
think there's anything sinister going on. I just think they're lunatics for legal reasons. A legend
lunatics who have like maybe they're think they're gangstaught or but the thing is is like every
time they react in a crazy way more and more people want to go out there because they see these
crazy videos. So it keeps going on. The legend that I think is going to happen is they're going to
end up shooting somebody or there's going to be a serious fight because the people drive away real
quick when they get nearby. They're like man that was close everyone take their tight little three oh
it feels so groovy now. Driving away but yeah I don't know. I think it's an interesting local
legend and because of things like YouTube it's become far far more popular. I mean like sometimes
you can engage in behavior that makes you more likely to become an urban legend like the Ucopie
people. Okay so we're driving away from Ucopie. They're chasing us down the street. I'm like oh
good thing I still have all this pain medication on me. You're like Jason no you're driving. I'm
like you take the wheelie. I'm just going to lay in the back seat for a while and be constipated
and you're like where are we going Jason? I just can't drive the Jason Jalopy wherever I want or
can I and you try to take it back in time but I'm like no no no don't do that. Only I can
activate the magical powers of the Jason Jalopy. We are going to Casablanca and you're like yes
played against Sam. No we're going to Casablanca in 1955. You're like yes is that when the movie
came out? I'm like no actually I don't know when that movie came out. I'm going to come out in 1955.
No we're going to Casablanca, California. So we're almost there. We're going to Riverside County
so go ahead hit that button right there. Take us back to the year 1955.
Car, the car does not sound that smooth. It actually sputters and barely gets us to 1955
Casablanca, California and I'm going to tell you a story. I'm going to tell you a story.
It was a beautiful day in the neighborhood. Two p.m. Kids are out playing, flying kites,
eating apples, having fun. There's a group of eight kids wrestling. Well technically only two of
them are wrestling but the other six are like fight fight fight and we have a dude named Kermit
Douglas. His whole body's all oiled up ready to go and then an unnamed kid who I imagine he's wearing
like a unit's heart he's like come get some big chest hair they're wrestling in Kermit's yard
and then they hear a ping kids look up in the sky and they see a dome like a silvery it was like
silvery and translucent dome in the sky and he goes ping disappears and then they hear a ping
and they see what looks like a flying saucer but it's flying sideways so it's like stationary but
it looks like a circle in the sky and they're said they could see light bending around the edges of it
at this point Kermit's like come on let's go let's go everyone else is looking at these things
Kermit's like what he looks up he sees it and he's like oh I better stop wrestling ping disappears
ping the dome appears ping disappears ping sideways flying saucer appears ping
disappears and the two vehicles started going ping ping ping appearing and disappearing appearing
and disappearing in front of these kids now one of the kids is like this is not good I'm out and he
runs away and he runs home and he tells mom mom there's some pinging out there you got to come out
and see what's in the sky now of course she's probably like oh great gotten to his dad's acid
again but she's like looks out the window she's like I don't see nothing and the kid's like oh mom
he runs back to join his friends to see if this is still going on his mom couldn't see anything though
he goes back and he goes hey so what happened with those UFO things and the kids go in unison all
seven of them go we don't just so can they go they went away you rent to go tell your parents and
then they just disappeared and the kids like oh shucks what do you want to do now you want to
kick the can and then ping the dome appears again ping and they start alternating the end and the
kids are like oh okay now now this is creepy because at the first point they're thinking oh you know
maybe we're seeing something wrong maybe it's a UFO but once the kid went to go tell their parent
and it went away it's almost like a stranger in the bushes like hey you want to come play with me
I'm gonna go tell my mom and then he like leaves gets in his van drives away but then you come back
and you're like oh mom doesn't care you go back he crawls back on the bushes that's creepy so the
fact that he left to go tell his parents made it stop they're like oh it's kind of a stranger
danger right and they didn't have a stranger danger back then lights are blinking ships are
coming in and out of existence and then they see the dome ship go 1950s 1950 sound effects it's like
bobbling like it's attached to a string they see it land in a football field about a half block
from kermit's house and she goes it's hovering about three feet off the ground so they're like
come on guys goonies never quit or whatever that stupid saying is they start never say die whatever
they're running through the yard to get to where the dome is and then they see it they all turn to
their left or right it doesn't matter it's by kermit's house they see an alien and they describe
this alien as this it had like a roundish head like a normal normal head big red round eyes
taking up a good portion of its face a big red round mouth it didn't have a nose it had four
little dots kind of spaced around its cheeks and they said they shimmered like diamonds
it had arms little arms moving around but it had no legs its body actually tapered off like
Casper the ghost so i know what you're thinking at this point i know what you're thinking at this
point Jason this is kind of creepy and it's quite bizarre we haven't even gotten started yet so they're
looking at this Casper ghost just kind of floating there wavy arms just kind of hovering there right
it's wearing a belt like all ghosts it has to have a fashion accessory it has his belt with a giant
like mirror type piece of metal on it super bright the kids are like oh i can't see i can't see and
then one of the kids in the group is like looking at the alien and he's like yeah that's nothing
he looks at the dome UFO in the in the football field and he goes that's the most beautiful thing
i've ever seen and he starts walking towards the domed UFO and two of the but everyone's staring
at this ghost he's not chill and not a ghost whatever whatever it was alien ghost maybe the
ghost of an alien who knows anyways this thing's floating around the corner there and everyone's
staring at that one kid leaves the group starts walking over there two of the older kids see what's
going to happen see him walking towards the ship they have to run they have to tackle the kid they
can't keep him from walking towards the ship once they tackle him multiple UFOs began appearing in
the neighborhood one lands on a nearby roof of a house one knocks off the branch of a tree
a walnut tree to be specific and then one seems to fly by and shoot out some sort of ray
now at this point the kids are screaming out loud because they've seen the alien guy hanging
around the corner they've had to tackle one of their buddies all these things are blinking in
and out of existence their parents and other people in the neighborhood come out to see what's going
on and they don't see anything they don't see a little ghost man mommy mommy know there's a guy
over there he has a weird belt buckle ah it's blinding me it's blinding me she looks over there
it's a shrub with a shiny ant on it she's like oh that's just an ant they don't see the UFOs flying
around they don't see the landed UFO they just see their kids like freaking out in the front yard
the parents have no idea what they're looking at but these UFOs are bing bing bing flying all around
dudes are getting tackled kermit's ready to wrestle an alien all the kids are freaking out
and then one of the kids turns around and in a you got all this chaos going around right
he turns around and out of thin air he sees an arm just like cut off at the shoulder it's like the
rest of the body is invisible and there's just an arm reaching out of reality and it's beckoning
him towards it it'd be like if you cut a hole through a curtain and stuck your arm through it
but that curtain happened to be existence and it wasn't a alien arm it wasn't a human arm it was a
metallic armored arm and it's just beckoning a child over towards it now there's drawings of the
arm and what it reminded me of is you know how we'll put our not we because we're not professionals
but you know how professionals will put their arms in those things to kind of control like radioactive
isotopes and like move aids from one vial to another they have to use like those mechanical arms
or they at least put their hands in gloves and you know like you see them in movies where they're
like reaching into a box that's what it looked like but it was this like metal sleeve over an arm
with fingers beckoning the kid over he doesn't go he doesn't he's like i'm not going over there the
arm's like snaps its fingers it's like dang it it disappears a dude appears in the field and other
kids looking out in the field and there's just some guy now there's just some random normal looking
human walk he was considered he was called a strange man so it wasn't one of the ghost guys
this is all happening in the middle afternoon by the way there's a man walking around now by the
ufo he pulls out two guns he goes jew jew doesn't make the noises actually shoots two kids and they
get paralyzed now i know what you're thinking at this point because i was thinking the same thing
i can understand if the if the parents walked outside and the kids are like oh no it's an alien
and the kids the parents look around the corner and they go that's weird there's nothing there my
kids must just be imagining stuff but if you were a parent and you walked outside and your kids are
running around they're going oh my god no aliens are getting us i would think they were playing
around if i saw a branch fall off of a walnut tree you're like oh no my walnuts if i saw a branch
get knocked off a walnut tree if i saw two kids running and then go paralyzed and hit the ground
i'm not going to be like oh those those rap scallions oh they're just playing around i'd be like
oh you know that they always play that game loss of central nervous system oh it's just an
old thing we used to play that as kids too you would go oh no there's some sort of emergency going on
but apparently okay so let me finish the story let me finish the story so two kids get shot with
paralysis ray and i'm gonna i'm gonna tell you this right now before i keep going this isn't
from backpackerverse this story is from several reputable ufo sources not even just websites but
from ufo literature okay so it's there's no twist to the ending where i'm like surprised i found out
it was invented in 2018 no this story goes back to 1955 when it was reported so where did i leave
off because it still isn't even the weirdest part yet two kids get paralyzed walnut tree is
destroyed or branch broken off you have the mechanical arm still we're coming up to this is
the my favorite part this is hands down my favorite part so now the ship the dome ship in the distance
a portal opens up like a little doorway right and out comes another alien now this alien looks has
the same head as the alien who was hiding behind the corner has the big red eyes big red mouth a
little diamond little like red things that sparkle like diamonds but he has two arms but at the elbow
it becomes two more arms so he has four hand like four four arms four hands on each like he has a
like a shoulder to elbow and then the arm splits and his body doesn't taper down like a little
caster ghost he has four tendrils he just kind of hovers above the ground upside of the ship he's
just hovering above the ground with his weirdo arms and his weirdo legs and then there's a kid
there we have a names a few of these kids we had kermit we have this kid his name is ronnie stricklin
he said that the alien telepathically told him hey go climb that tree we'll pick you up in 15 minutes
and he's like yes master yes and he starts walking towards the tree now an other kid as well must
have gotten the command because an other kid starts walking towards the tree with ronnie now you have
all of this chaos going on so kids are trying to just not get paralyzed themselves trying to save
their walnut trees they're like this is for my science fair project no everyone's it's basically
every man for themselves so they don't see what ronnie and this other kid are doing at first
but they do end up climbing a tree and they sit up there for 15 minutes so this story supposedly
took place between 2 p.m. and 5 p.m. this was going on i know i've been kind of saying then this
happens and this happens supposedly all of these events took three hours from beginning to end
these must be the worst parents in the world who they're like oh yeah you know kids love to play
the same game for three hours i love to play paralyzed on the ground that's such a popular game
they saw on leave it for beaver oh they love playing that game where they're just petrified
pointing at nothing going please mommy help me oh it's such a great game this goes on for three
hours so they are waiting up in the tree for 15 minutes and then you still have this core group
of kids and they're trying to get this is my favorite part of the story they're trying to get the kids
down from the tree they're like no ronnie no other kid get down get down from the tree i don't know
if it's the same tree as the walnut tree that would be hilarious the other branches getting ready to
break they're like no no i eat walnuts i have to forge those before winter we're going to hibernation
and their kids are just sitting up in the tree so then after 15 minutes a ufo comes down and they
said it's shaped like Saturn so it had like a ball in the middle and this ring around it okay this
is so great i love this oh did i tell you i didn't i did i should say this right now um put you in a
little bit of suspense here but i want to make sure i give credit i have read this story this weekend
and then just the other day chop top on youtube said hey have you ever heard the story of the
casablanca entities and i was like i just read that story but i wanted to give him credit so chop
top thank you for recommending this story he definitely sped it along i probably would have
waited a little bit longer to do this but i want to give i want to give you guys credit when credit
is due so back to the story there's this hovering ball there's this ball with like this Saturn like
ring right and Ronnie and this other kid are standing in this tree sitting in this tree now
little dudes a little little Martian guys are now walking out of the ufo and they're like hanging
off of the Saturn ring reaching for the boys they're like come on get in the ship get in the ship
and Ronnie and the other kid are like hypnotically trying to reach for the aliens
and their friends are like oh my god we're about to watch your friends get kidnapped go to another
planet so how do you get kids out of a tree how do you let me rephrase it how do you quickly get
kids out of the tree my scenario would be just throw stuff at them but i'm an adult so i could
throw hard enough to knock a kid out of a tree i could be like oh this rock will do it and just
like hit him in the ribs and be like but a kid can't throw that hard so they go and they grab a hose
right they go and they grab a hose and they're like hit it and they turn the water on and they
shoot him they're in a tree they're blasting these kids with the hose thinking actually
they're not trying to knock the kids out of the tree they're trying to wake them up so don't throw
rocks if a kid is hypnotized in a tree they start blasting their friends with this hose
and Ronnie's like what he wakes up from his hypnosis and he sees these little guys like
hanging off of the ship and they're like we'll get you next time and Ronnie climbs down the tree
but the other kid is still hypnotized and they're just blasting this kid with this hose and then
and then finally he does he falls he falls out of the tree the aliens can't get him so he falls
out of the tree and then floats through i love this he falls out of the tree he doesn't hit the
ground he floats across the yard and lands on a roof lands on a roof safely so somehow he fell
he started fall he levitates he goes back up because the tree is not as tall as the house
i'm assuming unless it's this giant tree he falls out of the tree he slowly levitates he ends up
on the top of the house walks off the house he walks off the house after just being magically
levitated across the yard these kids are watching their friend they're about to see him fall out of
the tree they're like oh no and then something catches him he slowly glides through the air they're
like oh good and then he just takes a step and falls off the house he lands on his head he falls off
a two-story house presumably even a one-story house but he falls off the house he lands right on his
head and then all the UFOs disappear so that is the story of the Casablanca entities and i'm
reading that i read about it on the cryptopia website which has been a huge resource for this
show in the past like week or two i found a lot of great stories from that and i read it and i go
this there's no way this story is true and i actually had a really hard time finding backup
resources for it and i thought this is the only site where i could find the story i go this is
the most likely fake or the author's just having a joke maybe there's an april fool's story or
something like that but i spent like the past two days every so often i'd kind of go back to it
looking for references and he mentioned a couple authors and he's like this UFO author covered
this story but he wasn't really saying what sources i could find it at and so right before i decided
to do this story today because i was talking to chop-top on youtube decided to do the story today
and originally i was going to say there's only one source for this it's this one website but
i went back revisited his article found the name of an author typed in that name of the
ardor Casablanca entities found a paper he wrote that includes this story along with very well
known UFO story the kelly hopkins story the hopkinsville story or whatever kelly's what it
doesn't matter it's a little goblin story that's fairly well known that there's a house and a
bunch of goblins attack it kelly hopskin it doesn't matter it doesn't matter the point is is that as
stupid as the story is it's very very obscure but it is listed with by it is written about by
reputable authors once i was able to get that author's name a bunch of resources popped up i
think Casablanca is just such a generic name it was really hard to find this stuff but once i was
able to match Casablanca to the author's name found article after article after article detailing
this stuff from again established UFO websites so is this story true again i don't want to sound
like a broken record but either they're making it up someone else made it up they're misinterpreting
real life events or it's true i think those are always the four things we can look at with this
type of story there's no evidence we could go out to see if there's a walnut tree with no branch
but let's assume just for the sake of fun that it's true because again we can't really prove it
either way there is a i had to read this article multiple times and i had to read a bunch of resources
on it there is a through line in this story that makes it genuinely terrifying every single thing
that the aliens do let's presume they're aliens every single thing the aliens do once they show up
is to divide and conquer the ghost shown up around the corner of the house distracted all the kids
so the one kid would start walking towards the ship and while people were focusing on getting the
kid from walking towards the ship the mechanical arm appeared to the one child beckoning him over
there the alien comes out with the guns to paralyze two kids whittling their number down from eight
to six you had the two kids hypnotized instead of hypnotizing all of them it was almost like they
simply wanted any one of those children no one was the particular target but it was all about
distraction and attraction it was a hunt the fact that the parents couldn't see anything makes it even
more creepy because what child wants to live in a world where they are surrounded by dangers that
are invisible to the people who can protect them the most this story has never been replicated as
far as i know there's never been such a massive alien presence in a neighborhood really in two
yards in a football field and a home there's nothing that parallels this why did this happen
in that neighborhood has it happened since or before but more importantly is that a viable
hunting strategy i mean it could have worked in almost any other location a campsite where a kid
is lured off into the bushes another neighborhood where kids don't play in groups but just a kid
walking home alone that's terrifying because it doesn't seem like they're after anyone particular
it seems like they were the alien equivalent of a human predator any child will do
so for all the fun and all the ridiculous stuff that happens in that story that's the terrifying
throughline they were hunting and they came close several times but hunters rarely give up
they may move where they hunt they may change tactics but eventually
they'll bring home that trophy dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address you
can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead rabbit radio dead rabbit
radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every
day but i'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys