For decades, there's been a conspiracy called the Clinton Body Count, a conspiracy that
says people close to Bill and Hillary Clinton have an unfortunate habit of dying.
This conspiracy theory is so popular it's often featured in memes, so why is it that
their latest associate who committed suicide in one of the most bizarre ways is not even
being talked about in the conspiracy theory community?
And then we meet a young woman in Boston who believes that she stumbled upon a nest of vampires.
Well this isn't just a few old monster men hanging out in the city, no.
She's discovered the National Vampire Association, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a great
day too, I hope you guys had a great weekend, we got a ton of stuff to cover so we're gonna
get started.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command, longtime contributor to the Patreon, longtime
supporter of the show, one of the earliest listeners of the show, give it up for Cantillians.
Woo yeah, come on in buddy, come on in, Cantillians.
Cantillians, a really really cool dude and he is in this episode because he sent me a
box of Bigfoot stuff, that's a Bigfoot call alarm.
So I just do that, right?
That's only going to be the sound effect on the show from now on and he sent me some
Bigfoot post-it notes and he sent me a Star Wars best dispenser, I don't know where the
Star Wars best dispenser came from, he sent me a bunch of cool stuff, a little Chewbacca,
that's a Bigfoot dude.
Cantillians, thank you so much, these types of presents always light up my day.
Cantillians, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode, if you guys can't send
me Star Wars best dispensers, that's fine too, just help spread the word about the show,
that really really really helps out a lot, I also gotta say this, this is the last week
of season 18.
So after this week, I will be taking a two week hiatus, feel free to peruse the back
of the catalog, I will just be laying on the couch like a big old lump taking a break from
the show.
But oh, however, I will still be putting out daily TikTok, so subscribe to the YouTube
channel, the TikTok Instagram, wherever you want to look at this stuff, that's not going
away because it'll take like five minutes to do.
So I'll still be doing daily updates on the YouTube channel and all that, those one minute
true crime videos that are really blowing up, they're really really doing good.
Cantillians, let's go ahead and touch the keys to the Jason Jalopy, we are leaving behind
Dead Rabbit Command, we are headed all the way out to Arkansas, we're headed out there
because this is an old school conspiracy theory, I remember back in the 90s, my stepdad totally
100% believed in the Clinton body count, this is an old school conspiracy theory that people
close to the Clintons having nasty habit of dying in very odd ways.
And like I said in the intro, this has become a meme, you can a lot of times show like a
picture of a van on fire and it said they were on their way to deliver some tapes from
Hillary Clinton and they blew up, it's a meme, you'll find a lot of memes about people being
associated with Bill and Hillary Clinton dying.
And you have everything from, I think there was a couple of plane crashes that happened
with people who were connected to them and that's when conspiracy theorists were kind
of like hmm that's kind of interesting.
How many private plane crashes can you have in a row that of all these people Bill and
Hillary Clinton are parachuting down?
And I want to say here too, I mean despite that Hannah Barbera cartoon version of their
friends dying, I'm not even getting into the politics of this thing, I really don't care
about the politics, just looking at the conspiracy theory, just looking at this particular conspiracy
theory, I'm basically accusing them of multiple murders but I'm not talking about politics.
The Clinton body count, it came to my attention and I think this is when it really hit the
mainstream was when Vince Foster, a very close personal friend of the Clintons, specifically
Hillary Clinton, I read a big write, I'll see if I can find it in the show notes but
years ago I read a big write up about Vince Foster.
He was the one, he was a close personal advisor of the Clintons and he got caught up in something
called Travelgate which was basically the conspiracy, this was the Clintons came into
the White House, fired a bunch of people so they could hire their friends to be in charge
of the travel bureau of the White House and this got in the media and it was a big controversy
and apparently he was telling people he was depressed, he didn't want to go back to Arkansas,
holding his head in shame that he got caught up in this so he shot himself.
That's the official story, now you'll hear that he shot himself twice in the back of
the head or he shot himself with two different calibers of guns, that's what I remember hearing
back in the 90s, I remember my stepdad hated the Clintons, he hated their guts so if a
leaf blew the wrong direction he's like "ahhh" so I remember and back then we didn't have
access to the internet, it didn't exist and so you just kind of heard you read stuff in
conspiracy zines or conspiracy books and stuff like that.
I think again the official story is that he shot himself once through the mouth and that
he was telling people he was depressed and the conspiracy theory is like "no that was
a cover" he actually killed himself multiple times but that's just the setup for the conspiracy
body count is this meme and this conspiracy theory supposedly, a bunch of people have
died associated with the Clintons, I'm not denying that but the question is are they
responsible for them?
Long standing boomer conspiracy theory, it'll be around long after they have passed on,
that's why I find this so interesting because it's such an old conspiracy theory and a new
meme that this story I'm about to tell you is jaw-droppingly not reported anywhere in
the conspiracy theory community.
Nowhere and I also think this is interesting because this is an example of the Streisand
effect, I would never have heard of this if a lawsuit had him enfiled trying to cover
up this story.
So on May 7th, 2022 in Perryville, Arkansas, so what is that like last month?
Perryville, Arkansas, this is nuts, you guys are not going to believe you have not heard
this before in the conspiracy community.
Mark Middleton, he was a close advisor to Bill Clinton, he worked with him when Bill
Clinton was in the White House, very very close to the president and a man who was responsible
for letting Jeffrey Epstein into the White House, inviting Jeffrey Epstein into the White
House seven times.
It was Mark Middleton.
Mark Middleton was basically the middle man between Jeffrey Epstein and Bill Clinton when
he came to the White House.
Now, Jeffrey Epstein apparently visited the White House 17 times and seven of those times
was Mark Middleton was bringing him into the White House.
Okay?
Weird.
We all know Jeff Epstein's a monster, anyone connected to him?
Right?
Him being in the White House with President Bill Clinton, weird, totally unsavory, right?
Makes you think about a bunch of stuff.
Bill Clinton was on the low lead express and all that stuff.
But that's not the craziest part of the story.
Because we know those two guys hung out.
We know that Jeffrey Epstein and Bill Clinton hung out.
Mark Middleton was the guy who would bring him into the White House seven out of these
17 times recorded.
Right?
He knows how many times he came and this wasn't recorded.
But anyways, Mark that, now making no side conspiracy theory that they don't write down
everyone's names when they visit the White House.
Mark Middleton on May 7, 2022 killed himself.
He killed himself 30 miles away from his home.
He lived in Perryville.
He 30 miles away, he went to a place called Heifer Ranch or Heifer Ranch, you know, like
the, that big cow from Rocco's modern life.
I think it's Heifer.
Heifer Ranch.
And the authorities, when they get called out for this suicide, they asked, did he,
was he invited here?
And they're like, no, he wasn't even supposed to be here.
We just found him like this.
And they're like, does he have any connection to this place?
And Heifer Ranch is like, no.
Like he might have visited at some point, but why he chose here to kill himself.
We don't know.
But that's not even the weirdest part.
The weirdest part isn't that this guy, he personally knew Jeffrey Epstein and introduced
him to Bill Clinton at least seven times.
The weirdest part isn't that he drove 30 miles to a place that wasn't his home.
The weirdest part is this.
The Vince Foster thing, the official report is he shot himself once through the mouth.
And the conspiracy theory is that he shot himself several times or there was two different
calibers of guns.
There was one gun located, it was like a 38 snub, something like that, that he used to
shoot himself and it was next to his body when he was dead.
That's the official report.
And you can say Jason, no, no, no, that's not the real story.
But that's the official report.
The official report for this story is that Mark Middleton, 59 years old, husband and
father, this is how he killed himself.
He brought a table out to somewhere on this ranch.
So he wanted to be disturbed.
So he brings a table and he has an extension cord, not a rope.
He takes an extension cord and wraps it over a tree, wraps around his neck, pulls out a
shotgun, shoots himself in the chest and then hangs himself.
That's the official report.
That's insane.
That is conspiracy theory fodder.
Now here's the thing.
I am not 100% sane that, oh, this means that the Clintons killed him and this is another
member of the Clinton body count and I'm not even saying that.
What I'm saying is I'm surprised no one else is saying that.
That's what I find really, really shocking.
This was reported, originally it was reported on radar online.
It's a gossip site.
It's a celebrity gossip site.
And their headline was quote, he was murdered.
It was their headline and then it goes on to say, "Bombshell claims surround makeshift
gallows, death of Clintons, special advisor who lets sicko Jeffrey Epstein into White
House."
So there's a little editorializing in that headline, but it's fine.
Radar online is a rag.
That was published like two months ago and nobody picked up on it.
The only reason I knew that this had even happened was the Daily Mail, which again is
a total gossip rag, covered this.
And the reason why it was in the news then is the family of Mark Middleton says we want
an official lock.
We want to seal all the documents regarding this.
We don't want photos getting out.
We don't want video getting out.
We don't want drawings getting out.
We want to tamp this down because they said they were getting harassed by conspiracy theorists
over this.
But I live in this conspiracy theory world.
I stumbled across it one morning reading the news.
I might have even been on Drudge Report, which is fine.
I want this news to be out there, but the conspiracy theory...
I always find it so interesting what the conspiracy theory community focuses on.
Now again, I'm not necessarily saying he's a member of the Clinton body count.
There is a logic behind doing this.
These are both gossip rags, but they're both quoting police documents.
They're not saying...
And then Elvis, who's still alive, came out of the bushes and said this.
They're quoting police documents and the police are like, "We think he wanted to guarantee
that he died."
So he shot himself with a shotgun and then if that didn't work, he would be hung.
There's a twisted and dark logic behind that.
And trust me, I feel really bad for this family and I can understand why they want to seal
these documents.
I'm not saying 100%.
I've always been like, maybe the Clinton body count, maybe there's something behind it.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
Like you can just read lists of things and it looks overwhelming.
I've never been like a super supporter of it or a super denier of it.
It's just because there's so many conspiracies out there.
You've got to kind of pick your ones.
You want to be interested in.
I'm just surprised no one else is talking about this.
That's my thing.
It's super weird.
This is something that people were accusing previous deaths relating to the Clintons 2B.
These just absolutely bizarre.
It's mostly planes falling out of the sky.
They're very easy to sabotage a plane.
And Vince Foster, one where he shot himself multiple times with two guns, tied up and
shot himself.
I heard all sorts of variations.
And then here's one.
The actual police report is so weird.
He shot himself with a shotgun and then hung himself.
That any conspiracy theory, they should have been all over this.
And that's what I find so fascinating.
There's always been that conspiracy theory about conspiracy theories that Flat Earth
is there to take a bunch of people away.
People who would otherwise be looking into other conspiracy theories.
They're looking at dumb stuff like Flat Earth.
Monkeys don't exist.
Trees are mountains.
And they just get wrapped up in that stuff.
And stuff like this just goes on the radar.
Again, I don't know if there's anything to it.
It could just be a man in a moment of desperation killing himself.
What I find weird is that no one else is talking about something this weird.
And something that's well known.
The Clinton body count is a meme at this point.
People who would never ever know the name Vince Foster can see the image of the van
on fire and being like, "We have secret evidence on Hillary Clinton."
And there's just a picture of a van on fire.
They know that this should be fought.
And it's funny because on the one hand, I find it odd that conspiracy theory community
isn't talking about it.
And on the other hand, for the family, it's probably good that they aren't.
Because you know what I mean?
Their family is going through this tragedy.
But fascinating.
The conspiracy theory community, man, if they're anything, they are unpredictable.
You can never really guess what they're going to talk about.
They'll talk about end of the world every single month.
You'll see it just take over whole sectors of the conspiracy theory community.
This happened two months ago.
Nothing.
Tragic story.
And I would never heard of that.
I never would have heard about it if they weren't suing to keep those documents closed.
So that's what we call the stricent effect.
When the harder you try to keep the lid on something, the more likely it is to get out.
Absolutely bizarre mystery, personal tragedy, and just an interesting look at how the conspiracy
theory community works.
What they cover and what they don't is very, very telling.
Very, very telling.
Cantillians.
Cantillians, his corpse, he's been burned.
Oh no!
We covered a Clinton story and they got to him.
Hey, as long as they got to him and not me.
We're going to reanimate him.
We're going to tie strings to his charred corpse and we're going to make him walk onto the
carbon helicopter and we're going to leave behind Arkansas.
We are headed all the way out to Boston, Massachusetts.
The carbon helicopter did break down a couple of times in midair but we were able to keep
it going.
The truth needs to get out.
The truth about this vampire story, I don't know why we would be added to the Clinton
body count.
All we want to do is talk about some vampires.
But in typical Dead Rabbit radio fashion, are we really talking about vampires or are
we talking about something far scarier?
No, not mummies.
We are kind of talking about vampires.
But we're going to take a look at this young woman.
She doesn't give her name in her posts but we're going to call her Pamela.
She goes by the name Butter My Toastitos.
That's her username but we'll get to the end.
At the end she has some toastitos and she's like, "But I have no butter."
We'll get to the end and we'll talk more about the user herself in a second.
And Pamela is someone who is special.
Pamela is someone who has a special ability.
Now we all want to be special in our own way, right?
I think that's part of the human condition but Pamela is definitely more special than
you or me.
She's psychic.
She can read people's minds.
This ability to read people's minds has let her stumble upon something known as the National
Vampire Association.
Pamela tells us this story.
One day she's in Boston and she's walking by Suffolk University.
There's a crowd of people just walking down the street, cars driving by, birds in the air,
sun, high in the sky.
And all of a sudden her psychic powers detect a voice.
A voice above all others in the crowd.
But see, not a voice voice.
It was a telepathic voice.
She heard a voice in her head.
I'm sure you can already see where this is going.
She heard a voice in her head and she turns and she looks.
And she sees a man walking down the street and she hears him in her head going, "I want
to eat you up.
I want to drink your blood but I can't."
The National Vampire Association told me, "I can't eat you."
The guy walks on by.
She turns and she looks and it's just a normal man among all normal people walking through
Boston that day.
But now she knows the truth.
He telepathically told her about the National Vampire Association.
She said once she was walking through Boston, mixed among a sea of ordinary humans, homo-sabians,
some may call us, she hears a voice in her head.
She looks over and she sees a man standing there.
Maybe he's checking his watch, maybe he's hailing a cab, maybe he's...
Other things you can do just standing there?
But she can hear the voice in her head.
His voice.
It's not like she's going crazy or anything, right?
It's not like these voices are in her own head.
It's not like she's schizophrenic or something.
She hears this voice in her head saying, "I want to have sex with you.
I want to have sex with you.
I'm an old vampire."
I promise you I said this part first.
I'm an old vampire.
I know I look like a normal person just standing here checking his watch but no.
I'm an old vampire and I want to have sex with you.
You know whenever I do stuff like that I'm always afraid I'll end up in some dubstep remix.
Perfect sample.
Her stories are this.
She's walking among people.
Totally normal.
None of them ever walk up to her and says, "How do you know about the National Vampire Association?"
Who told you?
How do you know?
It's always her standing next to normal people and then them telling her how much they either
want to have sex with her or how much blood they want to drink from her.
It's constantly going on and she believes that she's psychic and she believes she stumbled
upon this nest of empire.
She says another time she's walking through Boston.
This guy's walking down the street and he says, "Oh, how I want to drag you into the
alley and drink your blood.
You're so tasty.
I want to drink you up."
But the National Vampire Association told me I couldn't confound them.
This is creepy.
We've covered a lot of this type of stuff on the show, right?
But a lot of times it's gangstalking.
A lot of times it's like the military beaming stuff into people's heads.
I can't really think of a time where the gangstalkers themselves are supernatural.
These people aren't necessarily gangstalking her, but what she's created or what this mental
illness has created is a worldview where she is such a tasty bite that random vampires walking
down the street want to eat her.
She's hearing them and she's able to look at someone and go, "I'm reading his mind."
It's not like she just hears the voices in her head.
She is hearing the voices in her head, but she's also projecting it on this guy and she
goes, "That guy wants to eat me right now.
That guy wants to drink my blood."
One point she goes to Japan and she's in Osaka, Japan and she meets these two people at a
bar and they telepathically tell her they want to cut her wrist open and make her strip.
It's interesting because she keeps going back between the violent death of the victim of
a vampire and sexuality and raw sensual activities.
Her brain goes back and she's connecting these pathways and that's a really bad place to
be in when you start connecting violent thoughts, sexual pleasure and just random people.
I'm pretty sure that's a recipe for a serial killer.
So anyways, she's walking around, she's telepathically hearing all of these voices.
At one point her friend is with her and a vampire passes them.
This is the only time we kind of get an idea.
She says she was 17 in this story in this little anecdote.
Later on she's at college, so I think she's probably in her late teens, you know, 18,
19, maybe up to 22, something like that.
But when she was 17 she was still able to detect these vampires and her and her friend
are walking past this random guy and he goes, "Oh, I want to eat your friend up."
And she goes, "Why not me?
Why not me?"
She telepathically sends that back to him and then the man, the quote unquote, the voice
in her head responds, "She eats vegetables.
She's a vegetarian.
She tastes better."
And I'm like, "Hmm, interesting.
Interesting tidbit that my mind has fooled me into believing?"
Here's the thing, here's the thing, she definitely is suffering from some sort of mental delusion.
And right now in this story that she's written, she's thinking random people are vampires.
It's alarming because she thinks the vampires either want to drink blood from her and she
doesn't seem particularly afraid of that or have sex with her or both.
So unless she's watching like, Buffy 24 hours a day, I don't think she's going to snap in
the sense that she has to hunt these vampires down.
She doesn't seem particularly perturbed that these vampires exist or that they constantly
want to keep drinking her blood because in the end she's special.
Right?
Imagine being so special that not only are you psychic, that you are protected by the
National Vampire Association.
Basically she's Belle.
Is it Belle or Bella?
Who was the girl from Twilight?
I don't remember.
Whatever her name was.
Tracy?
Her.
You're that character from Twilight and everyone wants to eat you but nobody can because you're
special.
Obviously an undiagnosed mental illness is only going to get worse, right?
With treatment a lot of them can get better.
But if you're not even getting treated for this stuff and if you start to believe that
it's true and you think that these random people are sending you these thoughts, what's
the end result?
Well let's jump ahead.
It's really interesting too because you can go Jason, you've talked about vampires, you
kind of believe in vampires, you believe that it's possible.
Yeah, sure.
I used to play Vampire the Masquerade.
I love that role-playing game.
I do love vampires, right?
It would be awesome if vampires existed.
It would be awesome if there was a National Vampire Association.
It would be dope.
Don't get me wrong.
I believe in psychics.
I believe a lot of them are scam artists but not all of them, right?
I believe in telepathy.
So it has all the elements of stuff that I actually believe.
Why are you so dismissive of this young woman?
Well let's jump ahead.
This is actually her last post.
She posted that about two years ago.
And then one year ago she posted this.
This is the headline of this post.
"I'm coming here for help."
She actually tried posting this on a couple different subreddits.
She was posting this on the conspiracy subreddit but she also tried posting it on the DID subreddit
which I think is Disassociative Identity Disorder.
So this point she knows something's wrong.
Remember the start?
Probably before 17 she realized she was psychic.
She's doing the psychic thing for a while.
She thinks it's totally normal.
Two years ago she wrote the one about the National Vampire Association.
One year later and one year behind us she wrote, "I'm coming here for help.
I've been possessed by the United States Air Force."
I don't want to laugh but that's just a great title.
If I was in an alt rock emo band I think that might be the name of it.
But I've been possessed by the United States Air Force and she goes on to say that what
has happened was since November 2019 what happened was she lost control over her body.
Now not all the time and not total control but it was enough for her to be worried.
She was no longer able to move her arms and her legs when she wanted to.
It was almost like she had to ask permission.
It was almost like she had to fight against something and she is telepathically told that
she's getting these thoughts beamed into her head when she's like, "Why can't I move?
Who's doing this?"
The voice said, "We're the United States Air Force and you belong to us now."
She's all walking in a recruiting center.
She's like, "No, no it's trying to make her salute."
Next thing you know she's flying a fighter jet.
The United States Air Force has possessed her and so here we go.
This is what we were worrying about when this young lady was saying telepathically vampires
are saying they wanted to kill her but she's just like, "Oh you monsters.
The National Vampire Association won't let you do that."
And they're like, "Oh Zoinks foiled again."
Now she says that the United States Air Force possessed her and made her drive 125 miles
an hour down the road.
You got a need for speed.
The Air Force is going to do anything.
They're going to make you drive fast.
They made her drive 125 miles an hour down the road and crash her car.
She survived, which is good, but she said the United States Air Force did that.
That wasn't her.
She even, this is weird, right?
She's typing this out on the conspiracy subreddit.
They took it off the DID one.
They just said, "Go get help.
This isn't the place for this.
Go get some mental help.
This is like a reddit, right?
This is not a replacement for real medical help."
The conspiracy subreddit, they put up all sorts of stuff.
But anyways, she says when she's writing this post, she goes, "I'm not even typing out this
post.
Like I've lost control of my fingers.
The Air Force is making me write this."
This is interesting, right?
We talk about memetic diseases.
We talk about curses online.
Like was the United States Air Force making her write this post?
This is so absurd.
How did I start saying it out loud?
Is the United States Air Force making her write out this post so if other people read
it, they also get possessed by the Air Force?
I don't know.
Probably not.
I don't actually think this woman was possessed by one of the five branches of the US military.
It's weird too, right?
I can understand believing in vampires.
Vampires existing, wanting to drink your blood, wanting to have sex.
That all fits the vampire mythos.
Why would the United States Air Force possess you?
I mean, again, it makes you special, right?
But why would they do that?
Well, apparently, they're just doing it as like a flex.
They're doing it to just show how powerful they are.
And then she goes, "It's not just me, by the way.
It's not just me that they're possessing.
They also possessed my friend."
Now this is interesting.
I don't know if this is a, what do they call it, a folly, a do, which is a mental illness
shared by two or more people.
And her friend is also suffering from mental illness.
Or if at this point Pamela is full on hallucinating things.
Because if she can hallucinate a telepathic conversation, she says her friend told her
this, but now that I'm thinking, I wonder if her friend telepathically told her this.
She said the United States Air Force also possessed my friend and made her almost get
hit by a fire engine.
Like, there's a fire engine running down the road and tried to make her walk in front
of the fire engine, but she fought back the air force.
And then she said this, which so what have we faced so far?
High speed, car crash, force to get almost ran over by a fire engine, posting on Reddit.
Those are all three horrible things, right?
Those are all three of the worst things you could possibly imagine.
But then her friend, this is also one of her friend's punishments.
So we'll just read this quote here.
The United States Air Force quote forced, forced her by the way, this was not her, this
sounds like the greatest excuse ever, forced her, meaning the friend, United States Air
Force quote, forced her to eat a cheesecake piece and forced her to say, I like cheesecake
to her family.
Unquote.
That's kind of a cool possession, right?
I guess we're going to get possessed to do anything.
You just eat, just eat cheesecake.
Maybe she was lactose intolerant.
Maybe she was like, oh, my stomach hurts and the United States Air Force is laughing.
The mom's like, if you like cheesecake, honey, I thought it made you sick, but here's even
more and you're like, no, no, that's possible.
It's not written down.
It's not in the details.
So I just have to assume that she eats some cheesecake.
That's not a bad punishment at all.
They're like, Jason, we control you.
Go to Taco Bell every single day.
I'm like, you monsters with a big smile on my face.
So we have her wrapped up in this vampire conspiracy theory.
No one's really being hurt.
And then we go tour a year after that.
She's driving a car 125 miles an hour down the road intentionally gets in a crash.
The United States Air Force did this.
Really her last post, there's two final posts and this butter my toast, Thitos has not appeared.
Online sense.
Last post was a year ago or these last two posts were a year ago where people are like,
you need mental help.
Like the even the conspiracy board, they weren't like, tell us more, tell us more.
I also don't trust the government.
They're like, it sounds like you need help.
It sounds like you're going through some sort of mental health struggle.
And this is her second to last post.
Quote, I don't know what to do.
This person in my body is dangerous.
They threaten to stab me and my family all the time.
Do you have alters you can't physically control that threatened violence?
So now she now we're talking about homicide and suicidal.
I wouldn't even say this was ideation like she's trying to fight the urge to kill everyone
and herself.
Let's say it's a battle.
It doesn't sound like it's just like, oh, I wonder what would happen if I killed my girlfriend.
Type of thing.
She's trying to stop it.
And then that this is when people go, you need to go to a hospital.
Like you need to go and the very last post said, I'm going to the ER today.
And then she hasn't been online since we cover stories like this.
We've covered a lot recently.
I hope I'm not falling in.
We're right.
I find this stuff so fascinating because we talk about true crime most of the time after
the fact.
And in stories like this, we can see that buildup and we don't know what happened to this person.
Someone stabbing another person in the city of Boston.
It's just 3 p.m. on a Wednesday, right?
It's a violent city.
Most big cities are violent cities.
It wouldn't even be in the news.
If a young girl slaughtered her entire family, it'd be in the news, maybe.
But if a young woman grabbed a knife and just started slashing at people and the cops came
and they sprayed her with maize and taster and dragged her out, you would never know.
It might be a local news story, depending on what else was going on that day.
So we don't know how the story ends.
She's never posted since.
She may pop up and start ranting about some crazy stuff.
She may pop up and be like, "Yeah, I was really dealing with some hardcore mental illness
for a while, but I'm doing better.
I'm on the journey for healing."
We don't know.
We don't know how this story ended in real life.
I just find it an interesting reminder at the look of that precipice.
Honestly, we are all on.
Because if you take apart everything she said, a lot of us believe in the individual parts.
All she did was put them together.
Most people who believe in the paranormal believe in stuff like telepathy, psychics,
vampires, possession, experimental government, machinery, conspiracies within the government,
black book projects within the government where they're testing all this stuff.
We believe in pretty much all that stuff.
I guess I can't speak for you, but individually, if someone said there's a conspiracy theory
that the United States Air Force is trying to build mind control rays, most people wouldn't
blink at that.
We'd go, "Oh, that makes sense because I don't trust the government."
And it sounds like something you would do.
Right?
Did you know that human bodies can get possessed by some other world entity and can make you
want to do violent things?
Hasn't it told me that?
My head's spinning around and throwing up everywhere.
I was like, "Nope.
Never heard that.
I don't trust the government."
I was like, "Well, I don't trust the government."
I was
And since we already had, and I'm not judging, right?
I'm not judging, but I'm not judging.
I'm not judging.