A new computer program has shady origins.
A long time ago we covered the conspiracy theory that Bugs Bunny is actually a Native American
deity.
We have a bizarre update to that story.
And then we take a look at the bizarre scientific phenomenon when Deaf Schizophrenic hear voices.
What do they hear?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter and I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys had an awesome Halloween.
I know that I did or did...
I don't know, it's still Halloween.
I'm recording this episode right after the last one.
I haven't officially had my Halloween yet, but I will not go on a Halloween rant.
I hope it's good.
Right now it's 2PM October 31st 2021.
So that's when I'm recording this.
And hopefully it's a really cool Halloween.
This is the segment they play after their local man got shot, ran over and stabbed
to death in a one man mass casualty event.
And they'll just play that at the beginning.
They're like, "It started off as such a good day for body casters Jason Carpenter until
he walked outside and then all that bad stuff happened."
Something that's not bad is giving a hand to one of our legacy Patreons.
Coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now.
Give it up for Devin Bracken.
Everyone give him a hand.
He's walking and driving his semi with a knife in his hand.
I'm like, "Gulp."
Devin, you're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support the Patreon, I totally understand.
Just hope you spread the word about the show.
Really, really helps out a lot.
You guys have no idea just by telling people about the show how much that gets the show
to grow.
It's so important for you guys to do that.
Devin, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are flying all the way out to Columbia.
I was watching YouTube the other day watching I have my ad blocker uninstalled so I can
support my favorite YouTubers by watching their ads.
Otherwise, if I was not a YouTuber, I would have ad block installed.
But it is nice when people shut it up.
So I shut it up.
This ad popped up and I thought you dirty, dirty rats.
That wasn't the name of the product they were selling.
It wasn't as equal to Hungry Hungry at Pose.
I'm watching this ad and I knew immediately what I was watching was a product that was
designed.
Okay, let me back up here for a second.
Allegedly.
That sounded super.
I am 100% reserved.
Allegedly.
I am very, very, very allegedly sure that there is a new app that is out or style of
app and I go to the CIA developed that app.
I mean 100% this thing was designed in DARPA and CIA had their hands all over it.
It is an app that by simply using your cell phone, some of you guys may be really familiar
with it.
Some of you may use it.
It's ingenious, really.
By using your cell phone's camera, you can create a perfect 3D replica of a room you're
standing in.
And they show it.
They're like, "It's easy as one.
It's easy as C-I-A."
And they have this camera and all you do is you kind of move it around the room and then
you go back and you go back to Quantico, you go back to wherever you're based out of and
you can have a perfect 3D layout over some of them in London's bedroom.
It's ingenious and I'm sure that on the ad they show the guy kind of hovering, kind of
like moving the camera slowly around the room.
I'm sure that's the consumer version.
Because I'll tell you this right now.
Any criminal worth their salt is using this app.
Anyone who's doing any sort of job that has any sort of inside job applications, obviously
like smash and grab, it might be good to know what the front of Mervins looks like, but
you're driving your car through glass doors.
I don't think you're worried about square footage.
But if you're doing anything, you're going over to a friend's house and that friend's
selling drugs but you know he doesn't have any backup.
Like it's just him and his boys and you know they're just kind of punks.
You go, "I'm not encouraging this behavior."
But if you know you can steal from him and he's not going to get back, he's not going
to come back to you, right?
And he's not really a friend.
He's more of an acquaintance.
You walk in his house and you would get a perfect layout of his house.
So then when you did go decide to talk to him, you knew where it was.
Like you're putting in, you're making it like the Sims.
You're having all these people walk around and give you drugs.
You're like, "I'm the best drug dealer in the world in the Sims."
But yeah, dude, that's actually super creepy.
I didn't think about the whole like sexual crime thing.
I was thinking more of like home invasions.
Kids can like go over to girls' houses and like break in and then make a total map of
the house and then build a sim of them.
I mean, they're already in the house, right?
They could probably do something far more creepy, but I didn't want to think about that.
But yeah, so with this program, you can map out a house perfectly.
I'm sure the original CIA version, you didn't have Jason Bourne wasn't sitting there going
like, "Excuse me, sir.
We're trying to get a signal in your house."
And he's like turning around in circles.
I'm sure it's much easier, but yeah, and it's better than a photo.
And you can actually have furniture.
You can drag and drop into the house.
So you'd be like, "No, someone's bed wasn't that big.
It was a full.
It wasn't a queen."
So you get perfect of this 100% of CIA.
And I don't know if they developed...
Let me back up.
I'm pretty sure they developed it.
I'm wondering if they just said, "We're going to make this CIA run out of money.
We've got to buy a new pair of spy shoes."
So they decided that maybe they're getting a percentage of each sale of this, or if
the technologist just got out there.
For all I know, the Chinese sold it from the CIA and then they released it.
And so now, because there's a ton of different apps that do this now.
But the one main app I saw was...
I'm never going to name the website.
I'm not going to name the website because I'm making some pretty bold claims here.
It's cia.gov.
It's now also selling apps to do home remodeling.
But yeah, it's my conspiracy theory.
I'm pretty sure it's accurate.
If it's...
Let's say it went the other way around.
Let's say some dude in Idaho developed this app with his buddies and they took it to the
private sector and they were looking...
100%.
100% the CIA would have contacted them and say, "We're going to have a meeting first."
Because the technology can be used...
Think about all the horrible ways I came up with just sitting in my closet.
I mean, a terrorist could go in and map out a bank, an embassy.
So if it was not developed in-house by the CIA, whoever did develop had a very, very
long meeting with government officials and they got first look at it.
I think it's been being used for a while.
Yeah.
Super, super interesting.
I also find it very, very suspicious that when I'm not watching ads on YouTube to support
my favorite YouTubers and thinking that it's CIA- oh, CIA funded ads.
Every so often, I have not been able to figure out what triggers this, but every so often,
YouTube will constantly show me videos for schizophrenia medicine.
It's a weird loop it'll get into.
Pandora started doing it the other day as well.
If I was a more paranoid person, I might think something, but I'm not.
So I just think it's odd.
But a paranoid person could go, "Oh my God, are they listening to me?
Are they driving me crazy?"
There's an app for that.
There probably is an app that could drive you crazy, but we will talk about that when
I am on the verge of losing my mind because I went too far into the Google App Store.
Kane, let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jollopi.
We are leaving behind Columbia.
Oh, I forgot we were going to Columbia because we were going to be CIA agents.
I had this whole thing planned out.
We were going to be CIA agents.
We were walking around some drug lords' house, and then I totally forgot.
So the drug lords just stand there and he's like, "Hi."
And then we get in the car and drive away.
"Devin, go ahead and drive us away from this now angry Colombian drug lord.
We're headed all the way out to Dead Man's Curve."
Dead Man's Curve is this road in the Hollywood area.
But in a two-year period had 25 accidents.
Super dangerous curve.
And this was back in the '60s.
So back then, windows and cars were made out of glass and seatbelts.
I don't even think we're optional.
I just don't even think they were invented at that time.
So a car accident back then was pretty brutal.
It's January 24th, 1961 in Mel Blanc.
Mel Blanc.
You guys should know who he is, but maybe younger people don't.
He's a voice actor.
He's the voice of Bugs Bunny.
He's the voice of that dumb bird.
What was his name?
Not Woody Woodpecker, the little yellow one.
Not Woodstock.
The other one, Tweety.
Tweety.
Tweety Bird.
He was the voice of so many other voices.
I didn't write him down.
I forgot to write down.
I don't know.
Maybe he did Huckleberry Hounds and Porky Pig and stuff like that.
But he's done tons of voices.
A lot of them.
So many that I just assumed you would know his name.
And he's driving around Dead Man's Curve.
And the curve, it got a little too dead man for him.
Huge car accident.
Pssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss
That's a predicament.
I can't even think of a celebrity nowadays that would be the equivalent of Mel Blanc.
Because he was in all these cartoons and you grew up with the cartoons and your kids were
growing up with the cartoons in 1961.
There's no one like that today like a Brad Pitt gone in accident.
People would be sad, right?
But would the nation go into mourning?
Now to be fair I don't know if Mel Blanc, I don't know if Mel Blanc's coma.
I don't know if they lowered the flags to have staff.
I know that I would have been totally gutted but I wasn't alive in 1961.
But anyways, he's the voice of several generations.
He's in a coma and 14 days he's just laying there asleep and stuff.
Brain is not working.
And a doctor walks in and goes, "Bugs Bunny, how are you doing today?"
Just kind of a joke.
It says in the articles he was testing an experiment but I think he was just being
kind of a jerk.
He goes, "Bugs Bunny, how are you doing today?"
And Mel Blanc goes, "Ahhh, what's up doc?"
And the doctor realizes, wait a second, we've been trying to communicate with this guy for
14 days.
This is a 1961 level medical technology.
This guy's lucky he's even alive right now.
The doctor's flabbergasted.
He goes, "We've been trying to communicate with this guy for days now but let me try
another thing."
He goes, "Tweetie, can you hear me?"
And then Mel Blanc goes, "I taught I taught, puttycat."
So they realize that he can communicate.
This is true story.
I did not believe when this was sent to me.
I'll get into that in a second.
I did not believe.
I did not believe in the first question.
I think it said, "Interesting, what is your source for this?"
This is a true story.
He could only talk in cartoon voices.
Not till this day, right?
It's not like you're trying to have a conversation with him and he's like, "Why ought to shoot
you in the face?"
He's like, "Oh, it's your Sam and Sam."
He got better.
Within two months later he stopped talking in cartoon quotes.
He's like, "Aye, Arriva, Arriva!"
He's running around the hospital and they're like, "Oh no, he's speeding and tall as now."
He didn't get the powers.
He didn't get the powers of the characters either.
I don't know why I've added that detail.
Where's Mel Blanc?
He dug out of his room.
He's like, "I'm digging into Albuquerque."
He's eating carrots.
Anyways, two months later he makes a full recovery.
The only thing that isn't recovered is his body.
He's in a full body cast and they have to wheel him home and he gets better and he actually
soothes the city.
He goes, "Listen, Dead Man's Curve.
I was the 26th accident on there.
I almost died.
Soothes the city wins."
They have to fix the road.
They have to fix Dead Man's Curve.
The reason is a very, very interesting story, just like a weird tidbit of how the human
mind works.
But I was sent this story on the Dead Rabbit Radio subreddit by iteration 19.
Iteration 19 sent this over.
Really, really appreciate it.
And they sent it over in the context of, "This is an update to a story you did a long time
ago.
It was episode 140."
Can you believe that?
140.
It was that 600 episodes ago.
Is Bugs Bunny, this is the name of the episode, is Bugs Bunny really a Native American deity?
I really like that episode.
It's a really fun one.
It takes a look at just a bizarre conspiracy theory that was going around.
I think it was on the iceberg.
But the idea was, and that one, that Bugs Bunny, if I remember correctly, if Bugs Bunny is
the representation of an ancient Native American trickster spirit.
And it has moved through our reality.
It was never a fictional character.
It's part of our reality.
And what we have done is we have avatarred it.
We've created a physical form or thought form of this deity.
It used to be a trickster bunny in olden times.
And now it's the wisecrackin' Bugs Bunny character.
And it needed the creators to navigate its life cycle.
Because they didn't want to be like Felix the cat.
No one knows who that is.
Or Betty Boop, who just appears on women's handbags nowadays.
Bugs Bunny is an icon.
He's an icon.
And I would argue Bugs Bunny is more popular than Mickey Mouse.
Let me back that up.
I will argue Bugs Bunny is a better character than Mickey Mouse.
Maybe not more popular, but Bugs Bunny always seem to have more of a complex character as
opposed to the other like Felix the cat or Mickey Mouse or Betty Boop and stuff like
that.
So the fact that there's not much Mickey Mouse stuff in production except for little kid
things.
And Bugs Bunny just had a movie come out last year.
Was it this year?
Space Jam 2.
So Bugs Bunny is this, this was the theory.
Bugs Bunny is this enduring spirit that has become part of our reality and we worship
it now with these Bugs Bunny hats and these Bugs Bunny cartoons.
Oh, I want a Bugs Bunny to be my birthday and what we're really doing is praying to
this ancient native deity.
It's kind of the episode in a nutshell.
600 episodes, I'm just going off my memory.
And this is an interesting sign out to that because if I remember correctly in that episode,
the animators at Warner Brothers had to give this thing a life and like they were talking
about how its personality changed.
Bugs Bunny was originally a different character and slowly morphed and the theory was that
was the spirit making the physical representation of it fit more to its spirit.
Basically the idea wasn't an original idea like friends, let's make a show about seven
people coming to New York.
No, the coffee shop, this idea and that may be guided by writers and the actors, they
cast and all that stuff.
But this one, you had this deity who was navigating them.
Everything was left up to chance.
The spirit was controlling them.
And Mel Blanc was the voice of Bugs Bunny.
And after this accident, he continued to work in animation doing the voice of Bugs Bunny
for an additional 30 years, which is massive.
Obviously we have a new Bugs Bunny nowadays.
We have a new voice, but they are doing an imitation of the Mel Blanc voice.
Had he died earlier in his career, they would have had to hire someone else.
And that voice would have been different.
It may have not been the voice the spirit assigned to itself.
It's earthly vessel.
It's messenger on earth.
But when it's messenger was struck down in this tragic car accident, it may have been
locked in Mel Blanc's brain as well.
And that is why he did not answer to Mel when the loved ones were coming in, when the friends
and family were coming in to talk to Mel.
He's in that coma.
It took someone talking to Bugs Bunny to bring him back into our world.
And Bugs Bunny was once again able to have its image worshiped all over the planet.
Interesting conspiracy theory.
I really love covering weird stuff like that in iteration 19.
This is a really cool update to that.
Thank you very much.
I love the idea of thinking what if after that point it was no longer Mel Blanc.
Bugs Bunny was in control of that body.
However, I have absolutely no proof of any of that.
I don't know really much about Mel Blanc other than he voiced Bugs Bunny.
The only reason I know he voiced Tweety Bird because the doctor talked to him and he got
in a car accident.
That's pretty much I'm limited to my Mel Blanc knowledge.
Devon, let's go ahead and touch the keys of the carbon or car.
We are leaving behind Dead Man's Curve, which is a much safer place to drive nowadays.
We are headed all the way out to London.
[imitates car engine]
Specifically, we're going to the University College London.
And then we're going to meet a woman known as Joanna Atkinson.
She's the clinical psychologist based at that college and she's deaf.
This store, I got the bulk of my information from an amazing article written by Jemima
Atkinson for mosaicscience.com.
It's a really, really interesting article and the headline really says it all.
Can deaf people hear voices?
What Jemima is writing about is deaf schizophrenic people.
When they have auditory hallucinations, how do they hallucinate?
And it's one of those questions that the second you ask it, you have to know the answer.
I know I promised it on yesterday's episode and you're like, "Oh, I can't wait to hear
that and now you're listening to it now, so thanks for your patience."
You might have just looked it up.
In the meantime, can deaf people hear voices?
This article for mosaicscience.com, we're going to talk about...
50% we're going to talk about some stats and then we're going to get into Joanna Atkinson's
research on it as well.
It's just very, very fascinating.
The current scientific consensus on the question, do schizophrenic deaf people hear voices?
Deaf people hear auditory hallucinations is...
Yes.
50% of deaf people with schizophrenia hear voices.
But how do they hear them?
What's the mechanism there?
And obviously, when you have deaf people, you have people who were born deaf, who have
never heard anything.
Then you have people who go deaf, either due to industrial accident, ice pick through
the ear, or just...
It doesn't have to be...
It doesn't have to be that dynamic.
It could just be getting old.
But you have people who have heard throughout their life, but now they're considered deaf.
If you look at the research, it says that 50% of schizophrenics who are deaf hear voices.
And when they are talking to their doctors, they use words like "loud."
They use words like a whisper.
So volume.
And so the doctors go, "Well, if you're talking about volume, there's auditory."
Sign language doesn't really have a volume.
You can't whisper and sign.
You can yell and sign by signing very frantically.
You can yell, right?
In sign language.
So where were these things coming from?
Where were these volume words coming from?
So Joanna Atkinson, who is a clinical psychologist and she's deaf herself, she is looking at
these studies and she goes, "This cannot be accurate."
A person who has never heard noise at all, any words ever their entire life they were
born deaf cannot hallucinate a voice.
It's impossible.
So she starts digging into this.
She goes, "It doesn't make any sense."
Now for us who have hearing, we can imagine what it's like to be deaf.
But then, even if you're imagining what it's like to be deaf, you still can have a running
monologue in your head.
You can still imagine voices.
Because we've heard them.
We can imagine what it would be like to be deaf.
We can maybe close off our senses in like a tube that we have no sense of sound, no sense
of touch.
But we have inner thought, which are words that we've heard.
Super fascinating.
So this is what she figured out.
When a deaf person is talking to a hearing doctor, there is a translation error.
Because when a deaf schizophrenic is talking to a deaf doctor and they're using sign language,
there are no volume words.
There are none.
So it was a translation error.
The general scientific consensus was, "This is happening.
We don't know how, but when she says if there are deaf patients and deaf doctors, 100%,
they do not hear auditory hallucinations."
This is what her research said.
Deaf people who had never heard did not experience true auditory hallucinations.
But they still have hallucinations.
Because they're suffering from schizophrenia.
Now when you have these voices in your head, and we've covered these before on our show,
we've covered them before on our show.
And just in general knowledge, I think people have an idea of the stereotypical schizophrenia.
But these voices are telling you, "You're awful.
You're a horrible person.
No one's ever going to love you."
Like the CIA is coming after you, all of this stuff, right?
You start to have these voices in your head.
You're worthless.
You're nothing.
But they can't hear voices.
But the schizophrenia still, the mental illness still wants to convince them that they are
useless.
So what they, what they're, this is fascinating.
What their brain does is they hallucinate arms doing sign language in front of them.
It's a visual hallucination.
But it's talking to them.
You're useless.
Isn't that creepy?
Your brain wants to punish you so much when you're in the grip of this mental illness.
But it can't punish you with words because you don't understand audio hallucinations.
So hands will appear in front of you and make sign language telling you, "You're a piece
of trash and no one loves you.
You should just kill yourself."
The government is watching you right now.
If you don't leave the house within the next three minutes, it will explode.
You're seeing this.
So fascinating.
So if you've never heard anything in your life, they said, "What you'll see is you'll
see arms appear in front of you."
And they'll start doing sign language or you'll see a pair of lips appear in front of you
if you're adept at reading lips.
Now they said, "If I'm hallucinating, but involve someone I know, I'll see them.
I'll see them in front of me doing sign language telling me, 'I never loved you.
You're a horrible, horrible person.'"
This one patient would hallucinate her mother's lips.
Just her mother's lips floating there.
I would write if you're asking me to choose between hearing voices telling me I'm trash
or seeing my mom's lips float around me telling me the same thing.
I'm choosing the voices.
And then think about it.
Those are the people who have never heard anything.
What about the people who used to be able to hear and now they're deaf?
What do they hallucinate?
Do they also see the arms doing the sign language?
Oddly enough, no.
If you've never heard a single word in your life, it can't give you an auditory hallucination.
So it signs to you and tells you you're worthless.
If you used to be able to hear and you're fluent in sign language, you lost your hearing
when you were 30.
You're 52 now.
You're fluent in sign language.
You're a huge part of the deaf and hard of hearing community.
And you have schizophrenia.
You don't see the hands.
You hear voices.
But you haven't heard anything for 20 years.
You can hear the voices, but you can't understand what they're saying.
It's almost like the...
Because think about it.
If someone hasn't heard anything for 30 years and you wanted to communicate a message with
them, the path of least resistance would be to do the sign language.
But the voice, this outside voice wants to be heard so badly, it defaults to that.
Instead of doing the visual hallucination, it will talk to you, but you can't understand
it because you haven't heard anything for years.
So it's just mumbling coming from somewhere around you.
I don't know.
I know I've been diagnosed with schizophrenia and I hear voices when no one's around.
What do they say?
I don't know.
So why don't the voices talk to them on the side?
It's so determined to talk to people who have in depth since birth that it creates this
bizarre hallucination.
It's your mind's eye showing these complex symbols, hands making these symbols.
And I'm wondering, are they even human hands?
Like if you are...
We covered this a long time ago.
They had the program where you could...
People who had schizophrenia, people who were hearing voices, you were able to build a digital
avatar of that voice.
I'll put that on the show notes.
It was really cool, but it's a technique they're using.
And they could actually make the face look like the voice was really weird.
And all the faces looked really evil.
The ones they showed for photos of.
So like with the arms, were they masculine arms?
Are they feminine arms?
Assuming they didn't know who the person was.
If they know they're hallucinating about a person, it's them.
But were they human arms?
Reaching out from the darkness, telling you how horrible you are, how no one loves you?
Then there's a third group.
A third group of people who I, in a Venn diagram of any subculture, I would just not...
I would not put them in the Venn diagram.
I didn't know they existed.
Especially in one, because obviously deaf and hard of hearing, it's a subculture.
And now we're looking at a subculture of that, people who are deaf with schizophrenia.
And there is a subculture of that.
Well you have people who are deaf with schizophrenia, who are born deaf.
You have people who, over time, became deaf.
And then you have a third group, a group of people, quote, who had reached adulthood without
learning any formal language.
Unquote.
So not only do they not know American sign language very well, they don't know how to
speak at all.
Apparently there is a crossover.
You had enough of them to study who were deaf and had schizophrenia and had learned no language
at all.
They learned sign.
The reason why Joanna was able to communicate with them was later in life they learned sign
language, but they weren't fluent.
And they had no...
It says without learning any formal language.
So maybe they were like, "Oh shucks, come on down to the well and let's beat up some
beekeepers."
Or some, "I don't know, I don't know."
Maybe some weird hillbilly speak or something.
No formal language without learning any formal language.
So how do they get thoughts telling them they're worthless and the CIA is about to kill them
for beating up all those beekeepers in Louisiana?
No talking?
They don't have any language, right?
No formal language.
No talking.
And their sign language isn't up to par so they're not able to have the sign language.
They just see an angry face staring at them.
Scowling.
It doesn't speak.
It just stares.
That is...
I mean, that would have to be the most unsettling of all, right?
At least if it was speaking you could kind of have an argument with it.
You could try to fight it off, but you could just see your mental illness personified as
this face in front of you because you don't have any communication skills.
You're...
That's what's so fascinating and tragic about illnesses like schizophrenia.
Your brain wants to punish you so badly that it will get you no matter what.
Now again, I 100% am an advocate of professional help.
That is a hill I'm willing to die on.
You may have had a bad experience with a counselor and I always tell people...
People have good counselors, people have bad counselors.
I say it's like picking a boyfriend or a girlfriend.
You don't go with the first one, right?
You're a pair in a spare.
That's what they say, right?
You should have two counselors you should talk to and then one on the side if this
one gets a little...
It starts raining a little too much down in your notebook.
No, in all seriousness, you should get this stuff.
There's no shame in being treated for...
It's an illness.
It's like having a runny nose or having a stomach ache.
No one has gout and goes, "Nah, I'm good.
I'm good.
I can't turn my neck much and everything's super painful, but I'm not going to go to
the doctor."
You can't do that and normal people go, "Dude, that's so gross.
Your gout is exploding all over my Caesar salad."
With mental illness a lot of times because we don't see it until it's stuff's really
bad.
We just put it off and then other people don't encourage others.
I personally see no shame.
You know what I mean?
I think it's creepy that your brain wants to get you so badly it will do whatever it
takes to get you.
If you can hear, it'll give you horrible, horrible auditory hallucinations.
If you used to be able to hear, it'll still try to give them to you, but you can't hear
them luckily.
You just hear this mumbling.
You don't hear these horrible words, but then you can't hear it all.
It will make you hallucinate.
I just think it's creepy.
It doesn't matter how you access information, how you're able to have your senses work.
It will get you.
It'll make you have auditory hallucinations.
Oh, you can't hear.
You're going to have visual hallucinations of me telling you your trash.
Oh, you don't understand the language.
I'm just going to project a horrifying face in front of you, showing you how disgusted
I am that you exist.
It won't let go.
And you have to imagine like what if someone was blind and deaf and schizophrenic, had never
seen anything or heard anything, and was suffering from a mental illness this severe.
What could the brain possibly conjure up?
It would think of something.
It would think of something we couldn't even comprehend.
Dementia is a real life illness that needs to be treated by professionals.
It is a serious illness.
If you suffer from it, you should continue to seek help.
But when we talk about things like this, it really, really makes you see why people often
do confuse mental illnesses with demonic possession.
Because this sounds demonic.
No matter what you do, no matter who you are, it will punish you.
It will make you see things.
It will make you hear things.
Whether or not you can see or hear is irrelevant to this illness.
It will push you to the limits.
It will try to break you down.
It will try to destroy you.
It will try to destroy your will to live.
And if that doesn't sound demonic, I don't know what is.
It will try to break you down.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also visit us at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Tiktok is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
Bye.
[Music]
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]