It's been the dream of everyone who follows the world of the weird
To come across an ancient spell book and try to learn its secrets and now thanks to a library
You can do that online and
Then we travel to Bismarck, North Dakota a medium-sized town in a desolate state in America
But this town has had a string of mysteries cut and then we travel to Bismarck, North Dakota
Or a string of missing people all
Seemingly unrelated may point to a sinister
Conspiracy today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day, too
I really do hope you guys are having an awesome awesome day. So I'm gonna be taking a week off next week
It's my scheduled break. I take every 50 episodes
I take a week off, but I put the call out to my patreon supporters. I asked them a question this time
How would you guys feel about me doing best of episodes where I'm going to re-release some of those classic episodes that you guys may have
Missed with a little introduction and that's what we're going to do. They all thought that was a really cool idea
So thank you to all of my patreon supporters who voted on that
We're so next week. We're gonna have five episodes that are notable in one way or the other
Some of them might be my favorite episodes. Some of them may be episodes that I think
Could be more acknowledged. We're gonna re-release the golf rumors episode
Which has never fully been available on YouTube the golf rumors episode
It's gonna be a lot of the older stuff like I think the newest episode I have is like 120
But we're gonna revisit some of those old favorites you've may have missed it
And if that seems to go over well with you guys then when I take the week off will do
Best of episodes. I think that'd be a really cool idea. Let's go ahead though and move on to our first topic
We are headed out to the internet. We're just sitting down here computer. No need for a vehicle
Just walk over to a computer do it. I'm not gonna continue this podcast until you're sitting at a computer
Okay, there you go. Thank you for following my instructions. I appreciate it
And you're gonna go and you're gonna search for a library
Type it in I'm not gonna tell you can check the show notes. What we're gonna do
Actually read the adjustee what we're doing is we were going to Newberry library in Chicago
So being now we view this has become a magic school bus episode by the way
Now we get sucked into the computer and now we're in the library
We're in Newberry library in Chicago. We get mugged immediately upon arriving in Chicago
We're like ah should have stayed online and get forced to the ground
They take our wallets run out of the library and that was actually the librarian who was mugging us Chicago. It's quite a brutal city
But we're here to find three books three spell books
The book of magical charms. That's pretty self-explanatory. You're like, hmm. I wonder what's in that book
It's probably full of magical charms. The other one was cases of conscience concerning witchcraft that one apparently is
Should we or should we not hang witches? It's I guess in that book. There's a story about a guy going hmm
Probably shouldn't hung all those women
The book that's what that is and then the last book it seems odd
Seems like an odd title for a magical text and this is one of those things that you could be walking through your library
You could walk right by it not even know it's magical. It's called the commonplace book the commonplace book
So all of these books are written in the 1600s. They believe they were all written by the same two people
so they're written in a combination of old timey English and
Latin the pages are all like worn out and yellowed and gross and stuff like that and so Newberry Library
That rhymes. Oh, why didn't I pick up on that Newberry Library? It doesn't matter. There's been the news. Sorry
Just thought it was interesting if I ever need a rap lyric. I'm like, yo, I'll take you to the library
Oh, then I'll eat you like a new berry. So yeah, like it I got got flows
What was I saying before the freestyle started? Oh, oh, what no, what was it? Oh, yeah. Yeah, so these books at the library, right?
Newberry Library has that kid not gonna be able to say that anymore without laughing Newberry Library has these books and
They go we need to help translating these
Why don't we crowdsource and they actually have a whole website dedicated to crowdsourcing translation?
So I think this is something they've done before but they have released images of all of these texts online
You type it into a little text bar at the bottom
so you can actually translate it in real time and then all of the
Possible translations goes to a team and they that way you just can't write, you know, like stupid stuff all day long
They all go to a team and then they figure out. Oh, this is probably the most logical one
Or let's take this sentence from this one the sentence from another one
And then that way the books will be available digitally for anyone to read and people have already started
Translating a lot of this stuff. So this is some of the stuff they've come across
I love these their spells on how to get rid of a toothache
You're like, oh, that's awesome, but they require a dead man's tooth
Apparently you take the tooth of a dead man, which I mean technically
You know actually that raises a good question. How how does the spell know if the dude's dead?
Like if I find a tooth on the ground and the guy's still alive
Would the spell work?
if
So do they do teeth transplants? Let's say that I
Die and some guy really likes my tooth
So he takes his tooth out puts my tooth in and then throws his tooth on the ground
This is like what is it the ship of Agamemnon or whatever that philosophers thing if a living man puts a dead
tooth in his mouth and then throws his tooth on the ground
Wouldn't the dead man's tooth in his mouth now become part of a living body?
What if he took his tooth and put it in my dead skull?
How would the spell ten years later know which one was which?
But anyways, that's a thought experiment use that at your next dinner party. Hey guys guys
Sorry to interrupt the conversation, but I have a philosophical question for you. Let's say I find a dead man
And I need a new tooth also
They have a spell on how to get rid of the cramp
Which is not like the awesome name for some new super villain
It was like the old-timey name for menstrual cramps
So put away your I know you just sketched out the cramp fighting Superman this giant just
Uncomfortable force punching Superman in the face the cramp is menstrual cramps
Apparently you take some sort of rag and you just lay it on your thigh
So there you go ladies try that out and if that doesn't work
It's fine a dead man pull his tooth out try that as well
Cheat at dice games you're like Jason these are stupid you're telling me that they have these magical texts that I can help translate
Possibly in the world and you're telling me how to cure two things
But I have to dig up a human corpse how to fight a menstrual cramp and
how to
You know what I'm wondering why
Here's a question for you. Don't get mad. Don't get mad
Do super heroes like Wonder Woman and Captain Marvel?
Men straight
Now I'm not saying I'm not making a joke. I'm not and I'm not riffing
I'm not saying like the Legion of dooms like hey guys look out Wonder Woman's menstruating this week
So she's gonna be super aggressive. I'm not making a joke in the continuity of the comic books
Has that ever been addressed?
Has that ever been addressed where you have?
Spider Woman or Captain Marvel or rescue who's the female Iron Man?
Any of these characters Wonder Woman I already said black canary
Magic anyone anyone ever said
There's I have to be a plot point
I'm not saying that the point of the comic book was in Superman has to like fly around the world looking for a tampon for Wonder Woman
I'm not saying that I'm just saying has it ever been addressed ever in the continuity because some of these characters have been around
Wonder Woman's been around for what like 50 years at this point
Captain Marvel has been around since the 1970s the female Captain Marvel
Magic's been around since the early 80s all of these characters. I have they ever once addressed the fact that
They're like my stomach hurts like is that ever been I don't think so I
Honestly, and it's not a huge seal
They never announced that when Spider-Man has explosive diarrhea like there's bodily functions
But there's just weird now that I think about it and I guess it raises question does Wonder Woman even menstruate like being an Amazonian
She can have children right?
Like I don't know if she's ever had a kid in like alternate continuity
But I mean again you're going Jason Deanna Troy did she ever have a I don't know okay?
Maybe it's just kind of blowing my mind because like you can look say yeah Princess Leia probably has a
menstruate
I've already heard the clicks of half of my audience just be like nope
No, wait for tomorrow's episode. This is way too much the way too much
Yeah, I just wanted to hear about spell books and I was talking about I don't think it's a shameful thing that women have
Menstruation or periods. I don't know why they don't mention it
but I guess because it's just this natural thing that happens, but I guess that
You people don't people don't want to read about it people don't want to have like Wonder Woman being like
After I defeat evil then I have to go to the grocery store real quick because I don't like where would she even carry her tampons at in her costume?
Like she doesn't have a purse
Her plane is invisible
You would just see her flying by and then some maxi pads just like floating where the glove you assume the glove compartment would be
I mean she flies an invisible jet. So I'm just I guess they just never menstruate. I guess female characters never menstruate
But you would assume you wouldn't assume that none of these fictional characters ever go to the bathroom at all like spider-man is just full of
feces from
1963 to today he's never pooped like you assume those characters pooped so you would assume the female characters would also menstruate
But yeah, just weird
Yes
Let's get back to spell books
So yes, yes you with me - you're done fast forwarding. Okay, perfect
You can also cheat at dice. Don't fast forward yet. I got some good spells. They also have spells on summoning spirits
You can conjure up an ancient demon using this spellbook and it was all like really weird language
Well, I mean love it was Latin
I thought about reading on the podcast, but I couldn't make heads or tails of it
It also teaches you how to invoke the seal of Solomon, which I should actually do an
episode on Solomon King Solomon
biblical figure
And you guys are like great not another one of those episodes, but but hey, he's it's like it's one of those things like in the Bible
He's like I chopped that baby in half and people are like no no don't chop the baby in half and he's like
I've done good work today. I found out who the real mother is. That's how people kind of know King Solomon
Why is this man his big biblical figure? What a lot of people aren't aware of is that apparently he had a ring and a seal that allowed
him to
Control demons like actual like Satan like fallen angels who who sided against God with Lucifer go to hell
Solomon King Solomon somehow figured out to turn them into slaves and had them build these great works and work
It's a slaves. They're like mining gold for him like not like go get me some gold as Riyadh and
Comes give him gold. He's like ball Barath you grab this pickaxe
to put on this little miners hat and dig for five weeks in a row and demons like
That's an interesting story
I'll see if I can dig more information up on it
But anyway, so you too if you have this book if you can translate this section or actually this parts translated
You can just read it. You can invoke the seal of Solomon get some nice demon slaves. I'm not recommending doing that
Not do not get a bunch of demon slaves end up getting possessed and going to prison for doing awful things and saying
But dead rabbit radio told me to don't mess with it
But I'm just saying that according to this book there you can do it, but don't
Don't don't is what I'm saying is I can already tell you guys are googling Newberry Library. You're like, I need some demon slaves
Let's go ahead
But yeah, if you know any Latin or old-timey English or you just want to spend a fun rainy afternoon
summoning dark spirits to completely ruin your life or
Simply getting rid of a toothache. You follow the show notes
You'll be able to go down there or just Google Newberry Library
Actually go to the show notes because when I went to Newberry Library took me a bit of time to find that actual section if you go through
The show notes it will take you directly to the translation part of those books
So let's go ahead and move on to our next topic. We're walking out of Newberry Library. See you guys later
librarians are like
Spending our money throwing it up in the air. They're like making it rain with other people's money. We're like, ah
So I don't have any money. I'm assuming you don't have any money either you had if you had a second wallet
You go I know traveling with Jason is quite dangerous. We've been assaulted. He's pushed me in a pile of poop before
I got my second wall with is wrapped in a ziploc baggie in case I get pushed in a poop again
I'm like awesome. So we are traveling your pain. We're traveling to Bismarck, North Dakota
So let's buy some private plane tickets like Jason. Can't we just fly commercial?
Did I ever do the story of actually about that guy that minister? I think it was um
One of the big televangelists and I don't know if I covered this yet. He said I was about to make a joke about it
there was this
Televangelist minister who won't fly commercial planes. He had to buy private jets and
They asked why and he said because a flying a commercial plane is a tube of full of demons
Like that's where all the demons fly commercial. So he needed a private jet. I should I don't think I've covered that story
That's the story. That's basically all it is some weirdo saying something and they asked him to clarify that and he wasn't saying like
Everyone on a commercial jet is a demon, but demons always fly commercial jets
So it's one of those weird things
So anyways, he flies private jet. He has like two or three private jet
Anyways, we're flying private because I don't want to be stuck in a tube full of demons
You're like considering we just talked about evoking them definitely risk
So yes, you spend your life savings or maybe you're allowance. I don't know how rich you are to get us a private jet
We're flying up to Bismarck, North Dakota, and we're going back in time. This is a really really fan-saving
currency jet. We're going back in time. That's why I got you your life savings. We're going back in time to the year
1989 so
So Bobby Brown is humping around
Ace of Base is a few years away, and we are in Fargo, North Dakota. It's February 26th
1989 and there's this dude named Roy Hagel. He's 38 years old. He's from Bismarck, North Dakota. He's in Fargo
He's at a bowling tournament, and this is the last time he has seen a life, but not the last time he's ever heard of
Because on March 6th, he calls a buddy from Arizona. So he's in Fargo, North Dakota
Then what 12 days later? He's in Arizona. He calls up his buddy in Bismarck his hometown
He goes listen. I've been to nine states in nine days, and I'm out of money, but you know, I'm gonna I'm gonna get back to
Bismarck. I'm headed back to Bismarck, but he's like, okay. Yeah, come back here. Odd phone call to make
Four days later though, his car is found at Death Valley Monument
So the it's exactly what it sounds like. It's Death Valley. It's the place you don't want to go
We've covered it before and the very least it's a complete wasteland full of heat and vultures and buzzards and
Wiley Coyote and Roadrunner at the most there's been stories of hidden civilizations underneath that
But his car is found there
He's not
They see when authorities get to the car the keys
And his wallet are in the front seat and as you see me steal his wallet, you're like
Shaking your finger at me. I'm like, dude. I don't got any money those librarians. I take his wallet
We also see because now we're there with the investigators. There is footprints leading away from this car
Now what's interesting is the news reports don't say
the state of the car
And I'm not saying this so the news reports don't really say what the state of the car is as in that a breakdown
Was it out of gas? Who knows but
We see this car and there's footprints leading away from it and
We and the authorities follow the footprints for six miles
and then
Just an arid desert
Nothing past six miles, which is quite a long journey. I don't I wonder if they followed them on feet or if at a certain point
They're like, yeah, let's go get the car. Let's just drive alongside these things
Now the police were looking into this there was one suspicious thing
He's never been seen since the police are still investigating this there was one suspicious thing when Roy was a child his father disappeared
came back and
Then disappeared for good never saw him again
People thought maybe he was trying to emulate his father
Maybe he was trying to start a new life and that may be true
If you do decide to leave it all behind to start a new life don't start it in the direction of a desert
Don't be like hmm
Fortune is that way and you're like walking into
Doom like hmm. I wonder what's over the next ridge. It's a volcano like if you're gonna start a new life start it in Iowa or
San Diego or something
Never been found since
1994 August 2nd, so he was from Bismarck. He was headed back to Bismarck
He went on this weird nine-state and nine-day journey August 2nd
1994 we're in the city of Bismarck now
Michelle Joulson
She's hanging out
She has a job as she worked at like a casino. She goes. Hey, I got a little baby got a little baby boy here
I'm gonna drop you off with your grandpa and I gotta go take care of some business
I gotta go get a paycheck and maybe I'll play a little dice
Maybe I'll go to the casino a little bit and the little three-year-old's like yay. I'll see you mommy
I you're not gonna disappear, right? And she mommy's like no that was dark. That was super dark
Baby's like what does dark mean? Mom's like just just ignore it ignore this of this insensitive
Podcasts and she takes the baby to grandpa and says can you watch the baby? I gotta pay up this paycheck
Grandpa's like yeah, are you guys also has a baby voice?
Are you going to come back or are you going to disappear? And mom's like why does the people keep asking me that I'll be fine
But she's not she disappears
She's never seen again and she's reported missing within hours like she says I'm gonna go do this paycheck
I'm gonna go play bingo not cards not dice. Sorry misspoke totally
And I'm sure right when I said that people go mafia. Yep. She's gonna get abducted by the mafia. No, there's no bingo mafia
There's no blue-haired mafia there might be actually actually that'd be a good idea for like a really terrible
Comedy starring Melissa McCarthy where you have this bingo hall
That is like being run poorly you have a bingo hall
That's kind of like in disrepair Melissa McCarthy comes in to drop her mom off and she realizes
Well, we can make a lot of money doing this stuff like if we took a little bit off the top
But first we have to make this place look better
So it starts off like a lovable comedy where there's a busy like there's a there's like a bloodthirsty businessman
played by
The Rock in his first role as a villain
He's trying to tear down the bingo hall and Melissa McCarthy has to hold like bake sales
But like some stupid old woman puts a bunch of her son's weed in the brownies
So everyone's tripping out and then they hold like a bikini car wash
So there's like this montage of all these 80 year old women spraying cars down with hoses and stuff
Like that and it starts off like a little rascals and that's not in the little rascals
But it's I hope it's not a little rascals
it starts off as that type of comedy or these guys are trying to beat this businessman and then about say
45 minutes an hour into the movie
You're like just get back to them. It's same people
45 minutes to an hour into the movie the Rock admits defeat and
Falls in love with an old woman at the bingo hall. So like his character arc comes full stop because I don't know why I was trying to
Tear did my my great grandma used to play here. Not that's not the woman. He's dating
It's not the only day my great grandma used to play here and but I found true love with this 80 year old woman
Everything's going to work out and then the last half hour is Melissa McCarthy
Like becoming like straight up casino level mobster like chopping old people's fingers off if they can't make their bingo bills
Just like dunking their heads and like hot jars of my lanta. She's like how's your stomach now?
And it becomes just like this brutal the first hour
You're clapping and laughing at like stoned old women and bikinis
And then the ending is her like forcing old with selling old women into sexual slavery and you're just like
And it would be called the movie would just be called
bingo with a
Exclamation point and the bottom of the exclamation point is a bingo number
So everyone's like oh this is gonna be look like like a total romp
And then it just ends and it ends with Melissa McCarthy shot of Melissa McCarthy sitting on a throne made out of bingo cards
That's just and then it just there's no credits the movie just ends
So anyways I
Make that movie Hollywood make that movie anyways
Michelle Juleson is missing and
And she's never seen again
they
Find her on August and that happened on August 2nd on August 8th
They find her car at a comfort Inn in Bismarck and they
They had been looking for the car from the beginning and one of the
Detectives on the case was no one for finding stolen cars like that like just really really good at tracking stuff down
And he said I don't believe that car was there
He goes I can't say for sure that we specifically checked that parking lot of that comfort Inn
But I'm almost for sure that that car was not there on August 2nd because again like I said they started
They reported her missing after hours
Her car had nothing in it except for a half eaten gas station sandwich
And one thing the detectives thought was weird they found scoria
Which is like a pumice type rock in the intake manifold of the car
So it's kind like this car was driving in an area with a lot of scoria
There is not a lot of scoria in Bismarck. There is scoria in North Dakota
There's scoria all over but an interesting place where there's a lot of scoria
DeFallee and you're like Jason come on seriously these these missing people took place years apart
One wasn't even in the city of Bismarck. He was from the city of Bismarck and
There's scoria all over the United States. Why are you even connecting these two?
It's kind of bizarre not to that I say
November 16th 1996
Bismarck, North Dakota now North Dakota in 1996 had a population of 54,000 people and I was looking at this and they do have
couple hundred missing people every year, but the majority of them are
Found right away and then there's maybe like 20 or 30 where the detectives have to do some sort of follow-up
And then these cases have never been solved
The story of Roy Hagel the story of Michelle and the story I'm about to tell you of Sandra Mary Jacobson and
John Jacobson her five-year-old son
She is headed to Bismarck to go to dinner with her mom. She's in a neighboring town
She's driving to Bismarck and she calls the police in Bismarck 911. What's your emergency? I?
Was just driving through
Center Center, North Dakota and
I saw a ritual I saw a ritual it I mean I don't know it looked it looks satanic it
There's something wrong out here that I swear there's a bunch of sane worshipers out here
And they were having a ritual and I saw them
And I don't know if they saw me, but I saw them
I'm not in center anymore. I'm headed to Bismarck. I'm gonna go see my mom, but I think there's something bad going on out here in center
Now the police
Go that's really bizarre and they say
Why didn't you call the police in center? Why are you calling?
Bismarck is 40 miles away from center. You go. Why don't you call the police in center and she says I don't trust
Police in center and I don't trust the police that are closer to them as well. I trust you guys because I think
They may be part of it. I think there's a conspiracy you see there's just satanic conspiracy. I
don't trust them
Sandra does have
According to articles it doesn't go into specifics, but I think we can imagine it says she has issues with mental health
So that could be she has full-blown delusions about things
It could be anxiety or depression
Both of those would be considered a whole plethora of other symptoms would be considered mental health issues
Someone who is constantly anxious or depressed would be listed as having mental health issues as is someone who had
schizophrenia or
manic or manic depressive bipolar stuff like it's all in that umbrella. So we just hear words like
mental health issues not necessarily mental illness
But when she got to her mother's house her mom immediately
Could tell something was wrong with her daughter
In the mind that which makes me think that the mental health issues are a little more serious than she just has clinical depression
But the mom realizes something's wrong with the daughter and the mom says we need to go to the hospital
Let's go to the hospital. Just get you checked out. It's not gonna be a big deal. Everything's fine
And the daughter goes okay we go to the hospital
But can I get gas put gas in my car first the mom goes sure the daughter Sandra puts her five-year-old son in her car
Drives to go get gas. She is seen putting gas in her car
But all of that happened about 730
She goes to get gas the mom's at home by 10 p.m
She calls the police and says my daughter and my grandson are missing and again
Let this and the story of Michelle be a a
Wake-up call for you. You do not under any circumstances have to wait 24 hours to report a missing person
That is not true. That is probably one of the biggest
Dumbest myths that have ever come out of Hollywood honestly. I think that has cost people their lives
It's a narrative device in stories to make the characters go out and search
Instead of having a massive police force and do the search that is an adventures and babysitting plot device
That is not real life. If you believe someone is missing you can call police
Very very quickly. It's not you will never call up in the police go you got away 24 hours
That is 100% an invention of Hollywood and I think it's probably one of the most destructive myths out of Hollywood
She goes missing the next day her car is found at Centennial Beach, North Dakota
No Sandra no John and yes Centennial Beach is at a river
so the cops get there and
they go
We're looking for this missing person the mom said she had some mental health issues
She parked by a river
No one's in the car
They couldn't search the river at the time the weather was bad were in November. It's North Dakota and
It's a raging river and they go if the bodies went into the river. We'll never find them
The car is found
With a door wide open
Keys in the ignition purse on the seat
These three cases have all taken place
Seven years apart
We had 89 94 and now 96 and they were all linked in quite a few autoways
all the victims are
Related to Bismarck Bismarck in North Dakota
All of the victims one of the main things found about them is their vehicle. They're not getting snatched out of their house
Their vehicle is in a location where it normally would not be
All of them had items left on the driver's side seat
two of them specifically keys and
Purse wallet where they carry their money
These articles the the reason why I came across these three cases
These were written in an article called missing person cases are not forgotten. It was written by a reporter named Jenny Michael
She wrote this in February 22nd 2008 and it's really the last
Recorded article about these three cases. I've seen follow-up articles on one of the case or the other case
But only this article ever put all three of them together
Originally, I was looking up the story of Sandra Jacobson and I found this article and I was like it's just a missing story
It has the satanic Colton it it'll be interesting and as I was researching it
I came across this article and we start to see these connections coincidences
sure
Sure a woman who has a mental health issue sees a satanic Colt
Performing some sort of ritual and has enough interaction with law enforcement in her area. She doesn't trust them. She thinks they're part of the conspiracy
So right there you go, she's just having some mental health issues
But when we have a string of missing people who have these coincidences who have these similarities
Disappear off the face of the earth never to be found
All with abandoned vehicles all with items on their seat all either headed to or living in Bismarck
I'm not saying I do as a normal practice. I do not
Take to heart what people say in the throes of panic and a woman's frantic 911 call
while she's driving through North Dakota talking about seeing a satanic ritual and a
County-wide conspiracy. It's not something that you would normally put a lot of faith in
But when you have a total of four missing people
possibly connected and
Then you have stories of a satanic Colt operating in
North Dakota
There's a difference between being afraid of coincidences and
having a little bit of common sense
So if you live in the city of Bismarck or
anywhere in the middle of nowhere
Be a little more careful
Because we don't know why any of these people disappeared
They could be completely random completely unrelated and just tragic circumstances or
They could have stumbled on to a dark secret in the middle of the night
They could have known too much
And they just had to disappear before they said too much
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio Twitter is @dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
*Music*
[MUSIC]