In the back hills of Arkansas in the year 1855
Whoa horse whoa, what's gearing you so much?
We have to stop these people but how we don't even know if they're people they're not people
Pushing over a wagon
wagon catches on fire
Person standing in front of the silhouette of the fire. Yes, we don't know no human could push over
No human could push over a wagon like that
How echoing over the moonlit landscape of Arkansas we don't know how to stop these raiders
You already said that where I'm saying it again. Dang it. We don't stop these people. They're not people
Then what are they?
They're the Bigfoot and this is the story of the human Bigfoot war of
1855 today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day, too. You guys listen to yesterday's episode
I think you can tell how how healthy I am which is not very
The ending of that episode sounded like I was really trying not to cry at the story of Martin Guerrero
I was holding in the cough for about 15 seconds
And I was trying to say that final line so I could just finish the episode
Cough and then go to sleep. Yeah, I don't know what it is. It could be the combination of me
I've completely given up the nicotine. I'm not even on the patch anymore
So I'm feeling kind of good, but I'm quite miserable could just be coming down with something because of the weather
I don't know so this episode actually is only going to be one story, but it's a good story
But so this episode is probably gonna be a little short
I just need to get some more rest
But I want it I'm glad I saved this one because I think this one is definitely one that can hold up its own episode
Don't need anything else. So let's go ahead and jump into the Bigfoot human war or the human Bigfoot war
I really don't think it matters which one comes first, but this is from the conspiracy iceberg
This is also a recommendation from our Bigfoot or resident Bigfoot expert
Bennett Bennett, thank you. This is one that I've actually had on the docket for quite a while
I researched it probably like six seven months ago and just haven't reported it and then Bennett reminded me
That it existed and I was like, oh, yeah, I already have the notes on this one
So thank you Bennett for reminding me that of work that I had previously done
Let's go ahead and jump into this
So we're gonna get on our mighty steeds
That sounds like a witch, but it's not we're not jumping on top of old-timey witches
We're jumping on top of our horses getting on our mountian or horses. It's a better term
You're not just jumping up and down on them. So get on your steed young traveler
I'll eat your children. We're like, that's not a horse. You gotta get a real one. So we're taking our horses
We're gonna ride back into time
We're going back to the year 1855 we're going to the state
of Arkansas now
I think in 1855
It was still pretty like yeah, there was a government there
But it wasn't like super
It wasn't like it is today
I have no idea what I'm talking about
What I'm trying to say is
the state had like
U.S. citizens in it and then a bunch of natives in it as well, which might again might be the case today
But I think it was I'm trying to say it was probably more wildernessy wildernessy
Okay, so
Nowadays you can go to a little rock, but back then it was just rock
It was just a giant rock. It hadn't been carved down yet by the settlers
So we're riding through the wilderness of Arkansas on our horses on our mighty mighty steeds
And we're gonna meet the Choctaw tribe and they're we're gonna meet a dude named Hamas Tubby
So we're like poking his stomach. We're like, hey Tubby. Hey, he has a full on six pack
This guy is a massive warrior. He's like you can call me Tubby. Oh, you want Tubby? You're the one who's Tubby
Jason and I'm like, you're right
But at least my name is not Tubby Hamas Tubby
And he has a bunch of sons, right and they're recorded to be the Choctaw
tribe is already a very tall native american tribe, but apparently
Tubby and sons are pushing seven feet tall
Seven feet tall. So a couple inches taller than me. So massive people, right?
And they're in a group of even bigger dudes
And while Hamas and company are chilling
They're actually probably doing a lot to further the growth of their tribe
But while they're in the area you start hearing reports of raiding parties
People oh Tubby Tubby. I'm so glad you're here
They're like, what's the matter dude? And he's like
So I was walking with my girlfriend down by the river, right?
and
somebody like pushed us and then we ran away
The native dudes like oh, well, that's that's that's quite rude. He got pushed and they're like, yeah, he got pushed
Okay, you leave and then if someone else comes and they're like, oh Tubby Tubby. Oh my god
I was I was just walking by the river
But I had a bale of apples with me. I was carrying apples
And something came out of the woods and pushed me over and took my apples
And Tubby's like the plot of the plot thickens
Now we have a motive for this pushing action that's going on and then
No, no, okay
So let me be clear here
People weren't getting pushed at the river. The point is is that I was trying to build the narrative. There were multiple attacks
By raiders in the area against people
So whether or not apples or girlfriends were being pushed over the point is is that
Someone kept attacking
Choctaw natives in the area big people
I mean if a Choctaw was like, oh my god, that guy was so huge Tubby knows. Hmm. That's interesting because we're the biggest people around
And we haven't eaten apples in a while. So
They're getting word of these raiding parties in the area
Both at the river and beyond
So they try to find out what's going on. Who's attacking their people and then
Children start to disappear. So at this point Tubby's like, okay apples getting pushed or no apples getting pushed
This has gotten serious like we have to take care of this kids are missing
So they form up a
Posse they form up a search party to find who is taking these people
What they do is they have a 30 man crew
So they're like load up boys
Cloting up the rifles
Putting bullets in
Guys pulling up picture of his girlfriend
He's kisses it puts it on the top of his horse so you can see these he's riding in the battle
They're like, who's that? He's like, this is the girl I'm coming back to
Puts it on there. Come on boys. Quit messing around get your guns ready. We got to go find some kid killers
Like wait a second. How do you know they're killing the kids? He's like, I skipped ahead in the story
So this group at the person who skipped ahead in the story. His name is joshua la flor
He's half french half chock towel and he goes come on boys. Let's do this
We're gonna find these people. We're gonna push him into the mud. We're gonna do more than that. We're gonna kill him
They're like, yay. Yay. Some guy was like, really? You're just gonna push him into the mud
It's like, hey, it's improv. I'm just coming up the top of my head. He hops on his horse. Now, we're gonna ride with him
Come on. Come on, dude. Get your horse. We're gonna make some more of these tiny people
Among these seven tall soldiers. We're wearing like modern day clothes
They're pretending not to notice but they're like those guys are idiots
They think they can be in this battle with us
But anyways, we earn their trust halfway through the journey because they keep dropping stuff on the ground and we pick it up
For them because we're tiny. It's all people can't pick stuff up. So anyways, we're right. I don't know
We're riding our horses in this big cavalry band now
We're able to track these bandits down in relatively short order. It's not like the next day. They're like, oh look
But these guys are expert trackers. So we're able to get to where we're going and it doesn't take a lot of time
And at one point we're up in a hill and joshua was like get down get down all the horses
Are getting down. They're high. Can a horse kneel a horse can like get down
Can a horse sit like a sphinx can a horse sit actually? I think it's a good enough question
But like horses seem to be you know, it's funny and that's already going this segue on my episode
I'm trying to make short because I don't feel good
Horses
Are one of the most alien looking creatures that I think we see on a daily basis like yeah, you know
Water bears look weird and like insects are pretty disgusting
But when you see a horse it actually looks like
Some kid drew something and it came to life. It doesn't it's a big fat
It basically has the body of a maggot just like a big round
torso and then tiny little stick legs and then
Uh, I just a head shaped like an aquatic creature or dinosaur and then a tail
And it's so gross horses are pretty like gross looking
They're magnificent and they're kind of awesome to look at but they look like big brown maggots with stick legs like really
They're super super
Alien looking they don't look like they belong like a dog. Everything looks in proportion cat. Everything looks in proportion
Cows even cows look kind of weird too, but not as weird as a horse
Anyways, you're like, and what horses are you looking at?
Who was magnificent muscular beast on?
I don't know. I they just look alien to me. I'm not saying that they're not pretty
I mean brown maggots aren't pretty by definition, but
They just look so alien to me
anyways
We're riding these
Horses looking at me as I'm delivering that monologue the horse that I'm riding is like, dude
You're kind of a jerk and he's trying to fight. I'm like, come on horse. No, no, no, you're good. You're one of the good ones
You're one of the good ones. Oh, okay. Thanks Jason. So we're walking anyways
We come to this hill the horses are ducking down and joshua the floor breaks out this homemade telescope
It's basically just two pieces of cardboard and some nerds high glasses that he's told back in town
He's turning. He's like there's a raiding part. I see the party over there. That's the raiders. They're in that little forested area
Mount up boys
Get back on our horses check our rifles. Yep, according to the story. We're rocking sharp rifles
They're 50 caliber combat rifles. So getting putting those big old bullets in we're about to blow up some raiders
Joshua the floor. Let's go. We're riding down the hill now
Full charge not just dropping. I don't know why I'm making that noise
Just all it sounds like a dude's at some British cheese about to start rapping
The forest not the forest the forest stays there the horses
Crash into the forest. So the horses
Russian to the forest we're on the horses. So we all rush into the forest
And the first thing
We're hit with is the smell of death
Start choking and gagging some of the smell so bad some of the horses
Throw their
Throw their right. It sounds like a witch throw their riders off of them. Uh
Horses take off the smell is that bad
Imagine if somebody
Who never wore deodorant?
Died in an outhouse on a summer day and then that outhouse farted in your mouth
That is what the smell of this area is like
That is about enough. We're starting to gag
Oddly enough one of the guys is like
Oh, yes, my favorite smell in the world. He has a fetish for this by the rest of us
Now as we're combating this basically chemical weapon at this point, we can't stand the smell of death
We start to see these three figures
kind of hunched over a pile of something and while we're like our eyes are all watery
Trying to figure out what's going on one of them stands up and it's truly a monstrous man if not a monster itself
seven to eight feet tall
Seemingly covered in hair and holding like a chicken wing the arm of a dead child
Taking another bite or just looking at us
And we see there's two other figures like him
And they're standing by a pile of all the dead children that have been missing
There's been nine of them. I don't know if I said how many there were anyways
There's been nine of them and they're partially decayed and being eaten or have been eaten
And it doesn't matter because at this point we're
Throwing up and the creature
Kind of wipes its mouth off now joshua la flor. He's not freaking out. He's not throwing up. He's still on his horse
He's completely enraged by what he sees he he takes his horse
He grabs his sword and he
Charge and he goes running towards on horseback the guy who's standing up who's just eating the kid's arm
Running full bore. He's going to chop this dude's head off
And the creature turns and just punches the horse in the head and kills the horse instantly
Now joshua falls off the horse and the creature looks over at him and joshua pulls out his pistol and just unloads pop pop pop pop pop pop pop
Every bullet pop pop pop pop hits this creature
Empties the gun into this creature creature still coming joshua gets to his feet
joshua grabs the sword and just starts hacking at this guy now
He's drawn blood just slicing it up. He's cutting his blood everywhere. He's doing damage
This isn't some sort of mystical creature, but it is some sort of creature
And it's still coming towards him as joshua stabbing and slicing and cutting and then we're all in shock
By what's going on because this whole thing happened in a matter of seconds
From the time we all fell off of our horses or just smelled
the horrible stench
To where we're at right now
Everyone's frozen all these combat trained soldiers are frozen and us and then and then one of the other creatures walks up behind
joshua and while he's stabbing the first one
Desperately trying to kill it. The other one just walks up grabs the back of joshua's head and goes
Rips his head off of his shoulders and joshua just falls to the ground
Now I imagine the creature did some sort of Harlem Globetrotter move the head started rolling around spinning it on his finger
But whatever happened in real life at all the shock of people ended right there
Like seeing their leader killed made them not being shocked which okay
Let's take a second to go over this part real quick
That is a really really bad team
If you are a military man and you're trying to pick your best team
Can you can't can you do well under pressure? Well, it depends if it's really smelly
I can't but don't worry captain the second you die. I'll be ready to fight again
But anyways, everyone's kind of like whoa. What was that? I just saw a bunch of kids getting eaten
I just saw a horse get punched to death and I saw my captain's head get ripped off
It's time to fight everyone opens fire with their rifles now. They're sharp 50 caliber rifles
Creatures are like
Getting shot
Now it says in the story that every shot was a head shot because these guys were so good with these rifles
And I'm telling you that not because we're humble bragging. I'm like, all right
Dude, we're so good shooting people with these rifles. It's because it plays an interesting part in what's coming up
But anyways, so you just see this big foot
It's like close up of a rifle shooting then a big foot piece goes off his head and then another shot
piece go off his head and then slow motion
Bigfoot brains going everywhere and then I guess I want to be making that noise
He would already be dead all three of these creatures just getting massive 50 caliber rounds to the head
Then birds come back to the forest
They're french birds apparently
and
Nature has been restored now. They're like
Oh wait, no, sorry, then there's I forgot this part
So then they think they're all dead, right? But one of the creatures doesn't get shot at multiple times
Why 50 caliber rounds? So here's the epilogue
So they're like that good thing that was done and some guy has his back
To one of the raiders. He's like, yeah, can you believe these guys are such knuckleheads?
We killed them so easily
What a bunch of what a bunch of rum dingers and then the creature gets up and starts running
And they're like uh and so this young brave jumps off of his horse and grabs his knife and he's running through the jungle and the creature's like
And that dude's running behind him
Monsters running and then the guy jumps up
Sticks him with a knife and just kills this dude with this monster with a knife
Now he'd been shot up a bunch of times
So they did think he was dead or not. It doesn't matter. The point is is that the last one was killed by a knife
So the remaining people all of us basically there was 30 people in joshla flure la flare whatever
He died he got his head ripped off
So we start digging they make us dig the graves because we were completely useless in that fight
We dig the graves we dig the grave for joshua
We dig the grave to bury the children and then we just burn the body of the raiders
We burn the bodies of these bandits
slash monsters
Because they don't deserve a proper burial
And then we ride back home
And we get home and there's a little little kid walks up to you and be like hey
Hey, what what do you guys see out there? Is it true? Is it true the smell and the head in the head getting punched off and
And all of that stuff and we look down at the little boy and we go
I don't know if it's true. We're about to figure that out
We're about to figure that out little boy
He's like whether it doesn't make any sense and then bam
We're back in the present day and then we go and grab a history book and we look up and it says
1855 a little boy
asked the question of two strangers and
And they didn't have an answer
That little boy decided to dedicate his life to finding answers
That little boy's name was hawking
Stephen hawking so we didn't know it, but we actually inspired
Stephen hawking native american boy, but you didn't know that
Native american boy born in 1855
Anyways, the point is is that we're back in the future
Let's take a look and see how much of this story is true
Now like I said, I came across this story months and months ago and I did all the research
I just let it sit there and I thought I just I don't really I think it's totally fake
I think it's 100 fake. So I was like, I've done a lot of stories where I just talk about it and then go
It's fake and then move on. That's what was preventing me from talking about it
But when Bennett was like, yeah, you should cover it. I was like, I'll give it another look
So let's really dig into this thing here. There's a website called sasquatchhistory.wordpress.com
Which is really good website because I always like websites that take like love exploring stuff
But then also know that stuff needs to be dunked and debunked and debunked and that is what this podcast does
So let's take a look at what we can verify with this story
This is what the sasquatch history website says one those sharp rifles. They didn't come out in 1855
They weren't invented until 1870. So right there
We have a problem and they were 50 caliber rifles
But the thing is is like this website was saying that Native Americans really wouldn't have access
If they had access to a 50 caliber rifle, the ammo would be quite rare for them
They wouldn't be able to be super well trained on them to land headshot after headshot after headshot
Because it was a military grade rifle with military grade weaponry
It would be harder to get than say like a 22 round or something like that
So right there you go. Well, then it's not true because these
Weapons that are named in it aren't didn't exist at the time even if they did they wouldn't be
Plausible for them to use. Well, what's interesting is the story itself might be true
But the detail could have been added in later
So it could have originally just been they were using rifles and someone says oh no
They'd have to have 50 caliber rifles to fight these monsters
But apparently this story has some seed of truth into it
If we look at the original story that there these weren't creatures at all. They weren't bigfoot
originally it was just there was a bunch of raiders in the area and
They were killing kids at a certain point and these guys came out and they fought humans
And they shot a bunch of times in the head and that was kind of the end of it
And then the humans became more than human they became man beasts
And then over time they became beasts or bigfoot's
So now they're fighting giant hairy people in the middle of the woods
So you have that you have an origin of the story you have like an evolution of the story
The area where this happened in the Choctaw language. It's known as looking for killers
This little grove
Where all this supposedly went down
Is no one has looking for killers in Choctaw?
So it's possible something went down. However, here's the real kicker
I'm getting all of those details from that website sasquatchhistory.wordpress.com
And they could be making it up or they could be completely wrong because I tried looking for
The glenn I tried looking for what looking for killers means in Choctaw
I tried looking for earlier versions of the story. I couldn't find anything the real kicker to the story of whether or not it's true
Is there was no such person as joshua la flor the person did not exist at that time period
I'm not saying that there's not one now some guy's a bookkeeper in Idaho. He's like starts to fade away
He's like no, I don't exist at the time. There was no guy named joshua la flor. There was a la flor family
They were very very influential members of the Choctaw community. They were half french half Choctaw all of that stuff checks out
But there was no captain joshua la flor that person did not exist
There was a jackson la flor, but it was born after the events
So we have all these different little details that don't add up that make you go
The story's fake when you talk about people riding and shooting monsters in the middle of the woods
Which is really what the the monsters are eating children
Heroes show up shoot monsters into story
When you're talking about a story that's fanciful your details need to be on point
And it's funny because had they left out the name of joshua la flor or the types of rifles
The story would be much harder to just flat out debunk and say it didn't happen because these details didn't happen
But I think there's a more interesting
Let's assume that a version of the story happened that it wasn't humans fighting bigfoot
Which is possible because you figure that humans fought neanderthals for thousands of years
We had constant struggles with other species other humanoid species on this planet
The idea of a bunch of people in the wild wild west shooting at bigfoot isn't
Super out of the or like if you believe in that type of stuff. I mean, obviously it's not like a scientist
It's like you're right Jason that isn't out of the ordinary. In fact, it's quite plausible like I'm not saying that but
If you believe in this stuff anyways, then but I think there's actually a more interesting question to this
I think there's actually a more interesting theory to this. So let's assume that the events themselves are true
They didn't use the rifles joshua la flor is isn't in it. It's some other dude
People are getting attacked pushed by the river children go missing search party shows up
And they see in this wilderness a bunch of people run off and they see three
mighty men left behind
Tall men seemingly covered in hair
Almost supernaturally strong and these three men turn and fight to the death
With this band of 30 native warriors
One theory that's been put forth is that these guys were vikings
These were a band of vikings that had long lived in america as a separate
little civilization
And this is how they lived they raided other people. They took what they wanted like they did in europe
but this time they got tracked down and
Three of them decided to make a stand
While the rest of them took off
I think that idea is way more honestly bad ass than the bigfoot like yes bigfoot
I'm getting shot in the head, but I think I think the idea and I've always found this idea intriguing
I know they came out of that movie pathfinder, which was okay, but the idea of vikings versus
Like native americans. I find absolutely like visually stunning. I think that is such a not for them
They're like, oh i'm getting stabbed i'm getting stabbed and the other guys the vikings getting shot with arrows
It's not visually stunning for them, but you have two basically the two most alpha
Relations on the planet like I'd like to see ninjas fight as tech warriors
I'd actually like to see ninjas
Fight knights from medieval times
I'd like to see like as tech warriors fight
You could have as tech warriors fighting vikings. Anyways, that's another point. The point is is like
Wait, it's it's kind of the point the point is is that I think it's awesome when you have two societies
fight
But not like I don't I mean I don't really care about like russia and syria fighting turkey
That's not as interesting. I want to see
Like those ancient civilizations clash in ways they never did so to me. It's more exciting and exhilarating
To thank that in 1855
Some dudes were running up on some vikings that were eating children
And a viking a human turned around and punched a horse so hard the horse died and then the viking kept getting stabbed
I'm not saying the vikings a good guy in this scenario either. Don't get a twist and I'm not like yay go vikings
He's deserved to die because he's eating children, but
I just find that idea more interesting than the bigfoot but either way either way if this story happened
Something very very dark happened children went missing and were eaten
A brave man died trying to seek out vengeance
and three men
Or beasts or both
Were killed in that glen
but
Remember a bunch of them got away and just because we got no further reports in that area
doesn't mean
That they didn't continue their reign of terror
somewhere
in the american west
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @dead rabbit radio
The dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but i'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]