A groundbreaking and controversial new steady shows that depression is not caused by low
serotonin levels.
It's actually caused by having a bunch of bad stuff happen to you at the same time.
And yet psychiatrists disagree.
Very interesting story.
Now we travel to Australia to take a look at a terrifying cryptid waiting for us in the
woods.
And if you think you can run and hide from this beast, first ask yourself, is your life
worth the safety of your family and friends?
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a good day.
I hope you guys are having a good day.
I hope you guys are having awesome fun doing whatever you're doing.
We got a lot of stuff to cover so we're going to get started right away.
First off, walking into Dead Rabbit Command is one of our legacy Patreon supporters.
Everyone get on your feet and give a salute to Sniper.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in Sniper.
Hope you have that rifle ready.
We're going to do some cryptid hunting in the next story and maybe you have depression
from doing all that sniping.
We'll talk about that in the first story.
Sniper, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't support your Patreon, I totally understand.
I really do.
Just help spread the word about the show.
It helps out so much.
Please do that for Dead Rabbit Radio.
Sniper, let's go ahead and tashie the keys to the Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy.
We're going to leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We're going to burn rubber and head on out to a psychiatrist's office.
I don't really know if the Dead Rabbit Dune Buggy Street Legal but we're taking it there
anyways.
It's going to be a fun little ride hanging out as the temperature is not so hot.
It's hanging out in this Dune Buggy driving on the way to the psychiatrist's office.
We're interrupting all their appointments.
Just revving up the engine right outside their window.
This was an interesting story.
This story I came across during my vacation and it might have actually been right before
I went on vacation.
I was like, "Wow, this is huge.
This is a really big story."
I wanted to wait to see what the pushback would be on it because I knew there would be
pushback.
The pushback, it's interesting because on the one hand people are seriously pushing back
against this steady we're going to talk about but on the other hand everyone's doing it
very quietly.
Because even the pushback, even by pushing back against this thing, you have that thing
on the internet called the Streisand Effect.
The more you fight against something, the more popular or the more well-known the thing
you're fighting against becomes.
This is an explosive study that is ready to rock the world of psychiatry.
Depression.
Let's talk about depression real quick.
I've obviously gone through bouts of depression.
A long time ago I remember I was in depression when I first moved up here and I was prescribed
what was described as a low dose of Prozac.
It was basically just a low dose.
They said, "I've talked about this before on the show."
They go, "You're going to start taking this stuff.
You're going to have some weird dreams, dude."
They did not prepare me for how weird my dreams were.
I remember vividly, I don't even like bringing this up because I'm afraid that it's true.
I remember vividly dreaming that my mom and my stepdad murdered my sister.
Murdered my sister and they had buried her and I didn't have anything to do with the
murder but I knew about it.
I remember she was buried underneath a swimming pool.
At a YMCA, it was like a gymnasium swimming pool.
She was buried underneath it.
My sister's not dead.
She definitely wasn't murdered.
I remember waking up and I was terrified that I had unlocked some lost memory.
I didn't even want to tell anyone because what if it was true?
What if I had forgotten that my sister had gone missing?
I have a very strong sense of self.
I spent a lot of time alone.
Before I did the podcast, when I had a job where I had three days off and a row, it was
awesome.
Of course, I started doing the podcast.
For those three days, I wouldn't utter a single word.
I lived alone.
I wasn't out and about.
And basically, from the time I got home on what would be my Friday to the time I showed
up to work on my Monday, I'd have three days where I wouldn't say a word.
So I was constantly in my thoughts.
I didn't even notice I was going through that until I realized it.
I'd done that for months and months.
I was like, "Wow, I go three days without saying anything.
I've always been a fairly introspective person.
I recharge by being alone.
I'm constantly surrounded by people.
I can't relax.
I have to have moments, long moments where I'm by myself.
So I have a very strong sense of self.
I know how my brain works.
I know how my thought patterns work.
So when I started taking medication that was in effect changing things in my brain, I could
tell.
Going back, I was taking the Prozac and I could ... I remember when I was taking it, it tapers
off eventually, this feeling.
But I thought, I understand why a lot of SSRI drugs, why a lot of antidepressants have
black box warnings saying this can cause you to kill yourself or to hurt other people and
stuff like that.
Because if you didn't have a strong sense of self, of all of a sudden you started taking
a medication and you began having intrusive thoughts and you had never had intrusive thoughts
before or you started having these dreams that make you question reality.
I understand.
I go, "I get why teenagers shouldn't be taking this stuff."
Right?
It's very controversial for teenagers to be taking this stuff.
And I'd argue anyone without a strong sense of self.
And I remember I stopped taking it because I started working out more.
I was exercising all the time and I was like, "I feel great.
I don't need this medication anymore."
So I just stopped.
This is not medical advice podcast.
I remember I ran into my doctor at Safeway and I was like, "Hey, what's up man?"
We were talking a bit and I said, "Hey, I stopped taking that Prozac."
And he was kind of like, "Uh-oh, okay."
And I said, "Well, I've been working out a lot.
I've been working out a lot and I just feel good."
And I remember this very important to me.
He goes, "That's fine."
He goes, "You don't have to take it."
He goes, "It's such a low dose anyways."
He goes, "But you have to treat your workouts like medicine.
You got to do them every day."
Some form of exercise every single day.
You have to treat it like it's treatment.
That's a very good piece of advice.
But then, you know, obviously stuff happens.
And I remember I was kind of going, I wasn't really super.
Every so often, just not like a normal person, you have good moments and bad moments and
sometimes you're a little more depressed than others.
I remember at this point, I was talking, I had the same doctor.
A couple of years had passed and I was talking about, you know, feeling anxious, feeling down
and stuff like that.
And I was there to get treated for something else.
And he goes, "Well, for the depression, we can put you back on the low dose of Prozac."
And I said, "Pills aren't going to pay my bills."
And kind of chuckled.
He kind of chuckled.
And he goes, "Yeah, that's true."
Because here's the thing.
This is the way that, I don't know if it's because I'm a boomer.
This is the way that I was always, this is how I view depression.
There's two types, obviously.
There are people with chemical imbalances in their brains.
Right?
But for most people, depression is a series of events that are happening in a fairly
rapid order or maybe just one or two really heavy events that makes you depressed.
There are people out there who have bipolar disorder.
That is a brain chemical thing, right?
And then there are people who just like, "Wow, I can't believe the string of bad luck I've
had."
And it makes you depressed.
You go, "What's the point of even going on?"
You may not even be that depressed when you're thinking about ending it, but you're just
like, "Am I ever going to get out of this hole?
Are things ever going to change?"
Now what I figured was that people just knew that.
People just understood that there were different types of depression.
But recently I read this article, and this has been super controversial.
There was an article written in The Guardian by Andrew Gregory.
This was published back on July 20, 2022.
So I was on vacation when this popped out.
What it is, is that the way that depression, whether or not it is, we're going to remove
the bipolar thing, clinical depression, out of this.
We're going to talk about the depression where people go to the doctor and say, "Hey man,
things aren't working out for me.
I'm really depressed."
You got something for that.
The doctors go, "We do.
It's called an SSRI drug."
They're used by boosting serotonin levels.
So if you have low serotonin, you're more likely to be depressed.
So if we can boost the serotonin, at least you won't be depressed.
You still have to go through the motions in life, but this won't make you depressed.
And what happened was this serotonin theory came out in the 1960s, and by the 1980s the
pharmaceutical companies go, "Well, if depression is caused by low serotonin, we'll just make
a drug that ups the levels of serotonin."
And that has been the treatment for day-to-day depression for decades, right, for just standard
depression.
People go to the doctor and say, "I'm depressed.
We all know these pills exist.
We all know the doctors will prescribe them.
So we'll go here."
Recently, the University of College in London did a huge study led by Joanna Moncrief.
She's a professor of psychiatry there.
This is basically what the study says.
There is, quote, "No convincing evidence that depression is caused by serotonin abnormalities,
particularly by lower levels or reduced activity of serotonin."
This says that, "There is nothing to back up that theory at all.
That theory at this point is what, 60 years old, and there is no proof for it."
And what they did was they went over all of these existing case studies, and they said,
"Depression is not likely caused by a reduction of serotonin."
Some of these studies, they would artificially reduce people's serotonin levels, and they
did not suffer from depression.
So if the low serotonin level made you depressed, how come we can't replicate that?
They said, in some of these studies, we looked at the use of SSRI drugs, lowered the serotonin
level.
We didn't actually do what it was supposed to do in that particular person.
And what I thought was, this was when I read this, I remember reading this in the morning,
I wake up every morning, I read the news, I remember I chuckled to myself and I go,
"Dah, this was one of the quotes from this article in The Guardian."
It said, "Other studies," that they were researching, "other studies looked at the
effects of stressful life events and found that the more stressful life events a person
had experienced, the more likely they were to be depressed, showing the importance of
external events."
And I was like, is that not common knowledge?
And apparently, let's say you've had a bad run of things, right?
You go to the doctor, you say, "Hey man, things aren't working out for me, I'm really depressed."
They can prescribe you SSRI drugs to boost your serotonin level, but that's not necessarily
what causes the depression is the low serotonin level.
And what's interesting is in the article in The Guardian and Joanne Moncrief, they've
all said, "Listen, this is not saying stop taking your meds, this is 100% saying throw
them all in the garbage."
Because the problem is, there are bad side effects to just quit taking these.
The question that people are saying who are in support of this survey is, this is interesting.
They go, "There has been a debate behind the scenes whether or not serotonin levels cause
depression, but that debate is not known to the general public."
To the point that if you ask the random person on the street what causes depression, they
generally will say serotonin levels.
It is a common misconception that that is settled science.
Low serotonin levels equal depression, so high serotonin levels equals no depression,
so give me something to boost my serotonin.
That is not settled science.
And that debate has been going on behind the scenes, but it hasn't reached the general
public and now it has, almost in this whisper war.
And the other side of the psychiatry debate, they go, "Listen, we don't know how this stuff
works."
That was a common thing, they go, "You're right, we don't know how SSRI drugs make you
not depressed, but they do."
Same way that they don't know how science, apparently I just found this out, they don't
know how Tylenol reduces a headache, they haven't figured that out, but it does.
That was a comparison that was constantly being used.
We don't know why Tylenol makes the pain go away in your head, but it does.
They said, "We don't know why SSRI drugs work, but they do."
And then, I mean, at that point you have to open up the whole placebo thing, right?
If a doctor, if a medical professional gives you something and says, "This is going to make
you less depressed," is how much of that is the placebo factor?
They've even gone after the other side of the psychiatry argument who are saying, "No,
you have to keep taking these.
Let us debate behind the scenes that keep taking these."
They've criticized Montcrey for being a "radical" against the pharmaceutical industry, saying,
"Listen, she has a bone to pick with these people."
Absolutely, for lack of a better word, insane, right?
It really is.
It really is because these drugs are prescribed so readily.
Now, I was lucky I had, you know, I've always had really good luck with doctors, right?
My doctor could have been like, "No, you got to get back on those, buddy.
It'll help you out."
I've always had really good rapport with my doctors and they kind of know my journey
and where I want to end up, where I want to go.
So, he's like, "Yeah, dude, you don't need that stuff.
Anyways, just work out all the time."
But I mean, these drugs, I mean, listen, I'm not telling you to stop taking them at all.
At all.
I'm not telling you to stop taking them.
And there are people who need them, right?
People who do feel better on them.
But I think for the general public, I think the problem is the debate is not...
I didn't know that at all.
I mean, obviously, I chuckled because I always figured there was a good chunk of people who...
It was external life stressors that made them depressed.
Apparently, other people have to get a study on this, right?
They have to have a study done to show that depression is caused by external life events
that seems like such a no-brainer, really.
But they're just reading the studies and they're being told stuff and they're like, "Here
you go."
And then you take this and it really does.
Those first couple days, maybe a week, it really messes with your head.
I can understand why it's super dangerous.
I had a strong sense of self so I could realize those thoughts weren't...
Not thoughts, even, it was just like the dreams.
The dreams were so bizarre.
But when I woke up, I was terrified.
I honestly thought I had unearthed the memory of my parents killing my sister and I was like...
In that moment, when I woke up, that was one of the times I can remember feeling the loneliest
I ever did.
And I liked being alone.
That was like, soul lost in the darkness loneliness.
I felt like my parents had murdered my sister and I was the only person on earth who knew
that and I didn't know what to do next.
And I was going to have this guilt, this just guilt over my shoulders for the rest of my
life.
I mean, it was super weird.
Like I've...
It's one of the loneliest times I ever felt in my life and it was all in my head.
It was all made up.
And if you didn't...
So yeah, take them if you need to.
But I think that we should know this stuff.
We should know that it doesn't work.
If a doctor goes, "We don't know how it works, but it works."
That's better than just saying, "Yeah, it works."
Crazy, crazy science and conspiracy theory story.
I'm surprised this isn't bigger in the world of conspiracy theory as well.
Because I know they get tied into school shootings and stuff like that.
A lot of these school shooters, these young men, they get prescribed these type of drugs.
I'm surprised.
But again, like I said, it's kind of hard to find the articles on it.
And if you don't know what you're looking for and yeah, the debate is raging, however.
And the two sides are, they don't work or we don't know how they work.
Those are the two sides, right?
But either way, don't make any rash decisions.
I'm not saying to quit them or anything like that.
Don't take medical advice from a man in a haunted closet.
Sniper, let's go ahead and leave behind the psychiatrist's office.
I'm going to touch the keys to the world-famous carbonicopter.
We're headed all the way out to Australia.
I want to give a shout out.
I found most of this information on a website called abookofcreatures.com.
Really cool resource about cryptids, famous ones and obscure ones.
Kind of sucks that there's a note, like the most recent update saying we're on an indefinite
hiatus and that has been since July 2021.
So that sucks.
Whenever we lose a compatriot, whenever we lose a soldier in the war of the weird, someone
out there cataloging this stuff, writing articles, doing podcasts, it sucks.
But you see it a lot actually.
I think there is kind of a high burnout rate.
We have this resource for now.
If you're into that, I recommend checking it out because who knows how long it's going
to be up, right?
Abookofcreatures.com gave me a bunch of this information.
We're headed to Australia.
In Australia, there is a cryptid, a creature, a monster that is almost unparalleled to anything
we've covered before on this podcast.
Because the question is, how much do you value your own life?
Very rarely do cryptids make you think of these questions.
In Australia, in the forested regions along the coast sits up high in a tree the Yara
Ma Yahoo.
The Yara Ma Yahoo.
Let's take a look at this guy.
Up in the trees in Australia, preferably in the fig trees is where this little dude likes
to hang out.
Yara Ma Yahoo.
He's actually quite huge.
I don't even know how he gets up there.
I guess when you're a cryptid, you're just allowed to do things.
He's about four feet tall.
He's a quadruped, right?
He's a creature that runs on its hands and its legs.
He's about four feet tall and has this huge toothless mouth.
Almost imagine like a giant red furry frog.
He's all bristly and stuff like that.
Like a frog, he does have suction cups on his fingers and his feet.
He loves to hang out in trees waiting for his prey because the thing with this thing
is although it's a carnivore, it can't run.
It can't run fast at all.
If you see one and you're able to get away from it, it will just kind of waddle after
you.
So that's why its main form of hunting is just sitting there.
Sitting there waiting for someone to walk by.
It'll sit up in the tree for a couple of days waiting for someone to wander through its
forest.
And what happens is, imagine this, you're walking through a forest, you're having a
good time, and then all of a sudden a four foot tall creature fell on top of you.
That alone is going to throw you off your game.
You're just not going to expect it.
If someone threw a blanket on you in the forest, that would be scary enough.
But imagine this creature seems fairly heavy.
I'm imagining he's like a hundred pounds, a hundred, two hundred pounds.
That falling on you out of the middle of nowhere would freak you out.
That's not all he does.
What happens is those suction cups on his hands and his feet, they're not just for climbing,
they're for sucking blood.
So what he does is he puts his hands on you.
I'm assuming he takes your shirt off first.
He's like, ooh nice abs, you've been working out.
It starts sucking the blood out through his fingers and his toes.
You're like, ah.
And as you're laying there in the dirt, this creature you didn't even know existed feeding
off of your vital fluid, you're probably thinking, oh man, this can't get worse.
This is what they're talking about external factors relating to depression.
These creatures drink in me.
But he doesn't, he's not a full on vampire, right?
He doesn't drink enough of you to kill you.
He just drinks enough blood from you to make you pass out.
After you've passed out, something insidious happens.
This little dude opens his mouth and starts to swallow you whole.
You're like, Jason, Jason, this is another one of your creepy, your creepy vor stories.
He starts, after I described you as taking your shirt off, I was like, oh, and then you
get oiled up.
You get oil, your skin's all oily and the sun.
The Yara Mayahu begins to swallow you whole.
It doesn't have any teeth, so it's pretty easy.
Plus it can dislodge its jaw and its stomach distends.
So it can swallow a full grown man.
And as he's swallowing you, he gets stuck.
And so this is adorable.
This is the cutest thing encrypted's ever done.
What happens is the Yara Mayahu then has to do a little dance to make you wiggle into
your old boogie down in his stomach.
Because you're, let's say you're 5'11", he's only four feet long, so he has to roll
you up in a ball and by him doing that dance and shaking his little groove thing, you're
sliding more into his stomach.
But because his stomach distends eventually, he's still only four feet, well, I guess he
wouldn't be four feet tall.
He'd be four feet tall with a rolled up man in his stomach.
So now you're being digested in his stomach.
You're back to consciousness and you find yourself kind of pushing against, oh, let me
out of here, let me out of here.
You're getting sl-
You're slightly aroused and you're like, give me a-
You're fighting that arge, you're like, oh, please, let me go.
After he's swallowed you completely, he takes a drink of water and takes a nap.
So you're like chilling out in his belly and stuff like that and he's sleeping.
But eventually he wakes up and then he vomits you out.
And you just slide out of his stomach through his flush lips.
I don't really have a vorfetish.
It's just so funny because I get so many emails when I cover stories like this.
You slide out, you're like waving goodbye, you're like bye, yara, my yahoo.
You're sliding out, you're covered in puke and you're laying there on the ground in
the middle of this Australian forest.
And this is what makes this creature so fascinating.
This is what makes this story so interesting is because now you have to ask yourself a
question.
This creature is feared in these areas of Australia.
So the legend is well known of what happens when you run into one of these yara, my yahoo.
You've just been-
You had some of your blood sucked out.
You've been swallowed, digested a little bit and then vomited back out.
And you're fully conscious at this point.
You have a choice.
You can get up and just run away.
The yara, my yahoo cannot chase you.
It is so slow.
It doesn't have any sort of teleportation powers.
It doesn't move quicker through the trees or anything like that.
It's like a trapped door spider.
It waits for the prey to come to you.
You can take off running.
But if you get up and start running away, the yara, my yahoo will start yelling at you.
As you're running away, it will yell out, "Where have you gone, my victim?"
You just keep running.
You run, run, run.
And if you turn around, you'll see him waddling after you.
Now if you- you can easily outrun this guy, right?
If you run away, you don't get what's coming next.
Because that's not all he does.
Trust me, it gets worse.
After he throws you up, you have the ability to run away, get up and run away.
If you run away, what the yara, my yahoo does, he becomes enraged that his food got away.
So he then goes all over the region and drinks up every drop of water.
Every lake, every pond, every well built in your local community will run dry.
So you've basically doomed everybody near you.
You've destroyed them.
You've destroyed the local community.
If you get away from it, it will punish everybody.
So knowing that, knowing that you're laying on the ground in the middle of this forest,
this creature has just sucked out some of your blood and swallowed you and then did a
little dance and took a nap.
And now it's vomited you up knowing that would you run.
Because you could be like, yeah dude, I'm just a tourist.
I'm just going to hop on a plane and go back to where I'm from.
But it would.
It would drink up all the water in the area.
So what you do if you are a team player, you just take one for the team.
And the yara, my yahoo, as you're laying there, right, you're basically pretending to be unconscious.
You're fully awake at this point.
The yara, my yahoo will check to see if you're unconscious or even dead at this point, right?
He's already digested a little bit of you.
So he will walk up and he'll poke you with a stick and then he waddles away.
And then he comes back and he tickles you.
You can't do, you're half digested, the lips are all, you're smiling.
He tickles you and you don't react to that.
So then he walks even farther away.
He walks away about 50 yards.
He comes back, he tickles you more.
And then once he realizes that yes, you are still unconscious and/or dead, he takes another
nap.
Now you figure, well, Jason, that would kind of, you're basically asking someone to run
away and you're like, "Koochie, koochie, koo, you're already half digested.
I mean, it's not tickling as much as it would hurt."
Why would he do that?
Why he's basically asking them to run away?
Apparently, this is so bonkers.
Like, in America, we have Bigfoot.
This is what Australia's thing is.
There's a whole ecosystem.
If the Yaramah Yahu does not do this, so the Yaramah Yahu does not do this ritual, there
is a spirit living in the fig trees in Australia that drives the Yaramah Yahu insane.
It starts whispering in his ears and that whisper becomes louder and louder and louder and louder
and then silence.
Real silence.
Like, all of reality has gone mute.
And at that point, the Yaramah Yahu's soul leaves its body and the body just kind of
falls there and turns into a patch of glowing mushrooms.
So, why are you ever in Australia?
Bring me home some glowing mushrooms because that's pretty dope, right?
That's really dope.
I'd have a little bit of a Yaramah Yahu in my house.
I don't even know if the glowing mushrooms are real.
That is now the life cycle.
That is the food chain of the cryptids.
Absolutely bizarre.
But anyways, the Yaramah Yahu, he tickles you, pokes you with a stick, you don't react,
it thinks you're unconscious.
Now, the most terrifying thing of all happens.
You had your choice to run away and to save yourself, but knowing that you would doom
your community.
So you stayed there.
And then it starts to swallow you again.
Awww, swallowing you.
You're like, head first this time.
Woohoo!
I can enjoy it even longer and I'm fully conscious.
He starts to swallowing you and he's doing his little dance to kind of shuffle you into
his distended belly and you're kind of just sitting in there for a bit.
And then he goes, "Brrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
Really kind of figure out what's going on.
You're
in
.
He will totally transmogrify you into this creature, living in the forest, looking for
its next meal.
of the
two
three
of the
two
three
of the