A woman has an encounter with a strange man, and it almost kills her.
And then we take a look at the absolutely most bizarre conspiracy theory going around right now, and that's a high bar.
Our 5G towers actually causing the coronavirus today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys had a great weekend.
We got a lot of stuff to cover. We're gonna get started right now.
First off, we have to give a shout out to our latest Patreon, Mr. Twister.
Give a hand for Mr. Twister. Really, really appreciate the support.
Means a lot. Helps keep the show going. If you can't support the show via Patreon though, that's fine too.
Just help get the word out about the show. I know it's a little bit harder now that everyone's locked inside,
but whatever online form you're at, just say, "Hey man, I'm checking out this podcast."
You should listen to it. It's really, really dope.
And the guy has a really handsome sounding voice.
Second thing we gotta talk about real quick, and Mr. Twister again, thank you so much.
You'll be getting the keys to the Carpenter copter in a second.
But before we do that, Friday night we had the Dead Rabbit Movie Club. I had a lot of fun doing that.
Tonight's movie, if you want to join the movie club, you can watch it on Shutter, or I'm sure you can find it in other places as well.
Housewife. It's a movie called Housewife.
It's about a young woman who witnessed the murder of her sister, and was never able to get over it,
until she meets a self-help guru/cult leader who is willing to go to any lengths to help her resolve her problems.
It's really good. I watched it yesterday.
It's really good. Check it out. Housewife. It's available on Shutter, and you can find it in other places as well.
Let's go ahead and get started with the episode here. That's the first episode of the movie club for this week, though.
Let's get started with the episode.
Mr. Twister, fire up that Carpenter copter. We are flying out to...
Unknown City, USA.
Actually, to be fair, I don't know if it's in the United States. That's my own bias.
All the cool stories take place in the USA.
[hums]
Helicopters landing, things twister. The thing is, I don't know where the story takes place.
This was a story I found off of Reddit. It's very telling, and I think it actually kind of leads into our next topic as well.
This is an interesting one.
March 27th, 2020.
We're walking through the streets of Unknown City, USA.
And there is a Reddit user there. We're just going to call her Tori. That's a name I made up.
If that's actually her real name, that's not as far as I know. But anyways, Tori is walking on the street.
And we're walking on the street behind her. That sounds creepy. No, we're not.
We are... We're wearing a trench coat, right? And I'm the bottom person, and you're on my shoulder so you can see the story.
I already see the story. For some reason, that's not... That's less creepier than following her.
But anyways, we're watching Tori walk down the street.
She's walking her little doggies, right? Little doggie people are walking.
[imitates dog barking]
And she looks down an alley, and she sees a bizarre sight.
She sees a man sitting on like an old steamer trunk.
Like one of those big old trunks she would see in like some Agatha Christie movie, right?
Or just if you took a train today, they may still be there, I don't know.
But it was like an old-timey trunk. There was a man sitting on it smoking a cigarette.
And you're thinking, "That's not bizarre. That's actually less bizarre than me sitting on your shoulders as we're both in a trench coat."
And I go, "Well, true, but something about it made her feel off."
And she's walking, and she's on the opposite side of the street, so she's looking down the alleyway across the street and she sees the guy.
Something about it made her feel that this is out of place.
And she decides, "I'm gonna continue my walk, but when I'm coming back the other way, I'm gonna cross the street, and if he's still there, I'm gonna talk to him."
Now, it's kind of a bold move, right? You have the woman cross the street now.
Tori is now walking back home. So now she is walking on that side of the street, and she's walking.
And she doesn't see him in that first alley now. She sees him in a different alley, and he's comically slipping and sliding on ice.
Whoa, whoa, like Mr. Bean, basically.
Now, she doesn't really go into like his body proportions, but when I read the story, no matter how many times I've read the story,
because I read it once, then I had to read it again, prep reading the notes, and now I'm reading it to you, basically.
A picture of him is tall and gangly, and a bit older, but she never did--it's weird, because the story kind of fills in those details,
and I wonder if you--I picture him kind of gangly and stuff.
Anyways, whoa, whoa, whoa, he keeps slipping and sliding on ice, kind of like that scene from Bambi, but he doesn't have four legs.
He just can't find his balance on the ice.
Now, she says that her dogs are normally pretty, like, yippee, yippee, yippee, yippee, yippee, yippee.
One is always kind of angry, and one's super hyper, but this time, when this guy is having these--because now they're on the same side of the street.
It's just a different alleyway, as he's slipping and sliding on the ice.
Neither dogs respond to what's going on, which she finds very odd, because the hyper one wants lots of loves and kisses,
and the other one wants to beat, like, beat everyone up. They're both tiny, though.
She does start to approach him, though, and she says everything about him seemed old,
but in that sense--again, she wasn't really talking about his physical age.
She was specifically mentioning the clothing. The clothing looked out of date,
just like the big steamer trunk looked out of date and out of time.
She's getting closer and closer to him, and she goes, "Do you need any help?"
Like, he obviously needs help, right? The guy can't stand up on ice.
He obviously needs help, and he goes, "No. No, no, no, I'm fine."
He's still trying to get somewhere across the ice, and she goes, "Where are you headed?"
And he goes, "I'm headed to, like, this place."
And she didn't recognize that place. She had never heard of that place.
Now, it wasn't like Gumbo Land. It was like a restaurant or a store or something like that.
It wasn't like, "I'm going back to the mythical realm of Osreel."
No, no, no, it was like a place, like a department store, something like that.
We'll get to that detail in a second.
But she asks, "Where are you going?" And he said, "This place."
And then she goes, "Well, I hope you get there safely."
Because he's obviously having some trouble just standing up in an alleyway.
And, "I wish I could do more for you," as she says.
And then he turns to her and says, "Quote, you did exactly what you needed to, sweetheart.
Thank you."
And then he just continued. He finally got his footing and walked down the alleyway and turned.
And then she never saw him again.
Now, she goes home. She looks up the place. She's curious.
The whole encounter was really weird.
So she looks at the place he said he was going.
[GASP]
That place closed down 50 years ago.
Now, obviously, we don't know this person's real name.
It's on Reddit. They have a username.
They don't-- We don't know what city takes place in or what the business was.
We can't verify any of the particular facts.
So, is the story true or not?
We, as an audience, don't know. This was on the Reddit account or this was on the Reddit forum.
The truth is here, which has a lot of stuff like this.
Most of it is, "I woke up and my cat possessed me and now I want milk."
Just really, like, people with obvious-- Obvious mental problems, I think.
I'm not saying she has one, but I'm saying you get a lot of that stuff and then you get some legit stuff.
Things like that. But anyways, you have this here.
Now, the story itself. The girl walking down the street.
She turns the corner and there's a man out of time.
That's typical dead rabbit radio fare.
There's not enough meat to that story, so you jump up off my shoulders.
Now, I'm taking off the trench coat. I have normal clothes on underneath. Don't worry.
Don't worry. And we're standing there in the street and you go, "So, is that the story?"
And I go, "No, no, no. That's the preamble."
Because while that story is interesting, that's-- It's just a man out of time.
Now we get to the meat of this. Now, this story takes place March 27th, 2020.
Let me read you a bit more of this Reddit post.
This is the actual quote.
"Since then, things haven't been the same.
I have chronic, life-limiting health problems, but I've never felt like I was going to die soon
the way I've felt since this encounter."
Okay, let me remind you one more time before I read this next sentence.
This is March 27th, 2020.
"Short of breath, blew around the lips, pale, and no, no exposure to the virus.
Waking up from strange dreams and a cold sweat, a constant foreboding feeling.
I'm going to die soon. I even had a seizure."
Now, now, now.
"At any other point in human history, if someone said, 'I saw a ghost and now I have a fever,
I can't breathe, my lips are turning blue, my face is turning blue,'"
I feel like I'm going to die at any moment.
People would probably go, "Whoa, dude, this ghost."
The rest of the Reddit responses were, "Go to the doctor, dude."
You basically had 30 comments saying, "Go to the doctor!
You obviously have been exposed to the coronavirus!
What are you doing typing this out?
Go to the doctor."
And then, pretty much, I found this thread when it first happened, right?
And I was like, "What? I'm reading it."
Because a lot of this stuff, I skim because I read a ton of this stuff and it's like,
"At the end, you can tell it's a lark, you can tell it's whatever."
And I remember reading this and I'm being like, "Oh my God, this poor girl is dead."
And you just saw the comments fill up, "Go to the doctor.
Go to the doctor, please!
Comment after comment."
And it's funny because normally, in these types of threads,
you'll have people go, "Oh my God, the ghost must be in you.
Say this or go to this location and get it cured."
So what happened was she--
There was basically-- the thread went quiet.
Basically, people were like, "Dude, I hope she's still alive."
And then, maybe a day or two passed and she said, "Thank you, guys.
I went to the doctor and I was having some breathing issues."
She still has never said that she actually did have the coronavirus,
but I think the timing of the post and everyone being very aware of the signs of breathing difficulties right now
got her to go to the emergency room where she did get tested
and they gave her a bunch of breathing treatments.
Apparently, she does have, like she said at the beginning, some lingering health issues.
But almost died!
She in her post with, "I'm terrified.
I don't know what I saw, but I don't think it was anything good.
I wish I could go back and unsee it.
Maybe then none of this would be happening."
So I guess she does really combine the fact that she had shortness of breath
and her lips were turning blue to the fact that she saw this site.
Now, when she came back, when she comes back after saying, "Thank you, guys.
I did go get medical treatment because I was having, I was basically dying."
When your face is turning blue and your lips are turning blue,
that is the point where you need to be in the emergency room at Rhymes.
She said, "I still 100% believe I saw what I saw."
Like, that is, I was having this health issue, but I 100% saw this thing the day before.
But this woman could easily died.
And again, I think if she had posted this six months earlier,
when people weren't looking for the signs and people weren't aware,
I didn't know blue lips was a sign of someone about to suffocate.
I never knew that.
And now I do.
And, um, yeah, interesting, though.
The fact that a bunch of fellow weirdos on Reddit,
but yeah, and Anne, I just checked again today, she's still posting on Reddit,
she's still alive and healthy.
You know what? Here's my theory. Here's my theory.
Think about this. What if she was walking on the street and didn't see the creepy old man
and just her lips turned blue and she didn't get it treated and she died?
Maybe the old man was there so she would post on Reddit,
so a bunch of people would tell her to go to the hospital.
Hmm, hmm.
Maybe the old man wasn't a spooky old man,
but a guardian angel sent to save her life.
Also in the future mess, if you're listening to this podcast,
just go to the hospital for medical problems. Don't post on Reddit.
Let's go ahead and move on, but it's good that she didn't.
And I'm, we were all concerned that she was going to die,
but she didn't and that's good.
Let's go ahead and move on.
It's always good when humans don't die.
I didn't know if you needed to hear that from me.
Let's move on to our next subject here.
Our next subject is breaking news.
I actually didn't plan for this to be today's topic.
I had something else planned.
That'll be on tomorrow's episode.
Mr. Twister, fire up that carbonicopter.
We're headed out to Britain.
We're flying over the ocean.
We're heading on out.
We are headed and we know we're getting close to Britain
because we see plumes of smoke.
Just pouring out over the continent.
We can barely see the Emerald Isle, which is Ireland,
but we're flying over that before we get to Britain.
Bring us lower, Twister.
We're now flying among the cities we're going over.
Do they have skyscrapers in Britain?
Everything looks awfully small over there.
What's their tallest building?
Like 20 stories.
I think, I mean, like, is there anything bigger
than Big Ben over there?
Technically, there shouldn't be
because then it's not Big Ben anymore.
I saw this documentary once called G.I. Joe Retaliation
and they dropped this giant metal spear from the sky, right?
And it crashed into Britain and completely pulverized
the entire city of England.
And the buildings looked awfully small.
Those CGI buildings that got destroyed
as the Earth's mantle got rippled by that giant rod of God,
which is supposedly a real weapon.
I know G.I. Joe's not real.
Okay, no G.I. Joe's not real.
But supposedly if you drop a tungsten,
a big enough piece of tungsten,
or probably really any metal,
but I think tungsten, I just like that word, tungsten,
falls from the sky
and there's no explosive tipper whatsoever.
The gravity of it, when it hits the Earth,
will cause a explosion greater than or equal to a nuclear bomb
and you just kind of just let them fall.
I think they'd be kind of hard to aim.
I mean, I'm not saying the wind's going to be pushing them around,
but like, you're like fire, what?
What did you say? Fire in that delay, like that short delay.
Is the difference between hitting England or hitting Moscow?
And they probably have people working at the command centers
with better hearing too.
They're probably not like, what'd you say?
They're like, you can't work here.
If whenever someone says, hey, give me a cup of coffee,
you go, what'd you say?
Because eventually you're going to have to press a button
and launch a missile.
Like you can have a laser guided missile,
but you can't have a laser guided rock fall from the sky.
Anyways, I don't think England has tall buildings.
So we're flying among their teeny tiny buildings in England.
[imitates laser guidance]
We find the source of all these plumes of smoke.
They're cell phone towers.
More specifically, 5G cell phone towers.
Dun, dun, dun.
Now we've talked about 5G technology before.
It's this new loony bin conspiracy theory that,
I did a whole episode on it a while back, but basically,
so 5G, so your phone right now is probably 4G.
It's the cellular technology.
5G has smaller millimeter waves.
So you get like a better talk quality, better sound quality,
and your phones, the streaming services are faster and stuff
like that, but you need, because the waves are smaller,
you need to have more cell towers in an area.
Instead of a cell tower, say every 20 miles,
you have to have a cell tower every 500 yards or something
like that.
So you would have them all over a city.
The conspiracy theory for a while was that 5G caused you
to kill yourself.
That was a big conspiracy theory going around for a long time.
That the 5G penetrates your, "Oh, it's going through my cells.
Oh my God, it's messing with the water in me."
Does that.
There's this real famous doctor, scientist guy from the
University of Washington.
His name is Martin Paul.
He said that eventually it would make us all sterile.
Once it all gets rolled out, it'll make us sterile within
three years, and then eight years later,
it'll make us all brain dead.
Martin Paul saying that your brains are going to melt after
eight years of having all the 5G turned on.
No rational person wants everyone's brains melted because
they're human as well, right?
So the conspiracy theory is involving 5G has been going
around for a long time, but now it's hit a fever pitch,
because now in Britain, within the past week,
seven to eight 5G cell phone towers have been set on fire
because of the coronavirus.
This is a really interesting one.
I talked about this recently a couple episodes ago.
I said, "If you thought the conspiracy theories that came
out of 9/11 were crazy, you haven't seen anything yet."
That's actually, I underestimated that,
because I said after this is all done,
and the thing when you look at the 9,
and so they're already starting, they're going full bore on
this, and after 9/11, you know, after 9/11,
so I used to live in Orangevale, California.
We had a lot of peckerwoods out there.
If you don't know what peckerwood is,
it's basically a white supremacist street gang,
a way of life.
It's kind of like a West Side redneck peckerwoods.
We had a lot of peckerwoods hanging out there.
A lot of white supremacists where I grew up.
And I remember we had a mailman who was Sikh, really nice guy.
He had the, not the turban, and they're not called the turban,
but you know the headrest, the head, not the headrest,
the head thing, right?
And he was a nice guy, Sikh.
After 9/11, probably about two weeks after 9/11,
now, to be, and the Sikhs are not Muslim,
but even if he was Muslim, he would not have excused
what was going to happen.
But he was delivering mail, probably a block or two
from my grandma's house, where I lived on and off
for a lot of my time in Sacramento.
About two, three weeks after 9/11,
he was delivering mail, probably about a block or two
from my grandma's house, and a dude came out of the house,
shot him in the neck,
because he was one of them dirty Muslims,
put a bullet through him.
He lived, shockingly lived,
so it probably was a graze.
It probably wasn't a straight like through the carotid.
Doesn't matter.
He shot in the neck, is a shot in the neck.
So we had incidents like that,
but as far as people actually,
that I think was a people going,
we're at war, and that guy's the enemy.
And unfortunately, that guy was delivering mail in an area.
They had a lot of white supremacy.
And again, not people who were simply racist,
people who would beat up minorities.
Again, not people who are like,
"What a black captain on Star Trek.
I'm not watching that show."
These were people that would shoot you in the neck
if they thought you were Muslim.
That's where I grew up, guys.
So anyways, you have that.
This is a conspiracy theory
where people are actively launching attacks against it
as it's going on.
I haven't seen anything like this.
When we look at other conspiracy theories,
like people who say Sandy Hook didn't happen.
It 100% did.
That's a complete myth that it didn't.
Anyways, people, that took years
before people knocking on doors.
What happened to your kid?
I think it was a fake.
All that, all that,
just that's absolutely disgusting.
All that stuff happened years after the Aurora movie shooting.
Someone shoots up movie theater two years later.
Did your son really die in that movie?
I mean, can you imagine saying that to somebody?
Anyways, that'll happen afterwards.
This is happening now.
People are setting 5G cell phone towers on fire in Britain.
There's some interesting questions to come out of this too.
My first question is why so far, why only Britain?
Makes you think it's probably the same person, right?
We're the same group of people.
We're not seeing this in other places, but...
That's an interesting part of this conspiracy.
Let's kind of jump into this.
Within the past week,
we've had seven to eight attacks on 5G towers in Britain.
People are setting them on fire.
The telecom companies in Britain
are now going to YouTube and Twitter
and saying, "You need to shut this down right now."
"You need to shut this down."
And YouTube said, "We will."
And this may get wrapped up in this too.
So this episode may only...
You might be hearing this on YouTube.
I think if you're a subscriber, you'll get it.
If you're listening to the podcast, you'll definitely get it.
The YouTube algorithm will probably kick this into a...
They use the term "suppression,"
but I think it's more of not promoting it.
So you may not get a notification for this episode.
It definitely won't be able to get demonetized.
Even though I'm against the conspiracy theory,
it's pretty likely that the bot will nab me and say,
"Uh-uh, this is just you."
Because right now, YouTube's setting it up
that if you use the words "5G" and "coronavirus" together,
or in the same, you're connecting that conspiracy,
they will not promote your video.
They'll limit how many people can see it, stuff like that.
Some people say that suppression.
I think it's really just equibling of words.
Right?
YouTube's a private platform, and they're going to do what they want,
and this show could get deplatformed from YouTube at any moment.
And like I said, if that happens,
we're just going to be straight on the podcast.
I'm not going to be upload.
I'm not going to play that game,
where I'm running around fighting YouTube and stuff like that.
So if the show ever does disappear from YouTube,
you know where to get it, Dead Rabbit Radio,
anywhere podcasts are available.
I'm not going to go to Bitshoot or anything like that.
The telecoms are saying, and other people are saying this,
this is actually a quote from Professor Adam Finn
from the University of Bristol.
He says, "The internet connections these network give us
are the most important tools we are using to coordinate
our response to the epidemic and efforts
to be researched to overcome it.
Damaging phone masts is like knocking holes in your lifeboats
while your ship sinks."
If all of these towers are knocked down,
or a percentage of them are knocked down,
it's going to cripple the cellular network over there.
They don't do it is what they're saying.
And that's why they're leaning on Twitter and YouTube
to take action against this.
What's interesting is that YouTube will put these videos down.
However, a video just about 5G conspiracies
not related to coronavirus, they will not touch.
They totally leave up.
That's fine.
It's the 5G and coronavirus videos that they're taking a look at.
And obviously if a human listened to this,
I think they'd go, "Oh, this is fine.
He's actually dismissing this conspiracy theory."
However, the algorithm again, this episode may not be on YouTube.
And if it is on YouTube, it may not be on YouTube for long.
You know, Jorge, I hate to mispronounce your name, buddy,
but on YouTube, Jorge Duarte posted a comment a while back
about how some people believe that coronavirus is a cover
to keep us all inside while they're installing 5G.
So we have another version of the conspiracy here
that 5G doesn't cause coronavirus.
That coronavirus is completely made up
so that 5G towers can be installed in schools
and all these other places
that we normally wouldn't let them put a cell tower.
Now, there's a conspiracy theory about everything.
I would love to see the back-to-school celebration
where a guy goes open this locker and there's a 5G tower in there
or they're having the prom.
And the theme is best millimeters ever.
And it's just like, everyone's absorbing on these millimeters.
There's a lot of conspiracy theories wrapped around the fact
that now while we're locked in our house,
something bigger is going on.
We're arresting Ellen DeGeneres.
We covered that.
Some people believe they're using this time to build more 5G towers
because we want to let them do it anyways.
But let's get back to this main conspiracy theory
because you go, "Okay, so YouTube is putting this stuff down.
Why is Twitter? Why is Twitter involved?
Are people tweeting this a bunch?"
Well, it's hard to tell right now
because it definitely want to hit trending.
But Woody Harrelson.
I like Woody Harrelson as an actor.
I think he's like, I admire what he's done.
He started off as a comedic actor playing a big old dummy,
a brain-dead dude on Cheers.
That's how old I am.
I was watching Cheers and it was originally on.
That's the prequel to Frasier for you millennials.
And then he goes on and does natural-born killers
and does all these dramas and true detective.
And he's funny.
He does Hunger Games.
He does all this stuff.
I like him as an actor.
The problem is is that when you're an actor or you're a celebrity,
when you simply tweet something,
people take it as meaning more than if someone else--
people take it as meaning more than someone else.
He tweeted this thing and he goes,
he says in it, "I got this from a friend of mine.
A lot of my friends--" and I'm paraphrasing,
"I got this from a friend of mine.
A lot of my friends are kind of scared of 5G.
They're not really sure of the health ramifications of this."
He goes, "I haven't vetted this yet,
but I thought I'd share it with you guys."
Well, if you haven't vetted it,
you probably shouldn't have shared it because I vetted it.
It says, "This is a conspiracy theory."
I know I've been beaten around the corner.
This is a conspiracy theory.
Wuhan was chosen to be the first city in China
that was going to be the smart city.
It was going to have more 5G connected towers
throughout the city than any other city in China.
It was chosen to be that one.
They had 5G towers everywhere.
It was going to-- everything was going to be connected.
The stoplights were all using 5G technology.
Everyone's phones are going to be super speedy.
And they did.
They put these towers all through Wuhan.
It was the very first city in China
and it turns out that that was the cause of what's going on.
Now, it's interesting because there's two versions of this conspiracy theory.
One is--
This is what the Lunatic--
This is what even the more Lunatic conspiracy theory is.
The coronavirus is caused by 5G.
The symptoms of coronavirus are the exact same thing
as the symptoms of exposure to these millimeter waves.
That's actually the crazier version.
What other people are saying and what this Woody Harrelson report is saying
and what I found mostly on the internet
is that the coronavirus is real,
but it normally wouldn't have affected us.
It's the fact that the 5G towers are messing up our immune system
is what is making us sick from this normal natural virus.
And it's weird because both of these are fighting for control right now.
So you have two competing conspiracy theory.
Both of them are stupid
and both of them are saying something that's not true
and they'll never agree with each other the same way that
the people who don't believe in conspiracy theory will believe in either one.
That's what's going on right now.
We have people who believe that 5G is making you sick.
The fluid in your lungs, the headaches, the scratchy throat, the blue lips,
it's all caused by 5G.
Other people say, "No, no, no, no, no. The 5G is just weakening our immune system."
What's funny is that that one is stupid,
but it's definitely more believable than 5G making you sick.
Why? Because we see symptoms of this disease where there's no 5G.
No one's really addressing that part of it yet.
But I bet you the next one will be 5G.
I don't know why they hate 5G so much, but 5G made the virus stronger.
That's why it's in Idaho.
There's no 5G in Idaho.
The 5G actually made the virus mutate.
But here, let's go back to this thing.
I could make up conspiracy theories all day long.
It's actually quite fun.
But here's the thing.
Wuhan is not the first city to go 100% smart in China.
It's not. I looked it up.
Not only did I look it up within 5 minutes,
I found it on a website that agrees in the conspiracy theory.
So I didn't find it on a debunker website.
I didn't find it on some-- I didn't find it on Snopes.
I found it on a website that actually had an article saying,
"Maybe this is true."
And in that article, it says 16 different cities in China were chosen
to all go smart at the same time.
Five of them have the exact same amount of towers in them.
Hengzhao, Shanghai, Guangzhou, Suzhou, and Wuhan.
So it's just 100% not true.
And I vetted it in 5 minutes.
And it's funny because when we look at that Reddit story,
there's no information to really vet, right?
The whole thing could have been a LARP.
We don't know.
But in this where they're like, "That was a fact."
It said Wuhan was the-- and I vetted and vetted and I checked it
and they said Wuhan was the first city to go smart in China.
It was selected to be-- that's 100% not true.
It was one of 16 and there was five other cities
that has an equal amount of towers in it.
So it's a flat out lie.
And that's what really bugs me about this stuff.
People are getting terrified.
People are terrified right now, obviously.
And people are using-- people are spreading that fear.
And they're lying.
But it doesn't even stop there
because there's another conspiracy theory.
That the cell-- this is completely ridiculous.
That the cell phone towers are not being set on fire
by conspiracy theorists protesting against 5G.
They're not being set on fire by people trying to shut down 5G
in their neighborhood because they believe it's causing coronavirus.
There are people who believe that the cell phone towers are so dangerous
they are bursting into flames all on their own.
That's how dangerous 5G technology is.
You just build a tower and it blows up in your neighborhood.
"Oh, we better shut down 5G."
A human didn't do that.
They just-- that's how evil this-- that's Satan coming out of the 5G.
That's actually another conspiracy theory.
I was on-- how much time have we been talking so far?
Alright, this is gonna be-- I think I've given up time--
time-- time episodes for the quarantine.
I hope you guys don't mind.
I was on Deadline Hollywood.
Actually, it's just called Deadline now.
My favorite source of entertainment news.
Very storied background.
Maybe I'll do an episode on that website because it's pretty interesting.
But anyways, I was reading Deadline.
They had an article saying Dr. Deborah Birx,
U.S.-- I don't know what her actual position is,
but she's always hanging out with Trump.
She's always at his press conferences.
She's a doctor.
She's one of the head people with this coronavirus thing.
She says, "For the next two weeks, don't even go grocery shopping.
Don't even go to the pharmacy.
Just stay at home unless you absolutely have to go.
Just stay at home for the next two weeks."
Reading this article-- it's on Deadline
because at this point pretty much every website is talking about this stuff.
I try to limit it on this show, but this is just breaking conspiracy news.
Reading this article, we get to the comments and I go,
"I can't wait to read what the comments are on this one."
"Didn't expect this."
I expected people to take the normal political stuff.
You know, people would be taken sides and all.
So that's kind of what I expected,
but it would probably just kind of have a weird entertainment slant.
I don't know.
I didn't expect this.
This is a comment from someone named Anne.
I'm going to read this the way that it's written.
"What's about new videos saying all this is a cover-up
from effects of implementation of 5G?
China was first to get 5G.
Then Italy and Spain."
That's not true.
I know that's not true.
So you're telling me that they put 5G--
Anne, this advocate of free speech,
is telling me they put 5G towers in China.
Everyone starts puking out blood.
And then Italy goes, "You know what we need?
We need some 5G."
And then they have this massive death rate.
And then Spain goes, "Hey, you know what?
We've been missing fast cellular service."
And all this stuff is going on.
But anyways, so that's not true.
That's not true.
And even if it was true, it's all over the world now.
It's in Africa.
It's in Australia.
They're in places where it's not 5G.
But anyways, let's go back to Anne here.
"China was the first to get 5G.
Then Italy and Spain.
Some caught in crossfire.
Big cities have 5G.
And after we are over with this,
the vaccine will contain a chip to track people.
New world order.
That is why stock market is down.
New money will be printed.
What is making us sick is the radiation from 5G.
All the virus is radiation kill people."
All a cover up, unquote.
So, um, that's kind of weird that she admits that 5G is cause of a radiation,
but we're getting a vaccine.
I guess the implication is that the vaccine will be fake.
But that goes into this other conspiracy theory that Bill Gates
wants to get everyone...
Now we're getting to this New World Order anti-Christ thing,
and this is the story that in the Bible,
you get to a point where in the Book of Revelation,
where the anti-Christ says, "If you want to buy or sell, you must have the mark."
You must have the mark.
If you get the mark of the beast, you're doomed.
Now this episode is really going in a weird direction.
If you get the mark of the beast, you're doomed to hell.
Because the mark of the beast is the complete rejection of Christ,
is the story in the Book of Revelation.
Now, it's be--
In the 1970s, this episode is going really long, in the 1970s,
there was a conspiracy theory that the barcode was the mark of the beast,
because in the barcode, the number 666 appears.
Apparently it was put in as a joke.
So there was this idea that everyone was going to get a barcode put on their hand,
and you would have to have it scanned in.
Have you guys ever watched that movie, "A Thief in the Night?"
I wonder if that holds up.
It was an old 1970s, late '70s, early '80s movie about the anti-Christ.
Scared me to death when I was a kid, "A Thief in the Night."
Because that was the thing, that was always the term,
"Jesus will come like a thief in the night. You'll never know when he's coming, so be ready."
It's kind of an interesting--
That's from the actual Bible, "He will come like a thief in the night."
That's a really evocative phrase.
But anyways, and then in the '90s, it went from being a barcode on your hand to a chip.
I remember when I--
Because remember, I've talked about this before, it used to be really in a conspiracy theory.
I 100%, I 100% believe that Bill Clinton was not going to leave office,
that he was aligned with the United Nations, the Blue Troops,
the Blue Helmeted Troops who were going to invade the United States.
I was like 17, 18.
I think the first election I could vote in was the Bob Dole--
Yeah, it was, it was the Bob Dole Clinton election.
Voted against Clinton, obviously.
I thought he was going to take over the planet.
But I 100% believed that the UN,
where he was going to have the UN come into the United States,
and we were going to be fostered in this one world government,
and all that nonsense.
And we were going to be chipped, get a little chip in your hand,
because the mark of the beast is either in your right hand or your forehead,
because not everyone has a right hand, but everyone has a forehead, right?
And you're going to put a little chip in you, and it's going to use to track you,
and you would have to use it to buy and sell.
And then it became the RFID chip,
which is in certain products.
It's basically an anti-theft chip.
And there are some businesses where you can have them in planets,
so you could just walk through the door and things like that.
And then the conspiracy theory became,
maybe it is ocular, like, you know,
they have those new things that scan your eyeball,
and then it would be like some sort of like fingerprint system.
I don't know.
They started getting this weird biotechnology thing,
and this way conspiracy theories work.
They evolve over time.
If people were still talking about barcodes on your hand,
you'd be like, "What?
Why don't they use one of those little square stupid Q codes
that you find on products that no one ever uses?
Have you ever held your phone up to something
that had one of those little Q codes on it?"
And dude, no one ever does that.
I think that's a scam.
I think someone made it that up as a scam.
But anyways, that's another conspiracy theory.
The conspiracy theories evolve over time.
So I went from being a barcode to a chip
to a specific name chip, an RFID chip.
Now the conspiracy theory is this,
that Bill Gates funded a bunch of programs,
which that is an conspiracy theory he actually does that.
And the thing is, is that when you fund a bunch of programs,
you're spreading money all over the place.
One of those places eventually is going to do something
that raises a couple eyebrows.
There was a group back in 2015
that wanted to study diseases and birds
and develop these vaccines.
So they patented, they submitted a patent for the coronavirus
back in 2015 for a particular brand of coronavirus
that exists in birds.
They wanted a genetic manipulation on it.
They got the patent in 2018.
And Bill Gates happened to fund that program.
Therefore, Bill Gates owns coronavirus.
That's the consp-
That's part of conspiracy theory number one.
Secondly, here was the thing.
He farmed it out to the Chinese.
I do not believe any of this, okay?
Just so we're clear, I think this is 100% nonsense.
Just totally want to be clear.
This is dumb, but...
Bill Gates takes the coronavirus
that he now owns the patent to,
gives it to China and says,
"I want you guys to make a virus
that'll wipe out 20 million people."
And China goes, "Yeah, sure, why not?"
And they make that virus in Wuhan.
And then they unleash it, and it sucks.
Now, it is killing people.
This disease, it's rough and it's bad,
but it's not...
It's not world-ending.
So the conspiracy theory is that Bill Gates farmed it out to China.
China messed it up, released it.
It's not as big as he wanted,
because Bill Gates wanted to have a national,
and no, a global vaccine ID.
So what would happen is...
And he's mentioned this.
I believe he's mentioned this.
He's talked about vaccines,
and it's really hard to tell
where the conspiracy theory starts on this thing,
because I think this is absolutely ludicrous,
and I'm actually trying to read real news about this.
But apparently,
there's been talk of having a ultraviolet tattoo
put into children's skin that lasts for five years,
showing they've been vaccinated.
It would basically be like an ID.
So to know that you don't have COVID-19 or this virus,
you would walk into a store,
and you would scan your hand underneath the UV unit,
and it would be like, "Oh, he's had the vaccine."
Then if you go and you don't have it,
they'd be like, "No. You can't eat.
You can't buy or sell.
Oh, I really wanted to sell today.
Nope. Go."
That's the conspiracy theory that's flowing around right now.
But it didn't work.
See, even the conspiracy theory goes,
but the plan didn't work.
Bill Gates failed.
His disease didn't kill enough people.
The whole thing's ridiculous.
There was talk of having...
He did say we could have some sort of national vaccine ID thing.
A digital ID is what he called it.
And then people turned it into the tattoo.
People turned it into something that was tattooed on your hand.
I know for a fact that he was saying
that they didn't want to have some sort of digital ID.
That doesn't mean that it's like, "Show your papers,"
and you pull out like a holographic card
that shows a picture of you smiling,
and that means you got vaccinated.
It would mean more than anything,
something in your medical records.
But really, this thing is going to stick around for a bit,
and they'll figure out a treatment,
and then they'll figure out a vaccine.
That's what I knew back in January,
and that's what I believe today.
That it's not going to be fun,
and it's here, it's really everywhere,
and they'll figure out a treatment for it in the short term,
and they're doing tons of work on that,
and then in the long run, they'll have a vaccine.
And then we will be better prepared
when something like this plus E-Bolla hits,
which I'm actually like, "This sucks."
Don't get me wrong, this totally sucks,
because you imagine if this was something like airborne E-Bolla,
or just regular E-Bolla,
at a death rate of 50%,
and was in the water supply,
or people like you could be spread through coughing or sneezing,
we as a species will never take a pandemic lightly,
again, or at least within the next 100 years.
Because I guess we took Spanish flu,
Spanish flu hit, and then 100 years went by.
We've learned, I believe.
The next time some disease starts popping out of some country,
there's going to be strict measures taken by the world.
Now, I don't think the strict measures are going to be having a digital ID,
or a tattoo on your hand, or Bill Gates laughing over the whole planet
with his hands on his hips as they're all bowing in front of a 5G tower.
I think it'll just be people being more mindful of being clean,
and as governments try to cover this stuff up,
not believe them next time.
Anyways, anyways, the point is, is that these conspiracy theories are flying around the globe,
and they're flying really faster than the pandemic.
People who have absolutely no chance of catching this,
people who are at home, who are following all the social distancing things,
believe this.
And it's adding fear on top of fear.
It's irresponsible and it's dangerous.
Because there's also reports coming out of Britain
that not only are these towers being set on fire,
or just exploding according to some conspiracy theories.
But if that British telecom workers are being harassed and threatened,
my mailman was seek shot in the neck after 9/11,
survived, thankfully, the guy went to prison.
But that fear and intolerance just gets stoked
when people believe in sane conspiracy theories.
And 9/11 was a like one-off event that freaked everyone out.
This event freaks everyone out every single day.
People say things are gonna get worse before they get better
as far as the coronavirus is concerned, and that's probably true.
But as far as the conspiracy theories surrounding it,
things are gonna get worse and worse and worse.
And it's up to us, the people who can see through this nonsense,
to make it better.
You just gotta get the truth out there.
Just gotta get the truth out there, 'cause this is gonna get rough, guys.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is gonna be our email address.
You can also hit us up at Facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[Music]