Central State Hospital in Millageville, Georgia. A spooky structure that holds thousands of
terrible secrets. This insane asylum has been closed for a while now, but its terrors continue
to haunt the community. So much so that it's possible that a small artifact from this asylum
may have caused the murder today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host, Jason
Carpenter. I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a lot
of stuff to cover today, so we're gonna hop right into this thing. First off, let's give
a shout out to one of our legacy Patreon supporters, Nicole Gerrand. Nicole Gerrand, thank you so
much for supporting the show. Nicole's doing a little pirouette, so she's getting dizzy,
probably shouldn't have driven a vehicle when you're that dizzy, but you're gonna be our
captain or pilot this episode. If you can't support the Patreon, that's fine too. Just
help spread the word about the show. Really, really helps out a lot. Nicole, I'm gonna
toss you the reins to our newest vehicle, the Carpenter Cart. It's not super impressive,
it's just a big old wooden cart. You get to ride a beautiful stallion or giant rabbit.
We'll attach it to a giant rabbit. You're riding a saddle. Hope you brought a rabbit
saddle. You're riding the rabbit. The rest of us are sitting in a big old wooden cart.
And the Carpenter Cart is gonna take us all the way out to Millageville, Georgia. So hop
to it, rabbit. It's a super slow journey. We have to buy a bunch of carrots and let
us along the way. We get there. We're gonna spend the whole episode at Millageville, Georgia
because there's a lot of craziness that's come out of this asylum. All of a sudden, we travel
back in time to the year 1842. So we're all dressed up in old-timey clothes. The rabbits
dressed up in an old-timey dress and a little bonnet. Super cute. But Nicole is continuing
to lead this way with the Carpenter Cart. Back in 1842 in Georgia, they go, "You know what?
We need to put all these people to work building something. What do we build?" And then someone
else goes, "You know what? I've noticed we have a huge problem with lunatics in the state. Why
don't we build an asylum?" So they do. It's like peanut butter and jelly. They both come together
to create the Georgia State-- this is the name of it. This isn't just me listing insulting words.
Georgia State Lunatic Idiot and Epileptic Asylum. And I just imagine underneath it, it says,
"And they're stinky, too." Like, how-- I mean, I get it that idiot used to mean, like,
not that you're just dumb or that you don't know how to do something. It actually meant that you
had some sort of medical problem. But, I mean, you could be still a little more sensitive than--
and again, I mentioned this in another episode. The same thing. I feel bad for the epileptics,
because they're just like, "Oh, yeah, you know, I have epilepsy. This sucks." And then they're just
housed with much idiots. That's horrible. I mean, because I have a friend who's epileptic,
and he's totally fine. I mean, other than the epilepsy, but he's like-- he's totally like sane.
He's not crazy. He's not an idiot. Definitely not a lunatic. So I feel bad for them. I wonder if
they have their own wing to the hospital, where they could just kind of like hang out by themselves,
play Parcheasy, invent Parcheasy, and then play it back in 1842. But you had the Georgia State
lunatic idiot and epileptic asylum. So it opened in 1842, so you can just imagine it probably wasn't
the best place to be. I don't think any place was the best place to be in 1842. But by the 1960s,
things were even worse. It was completely overcrowded. The only thing worse than being stuck in a
lunatic asylum is too many lunatics. Now, when I say overpopulated, it's not like you-- it was
built for 400 people, and there were 600 people. It was basically built for 400 people. I think it
was built for about 1,000 people. There were 12,000 lunatics and idiots running around in there.
You had a doctor-patient ratio of one doctor for every 100 patients. So let me do my math. What is
that? 120 doctors? That sounds like a lot, actually. I don't think I've ever been in a play-- I don't
even think hospitals have 120 doctors. Actually, it's funny that I say that because it turns out
that a bunch of them weren't doctors. The state kept having to go in. There's so many complaints
coming about this place. First off, number one complaint was, "Can you guys change the name?"
So they did. They eventually changed it to just Central State Hospital. State regulators had to
keep going to check this place out, and it turns out at one point, they were like walking down the
halls, and there were all these doctors hanging out. Plain parts easy. Did you know that? A bunch
of idiots invented parts easy. The state regulators were walking through the hospital, and on their
count as they were going through, they found 48 doctors working the halls. They weren't even doctors.
There were just people walking through, like, "Hey, I'm a janitor. I came in for a janitor job," and
then they said, "Hey, do you want to be a doctor?" There was 48 people working there, and one visit
who weren't actually doctors. And it's not like they were nurse practitioners. They weren't anything.
They weren't anything. They were just people claiming to be doctors. Not escaped lunatics,
by the way. People who would come there to get a job who were getting paid to be doctors who had no
degrees of any kind. And then, of course, you had the rumors. So those are real. Those weren't rumors.
Those are actual little things that happen. You had the rumors that kids who were put in the asylum
were locked up in little cages. And then there are other stories of just inhumane treatment. You'd
have people who were in straight jackets all the time. They basically lived in the straight jacket,
which seems incredibly uncomfortable. I think that's kind of the point. Now, this place,
open in 1846, it didn't close until 2010. Now, I'm not saying it was as bad as 1846. I'm not
saying the Confederacy was running the place, but when I was reading about it, I was like, "Oh,
they probably shut it down in the 60s. You know, after they found out there were a bunch of people
there pretending to be doctors?" No. It was in operation up until 2010. And you can still visit
it. I don't think you can, like, run around it and play laser tag or anything like that. There are
still a bunch of graves in the area. Now, when I say a few graves, we're talking 25,000 unmarked
graves. Those don't even include the graves that have a little nice little headstones and stuff
like that. So this place is ripe for urban legends, right? You have the mass graves. You have the
verified history of this place. And looking into this, I found a Reddit post from someone who really,
really, really loves this asylum. I don't think I've ever met such a fan of mental asylums as I've
found in username SixWeird6America6. So that's our source for the rest of this stuff. SixWeird6America6.
They write out this giant block of text. People are just going, "Hey, do you guys know anything
wacky haunted places in Georgia?" And someone goes, "Yeah, someone appeared. Someone appeared out of
the mist." I know. Thanks for asking, my fellow friend. They're like, "Not your friend, you weirdo.
You just magically appeared in my room." SixWeird6America6 has this huge block of text about
Millageville, Georgia's number one insane asylum. This list includes a bunch of weird details. One
of them, it keeps going on about this guy named Jim Bonner. He keeps calling him a child murderer.
And I was like, "Well, I was able to verify that when a lot of them were just like an inmate took
a hacksaw and chopped off a doctor's neck." And I was like, "I'm sure that happened over the course
of 100 years. I mean, it's horrific. I'm not being like, 'Yah, no. That's lame. Give me some more.'
I mean, I'm sure that happened, but I can't verify it." Jim Bonner keeps getting called a child
murderer. This is kind of a little, I don't know if I technically call him a child murderer.
Jim Bonner apparently was a voodoo king, is what SixWeird America told us. And that what happened
in real life, I don't know if he was a voodoo king, but he maybe he's just a voodoo prince or a voodoo
duke, but he poisoned a family and it killed the wife and four of nine children. And the
dad ended up going crazy and had to be put into the insane asylum where he died shortly later,
of stomach problems, which is what killed the family. My question is, are you a child murderer
if some of your victims are kids? Like, is that a rule? I'm not, I don't mean FBI's like, "Oh,
here, let's listen in on this podcast." But you know what I mean? Like, at what point, like,
if you went into a town and you shot nine people and four of them happened to be, I don't know,
Irish, are you then the Irish killer? Like, would that actually be your designation? I'm not saying
it's okay to kill kids under any circumstances. I'm just questioning him being labeled. I feel
like I'm a defense lawyer. I'm like, "Sir, listen, yes, my man did slaughter an entire family,
but let's not refer to him as a child killer. Just a couple kids died."
Anyway, so child killer voodoo king Jim Bonner, he's included in this list. Apparently, there's
been a bunch of UFO sightings at one point. Weird America said that there was a, again,
I would love to verify this. I would love to verify this, but I couldn't. I tried, I tried really
hard. Apparently, on August 25th, 1887, this saucer-shaped dent in the ground appeared,
which I think there's a most commonly known as holes. I think there's most commonly known as a
hole, but anyways, a saucer-shaped dent appeared in the ground. And okay, that's notable, I guess.
But then millions, millions, not 25,000, which is already a huge number, millions of grasshopper,
not grasshoppers, because again, that would be notable enough. Millions of grasshopper-sized
frogs jumped out of a hole. I mean, that's the end of the world, right? I mean, that would
have 100% be in the newspaper. I should have been able to verify that. Millions of grasshopper-sized
frogs jumped out of this hole and they covered 600 feet of ground, which is the least, I don't even
know why that's in there. That's the least remarkable part of the story. Someone's going to be like,
millions of grasshopper-sized frogs, but how much ground do they cover? And you're like 600 feet.
Wow! It doesn't sound like a lot, you can't fit a million of anything in 600 feet. Maybe a million
needles. I don't even know about that. Anyways, I wish I could have verified that. I wasn't able to.
So we have UFO sightings, apparently, because there's security around the place. Laser tag
or not, there's security around the place. You can't get into it because it's an old crumbly,
most likely haunted and cursed insane asylum. Weird America says that there's security there,
which is obvious, but they said the security there is actually from the Department of Defense.
It's a subsidiary of the Department of Defense. This is a high-level government area, most likely,
because you know, the end of the world started here with the million grasshopper-sized frogs.
Apparently nearby there's a place called Buzzard Island that has a bunch of buzzards on it.
Again, not super notable. When we're talking about millions of grasshopper-sized frogs and
just being a haunted asylum, I don't care how many buzzards are nearby. I've never looked
into Amityville Horror and go, "But what is their foul population? How many chickens live nearby?
That'll seal the deal." Apparently there's been stories of cursed devil dolls, human trafficking,
because you know if you're moving people from one state to another, you know, stop off at the
haunted asylum, that's a good place to, you know, get your refreshments going. I love this. We have
this great quote, "The asylum and even cemeteries are littered with tons of suicides." Scientific.
How many people committed suicide last year? Scientists goes, "Tons, tons of people." They're
like, "Okay, let's put it on a chart. We're done. Tons of suicides." And we have tiny frogs,
we have Buzzard Island if you're into that thing, you have tons of suicides, you have UFO
sightings, devil dolls, and again, I don't know why they included this, the world's largest kitchen.
Why? You're trying to wow me, weird America. You're trying to make me go, "Whoa, spooky,
I don't want to go there." Now I know, first off, I don't think this place has the worlds,
the worlds, the biggest on the planet's kitchen. I'm, I'll believe in grasshopper sized frogs,
a million of them, before I believe that this insane asylum has the biggest kitchen on the entire
planet. But if it does, if you're really into kitchens and you can get past Department of Defense
security, here's the place to go, just watch out for the Buzzard Island on the way. There's just,
and it's a list and list and list of all of these murders. And when I talk about, you know, I can't
source this, I can't source that, I mean, again, when you're like, Jason, how are you going to find a
news article from 1887 about millions of grass? First off, that should have been the only news
reported that day in every newspaper ever. Millions of grasshopper sized frogs, that should
have just been the headline everywhere. I don't know what else was happening in 1887 that would
beat that out of the news. But then we have this, which again sounds, I wish I could verify this,
I 100% wish that I could tell you guys that this story was true. I looked really hard,
it gave me some ideas for future episodes because I have some really cool stuff coming up.
So in 1975, according to Weird America, a patient escapes from the Allen building.
He's running away, he's like, oh, how am I going to get away? He sees a buzzard, he grabs onto
its legs and he flies away on the buzzard. Ha ha, freedom! But he doesn't have a good,
fun-filled adventure. What he does is he goes to a school, the buzzard's like flying over school,
and he lets go. See you later, buzzard. He takes the school hostage, he takes 70 children hostage
and five school staff with an assault rifle. And then we have this, let me read you this exact line
that was written here. "Teacher, put first off before he does lie to you." Because it doesn't
make any sense. A guy has a gun, he's taken control of a school, that's obviously tragic, right?
And everyone's sitting around and they go, well, what do we do now? What do we do now? And then
this happens, this sentence happens. "Teacher puts bullet in backwards, saving everyone.
Kids grab gun from teenage patient." So I mean, I get what they're trying to say that somehow a
teacher put a bullet in backwards, but I don't know how or when or why. If you could remove the
gun, it's not like you remove the gun, put a bullet in backwards and they go, here you go,
just keep the gun and don't put the bullet in backwards. You have the gun. I mean, they should
have just said he stuck his finger into the barrel of the gun, the guy pulled the trigger,
the teacher's hand inflated like a Looney Tune character and smoke appeared and he goes,
ow, my finger, and then the kids took the gun. Why would you go, just take the gun.
Did the teacher have bullets on them and they're just like throwing them into the barrel backwards?
A lot of this stuff you can't verify, but I was able to find a interesting story I was able to
verify. Nicole, call in that carboner copter. We're going to fly just a short while and we're
going to use our time travel technology to take us to the year 2019. Very, very recent story.
We're still in Millageville, but we're farther away from the asylum now. Nicole's going to land
this helicopter in this residential neighborhood. We're just kind of hanging out. It's May 12th,
2019. It's 1 a.m. We're the house of Clark Heindel. He's a 69 year old yoga shop owner, not
yogurt shop. That would be awesome. And then there's a woman there named Mariana Shockley.
She's a 43 year old professor at University of Georgia. We were there last week. Also,
there was Morris Lillard, 41 years old. He's actually Mariana's boyfriend. He's a car salesman
and I almost will 100% start calling him Matthew Lillard at some point during this story, but
Matthew Lillard, the actor, had nothing to do with any of this. They're all hanging out at Clark's
house. They're all hanging out at Clark's house. Clark has a hot tub and a pool. That yogurt money,
man. Yogurt money can buy you a lot of stuff. He has a pool. He has a hot tub. They're all
hanging out. And at a certain point, Clark goes, "I'm going to go swim in the pool." And Mariana
says, "I'm going to sit in the hot tub." And Morris says, "I'm going to go out and chop some wood.
I'm going to go out into the woods. I'm going to go out into the spooky, spooky forest
and get some wood." I'm assuming they had some sort of fire there. I don't think that was just
his fetish. He's like, "Oh, now that I have time alone, I'm going to chop down trees." He goes off
to chop down wood. He eventually comes back and he sees Mariana just sitting in the hot tub
and Clark is still doing laps in his pool. His pool shaped like sprinkle toppings.
And Morris comes back and he realizes Mariana's not moving. She's just kind of sitting in the
hot tub. And it starts to alarm him. He goes, "Yo, Clark, what's going on, dude? How come Mariana's
just like not moving? She's an animate. She's human. She should be animate in some form or
fashion." So he runs over there and he notices that she's not breathing. She's just sitting in
the water. So he pulls her out of the hot tub and while he's doing it, he says that he bangs her head.
So save your questions till the end. He's pulling her out of the hot tub and he bangs her head up
and they begin to do CPR on her. And after about a period of time, some articles say 45 minutes of
CPR and other articles said for two hours they were trying to do CPR. At a certain point they're
like, "We got to call authorities. Get some trained people down here." Because I'm pretty sure CPR is
not supposed to take 45 minutes. So they call ambulance, police, everyone shows up. The cops
say when they walk in, the two guys were super cagey. They weren't really giving direct answers.
And they also, they could tell they were doing CPR, but again, depending on what article you
read, it was the cops, the cops were suspicious to say the least. They wasn't what you would think
someone would do if someone had died of their house. So they separated the two people. They
separated Clark and they separated Morris. They put them in different rooms. They began asking
them questions. And Morris was like, "Dude, I went out to the woods, shopped out some trees."
They were all naked too, if that means anything. I don't know if it does, but they're all naked.
So he's out in the chopping wood naked. The cops thought that was kind of weird. Everyone was
naked, but maybe some weird sex thing. They don't know. They just want to figure out what happened
to this woman. At this point, she's picked up. She's taken to the hospital. She doesn't make it.
She's actually dead. The cops are talking to Maris about what's going on. Clark's sitting in another
room. He had been interviewed already as the group. I don't think they'd interviewed him as a
individual yet. And then they hear a BAM! They're like, "Oh, great." They go into
one of Clark's room and he had shot himself. Killed himself on the scene and left a note
explaining what had happened. He said he was killing himself because he was so embarrassed
that this woman died at his house. Now, as outside observers, obviously the note said more,
but that's all we know. The note said that he was embarrassed that this woman died at his house.
So he shot himself. That doesn't make sense at all. But what's super weird about this is that the
cops are now charging Maris for the murder of Mariana. And this is their story. Something went wrong,
obviously. And he beat her up. And that was why her head had injuries to it. He goes, "No, no, no,
it's pulling her out of the hot tub." I don't know what to think about this side of the story
as far as whether or not he did this. I don't know how you would pull someone out of a hot tub
and it would bash their head up. I mean, I don't... She wasn't like clobbered,
but she had injuries to her head. I don't understand how you could do that physically.
What's so weird about this is that Clark and his letter wasn't like, "I did it." It wasn't like,
as far as we know, the letter hasn't really been brought into evidence. But it's not like Clark's
letter said, "Maris did it and I'm so embarrassed that I brought Mariana." It's just like, "Oh,
I feel embarrassed. I can't believe someone died at my house. So I'm going to kill myself."
Maris is on trial for murder. Maris is saying, "I was out in the woods. The guy that should be
the suspect is the guy who shot himself the night of the murder. Why am I even being charged with
this? I wasn't even around when it happened. I showed up. He's swimming. She's dead. And I'm
shocked that they're actually charging Mar... Again, we don't have all the information, but I would
be super... I would either say both of them did it or Clark did it. But I don't think... What did
he do? Like walk off into the woods, sneak back, kill her? And because Clark's letter didn't say,
"Oh, I know this guy did it." It's super weird. But anyway, so Maris is on trial for this murder.
And this is currently going on. This trial is currently going on. I just can't imagine...
First off, I can't imagine killing yourself. Secondly, I can't imagine killing yourself
because you're embarrassed because someone got murdered at your house or just died at your house.
And then third, how is he not the big suspect? I would have thought the cops would have been like,
"Well, he's probably that guy. That guy who's dead the night this other woman got murdered."
But anyway, so Maris is on trial. The reason why this is tied back into Millageville is
Weird America. Weird America actually in this giant list of stuff that I kept trying to verify.
I wasn't able to verify tiny frogs, but I was able to verify this story. I went and I looked
into this because it said, "A guy did this, killed this woman," and stuff like that. But Weird America
has a little paranormal spin to this one. I don't know if any of this stuff is true. I don't know.
Literally any of this stuff is true. But according to Weird America, according to our source,
Weird America, Clark had a six-year-old son who had died of cancer. And Clark was so...
I'll say this, if this story is made up, Weird America has some serious issues. This story is
true. That is just really creepy. Clark had a six-year-old son who had passed away and Clark
began to wander the halls of the asylum to get his mind off of his son, get his mind off of his
loss. He's like, "I'm gonna go to this spooky, spooky place to not think about my son." While he
was doing that, while I was taking his daily walks to the spookiest place on earth, he was also like
trying to research root work, which is an offshoot. It's like a magic branch. So it's basically,
it's magical stuff, but it's all based around roots and herbs and 11 herbs and spices and all
this stuff. He was also doing that stuff on May 2019. So earlier that month, before all this stuff
happened, when he was walking around the lunatic asylum, he sees a doll. He sees a doll laying
there in the dirt. And apparently, I mean, Weird America could be making all this up.
I don't know if he's like Clark's personal buddy, but apparently Clark's son, Clark's son who had
passed away, loved to pick up toys and bring him home. Who doesn't? Who doesn't love to do that?
And so when he's found this doll, he goes, "Oh, this is just kind of what my son would do. I don't
think I'm gonna let him walk around this spooky asylum with all these frogs and buzzards everywhere."
But he takes the doll home and this doll is supposedly one of the cursed devil dolls that
is known to haunt the asylum grounds. And then later that same month, because it was May 12th
and that happened, he invites those friends over and that happened. Now, there was also another
detail here, because when the cops came in, they're like, "What is going on here?" They said,
it really wasn't consistent with CPR. Some stories say they were doing this for 45 minutes.
Other stories say they were doing it for two hours. What Weird America says was, when they
brought the body out of the hot tub, the reason why it took so long was because Clark was trying
to bring her back to life, not with proven life-saving techniques, but with root work. He began grinding
up stuff and pouring it into her mouth to cure her of being dead. Apparently, he was also pouring
ayahuasca into her mouth as the cops were coming in the door. Ayahuasca is that super potent hallucinogen.
I can only imagine what it would do to someone who was brain dead. Like, that would just be insane,
literally. But he was apparently giving her ayahuasca as the cops were coming in and covering her in
leaves and things like that. And Marcus, I think it was calling him Morris, it's one of the two.
It's Marcus. I don't have to worry about calling him Matthew Lillard. It's Marcus
was thanking the whole time. This looks like some sort of ritual to bring back the dead.
He was very, which is what CPR is, but you know, it works. Pouring ayahuasca into someone's mouth,
who drowned, is not advisable. And then he shot himself. So the story then has another
paranormal element to it. Again, what's interesting, I always find interesting about people who,
I don't want to say make stuff up, but people who say stuff that's unverifiable,
is they have the option of answering all the questions. If you are descended from the Atlanteans,
you can just make up whatever, because no one can ever prove you wrong, because you're totally
making it up. I always find it intriguing when people, if they're making it up, get stymied,
because if I was making the story up, I would say the letter actually said that he was killing
himself because if this cure didn't work, then he could never bring his son back and da da da da
and then it fills in the gaps. Weird America doesn't really talk about the letter, doesn't answer all
the questions, just answer some of them. And I always find that intriguing, because if you were
100% making it up, you would answer everything. But in this case, Weird America doesn't do that,
so I found that an intriguing footnote. So is it possible that this is just a bizarre,
true crime story? People were out naked, drinking, having fun, something went wrong, a woman got
murdered? Happens all the time. Happens all the time. Or is it the story of a woman who accidentally
died and a man who had spent years trying to figure out a way to contact the other side,
trying to figure out a way to bring the dead back to life? When he is given the opportunity,
he tries out his root work and it doesn't work. And that's what he's embarrassed about,
that he could have actually called the cops earlier, but he had spent so much time investing
his energy into this foolish notion that he can bring back the dead, that when it didn't work,
he realized he was responsible for this woman's death. Or, let's put on our conspiracy caps to
wrap this up. Is it possible that all of these events would have never happened if he had not
picked up a cursed doll at a long-closed insane asylum? With him swimming and Marcus out chopping
wood, what killed Mariana? Is it possible it was some darker force at play that was invited into
Clark's home when he brought in the dusty and muddy doll that he'd found on his journeys?
And if so, where is that doll now? It was once the treasured toy of a child trapped with thousands
of maniacs until it eventually became discarded, another piece of debris littering a cursed hospital.
Someone brought it home and unleashed that curse, and now that doll is still out there
waiting to be brought into someone else's home. If that part of the story is true, it's still
out there, it's not like the police would gather it for evidence, so they don't just go around pick
every spooky thing in a house and go let's take this back to the station. Like, it would have
still been in his house, they would have had an estate sale, some would have been sold off,
it could have been packed up in storage and put in some sort of locker. Is that doll still out there?
Did it somehow find its way back to the asylum? Not like it walked, not like it got a cab,
I'm talking like it magically disappeared, okay? I'm like what can Spursy Caps on and fade it away
when the cops aren't looking. Where is this doll now? Is there really a cursed doll out there
that if you bring it home within a few weeks, people just die? Obviously that sounds ridiculous,
but when we explore the world of the paranormal, this stuff is possible, it's definitely more
possible than putting a bullet in a gun backwards without someone seeing. So where is this doll now?
We may never know the truth of what happened that night at that house, but that doesn't mean
we shouldn't be safe. It is tempting to take those little trinkets you find out on your walk,
the shiny rock, the discarded toy, the baseball hat covered in leaves, it's very
enticing to bring those things home. A trophy of a fun day out. But be careful the next time you do.
You may not be bringing home just a trinket, you may be bringing home a curse
that could kill you and your loved ones. You may be bringing home something much more sinister,
you may be bringing home a vessel that contains the dark energy of 25,000 maniacs.
Assuming you live by that, assuming you live over there, you're in Alaska maybe like three or four
maniacs. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at
facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day.
Glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys.
(upbeat music)