Today we meet a doctor who operates out of an RV and says that he's capable of performing almost any operation
Because he learned at the best school of all YouTube
Now we meet a man who believes that vaccines are actually full of tiny UFOs
Why you ask because he believes that all germs are actually cryptids today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*Music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys have a great weekend
This is our Friday episode. I hope you guys have a lot of fun this weekend
We are going to give one more shout out to Veronica the Haunted Doll. She is our co-host for this week
She's always hanging out around the recording studio, but I got it right next to the mic. Let's hear it listen to her
*Music*
See that's Veronica saying what's up?
That's Veronica's
Let's give a shout out to one of our legacy patreon supporters right now Sergeant Clowney
Sergeant Clowney long time supporter of the show really really helps out really really appreciate it
You're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you can't support the patreon
That's fine too. Just help get the word out about the show that really really helps out a lot leave reviews tell your friends talk about it online
Really really helps the show grow sergeant clowny. Let's go ahead and hop in the dead rabbit dune buggy
We haven't used that one in a while
Jumping over sand dunes war pups chasing us the second we put the key in the war pups are right on us go sergeant clowny go go
They're trying to throw bombs at us, but they suck they can't do it. We're headed out to Nevada
That's why we want to have this dead rabbit dune buggy. We're headed out to the perpetual desert known as Nevada a lot of this information
I got from an article on oxygen. It's a website called oxygen. It was written by Ali Vander Hayden
So appreciate that one to give the journalist a shout out here. We're taking that dead rabbit dune buggy
We're gonna go through a time travel cave and we're now in the year 2012
We pull up outside of this broken down RV in the middle of nowhere a k a anywhere in Nevada
And inside the RV right now is a young man. His name is Randy David Valenzuela, Jr.
Now Randy has HIV and he'd been taking a bunch of medication for it
His doctor was like, okay, you know, this is treatable like we can at least keep you alive
Right, that's no longer the death sentence that it used to be but you're gonna have to take this cocktail of pills
But Randy wanted a cure Randy wanted things to change
He was on the medication for seven years
But he honestly believed that there was a cure out there somewhere and he finds the answer to that cure on Craigslist of all places
Right on Craigslist. He meets a man named Rick van Thiel and he goes to this dirty old RV which should be your first
Sign that something's not right. The doctor says hey, yeah, come to my office. It's in the middle of nowhere
You're gonna have to walk past five dead cats to get to it
But there you go
He walks into this RV and there is dr. Rick. It's the name he went by Rick van Thiel
Rick van Thiel goes I can cure I can cure AIDS
See the government doesn't want people to know that the cure for AIDS is out there because they make more money from selling the pharmaceuticals
Then they are for treating it, but I've invented this thing called ozone therapy
I'm gonna put these needles in your arm and then your blood gets sucked into this machine and it gets processed and it comes back
And goes into your other arm totally works. It's a hundred and twenty dollars a day
You have to do it for eight weeks straight and Randy's in Randy is ten toes into this thing
He's like let's do it. So he actually goes through eight weeks of therapy and he feels better. He feels better afterwards
He tells his mom about the doctor his mom is Dominguez Valenzuela. She's like oh, this doctor so amazing
He can see he's curing HIV and the mom's like oh really can I meet him and
he's like
Well, yeah, but but don't judge a book by his cover show the mom goes there
They show up to the trailer and the door opens up and dr. Rick's like hey, what's up? Randy awesome?
You're here. You're here for your other treatment. Oh, is that your mom? Oh, it's so nice to meet you
The mom's standing there and she's thinking wait a second. This is a doctor first off
We're in the middle of nowhere. That's the worrisome thing number one two. He's operating out of an RV three
Dr. Rick is completely naked
Dr. Rick's medical office was also where he he made porn in there, which is great
Right when you want to go get treated for assist
You want to go have something pulled out of you? It's great to know that people were banging on the operating table right before you got there
He shot porn there. He actually like when the police so you know where this story is going when the police go into the place
There's like shelves of medical supplies
It's just stuff randomly shrewn about and then porn videos on top of the medical supply if you're lucky
porn videos on top of the medical supplies there are also sex toys everywhere
So again like going to the doctor's not the most comfortable thing to begin with but imagine if you walked into your doctor's
Office and you sit down and you're like whoa wait what I sit on and there's like a plug there
There's like a french tickler. You're like what you're trying different chairs. You're like oh this one this one's kind of comfortable
It's a porn studio
Doctors office in the middle of nowhere when the police eventually do show up one of the detectives said it reminded him of a saw movie
There was so much not like blood on the walls, but he said there was so much like just bloody stuff around bloody tools
Hopefully again just bloody tools that the cops like hey dude come over here look at this the other cops like nah
Nah, the dude's like pointing out a box that's labeled sex toys is like no if you thought that was bloody cost like no no no no
Seriously, I'm about to quit. I don't want to look. I don't want to know what's in that box
So what happens is well, let's back up a little bit
Randy takes another HIV test and it comes up negative now apparently one out of every 12 like self-administered tests for HIV
Comes back negative. It's a pretty high percentage for very very serious illness, right?
So he thinks he's cured there is no cure for it
Unfortunately, he thinks he's cured and then he contracts it again or really he just he took another test and it showed that
He still had it so he begins going back to dr. Ricks and
He starts doing the treatment again, but the mom's like it was different the second time like he didn't have him come every day
It was just a totally different setup
Randy passes away three weeks later after visiting dr. Rick again
And so the mom alerts authorities to what's going on there now
He didn't get charged with Randy's death because he didn't do any like Randy died of complications due to I think it was drug abuse
because he was using meth it was like drug abuse and
Just HIV it was a bad combination
So the cops go because you can't practice medicine without a license the cops go to the place they see the mess
They obviously know that it's not legal the ozone machine that was pumping blood in and out of this dude
He wouldn't clean so if you had hepatitis C and he's like oh, I know how to cure that ozone
You weren't getting blood that was HIV infected. You're like oh, I have a serious case of the munchies
I probably shouldn't smoke all that weed. He's like oh, I have a cure for the munchies ozone therapy
He used this machine for everything
Bloody tools would be used on one person that person would leave and then another person would show up
You get hepatitis C get all sorts of horrible disease HIV all sorts of horrible diseases from this place
There's a video of him on YouTube. It's disgusting. I watched it. He's naked
They don't show anything but they show him take his clothes off and he removes a cyst from a guy's back and the guys like ow
ow ow ow ow ow ow and the doctor's like just hold it he's like
Pops it out looks like a little chicken nugget popping out of this dude totally on YouTube this guy
It's a video and he said he goes the way
I know how to do all these procedures is I watched the procedures on YouTube and then he knows how to do it
He was performing abortions here
So basically any possible procedure you could think of you need a tooth pulled there you go
You need a film you need to film a porn there you go
It was a one-stop shop for everything now
He was a believer of the sovereign citizen movement, which is basically this super bizarre movement
Where your name is actually a corporation name and the government
I don't even know if I can explain it in less than three minutes
The when you are born your your name is spelt in all caps
Which makes you a corporation and then the government then takes a loan out against the corporation of Jason Carpenter
So if I file it means one of two things one
There's a secret code that if I file some court paperwork and say the right things in court
The government goes oh great. He figured it out and I get all the money
That's been accumulated under my corporation. That's one weird part of it. The second weird part is
You don't believe that laws really apply to you because you never agreed to become a US citizen
You were born on US soil, but you never signed a contract or became a US citizen
So a lot of times you can watch YouTube videos. They don't believe that they're driving through town. They'll be in a car
They're not in a cloud car. They're not caribabers floating around like they are actually driving through a town
But when they get stopped by the police they go I'm not driving
I'm traveling and apparently in the Constitution like you can't be stopped when you're traveling or people have a right to travel
So they believe the right combination of words will get them out of trouble
Those videos almost always end with cops busting their windows open and pulling them out of the car
So it doesn't really work that well, but he was one of these guys
He was one of these guys who believes in the sovereign citizen movement
So he didn't believe that he needed a license YouTube was good enough for him
He'd watch a YouTube video on sister move all and then remove a cyst
But I'm wondering if there was a weird like cycle where he just started watching his own video of him removing his cyst
And he's like oh this guy's awesome. He's naked and he knows that oh, that's me
Then he just goes in and starts popping cysts out of people
He ends up getting arrested and then he hangs himself in jail before he can serve time
He wasn't facing murder charges for this guy
But he was definitely facing a lot of time for practicing without a license and doing it so many times and recording evidence of it
So it's try obviously. I think that's a tragic ending. I don't like when people kill themselves
He probably would have done like five or ten years and gotten out, but he was also kind of old at the time
So still still though he ended up hanging himself in 2017
So that's the story of dr. Rick. He needed a procedure done. There you go 120 bucks. You couldn't I mean you're probably
Here's the thing with that sure you get the cyst removed, but then you're like the couple days later
You're like oh, why are my eyes yellow? They're like oh you come in you got you got jaundice you got jaundice
I don't know probably totally unrelated to my bloody tools, but here you go come back in we'll fix that
So then he's pumping out your jaundice blood and you're like oh, I feel so much better now and couple days later
You're like oh, why do I have the avian flu doctors like oh, I don't know I don't know
There's a bunch of birds. There's a bunch of birds waiting in the in the waiting room reading magazines
He's like I don't know but come back. We'll cure as we actually not think about it. It's actually a really good
That's a really good scheme what you do is you treat the patient for the illness
They have but give them a new illness and you just keep that cycle going you just keep it going and and
While you're there you could be like so you like movies and you're like yeah sure
I mean could you just get this cyst out of my back and cure the ten other diseases
I've gone recently like yeah, yeah, yeah, but to relax. Let's put on this movie
So you're like slaying there you can't move you're getting cysts removed and you have to watch one of his porn movies that actually
It's funny. Let me wrap it up like this
I forgot to say this detail they found when the cops are investigating this they're getting a bunch of people to come forward
Women were saying oh, we didn't have to pay
Sometimes we would just have sex with him and he would perform the procedure for free
And you're like okay, you know fine, whatever and then they go on on on on no sometimes
He would have sex with us while performing the procedure
I don't care if he's a sexy as a woman on the planet if I'm removing cysts from you while we're making love
If you can't hear that that's just me shaking my head there is no way
Anyone could do that apparently this guy could but he would have sex with women while performing procedures
I hope I really hope I actually looked for some of this guy's porn movies and I couldn't find them
And and I'm very very thankful of that. I was trying to do my due diligence
I said there must be some of these videos out there because he made a bunch of them
They showed clips of them on the news
What medical procedure could you possibly do and at the same time have sex with a woman? I
I'm not even gonna even gonna think about that. So instead
Sergeant clowny. He's like he's already in the carbonic after he's trying to get the buddies like cologne work work
Okay, wait for us wait for us. We're leaving behind this little shack in Nevada. We are headed out to
Helicopters flying around we are headed out to a little field
We land it's nothing but grass grass as far as the eye can see we all step out of the carbonic hopter
We look it's beautiful out here the skies blues couple white clouds in the sky birds flying around we're like, oh great
They're like, you know where doctor we can go to
We got cysts. We're like sorry dude birds fly away and as we're sitting in this grass field
I turn to you. I have a podium and I walk up to it and I go
New today on digital and Haitian Thomas Jane starring the gripping psychological thriller the vanished
Directed by Peter Fastinelli a family vacation takes a terrifying turn when two parents discover that the young daughter has vanished without a trace
Stopping at nothing to find her the search for the truth leads to a shocking revelation
Where nothing is what it seems in this intense thriller own or rent the vanished on digital today and watch it at home tonight
Raided are from paramount pictures
So I step off the podium and now we're standing in this field of grass
We're sitting in this grass field though because of this post I want to talk about now
Recently AZ sent me to the reddit for gang stalking and I was like, oh my god
This is so insane and I did a story about a guy who was being gangstalked by his own family
It's like this is nuts and then like anyone who ever finds anything on the internet
They realize that that it's never truly the end Chris founder of the golden rabbit brigade a longtime supporter of the show
Chris sends me a link. He goes. Oh, yeah gang stalking, right? That's a thing
But have you heard of gang stalking MK ultra subreddit? And I was like I have not I
Have not good sir. So I pulled it up and it wouldn't make the people in the gang stalking subreddit blush
It's so insane
There is a guy from gang stalking MK ultra who's now posting on
Gangstalking subreddit and people are like you're crazy. That's how nuts this stuff is
So, thank you Chris and thank you AZ both you guys for turning me on to this crazy subreddit world on the gang stalking MK ultra subreddit
There's a username. Don't chill me bro. The last time that this account posted anything was about three years ago
I believe they're still posting under different a different name, but we'll get into that later
But right now let's take a look at this. So
This is from a post labeled a theory germs are cryptids
You're like that is actually an interesting conspiracy theory
It's not so far off from monkeys don't exist or that mountains are really trees like you you get a sense of it right from the beginning
Germs are cryptids. They're too small for us to really see it's one of those things that we take
Scientist advice on what they are because we don't know they're looking through the microscope and they're like hmm
It appears that the virus is multiplying at a rapid rate and we're like can we see and he's like no no
This is my microscope. You can't see you got to bring your own you got to find your own viruses
We have to take them out their words. So germs are cryptids are actually a very interesting conspiracy theory, but that's not all
It's not all that would actually be enough. I would be really interested to see just someone explore that not this guy
Not this guy. So that's promising right? That's very promising conspiracy theory. Let's see what this guy has to say about germs are cryptids
Quote I had a realization when you wear fur or sleep on the grass and wake up itchy for about 15 minutes
It's 1500 years while everyone builds swords and chases aliens
Stand in the middle of the middle of this grassy field
And you look at me and you go way way way wait what what is any of that have to do with your weight?
How do you even parse that out at all? Let me read this again now that the shock factor is worn off
This is a real sentence a human constructed. I had a realization when you wear fur or sleep on the grass and
Wake up itchy for about 15 minutes. It's 1500 years while everyone builds swords and chases aliens
And you go Jason. That's obviously taken out of context. You're reading the first sentence of this post
He must clarify that and so what does that mean? So when you fall asleep on the grass?
Let's break it down when you wear fur when you're putting on fur or when you fall asleep in the grass
After about 15 minutes, you'll start itching which we know is caused by chiggers
It's little bugs in the grass that bite you and make you itch
but he's saying that if you wear fur or you sleep in the grass what actually happens is
1500 years passes and
Society evolves where everyone starts building swords and fighting aliens at least like that's what I'm thinking saying, okay?
So there's like there's 15 minutes in our world and then 1500 years and in other world where this is going on
What is this has to do with germs? I'm not for sure, but this is literally his first sentence in this passage
So then he goes on to say you can test it for yourself
You can test this theory for yourself
There's actually a bunch of nonsense in between there. He talks about icillipho pods which aren't real a
Cellophopod is a mollusk like an octopus but then he has a picture of this weird like monster and
keeps calling it an icillipho pod and then says I don't know what it is
So I'm actually skipping I'm skipping some of the nonsense because some of it's just so random
He starts talking about goat men and deer wear fur and maybe that's why we itch
It's like some genetic thing. We're not related to gomen or we're the gomen don't exist
So we're definitely not related to them, but we're not related to deer either
So I'm actually sparing you some of the insanity. It just doesn't make sense. It doesn't make sense at all. What in the world?
Dude, where's a goat man coming out in this? I love it too because he goes this is that this is the next sentence
I'll read you this
This is the next sentence after he talks about 15 minutes. It's 1500 years
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
So for example goat man maybe and actual deer are from wearing fur or the genetic memory of such what does that mean?
What does that mean and it's great that you're even saying I don't know maybe the goman's involved
I don't know. I don't know you gotta ask the goman. What is a goat man? Is it chupacabra?
Is it a satyr? Is it who is the goat man? I was wondering I imagine it's some sort of actual cryptid
But then it's just a deer
It's just a deer running around but apparently there's some sort of genetic myth. I've never I don't think I've ever worn fur
I have worn fur actually in plays in costumes and I've worn fur for hours. I've never itched
But anyways, so let's get back. There's more nonsense, but let's get to
There's here's the thing there's nonsense and then there's nonsense that kind of makes sense
And I could just read off nonsensical phrases all day long, but it's just mind-numbing
It's totally mind-numbing. Let me move to a part where it this part
Okay, this part at least makes a little bit of sense now
You know where in the middle of a grass field because he goes you can test it for yourself
You can test this theory about goat men and deer and grass
Here you go quote
sleep on the grass with no shirt and
When you think about your back think put it here
Eventually you will get a sand flea
Which I don't know that is maybe that's another term for a chigger but
And when you think about your back think put it here
So you're you're commanding something to get on your back
When you think about your back think put it here eventually you will get a sand flea or dinosaur
or something
There's a huge difference obviously
Do I have to explain this there's a huge difference between a flea a flea on my back and a triceratops
So you can get a sand flea or a dinosaur or something or nothing really is what's gonna happen
But let's continue here. You have itch. I'm not gonna complain about the grammar
I'm not gonna complain about the grammar in this post because so much of it doesn't make sense anyways
You're already laying on our backs
Thinking put it here and then dinosaurs show up. That's mind-boggling enough
That's mind-boggling enough that someone could write that and go that'll work that that makes sense
Here's the rest of it
You think yeah sand flea or dinosaur or something and you have itch for about 15 minutes
After it stops itching
Think about what you were thinking about on your back. So I want you okay. So that's perfect
We'll pause here before we move on to what he says
You've been laying on your back. You say put it here something is on your back now most likely just grass
Maybe a dinosaur we're laying all here for 15 minutes. What are you thinking of?
Here's what he goes after it stops itching think about what you were thinking about on your back
swords and caves
So apparently that's where he's getting the 15 minutes to 1500 year time jump where
When he's on his back 1500 years have passed at some point and I don't know in human history in that time period
But apparently when he lay wherever he lays down he thinks of swords and caves
I'll tell you this right now
I'm not a psychoanalysis dude at any way shape or form. I've never been trained in it. That is sexual, right?
Like that's just armchair psychology 101 swords and caves whenever he lays down
He's like oh, yeah, my sword my sword is going in and out of that cave
I remember once I came across something a long time ago and it said people who fantasize might have mentioned this before on the show
People who fantasize about hiding underground want to crawl back into their mom's womb
And then I was thinking oh man. I was thinking about all I was thinking about all the times
I was like dude if zombies ever attack I'm gonna have like an underground bunker
So like the zombies can't bust down a door if there's no door
It's just like an underground bunker or like the cops are surrounding my place. They're like you're way too cool, bro
We're gonna like blow you up and I'm like no way cops and then I like run
They're the cool police. I run and I hide in a bunker
I've always thought about hiding in bunkers, and then I'm like oh great. Thanks psychoanalysis guy
I gotta figure out another place from zombies actually by the time zombies attack. I'm not gonna care what that guy thinks
I'm not gonna be like all my let zombies eat me. Just no one thinks I'm a pervert
At least at least no one thinks that I'm weird is there ripping my limbs one for one. I'm going in that bunker, dude
I'm going in that bunker, but that's me
I'm gonna this guy because if every time you lay down you think of swords and caves
That's definitely sexual and then he says then he says this you can cure this you can cure this what we're curing
I don't know. I'm assuming we're trying to cure the germ remember when this started off with germs or cryptids
Then it wasn't that a nice quaint conspiracy theory. Here's here's where we're going quote you can train it
Practice making the cure faster and faster. What are we?
What's going faster and faster is the sword in and out of the cave that's okay?
So I'm not let's not imagining the swords in the caves dude, but what cure are you talking about you can train it
Practice making the cure faster and faster you can talk to the people all I show my back
Ankle's is to claws coming out of a cave and they go get it. What are you talking about?
So he's walking down the street, right? He's no longer laying on his back
He's walking on the street and he sees people and he's like hey guys look at my look at my calves
Look at him people on the street like what and the guys like uh-huh. Yeah, they see the claws in the cave
Then he walks away people like what is going on?
They're cured. They've been cured. They've been cured of all their diseases all I show is my back or ankles is to claws coming out of a cave
And they get it some people so here now we're gonna get back into
The germ stuff we're slowly becoming sane again
Some people can clear their germ in less than five seconds mine takes about a minute if you don't have swords
It'll take 1,000 years
so
I
Don't know
Even me it almost feels like a coded message
It almost seems like there's some guy in
Washington DC and some CIA headquarters and he saw this on red and he's like it's a go guys
We know where was Thomas at?
Helicopters flying out like it's so random. It seems like it's some sort of code
Some people can clear their germ in less than five seconds. What germ he still hasn't explained
Is it the back ankle claw germ? We don't know or is it all germs? We don't know but anyways
Some people can clear their germ in less than five seconds mine. It takes about a minute if you don't have swords
It'll take a thousand years
He does clarify that it's maybe not a thousand years
He does say that he says you know some people can do it in less than five seconds takes him a minute
Some people a thousand years and then he goes maybe ten minutes or so
So you know one of the other thousand years ten minutes either one at this point
Sand fleas dinosaurs it doesn't matter at least he gives us that option right that's gonna be my new timeline whenever someone says
Hey, can you wait ten minutes? I'll be like I could wait a thousand years and I'm gonna point at my ankle
So he ends it like this we started off so strong with germs or cryptids. So we started this off
Then we get to these last two sentences, but then when you find out it's true
You realize vaccines are little UFOs and we're screwed
That is such a good conspiracy theory dude like it's not true obviously
But that is a conspiracy theory that could catch on germs or cryptids I could see people believing in that
Vaccines contain UFOs dude. That is so timely right now
Do you imagine pushing that conspiracy theory that aliens a little microscopic little flying saucers
Floating around in your bloodstream and when you look at photos the white blood cells of those are actually like
UFOs that's why they look like little plates little floating around in you and stuff like that
Oh, dude, there's so much wasted potential because that is a legit
Really good conspiracy theory someone can build off of germs or cryptids germs are in in this sense
You would say like they're cryptids. There's something that don't exist that shouldn't exist naturally
It's an undiscovered creature we refer to all these germs as if it's some sort of biological thing
But it's still some on the border of paranormal. It has a physical body, but it's it's ghostly in some way
That's such a good conspiracy theory and then vaccines actually contain miniature UFOs by getting the vaccine
You're getting an alien invasion in your bloodstream. Come on. That's good stuff
And it's so wasted because he's talking about goat men and dinosaurs and swords and caves
And he it's like even he knows even he knows that that's a good conspiracy theory because that's not how he ends off this rant
He doesn't end off saying oh, you know that vaccines have UFOs in them. That's great
Do you have anything else to tell us and then he says so how close do you live to the swamp?
What in the world
What does that mean
What is it have to do with anything? There was no buildup to it at all
He's talking about laying in grass and now he's asking me how close I live to the swamp or pond. He also says, you know ponds as well
Dude this guy is almost like the Nikola Tesla of conspiracy theories like
When they ask you a little too much credit, but you see a glimmer of genius in it germs are cryptids
Oh, I love that
Vaccines contain UFOs. I love that but everything else is so much nonsense
I almost feel like this is what it can this is like the in the look inside of someone whose brain has been so fractured by conspiracy theories
They can't even spout out conspiracy theories anymore. Well, they can but it's mixed it was so much nonsense
So much white noise that I mean this post was four years ago and it had like zero comments
Obviously who's gonna comment on this right this guy's gonna hunt you down put you in a vaccine
Shrinking you down. I guess if he has that technology
Then he doesn't need to really do it if you're that level of genius, you don't need to be stringing people down other than you just want to but
fascinating
Stuff very very fascinating stuff a fractured mind may actually see a bit of the truth
This is a possible that germs viruses bacteria
Aren't what we think they are
There's something darker evil. There's something that evolved over time
We used to fear werewolf and Dracula, but now the real monsters are hidden
Everywhere we breathe them in every minute. We pick them up when we touch contaminated surfaces
We can do our best our bodies are still invaded with a cryptid with a monster with a creature that wants to destroy us
But nowadays you can't use the crucifix to stop them. No silver bullet can destroy a bacteria
The only thing we can do is look to our intergalactic neighbors and ask for help
The aliens are more than willing to help is they shrink a fleet of UFOs
To fit into a hypodermic needle the close encounter doesn't come with the UFO in the countryside
it comes as a
Armada of alien starships flies around your liver slowly blowing up little goat man germs who have built a camp on
Your left rib cage. It is a war not of the world. It is a war of survival
Aliens versus cryptids
dinosaurs versus
And all of it is happening inside the human body
Sometimes the worst monster isn't the boogeyman under your bed
Sometimes the worst monster isn't even man himself. The worst monster is what is inside of us
So there you go next time you go to your doctor look around be thankful
They're not also porn stars the next time you go to your doctor. Just think
Just thank them and say thank you for putting the aliens in my body
Because otherwise
Well, who knows what would happen?
That doctor will look at you with a knowing nod a wink and then he'll turn around and
Point at his ankle
Dead rabbit radio gmail
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/ dead rabbit radio
Twitter is at dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day. I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
*Music*