A mysterious beast slaughters, mutilates, and eats villagers.
And the government can't stop it.
And then we take a look at the phenomenon known as the third man.
When you're lost in the middle of nowhere and someone appears at your side seeming to
help you, are you going crazy?
Or have you finally seen your guardian angel today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day.
I hope you're having a great day too.
I am broadcasting live, not really, but I am broadcasting with a half-shaved head.
I was giving myself a faux-hawk yesterday and my clippers I realized halfway through
are much more dull than I had thought they had.
I bought them a couple years ago, I should have figured it out.
I don't have any oil for it.
So I got one side of my head looking pretty smooth, looking pretty tight.
The other side of my head, not so much.
So I got to go and buy a pair of clippers.
And I don't care.
I mean, the point of the way I wear my hair anyways, I always look like I'm either a bushman
or a viking.
And their hair wasn't that even either.
So I'm not too worried about it.
But if you happen to see me about today and wonder why is his hair half-cut, that's why.
So we're going to go ahead and get started with our first episode.
Now our first episode is a bit of a double header because we're going to talk about what
seems to be like one of the most badass jobs.
So from the year 2016 to 2018 in India, there's a man eating tiger and here are two cubs walking
around.
That's my tiger noise.
That's the prowl before they go "oww!"
And they're eating people.
13 people are killed.
And the villagers are like, "Dude, this totally sucks.
This tiger's eating all of us."
And the reason why the cubs were also targeted because the mama tiger would kill someone
and then let the little cubs eat it.
So they have all become officially man-eating tigers, which means they have to be put down.
They have developed a taste for that sweet, sweet human meat.
Someone has to take them out.
Now this is dope.
This is what I thought was so dope.
There is a hunter named Nawab Shafath Ali Khan.
And he is the...
He's like a big game hunter to the point where he's basically the James Bond of big game
hunters.
The government calls him up and they're like, "Khan, we need your help."
And he's like, "I'm already on it."
And they're like, "How'd you know we wanted that rhino killed?"
He's like, "I know.
I read the news."
He goes around and they hire him to take out wild animals.
And they sent him to kill a rogue elephant, or more than one.
He actually killed his first rogue elephant when he was only 19.
They were having this huge boar infestation in the area.
And they're like, "Hey, we need you to go and call the boar in this area."
He killed 250 of them.
And he's like, "I'm just doing a social service."
They were like, "You're kind of nuts, man.
You're like killing all these animals."
Conservation groups hate him.
And when this case first came out, all these people were getting killed.
And conservation groups were like, "No, no.
You don't know what happens if you find the tiger and it's not the right tiger and you
shoot that one."
And he's kind of like, "I've been doing this job for a while.
I know what I'll be tracking."
And they're like, "No, you must have harmony and balance with nature."
Now, I don't have a problem with obviously conservation efforts.
But if you have a tiger that's killed 13 people, and in the months before they hired him, he
had killed three people, not him, the tiger.
The tiger had killed three people in one month.
So the government's like, they'd let it go on for two years.
The government's like, "This is just going to get worse."
And Khan was like, "The area is starting.
There's not a lot of other animals for the tiger to eat where the tiger's at.
So it's just going to keep eating humans until we stop it."
Conservation groups try to block him from the hunt.
The court ruled that you can go out and kill the tiger.
But actually they ruled that you can capture the tiger, but if you can't capture it, you
can kill it.
So Khan tried to capture it.
I'm sure Khan had his fingers crossed behind his back.
And he's like, "Oh, yeah, sure.
Capture it."
Again, this is just totally badass.
So he goes to hunt it, and he shows up at the place, the village area, and he's like,
"I don't need jeeps.
I hunt on elephants."
So he's riding elephants.
Him and his team are riding elephants through the area.
Now I imagine, I know India's quite populous, but I imagine this particular part of India
is more like on the outskirts.
So it's not like he's riding elephants through Mumbai, like shooting the tiger as it's running
through the streets.
I don't think it's like Black Hawk Down, where it's like this huge urban warfare.
Although now that I say that, that would be quite cool.
Eventually it takes him about a month.
This thing had been around for two years.
It takes him about a month or two.
They do corner it.
His son takes the shot.
His son actually does end up killing the tiger.
Family business.
And so people complain that it was killed and stuff like that.
And he's like, "Listen."
He also, he's pretty good at his quotes too.
He is basically the James Bond of hunters.
His quote was, "When people complained about him killing it, him killing animals in general,
he goes, 'Blame the courts.
Blame the courts.'
This is his exact quote.
'My job is of a hangman.
I am the man who is putting the noose on the convict and pushing the button of the gallows.'"
So it's not his decision to kill these things.
The government is saying, "Go take care of this."
And he's like, "Okay."
Just like a hangman is said, "You gotta kill this guy."
And the hangman's like, "Okay.
It's a living right?"
But they do kill it.
And then when they asked him before he started the hunt too, this is another quote.
"Before he started the hunt, they were asking him, 'So why do you want to kill this tiger?'
And he goes, 'I have no desire to shoot the tiger or even capture it.'
They have called me because they are incompetent.
He's killed all these people over two years.
Takes care of it in a month."
So.
He's just gonna go on now.
It's a family business.
His son will carry on his legacy.
I find that interesting.
That's a much longer segue than I expected to the story that I do want to address right
now.
And this is the story of, I talked before about cryptids who killed people and I found one,
the poplick monster.
I may have found another one.
I think it really depends on what you believe, but it definitely has racked up quite the
body count.
We're going to Malai.
Sorry, we're going to Malai.
It's the year 2002.
It's August.
People are just kind of wandering doing their things in their village, fetching water, making
clay pots, watching friends.
I don't know.
It's not back in time.
So I mean, they was a village, so they didn't have a huge infrastructure, but you know,
it's not like they were just sitting around doing like shadow puppets and stuff.
This guy goes, 'You know what?
I'm gonna go out.
I'm gonna go get some more water.'
And everyone's like, 'Okay.'
You know.
'Bye, dad.'
They should have hugged him.
That jokes in bad taste.
Guys walking off through the darkness to go get some water.
He's glowing green eyes.
All of a sudden we see beast vision running towards him.
A point of view of the creature, like a bad horror movie.
The man is beset by a creature, knocks him to the ground, attacks him, rips off his hands,
and then his legs.
A short time after that, man's walking around the village on the outskirts, not thinking
safety in numbers, walking around the outskirts.
They can, 'Hmm, I wonder what's gonna happen on friends tonight.
I wonder if Ross and Rachel will ever end up together.'
Creature attacks him.
Huge claw shreds him, ripping out both of his eyes and both of his ears oddly enough.
Short time after that.
People are getting a little airy at this point.
A woman is doing her laundry.
I don't know specifically what these people were doing.
I just know that they were attacked.
So a woman's doing her laundry, she's hanging it up on her clothesline.
She's thinking, 'That Chandler being.'
All of a sudden, gets attacked from behind, smashed to the ground, feels powerful jaws
begin to close over her head.
Oh wait, no, for this to happen, she gets smashed from the front, lands on her back,
feels powerful fangs start to claw into her head.
Something eats off her nose and her mouth.
These are the survivors, by the way.
We've dead 20 horribly maimed by this creature.
The four legged creature that's just attacking people on site, really.
The police come into the area, the paramilitary police come into the area, a bunch of game
rangers come in, they're searching for it and they can't find it.
Finally though, they do find a large beast roaming the wilderness and they light it up.
Kill it.
So, oh, it was a hyena.
It was just a rabid hyena.
It's a one-off incident, freak of nature.
Now the villagers are saying, 'We saw it and we knew what it looked like.
It wasn't a hyena.'
It was like a quadruped, it was like a predator type, not like alien predator, but like a
four legged, like, hairy creature monster.
Well, they said hyenas had really small legs and the creature that was attacking us was
much bigger and the government's like, 'No, it's, we shot it.'
It was a rabid hyena, it trusts us, that makes sense.
That's why the hyena would be attacking people, that's why it was just like super vicious.
It was crazy, it wasn't thinking.
People are like, 'You know, maybe, maybe.'
Seven months later, villagers are going about their day.
Now I want to say this isn't one village either, this is a massive landscape with multiple
villages because we'll see the number pop up here in a second.
It's not just like one village of ten people.
This is a pretty big land mass with these different villages in it.
Seven months later though, the villagers are walking around just doing villager stuff and
they notice a lump in the field, probably about 30, 40 feet away.
They walk over to it and they're like, 'Oh, I hope, I hope that's not what I think it
is, it kind of looks like a human body.'
Old woman with her head crushed and intestines half eaten hanging out of her body.
They're like, 'Oh no, this isn't good.'
Short time after that, more attacks.
People just getting horribly disfigured by this creature appearing out of the darkness.
They find another old woman, head just completely just, 'pfft,' guts ripped out half eaten.
And then what really started to spark the panic was they found another body, not quite
as large as a woman's, a baby, half eaten.
Four thousand people from all these different villages in the area, four thousand people
just packed their stuff up and left.
They marched all the way to this community center and it was like 100 kilometers away
from the villages.
They had like this big community center.
Four thousand people just said, 'We're done.'
Packed up the stuff that they had and they marched all the way there and they said, 'We're
staying in here until that thing is killed.'
Because this second round of attack, three dead, sixteen wounded, just seven months after
the first attack.
And the government says, 'Listen, there must be another rabbit I eat, right?'
And the villagers are saying, 'No, this is the spirit of the creature that you killed
coming back for more blood.'
That story happened in August 2002.
There was absolutely no follow up to it.
Now and this story was from the BBC.
This wasn't like from some fringe website.
The Mollowai Terror Beast is what it's called, has popped up now on cryptid websites.
These initial reports, there's tons of people quoted, there's doctors and politicians and
villagers and things like that.
These are very, very well sourced stories and there was no resolution to it.
There's no, 'Oh, they finally killed it and there was another rabbit hyena.'
There's nothing.
The story just ends with that second news report of the mass migration of people.
The end.
Nothing.
It's very bizarre.
Now, it's fair to say that back in 2002 internet record keeping isn't to the level it is now,
but it's kind of creepy.
What if there was something out?
I mean, like, it's just weird to me that the story just ends, that there's absolutely
no follow up.
Did the 4,000 people eventually go back to their villages?
I doubt they're still in the community center, but did they ever catch this thing?
Was it ever yes another rabbit hyena?
This is what they killed the first time not the right creature, and if it wasn't, if there
was a cryptid operating in that area and it knew it was being hunted and basically the
hunters kill another creature and they think that's it, what level of intelligence would
you need of a natural predator to say, 'You know what, I'm going to lay low for a while.
I'm going to lay low, let them get not scared of me anymore and then I'm going to come back
when they least expect it.'
Weird.
It's a weird story.
I imagine if you had a cryptid that was smart enough to lead the hunters to go kill another
animal and then come back around and start eating people again.
That's incredibly unlikely.
It's incredibly unlikely.
But yeah, I think the story is interesting because it is a cryptid with a body count.
It came back from the dead or just another hyena got rabies.
And there's no resolution to it.
It could still be going on or just have ended with them never catching the second creature.
Those poor people could still be at the community center and they never found out that, yes,
Ross and Rachel did end up together.
Mollow-eyed terrorbeast.
Another cryptid with a body count.
I bet you there's a lot more out there.
And what's funny is I bet you there's a lot more out there because the people who see
them don't come back to tell the tale.
And that actually leads us into our next story.
This is a phenomenon I heard about a long time ago.
I've always found completely interesting and you can look at it from a few different ways.
You can look at it from a scientific view.
You can look at it from a paranormal view.
I'm going to read you this poem here.
You're like, "Oh, yeah, Jason.
I've always wanted Jason to read a poem on his podcast.
I'm going to read you this poem."
I didn't write it, but I could have because I'm not good.
This poem is called, "Well, It's an Excerpt from the Wasteland" by T.S. Eliot.
Who is the third who walks always beside you?
When I count, there are only you and I together.
But when I look up ahead of the white road, there is always another one walking beside
you.
Gliding wrapped in a brown mantle hooded.
I do not know whether a man or a woman.
So T.S. Eliot wrote that from a much longer poem, but that's the section that we're going
to be talking about because there is something known as the third man phenomenon.
And it's named after that poem.
And that part of the poem is based on a real life event.
Back in, like, 1919, right before the outbreak of the World War I, of the World War I, of
the Great War, there was a guy named Ernest Shackleton, or I'm sorry, Sir Ernest Shackleton.
And he's a really fascinating guy.
I have read a lot about him to prep this episode.
And I was like, "I think the story that goes into this is more fascinating, but I don't
know if it really fits this show, but I'd recommend taking a look.
The show notes are there."
A really, really just adventurous guy.
But he came up with this plan.
He wanted to take a boat to one side of the South Pole, walk across the South Pole, and
then be able to get on another boat.
He was an adventurer.
And he was going to be considered one of the greats of the heroic age of Arctic expedition.
And that's all, because I can go on and on.
It's a very fascinating story, but it's a daily podcast.
I only have half an hour.
Anyway, so while this was going on, it didn't work out.
And his ship got crushed by ice, because it froze, and then the ice froze more, and it
crushed his boat.
And they had to live on an iceberg for a couple...
I guess I'm talking about it a little more.
He had to live on an iceberg for a couple months, and then him and his team goes, "We're
going to take a smaller boat.
We're going to go to this island, the South Georgia Islands, and there's a wailing station
there.
Everyone else stay behind on this iceberg.
Ice flow.
We're going to take this boat.
We'll go get help."
And that's what the boys do, and they end up on the wrong side of South Georgia Island,
and they have to hike for 36 hours over these mountains, because they know that if they don't
make it to the research station, the wailing station, everyone on the ice flow is going
to die.
It was like another 40 people left behind.
So they just walk.
And Ernest Shackleton, when he got back, everyone survived miraculously.
He said, "You know, there was three of us.
It was me.
My two other guys were marching over this 36 hours march over this mountain.
He goes, 'But there was a fourth person there.'
They're absolutely like, 'I always felt like there was a fourth person marching with us.'
And the other people fell to two in that expedition.
Climbers have talked about, they're climbing up mountains.
They get really, really high up in the mountain, and there's a ton of stories about this stuff.
They'll be climbing, and a climber will climb up with them and be like, 'Hey man, what's
up?'
And they're like, 'Oh yeah, it's really good.
Really good climbing, isn't it?'
'Yeah, it's great.
What's your name?
My name's Jimmy.
Hey, my name's Jason.
How you doing?'
And the one guy who actually did talk about Jimmy said, 'There was another climber with
me.'
And he told me, 'Hey man, check your oxygen gauge.
You might want to make the mix better.
Yeah, this is how I do it.
See?'
He goes, 'I'm looking at him.'
He goes, 'I could hear the sound of his oxygen tank.
We had this long conversation.'
He goes, 'We get to the top of the summit, turn around, completely gone.'
There was another guy who was also climbing Mount Everest, who was climbing up and this
guy was just like, 'Come on, keep going.
No, no, no.
I think maybe now it's the time for rest.
Yeah, let's catch your breath for a while.
You feeling good?
Yeah, yeah, I'm feeling good.
Okay, you want to start climbing again?'
He's a very encouraging voice to the point where this climber, he had a snack in his
pocket.
He took it out of his pocket, broken in half, turned to give it to the other guy.
There was no one there.
He was alone on the mountain.
And this thing is called the third man phenomenon, and it's this almost universal belief that
when you're trapped by yourself or you're in extreme circumstances, you will sense
somebody else there to encourage you on.
There was a guy named Ron de France.
I don't want to just keep reading off incidents, but I find this fascinating.
There was this guy named Ron de France.
This will be my last one.
There's a guy named Ron de Fran Ciesco, September 11th.
He was on the 84th floor, the plane hit, and he's like, 'Oh, the building's on fire.
I better go down the stairs.'
And he starts going down the stairs.
Everyone else is running up because the floor is down there on fire.
We have to get away from the fire.
And he goes, 'I'm going to go downstairs anyway.'
And they're like, 'You're going to die.
You can't go down there.'
And it is on fire, and he grabs a piece of drywall, and he decides to start trying to
push his way through the fire, and it's too hot.
And then he hears a voice on the other side of the fire being like, 'Come on, you can
do it.
You can do it.
And I know it's really painful and scary right now, but you can do it.
You have to do it.'
And he pushes his way through the fire.
That voice, there was no one on the other side of the fire telling him to keep going.
And he survived, obviously, to tell that tale.
Third-Man Phenomenon is so common.
There have been multiple scientific studies done on what causes the Third-Man Phenomenon.
There was a recent one.
They talked to 83 hikers, 83 mountain climbers.
So what the study basically showed was that half of them had bizarre encounters, but not
to the level that it would be classified as a psychotic episode.
And then I think it was like 23% of them, because I don't have my notes in front of
me.
But 23% of them had what they would be classified medically as a psychotic encounter, i.e.,
a hallucination.
But they also had symptoms of mountain climbing sickness.
Probably like they had symptoms of brain swelling, because of the oxygen deprivation,
things like that.
But a good quarter of them, a good 25% of them, had a psychotic episode and were physically
totally fine.
They had no oxygen, loss, they had no brain swelling, nothing like that.
So you had people who at the bottom of the mountain were completely mentally healthy.
They go up the mountain, they have a psychotic episode, they come back down.
And all of this stuff generally ends right after the event.
It's not like this invisible friend's hanging out with you for the rest of your life.
And that's what the third man factor is.
There's two, I mean obviously the first explanation is, and again they've tried replicating this
multiple times, there's all sorts of studies done where people have said where.
And it's hard because you can't take someone and put them under stress and make them like
see somebody else.
But they go maybe it's disassociativeness, maybe they're so stressed out they're actually
seeing another person mimic their movements to help them through something.
It's some sort of coping mechanism.
Some people think that it's related to oxygen deprivation or just a high stress event.
Some people think it's the physical toll on the body because sailors, people who are stranded
at sea will wake up and there'll be another person on the raft.
This is quite common among survivors of horrible events.
They'll see these things.
Science is really trying to figure out what it is.
What causes the brain to begin to hallucinate, what causes an otherwise healthy brain to
begin to hallucinate or have psychotic episode.
Now obviously the other side of it is, it is a guardian angel or some sort of spirit.
There's an old legend that if you die on a mountain climb, that you, it is then your
job to protect other hikers and climbers from having the same fate.
Now personally, if you died doing what I'm doing, I don't want your advice.
I think that's good advice to take.
If I'm trying to learn how to drive a bus and a ghost of a previous bus driver shows
up and he's like, "Hey, you better use your turn signal."
I'm like, "We're on a freeway.
I don't think I'm using my turn signal right now."
I would be a little concerned if a ghost of a hiker was trying to help me.
But that's the other thing a lot of people think that the third man factor is either
an angel, a spiritual guide or, interestingly enough, I know I mispronounced that word but
I'm going to keep going.
It's possible that the third man effect is a scientific thing.
It's a scientific process and that is where the stories of guardian angels come from because
people back in the olden times would endure these horrible things and then they would
come back and tell their people, "Yeah, in the middle of the desert when I was all trapped,
this dude showed up and just helped me through the desert and helped me find water."
It's always the weird thing too, is that their advice is always helpful.
They'll say, "Hey, check your oxygen gauge."
The guy will look down and be like, "Oh yeah, I probably should check my oxygen gauge.
You're right."
Keep pushing through the fire.
You'll be okay.
The guy pushes you through the fire and is okay.
So if you back in olden times and even today but even more importantly in olden times when
these stories were first being told about angels and messengers of God, that would be the only
way you could explain it.
You'd say, "Yeah, this ghost or this person who wasn't real helped me through this horrible
tragedy and then left."
I just talked about the talking tumor on Friday.
It could be some...that is basically a level of the third man factor.
But what was interesting was in the paper I initially read for this topic, for this episode,
there's a scientific research about the mountain climbers having the psychotic episodes.
And they were saying that, you know, the climbers come down and they go, "Yeah, I did hallucinate,
but it was very helpful.
It helped me to keep going.
Help me to push on."
The paper, the article says, "Yeah, because you had a good psychotic episode.
If you had a bad psychotic episode, you wouldn't live to tell about it."
So we talk about the third man factor.
But is there an opposite one?
Is there a time when a sailor is sitting on a raft in the middle of nowhere?
And instead of the encouraging man sitting on the raft with him saying, "Just give it
another day.
Just give it another day."
What happens when he wakes up and there's a man sitting on the raft and he goes, "You're
never going to live.
Just give up.
It's all over."
We would never hear his story.
Or what about when the guy's climbing in the middle of Mount Everest and another climber
shows up and they're talking and he goes, "I think your gauge is broken on your oxygen
tank.
I think you need to turn it up.
I think that's..."
And it starts messing with you.
Or go left.
Go left here.
I know a shortcut.
We never hear those stories.
It's weird because it is a phenomenon that is only positive because only the people who
have the positive experiences live through it.
But are there out of for every third man event that we have, are there hundreds more of people
lost, of people trapped, of people cornered by flames and someone appears in front of
them and says, "Come with me.
Come with me.
I know a way out."
And we just find a body, a set of bones, or nothing at all.
Who was their third man?
Okay, so I didn't want to ruin the narrative because I really like this episode.
I really like the way it's turning out.
But I'm editing it.
I'm editing this at the end.
If you stick around and listen to it.
I'm editing the episode and I start listening back to it.
And I'm talking about how I don't want to get lessons from somebody who died doing what
I did.
Now, I haven't driven a car in maybe seven years at this point.
Maybe longer, maybe closer to nine.
So what I said, if a ghost told me, "Hey, you better use your turn signal right now."
My response was, "Dude, we're on a freeway.
I don't think I'm using my turn signal."
Because I was thinking, "You don't turn on a freeway."
I realized editing the episode, that you have to use turn signals to change lanes.
So really, even in my example, there's most likely there was a semi-barreling down the
road and the ghost of a bus driver showed up and said, "Dude, you haven't driven in
nine years."
"You should damn turn signal."
And I'm like, "Nah, man.
We're on a freeway.
You don't use turn signals on a freeway."
And then I just doom myself and all my passengers to a lifetime of also warning future travelers.
Although I'm sure the ghost would be like, "Dude, you do not get to warn anybody about
anything ever."
So I figured I would just...
I'm sure, honestly, I think probably most listeners listen to the show when they're
at work or during their homework and that small passage probably didn't jump out to
them.
But I was like, "Oh my God."
That's why.
My exit music queued up here because I didn't mute it.
But we'll just go ahead and end it out here.
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @jasonokarvinor.
Here we go.
We'll just let it fade out.
I'll do a little mix fade out.
Thanks for listening, guys.
I just had to add that in there.
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]