When a young woman is deep asleep, she hears a voice in her head say "Defend yourself!"
Just in time to find two invaders breaking into her room.
Then we meet a man who's traveling through Utah and saw a strange otherworldly sight.
Or did he? And then insanity week continues. As we travel to a small town in the middle of America,
prepare yourself to examine
the parable of the automobile. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. Hope you guys are having a great day too. Buckle up.
This is another weird one. First off, riding into Dead Rabbit Command on the back of a gilded gopher.
It's our newest Patreon supporter, Jizz Leopard. Everyone give a round of applause to Jizz Leopard.
He's really that poor gopher. I just imagine a giant leopard on the back of this little gopher being like "Ahh!
Jizz Leopard, you're gonna be our captain or pilot this episode. Please don't eat the gopher."
That's too late. You guys can't support the Patreon if you don't eat gopher's. That's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show really really helps out a lot. We got a ton of stuff to cover.
So Jizz Leopard, I'm gonna toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy. We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit Command.
We are headed out to Houston, Texas.
*Pfft*
Jason Jalopy is an old-timey car driving us all the way out. It's April 5th, 1993.
We're in Houston, Texas and there's this young woman she's sleeping in bed. We don't have her name. We'll call her Makayla.
In the middle of her dream, she hears a voice yell out "Defend yourself!"
And she wakes up to an empty bedroom.
So she doesn't really... Maybe it's just her head. I mean, that's usually where dreams are, but maybe she was just imagining it.
She wakes up. She's in this room by herself for just a moment. And then walking through the walls.
Just phasing right through. She sees two gray aliens.
She's panicking obviously. And one of them begins to approach her, is getting closer and closer to her.
And she remembers. She's thinking "What am I supposed to do? What am I supposed to do when someone attacks me?"
"Defend yourself!" She remembers that. That was it. That's the reason I had the dream.
She reaches out and she grabs this gray alien's head.
And she grabs on to its big black eyeball. And then she pulls.
It turns out, and I've heard this before in alien encounters, it turns out that the giant black eyes
on the gray aliens are hard plastic.
Or some sort of biofilm that is not their actual eye. It's the equivalent to
if an astronaut went to another planet, like the documentary Planet 51 starring the rock.
If an astronaut went to another planet, they would think or
they'd think we were a cyclops. We had a giant head and then one big visor.
And if you lift the visor up, you would see Joanne "The Rock" Johnson. But otherwise, it would just look like a cyclops.
That this is some sort of protective coating. She grabs on and she pulls it away.
And this mucus begins to cover her hands.
Whatever was either the adhesive here or was some sort of organic liquid,
similar to blood, like "Come on, we can stuff that can be attached to you."
And be attached fairly permanent, but it's still not part of your makeup.
But she rips this off of it. She rips the eyeball off. Doesn't rip the eyeball out.
Doesn't poke it in. It would be the equivalent of taking someone's sunglasses off.
But a bunch of mucus is shooting out. After she peels this eye visor off, the gray aliens retreat.
I found that story on ThinkAbout@Docs.com. They got it from Trisha McCannon.
She wrote it for the International UFO Library Magazine, June, July issue 1994.
It's a very, very brief story. The reason why I wanted to cover it was,
one, and gray alien gets beat up. I like that.
Two, I think it fits in with "Insanity Week" because we see these visions of these gray aliens
all the time in literature, movies, things like that.
And we're, at least at a certain point, we can be comforted by the lore.
It's not so comforting when they're trying to drill a hole in your brain.
But if you see a gray alien, you know what a gray alien is.
You see a ghost, you know what a ghost is. But when you see things that are
outside the realm of possibility, it's even more disturbing.
Like the episode I did that, to this day, I get emails about.
To this day, I get emails about how disturbing this episode was.
I'm not going to give away the punchline. Those of you who listen to it will remember
it was the one about the two kids in Mexico who came home one day
and went into their kitchen and they saw something that drove them mad.
And you gotta listen to that episode to really get the gimmick.
Don't give it away. Don't give it away in the comments, but it just doesn't make sense.
It would drive you mad to see something like that.
And that episode was like episode 200, 300, something like that.
I get emails to this day, in YouTube comments to this day,
about how disturbing people found that episode.
And so when you look at a gray alien and you know the big giant head,
you know the big black eyes, but what happens? What's under that?
If that's not really their eyeball, if that is the equivalent of a pair of sunglasses or a protective visor,
what do they really look like?
What if the whole, and I've heard this before, the whole gray skin
is an astronaut suit. That's why a lot of people say it feels like plastic.
It feels rough when you touch a gray alien, but it's actually a super tight space travel suit.
So what are they?
Like, could you imagine peeling one of those eyes off and looking and seeing
something truly alien? Something you had never imagined was possible.
Something that evolved on another planet. You're looking at its real eyeball staring back at you.
All the TV shows, all the video games, all the cartoons, action figures, everything,
prepared you for a gray alien encounter. But when you peel that back,
you see something that no one else on earth has seen, or at least survived to tell the tale.
Just a leopard, let's go ahead and hop in the dead rabbit, Durgible.
We're going to leave behind Houston, Texas. Have a good night, but Kayla, she can't sleep.
I'm okay, but she can't sleep. She's like, no, I think she'll come back. Oh, don't worry,
they'll come back. They will come back this time with reinforcements, but we won't be here.
Just leopard, we're leaving behind Houston, Texas. We are headed out to a remote part of Utah.
We don't know exactly where the story takes place. A remote part of Utah is what, 98% of the state
takes place somewhere in Utah. I also want to give a shout out to Jim Jam. Jim Jam is the one who
recommended this story. I don't know if I've announced this on the show yet. It's been up and
running for a couple of weeks. We actually have a Discord for the Patreon supporters that we've
been doing. If you are a Patreon supporter, you can listen to me record an episode live every
Sunday morning, which has been a lot of fun. It's been a lot of fun and allows me to kind of test
out material. And sometimes I'll ask you guys questions, how does this story work? So if you're
a Patreon supporter, that is a really cool thing to check out. If you've been thinking about joining
the Patreon, now is a great time to do it. We do have this Discord setup. It's really cool.
So Jim Jam sent this over to me. Very, very brief story. But again, it's the implications of it
that I think are interesting. We're in Utah. We're at a gas station. A little turgible is
landing on the roof of a gas station. Everyone's like, "Look, Martha, it's one of them floating
machines." We jump out to get some Wetchum-a-Cullet bars and some Sprite Zero. And we see a commotion
in the parking lot of this gas station. This was posted by Monkey897. And they were telling this
story. They were driving through remote part of Utah late at night. They stopped at the gas station.
And there's 10 people in the parking lot. They're just standing there in a circle,
swaying back and forth. They're not making any noise. They're not chanting. They're just
swaying as one movement standing in a circle. In each of their hands, they're holding a glowing
white orb swaying back and forth in the middle of this parking lot standing in a circle.
That's it. That's the whole story. Monkey gets back in his car. They drive away. Apparently,
this happened at night in a remote part of Utah. That's all we get. This was posted on the Utah
subreddit. And I actually reached out to Monkey. And I was like, "Hey, is there any other information
available?" It never got back to me. Other people were like, "Whoa, dude, do you know where that was
at?" And he was like, "I don't know. Remember?" No detail whatsoever with this story. None. And then
he just goes on. I looked at other Reddit posts. He's posting. He's just a normal person. He's not
in a bunch of weird subreddits. He's not a member of the MEPH subreddit. He's not a member of all
of these UFO crawler sightings subreddit stuff like that. And the reason why I wanted to cover
this story, I was hoping for more information, obviously, to either suss out whether or not
this was a lark. And he's like, "Oh yeah, and then the next day, like, 10 of them showed up at my door
and they had an 11th sphere and they, ah, okay. And now I know you're making it up. Or you're in
great danger. One of the two. You're either totally making it up or you're about to be absorbed
into a cult. Either or. I can't help you either way. But no, nothing. And I started thinking about it
and it actually stuck with me because I think about it. I read all. I read constantly. That's all I do
for this show. I'm reading paranormal ghost stories, conspiracy stuff. It's not an exaggeration.
And so that's why my vacations are so valuable to me. And so when a story sticks in my head,
that's meaningful. Because I just go through stuff. Sometimes I'll read two, three paragraphs,
dismiss it. It's just not interesting. Sometimes I'll read whole articles and
decide not to cover them, whatever. This story stuck with me for weeks. I thought, "Oh, that's such an
interesting story." And here's why. One, the visual is interesting, right? Just on a basic
story level. It's an interesting story. I love paranormal stuff that is on, in society, but
on the outskirts of society. The hidden war, the masquerade. As a vampire, the masquerade players
know very well. It's this idea that right next to our reality, there is a shadow reality,
something else going on. So I like that urban magic type of thing. This is happening in a fairly
open, spot-to-remote part of Utah, but it is in a parking lot of like a Circle K, 7-Eleven,
whatever it is. You have that element. But then secondly, it's funny to think that we as paranormal
people, right? We are half ghosts, half skeleton. We as paranormal people, people who investigate
this stuff, if we were driving through an area in the middle of nowhere and we saw something like
this, we'd be like, "Oh dude, probably take notes. We would be the ones who'd get killed by the cold."
But you take notes, I'm not advising you to do this, but you would observe and report is what
I'm saying, right? You would remember where you were at, the very least. This is what we do. This
is what, this is our hobby. And the world of the paranormal, the world of the weird, doesn't care.
It really doesn't. It's so interesting because ghost sightings can happen in front of the believer
and the non-believer. UFO abductions can happen to the people who love UFOs and have watched all
the UFO documentaries to someone who doesn't believe in them at all. The paranormal world
doesn't care. It's very, very fascinating the way that works. And that's what happened here.
This guy just didn't care. He stumbled across some weird cult that may have been summoning the dark
god of Kanuna and he just wanted his big gulp. It could have been a weird wacky religion that's
looking for new members. It could have been a lark and they were trying to get people interested
in it and they're starting, "Who knows? Who knows?" But we would have, we would have at least figured
out where we were. And so I love this. I actually love this story. The fact that we don't have a ton
of information about it and the fact that he was so plosive about it and just posted it on
this Utah subreddit. It wasn't even like, the truth is here are some x-oriented subreddit or even
the x-board or anything like that. It was Utah. But I find it interesting. I find it fascinating,
man. He just kind of went on with his life and every so often he might remember this story. He
might be like, "Oh, you know, remember that the giant Chloe norms are invading Earth and great
Lord Kanarnar is taking over the United Nations, absorbing the souls of our leaders?" He's like,
"You know what? This reminds me of that time I could have stopped the invasion of all reality."
But every so often he might remember this story and think about it or he may never. Again,
like this story stuck with me. I might have thought about this story more over the past two
or three weeks than he has. Interesting. That's, that's, that, that to me is very, very interesting.
The reality and the unreality living next to each other and people who aren't interested in at all
bumping into it. A lot of times I'll see people who are like, "I love ghosts. I believe in ghosts,
but I've never seen a ghost. How can I see a ghost?" And they're frustrated because they want proof.
Some guy who doesn't believe in ghosts will have this totally intricate story about how he was in
a cabin one day. This old spectral minor was hanging on the window, "Let me in. Who's got my big toe?"
And you're like, "You still don't believe in ghosts? No, I might have just been an optical
illusion." I mean, the fact that he did rip off my big toe might be more than an optical illusion,
but I still don't believe in ghosts. I think that's just a fascinating thing.
Gislepper, are you ready? Gis gives a little nod of his head.
Gilded Gopher, are you back alive? Gilded Gopher does a little bow. Gislepper, not
Natasha the keys to the carpenter copter. We are leaving behind Utah and we are headed out to
a small town in the middle of America. We're in a small town in America. Let's call it
Pleasantville. It's a small town. You've lived here all your life. You've actually been very,
very successful in life. You're the town judge. So people come to you, "Judge, judge, what should I
do?" You're like, "I'm not a life counselor." But they're like, "No, no, like should I arrest that guy
the cop that cop is walking up to you?" Should I arrest that guy? The guy's shooting at
a bunch of people? Yeah, you should do that. You help people with their problems.
People come to you, you know, chicken thieves and you have to decide their
fate. And you're very well respected judge. But there's been a bit of a controversy lately.
You're starting to hear people complain about these new-fangled machines called automobiles.
Now this is a small town. And for as long as you can remember, the horse and buggy was good enough
for the people of Pleasantville. But these automobiles are coming into town and you've
heard about them. You've never actually been in one. But you've heard about them. They're loud,
roaring machines, fancy pieces of steel fused together for a smooth ride down any country road.
But see, there's a few local residents of Pleasantville who think that the cars are menaces,
thinks that they should be completely banned. Those cars are driving through town, they're
scaring the chickens. Why did you know the other day Billy Bob got drunk, got behind the wheel of his
automobile and smashed over Miss Henrietta's chicken coop? And you go, "Hmm, that is troubling."
Because you've heard that there have been four cases of automobile accidents
in the small town of Pleasantville recently. Now all four of those incidents were tied to
reckless driving. All four of these people were driving over the speed limit, driving in crazy
ways, and two of them were drunk. But these people in town want you to get rid of the automobile.
It is a very loud mob of people shouting at you to get rid of them.
In town there is a small automobile club that has 45 members. And they're pretty open about their
ownership of their cars. They love them. They really love the cars, they love the convenience,
they love the power, the speed, they love the way they look. But you have all these people
complaining in town and you have these 45 people who love their cars. And you have these four accidents.
Henrietta's chicken coop got smashed. Things could get worse. So you decide to ban automobiles
in Pleasantville. And of course the mob is happy. You've made them very, very content.
But the 45 owners of vehicles say that's not fair. Like, sure, listen, we actually have a code of
conduct here at the automobile club. We don't speed. We don't drink and drive. We follow laws,
not just county laws, not just city laws. But we've made up laws for ourselves to regulate
our behavior in these automobiles. And you say, listen, I got four accidents already with these
automobiles. They're too unpredictable. Who knows what damage will come from them?
The leader of the automobile club goes, well, think about this. What if we had our own roads
to drive on? What if we had our own private roads that we drove on? We could drive them around our
own property. You wouldn't even have to worry about them. If you're worried about people causing
accidents, we wouldn't even be on the roads. We wouldn't make horses more skittish. People
wouldn't be jumping out of the way. Just let us drive on our own property. You say no. The people
have spoken. The majority of town have spoken. You are not allowed to operate your motor vehicle
in the city of Pleasantville. The leader of the automobile club says, I understand,
but it's going to be hard to regulate this. We own these vehicles. And we've used these vehicles
to help people before. You may not know that. But when Mrs. Margaret, her wagon broke down,
got stuck in the mud, I personally used my automobile to help get her wagon out of the mud.
I've also given people rides in town when they don't have a horse and buggy. And you say, listen,
I've already made my decision. Automobiles are illegal in this town. The leader of the automobile
club looks at you and he goes, there might be more people in this town who own cars than you know.
One day, Mr. Jones is walking out to his barn. Mr. Jones is a member of the now banned
automobile club. And his beautiful machine has been sitting inside of a barn for the past few months.
Every day he goes out to wash it, to maintain it, to just kind of look at it. He misses driving his
automobile, but the law won't allow it. At that time, his nephew, Tom visits. Hey, uncle, Tom says as
he walks onto the farm. Mr. Jones turns around and goes, oh, my favorite nephew, Tommy, you're here
to hang out with me for a while. You betcha. I'm going to help you with chores and all sorts of
stuff. My voice changed to be more like a child. And Tommy is helping out Mr. Jones doing a bunch of
chores. But at one point, Tommy goes into the barn and he sees this automobile. It's not covered up
by a tarp or anything because Mr. Jones had been working on it that morning. Tommy, his eyes,
what is this? Is this one of those automobiles I've heard so much about?
It is Tommy. Can I get a ride in it? This would be so amazing. It'd be the bees knees.
Mr. Jones goes, I'd love to give you a ride in this machine, but automobiles are illegal.
It would not be right for me to give you a ride in this car.
Aw, shucks, Tommy says. But what if we just drove around on your property? No one would know.
Mr. Jones thanks about it for a while and he goes, well, I have wanted to use my car for a while.
It's just been sitting here too. You would love to ride in the car, obviously. You betcha.
Yeah, sure, Tommy, get in. Let's go for a ride, but only on my property, on my legally owned property.
But this second Mr. Jones starts up that car.
Mrs. McCaggardy in a farm not too far away. Here's the vehicle. What? The busybody says.
I bet you it's one of them automobiles again. And sure enough, she goes out and she sees this
devilish man driving in his pristine automobile. Tommy with a bright smile on his face.
Driving around the farm. That's enough to get Mr. Jones arrested.
When the authorities show up to arrest Mr. Jones, Tom is trying to intervene. No, no, no, no, no,
you don't understand. My voice gets deeper when the police show up and he didn't break any laws.
We didn't leave the property and the officer goes, it doesn't matter. The law is no automobile
operation at all in this city. And Tommy goes, but I was the one who wanted to ride in the automobile.
The officer said, it doesn't matter. He's the adult. It was his decision to drive the automobile.
He's in trouble. Aw, shucks, Tommy says. And then they go, Tommy, we need to get you
back home. And they put him on the back of a horse to ride back to his house as you would
normally travel in this town. And the horse bucks Tommy off. He falls to the ground and gets a black
eye. The horse said that was the horse he thought it was Tommy. Twist ending. Tommy now has this big
black shiner, but he is eventually taken home. And when his parents ask, what happened? How'd
you get this black guy? He goes, well, I was at the farm with Uncle Jones. And I was driving around
his automobile. And before he can tell the whole truth, his parents go, you got injured in an
automobile. I knew I should have been worried about Uncle Jones. So this goes to trial. There's a huge
trial in town. Everyone's there, of course, you have the people who support the automobile club,
but they're undercover. They don't want anyone to know they're on Mr. Jones' side. And then you
have the brain mob of people who warned everyone about how dangerous automobiles were in the first
place. And they bring Tommy up on the stand. They ask him about what happened. And he says,
it was my idea to get in the vehicle. My voice is even deeper now. It gets deep in different parts
of the law process. It was my idea to be in the car. I saw the car. I wanted to get in it. And
the prosecutor goes, well, Mr. Jones showed you the car. No, he didn't. I walked into the barn and
it was there. Yes. But by leaving the car uncovered, he knew you would be fascinated by it. He knew you
would want to be in the car. You see, it wasn't your decision at all. Tom thinks about it for a
second. He goes, yeah, yeah, I guess if I hadn't seen the car, I wouldn't have. See, he led you
on to want to be in the automobile in the first place. It was him. He's a monster. And all of the
people in the crowd who hate automobiles nodded, nodded along to this. Tommy starts to think,
maybe, maybe he did lead me on. Now remember, you're the judge of town and you're sitting,
you're the judge for this trial. I didn't say that. Did you think you're in the audience? No,
you're actually the judge of this trial and you're sitting there and you are hearing this,
but you also see what just happened. This prosecutor, this very clever county prosecutor
that you've seen in hundreds of cases just got that boy to admit that he might have been tricked
into getting into the automobile and you do you register that you know that's interesting.
Like, does the boy really regret it? Or did the boy really want to write on that automobile of his
own volition? This trial continues, but it's not looking good for Mr. Jones. The fact of the matter
is he did break the law. He was using a vehicle. He was driving an automobile. But his defense
lawyer isn't shabby either. And as the defense lawyer gets up and says, listen, here's the facts
of the matter. We have 45 automobiles in town and we've had four accidents, five if you want to
include Tommy getting his black eye, but that was from a horse after the car. If we want to talk about
accidents directly related to cars, we only have those four and those are people who are driving
irresponsibly. Two of them are drunk. When we look at the amount of horses in town, we've had
far more accidents involving horses than we have ever had with cars.
Now, obviously the argument is there's more horses than cars. So of course there's more
accidents, but the defense lawyer goes, listen, there are more horses. Correct. But there are so
many horse accidents. People falling off. Look at Tommy here, got a black eye. People falling off
horses. Horses going skittish, whole wagons being dragged off into the dirt. Horses biting people.
That's apparently that. I don't know if horses are around biting people, but horses robbing banks.
You have all of these incidents with horses. And yes, a car ran over Mrs. McTagarty's barn.
But it just could have easily been a wild horse or a horse drawn carriage with a careless driver
who we also have people who drive carriages drunk. The henhouse is going to be smashed by either
vehicle. It doesn't matter what the vehicle is. A horse and carriage out of control can do as much
damage as an automobile going out of control. They can both kill, they can both maim, they can both
destroy property, your honor. So why are automobiles illegal and horses and buggies not? And you're
sitting there as this judge and you look at the crowd, the numerous crowd, the majority of people
who have spoken over and over and over again. Automobiles are dangerous. The people who use
automobiles are dangerous. They should be banned in Pleasantville. Statistics be damned. Facts are
not relevant. We do not like automobiles. Four accidents are four accidents too much.
Then you look over at the people who you know or have a suspicion. They are members of the
automobile club. You think of the statistics, you think of the emotional damage, you think of the
case in front of you right now with Tom and Mr. Jones. The audience awaits your verdict.
This is what's known as the parable of the automobile. It was written by a anonymous author
named Encephalon back in the year 2000. It was published on a website.
No one is the North American man of association, aka Nambla.
Welcome to insanity week because this is a level of insanity. That's clever.
If I present the same story to you with what they want, the North American man boy love
association. I'm not putting this in the show notes either. I found this because I was covering
a story about this insane politician who had all these really, really wet... he actually
was tried running for office in Virginia or Washington DC. I'll put his stuff in the show
notes. I'm not going to cover the whole story. It's too gross, but he was grosser than this.
Groser than what we're about to discuss. He was running for political office and he said in his
statement of whatever the politician, their platform, he said in his platform, "The parable
of the automobile must be tested by democracy." I go, "What's that?" Then I spent an afternoon.
I condensed. That's a very, very, very long story. I condensed it and made it a flow a little bit
better. I kept the core of it. This politician was eventually arrested trying to get a 12-year-old
girl on a plane flight from California to DC and she was wearing a wig or he was wearing a
wager. They were both wearing wigs. Now he's in prison for 20 years, which is where he belongs.
But on his political platform, he just had all this craziness and he had this thing about the
parable of the automobile must be tested by democracy. I go, "I gotta see what this is. I gotta go down
this rabbit hole." Let's break down what they're saying because now that you know, for those of
you who stuck around here, why is Jason just telling this old-timey story, the automobile club
of 45 members in this small town, 45 dudes. If you live in a big city, there probably are at least
45 active pedophiles. But if you lived in Pleasantville, if you lived in some tiny little town and
there's 45 of them, so anyways, in this small town of the turn of the century, there's 45 boy
lovers. Except so, they're not getting monetized on YouTube. There's 45 boy lovers and that's
where the automobile club represents. And all these people the whole time who were complaining about
how much damage they caused and how they're horrible, they were us. They were normal people
going, "Dude, you can't be doing that. What are you doing with those kids?" And they go, "No, no, no,
those four people you arrested, they were breaking our rules." See, those were rogue child molesters.
Those were the bad ones. See, we do it with love. That's why you put love in our name.
Disgusting. I don't know how much I want to break down this story, but
that's their logic. That's the insanity of this. And I could see someone, a member of Nambla,
reading this and being like, "Oh yeah, man, this is exactly, this is right. Like, we get treated
like we're ostracized if you look at the facts." But the facts don't make, first off, no one's ever
used a child to pull a buggy, to pull a carriage out of a ditch. That doesn't make any sense at all.
Right? None of that stuff makes sense too. The comparison to, you can get just as injured on
a horse as you can in a car. No, right? Because one of them, the horse, represents traditional,
consensual sex between adults. And whether it's like one adult or it's polygamy or group or whatever,
it doesn't matter. They're consenting adults. You can have a whole wagon drain. Doesn't matter.
And if a couple people get injured in that, that would suck for them, obviously. I'll probably do
an episode on it. But that's the horse and buggy. Whether or not they're smashing over Mrs. McCartney's
in-house, it's consensual adults. You're just gross, dude. You can't compare that. And technically,
hopefully, no one's getting injured. And one shouldn't exist. The automobile club
should not exist in this comparison. The horses, you know, hopefully be safe about it. Don't put
a bit in your mouth and try carrying five passengers on your back. I think you'll be fine sexually.
But this is their comparison. It's more people get more people statistically, if you want to
look at raw numbers, I guess, more, I actually know this doesn't make sense. More people get
injured during consensual sex than it does with nambla dudes. And even if I was having consensual
sex with someone and I stubbed my toe or she accidentally, I don't know, bit my dick or something
like that, that's way better than anything these sickos are doing. Right? So anyways, that doesn't
make sense. Using your boy to pull a buggy out of a ditch doesn't make sense. When you think about
it as the parable of the automobile and the boy coming over and seeing the car and being like,
"I want to ride in the car," you do go, well, yeah, of course, like, who wouldn't want to ride in a car
when they're brand new. But if you have to make that, if you make that in the real world, what
they're really talking about is, I don't want to go into detail, but somebody coming over and seeing
and act, either a pornographic magazine video or something like that and going, "Oh, I want to do
that too." That's what that is a connection to. And so the character was saying that I wanted to do it.
And they're saying, "No, he showed you material that made you want to do it." Did you guys know
there's a Spider-Man comic along those lines? It's technically canon. I think it's actually
really important comic book. It turns out Peter Parker was molested as a young boy,
because of something like that. And that happens. It happens to a lot of boys. It happens to a
lot of girls. It happens to a lot of boys. And I think with boys, we dismiss it. We don't talk
about it. So it's more hidden, but it happens to everyone, not everyone statistically, but it
happens to a lot of people. It's not something that you need to be ashamed about. It is something
that you talk to people you feel comfortable with. But yeah, that happened to Peter Parker.
That happened to Peter Parker. He came over to some guy's house and the guy showed him some
magazines. And then Peter Parker got molested. And I know like people have joked about it in
the past. I think that's really important. I think that's really important because there are a lot
of young people, not just young men, but a lot of young people who could read that comic book and
go, "Oh, like it's not that it's not a big deal, but it's something that you can get through.
Something you can get through and get past and thrive." But anyway, so that was that corollary
there. This story doesn't have any crazy, fantastic ending. It doesn't have any horror
ending or anything. I can't make up anything creepier than what we just read. So we're just
going to end it like this. Sometimes the worst insanity is the insanity that hides itself as
sanity. They make a good narrative when you don't know what they're arguing. And I think that happens
a lot. I think a lot of times we hear a story and it sounds good and we nod our heads. We start
agreeing with it and we don't know what the end game is. Could be something simple. Could be a
politician trying to get your vote. Or it could be something nefarious, disgusting, unnatural.
This story is right about one thing though. You don't know how many members are in the automobile
club. And that's the scariest part of all.
[Music]
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also do this up at
facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio. DeadRabbitRadio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day,
but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one, guys.
[Music]