A trio of true crime stories that'll really make you consider
Existing on the planet earth you'll really wonder about whether or not you want to stick around you should
But you'll question it and then we travel back to the conspiracy theory iceberg to look at the only conspiracy theory worth researching
There is no conspiracy theory today on Dead Rabbit Radio
*Music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I can barely say that with a straight face, but I hope you guys are having a great day and hope you guys can say it with a straight face
It's so hot in here. I'm recording in the haunted closet
That's not like the name of a studio if I'm recording in the literal haunted closet
I gotta run my AC and shut it off come in come into a place where the dead has not departed to record this podcast for you
The temperature goes up immediately. I don't even know why they're running the AC for an hour before
Recording each episode, but I'm here for you guys. You know who else is here for us. He never leaves us alone
He's always hanging out in the most convenient part of our body
Is there an in is there an inconvenient part of the bunny stick your finger up your nose?
I want you to pick out our newest patreon supporter. It's boogers. Everyone give a round of applause to boogers you pull him out
He's like my he's like this is not what my name means. I'm not a booger
I don't know boogers. Maybe it's like a ghost of a guy named Gus that
Little less disgusting so pick your nose pull out a booger name it Gus boogers
You are gonna be our captain our pilot this episode if you guys can't support the patreon or if you guys aren't a booger
That's it's preferable, but just helps her the word about the show really really helps out a lot
I actually didn't say that in the last episode with Robert Reith
He was the village person dressed up as a carpenter if you're not a village person
If you don't have a sexy carpenter outfit like Robert Reith or you're not a booger like boogers
totally fine
Both are preferable if you're not those things just helps read the word about the show really really helps out a lot
Robert Reith we're waving goodbye to him as he fades away like a force ghost and boogers
We're gonna toss you the keys to the dead rabbit dirgeable
We're leaving behind dead rabbit command take your salty gooey hands put all over the controls for the next person has to play
The dirgeable we are leaving behind dead rabbit command. We are headed out to a courthouse
We got a court date dude. This kind of sucks
So the other day a patreon
I'm not gonna say who was was driving the Jason Jalopy a little too fast a little too wild got a traffic ticket now because we're all
Fluffle because we're all a family of rabbits. We all have to attend the court hearing and
We're here in court. Well while we're in this courthouse. We're gonna fight this speeding ticket. We get an elevator ding and
Listen man, I've been to court a couple times myself and I've had friends who've gone to court
Everyone's miserable every single person at the courthouse is miserable the person working in the cafeteria is miserable
The judges are miserable. It's not a great place to be I was in court
I was in court when I ran into a solar plexus clown glider. It's a bad place
Interdimensional
Creatures hang out in court rooms. I'll put that episode in the show notes
But ah you don't want to go to court or have anything to do with court or watch the show night court actually that show is pretty funny
I can't make a joke about that being bad
We're in this courthouse
You just want to get the speeding ticket taken care of this very long introduction for three very short stories
But we want to get this speeding ticket taken care of we're in this elevator now
We know every time this door opens a weirdo is gonna get inside
Because that's how the story is framed and that's what happens in real court houses ding elevator door opens and inside steps. Oh
Good this guy is actually a US Marshal
His name is David Timothy moon and we're like, oh, what do you hear for and he's like, oh, you know
I'm a US Marshal so I like do Marshal stuff and we're like, okay, that makes sense
Maybe he'll protect us for the rest of this
Adventure there. We're on this very linear and this very vertical adventurer on we go up another story
the elevator opens up
The elevator opens up and inside steps
Ronnie Lou Helton. He's 73 year old man. So we see this old man walk in he looks like the dude from up
He's just kind of saunter's in and so we know where the marshals here. He's obviously working. We ask hey Ronnie
What are you here for and he turns to us and he says so the other day?
This is totally blown out of proportion
Proportion and everything I'm about to say is alleged because I haven't been found guilty of anything yet
But on April 7th, 2021 so very recently I was minding my business in Corbin, Kentucky
And I was walking through a neighbor
I don't want to tell this story from his point of view
It's gonna sound super creepy because I have to keep saying I did this stuff
So this dude named Ronnie Lou Helton was living in Corbin, Kentucky, and he's walking down the street
He's walking through the Gordon Hill Pike neighborhood. It's 4 p.m
This is prime time to be like hanging out doing little kid stuff playing with GI Joe's or Paw Patrol or whatever kids play with these days
There's a little three-year-old boy in the backyard. Look at me grandma. I'm a three-year-old boy
I don't have imagination yet. I don't know if I'm a jet or a knight
The grandma's like oh great this kid's gonna be a struggle. Three-year-old boys running around his grandma's backyard
Now Ronnie is walking through the neighborhood and he has predator vision
Not predator vision like he'd vision, literal like sexual predator vision. He's like he just sees normal
He just sees normal. There's no like red heat signature, but it's just creepier
He sees this three-year-old boy running in the backyard and he walks up to the fence
Hey, how would you like to come over the fence Ronnie says and the boy's like, you know, probably not and
Ronnie reaches over the fence grabs the boy's hand and starts to lead him along the fence line now Ronnie's a short man
Ronnie's about five foot one and
The boy is three years old so he's obviously short so we're talking like a picket fence
But Ronnie's really not tall enough to reach over and grab the boy, but he noticed there's a part where the
Ground on the boy side of the fence kind of
Lumps up and the fence is technically shorter at that point
So he's leading the boy over to this lump
And he means to pick the boy up and run away with him as this is going on the grandma who's supposed to be babysitting this kid
Looks out and sees
Ronnie leading this kid down the fence line and she goes let go of my son
My grandson, let go my grandson. She's easily confused
Ronnie let's go with the boy the boy runs deeper into the safety of the yard
Now stranger abductions. They're super rare. They do happen. They're terrifying, but that's not even the end of this incident
To make it even creepier. I mean this is like 4 p.m. It's so casual
You have to think that this guy has done this before
Allegedly he then yells to the grandmother quote all give you a
thousand dollars
for this little boy
unquote
That's really creepy the fact that he knew that he had a number
He's probably in the past been like I'll give you 750 dollars and they're like no dice and they're running away
And he's like, hmm, maybe I should up it next time
He's obviously
Doesn't done this enough times to know a thousand dollars is the sweet spot
He yells out I'll give you a thousand dollars for this boy
They say no like you should and the guy then turns and gets in his car, which was just parked right there
They get his license plate number. They turn it over to cops the guys arrested. He's actually charged with attempted kidnapping and
Because he yelled out a price. He actually got charged with human trafficking as well
We're standing in this elevator here with this man who tried to abduct a three-year-old boy and then offered a
$1,000 price tag for the boy and it's so funny because if it was just the kidnapping I probably wouldn't even cover it
I'm like boring
Who then tries to kidnap a three-year-old out of a yard
Call me later when you find out the old man's really a skinwalker or something interesting the fact that he's yelling out a price makes it so chilling
To me. He's probably bought kids before
Allegedly
Allegedly, there's a US Marshal in this elevator. I gotta be careful what I say legally, but it's just creepy
It's so and the fact that he thought the grandma would go you almost tried stealing my grandson
But now that you offered me a thousand dollars come in for some tea. Let's talk
No, he's awaiting some serious serious charges
So we're now in this elevator with this man who tried kidnapping this little kid. That's not cool
It's more than uncool it's disgusting, but the elevator we're still stuck in it
The door opens up another man gets on into the elevator steps
Kevin Wayne Van Levin. It's a 59 year old home inspector
We go hey, we don't learn our lesson by asking the first guy what he was in for we ask this guy
What are you in for and he goes? Oh man, you guys won't believe it
Well, you guys probably will because there's video evidence of it
But this is my story and then he does wavy lines and we're flashbacked into this memory of his reluctantly
We do not want to be in this memory. It's March 12th
2021 again super recent
Those chemtrails are finally starting to catch up with everyone and infecting their brains. We're in Oxford Township, Michigan
Kevin Wayne Van Levin is a home inspector and he is doing what his name implies. He's inspecting a home
He's looking at it and he goes yeah
Four walls four walls a ceiling perfect. Check that down. There does seem to be some sort of foundation or floor
Yeah, it's a floor
He's very very good at his job. He's very thorough
So when he's doing his home inspecting the people whose home he's inspecting they say we're gonna go out get a bite to eat
You do your thing but when they did leave him they didn't expect what was gonna happen
But they had a video camera and so they're out grabbing a quick bite to eat and all of a sudden
Their phone goes off there they're like tone goes off their phone and it shows that they had movement in
their babies nursery
And they're like, oh no, we forgot the baby. I don't know like he's a home inspector. He's walking around the home
Why would you even care that motion sensors were going off?
It pops up on their phone that there's motion in the nursery and the mother she goes
I didn't really I didn't I wasn't really bothered by it, but for some reason I
Decided to look at the video and this is the video we have we see Kevin walk into the nursery. It's very very nice
Nursery, it's I didn't even know was a nursery doesn't have like the
stereotypical crib and like the haunted rocking chair and stuffed animals
It looks more like some weird art deco room
So that's gonna have a real imaginative life, but anyways, it looks very
Spartan as a nursery
Now this is now an interior design podcast you wouldn't know is a nursery except for the fact that this man Kevin picks up an Elmo doll
this tickle me Elmo doll and
He is walking around the Elmo doll and then he turns his back to the camera and he's kind of like in the closet now and
he is
Humping Elmo and you go Jason. How how do you know?
How do you know if he has his back to the camera and he's halfway in the closet? How can you tell?
well, you can you can tell right you can tell from the motion of his arm and
Almost moments of ecstasy. Oh tickle me harder. You can tell he's banging this this doll
Now he might have known there was a camera there
I hope he didn't know he did turn his body enough that he was trying to conceal it from something
But not so much that you can you that you know, right when you see the arm kind of moving not Elmo's arm
but Kevin's arm and
Then you see Elmo smoking his cigarette afterwards
He uses this Elmo doll to masturbate on and then to make things worse
He puts the Elmo doll back where he found it
So the idea was that no one would be the wiser except for him and Elmo and there would just be this
Soaking disgusting Elmo in the corner of this nursery
Well, they were watching it. They're watching it live
They called the police the police actually apparently according to this article. I read on the mail online
By Lauren Lewis the police I believe got there as he was leaving and
He said oh, no, no, I totally wasn't
How do you how do you come back from that?
You're just standing there and two police officers show up and they're like, hey, are you Kevin van Levin and he goes
Yeah, yeah, that's me and they go. Did you have sex with?
You immediately would think how did they know how did they know?
Red fur all over your crotch. You know, how would they know you wouldn't think to come up with a cover story that quickly for that, right?
So he does though apparently he's like no, no, no, it was totally consensual. Elmo. Okay. Want to me?
He denies it. He totally denies it
But then they say well, there's video of you and then he's like, okay, you caught me guys
You hold his hands up to me handcuffed. They're like, we don't want to touch your hands. You know what you're just doing
So he is facing
What was the it was a weird mischief vandalism or misdemeanor
Malicious vandalism and it carries like a two-year sentence and I think because there's the sex angle to it
an odd part of his bond he's not in jail right now. He's able to bond out one of his
conditions of his bond is he can't be in a
House that he doesn't own that kind of makes him like a vampire, right?
I think he can't come in your house without special permission. There's this zombie apocalypse. They're like come in come in
He's like I can't the law doesn't allow it, but he goes in the eyes in a toy factory
He's like you guys wait there. They're like a food supermarket. He's like I'm gonna go to this stuffed animal factory
Woohoo the apocalypse has done me right. I will have to say this though the home and I thought this was very noble of
Kevin he's a home inspector. He's in someone else's home. It's March 12th, 2021 as he's sexually assaulting Tickle me Elmo
He's wearing a mask
He is very courteous of COVID restrictions that it's salute to you Kevin
hats off hats off to you the fact that while you were committing this disgusting crime you continued to wear a mask
He should be an example for us for us all
So there we go. We got two
Creepy stories from these weirdos legend weirdos that we ran into this courthouse
But I said there was a trio of stories and we're looking around. I'm looking at you. I'm checking
Have you been delmo recently? You have no fur on your crotch good to go then we realized the grossest story has been here all along
Deputy US Marshal David Timothy moon has been lurking behind us the whole time. He wasn't lurking. We knew he was there
He was eating a ham sandwich. He's like hey, I'm still here May 2019
David Timothy moon
50 year old man
24 year veteran of
The US Marshals this guy had a long career. He actually didn't even answer to the local
Deputy Marshals in Phoenix, Arizona, which is where this story takes place. He his bosses were in DC
This guy was a highfalutin dude
But even highfalutin US Marshals gotta buy houses
They have places to live. They don't live in yurts. They have to live in a home
So when US Marshal David Timothy moon
Was house hunting? He's like oh this place looks great. The neighborhood looks awesome. I read that thing about home inspectors
They're supposed to have four walls and a roof looks good to me
He's walking around this house and at one point the real estate agent goes into another room and that is when David
Timothy moon makes a decision
He realizes that one of the rooms in this house that he's looking at buying is a three-year-old girls bedroom
Now the girl's gone. The girl is absent. Nothing bad happens to the girl and David walks into this empty room
He looks from side to side. He's skulking now. He's skulking through the room
He's crawling on all fours like the grudge girl
he zeroes in on
Something in the corner of the room now I'm gonna say this this room looks like a little kids room
To make this whole thing even more disturbing. There is giant stuffed animals and like Disney characters and stuff Disney characters
There's not like animated characters running around. It's not toon town
But she has all of this stuff
It looks like a little kids room to make this all even creepier
But somehow if you walked into someone's room right now, would you be able to tell what their dirty clothes hamper was?
I couldn't
Vines on the floor my dirty clothes on the floor, but
Apparently he was able to walk into this room. He's probably scoping it out the whole time
He's probably like hey
Can we take another look at this room and the real estate agents like we've been
Ten times already. He's like yeah, but I think I left my watch in there and he's still wearing his watch
He's like he's able to zero in on the dirty clothes hamper of this little girl
He begins and the reason why we know all this stuff
It's because this was also on video. He begins going through the dirty clothes and
he pulls out a
pair of the this I so disgusting
He pulls out a pair of the little girls underwear and goes
He's just sniffing it. He's just in hate
You know how disgusting children are how filthy they are
They're the ones constantly picking their nose and picking their butts and being super gross and never taking baths and stuff
I didn't man. It was a struggle to get me to take a bath. I was 12 years old
I hated taking baths and showers. They're gross dude and this dude is smelling her underwear
And then he throws him back. He leaves the room and then a couple minutes later
He's able to ditch the real estate agent again
Run back into the room get another sniff of these disgusting dirt. It's dirty clothes, bro
It's dirty clothes and he's smelling them and
Then to just make the thing funny
So gross that's so gross. There's an interview ABC 15 when they're interviewing forensic psychologist John
Bellatoro was very interesting quote quote this isn't someone who's unsure and needs to look around and try to figure out
Is this the thing that arouses me? He knows immediately
Unquote just like the guy in the first story. This isn't someone who is driving on the road and he goes
You know what? I think I'm gonna do today for the first time ever. I've just had this thought
I'm gonna kidnap a young boy. This is someone who's thought about this over and over again
This is someone who has fantasized about this and they knew this was what would turn them on
With David Timothy moon. It's not alleged. He actually pled guilty to this crime
We'll get to that in a second, but it's on tape. He's sniffing a little girl's underwear
Like what is going to say that it's back as it's just on tape the whole thing's disgusting
But as an outsider as a non-pervo you look at it and you go why why why any of that?
Did he pick that house because he knew a little girl lived there?
Is that how creepy this is or did he just happen to be in a house and see a little girl's room and go?
I bet you there's a hamper in there like what is the logic behind this?
Outside of just the disgusting part of the fetish. There's so many other pieces now. He said he told the court
It's the biggest mistake he ever made and they believed it. They believed it
It was kind of like a one-time thing. It was just like he happened to I mean who hasn't been house shopping and been like
You know what? I'm missing in life the disgusting smell of used underwear. That's what's been missing in my 50 years of life
He got charged with all this stuff. He pled guilty to
Misdemeanor trespassing his sentence. I mean you can argue over what type of this ought to me
This is reeks of no pun intended this reeks of a sex crime, right?
No one's like this is my path to fortune and fame smelling underwear
The only thing that works is like some sort of fetish
He pleads guilty to misdemeanor trespassing all he gets for this is
Unsupervised probation no one's even keeping an eye on him your hamper right now your hamper may be unsafe
He may be hiding in the shadows right now
Trying to get a whiff of your clothes unsupervised probation and when he completes this program of not being supervised
It's not even a program. It was the same thing he was doing before he got arrested
This can be expunged from his record. No one will ever know he was the panty sniffer of Phoenix, Arizona
And you could go maybe it is maybe it is just a one-time thing
Maybe he was just walking through and he happened to fall and trip into the little girl's room
And then he was getting up he accidentally fell into the hamper and smelled underwear twice maybe
But also according to the police report when he found out the police were looking for him. He threw his computer away
So we're
These three dudes we just had to pay a speeding ticket and now we're sitting with a guy tried kidnapping a little boy
Allegedly a guy who was banging Elmo allegedly in a man who's blood guilty to sniffing little girls underwear technically
I guess he probably pled guilty to entering the room
Anyways
So that is that story I actually
Interactive adventure I questioned that but I was like nobody wants to pick any of those numbers none of those are fun
But I didn't want to package them all in one
Story we pay our speeding ticket we get out of there boogers
Let's hop in that carbonicopter. We're leaving behind all these alleged pervos. We are headed out to the conspiracy theory iceberg
The conspiracy theory iceberg there's a lot of icebergs out there they keep evolving
I actually have appeared on a conspiracy theory iceberg
12 inches sent me a video from parallel pipes. They did a breakdown of the conspiracy theory iceberg
It's one of those videos
That's about an hour long and they just go over everything
That rabbit radio is listed on there and he says it's a really cool podcast and I agree with that
I don't know why I'm listed on the conspiracy theory iceberg. I'm actually down low enough
I'm next to solar plexus clown gliders, but it's dope
I'm actually become meta the man who started reporting on these conspiracy theory icebergs has now become part of the iceberg itself
But but with the conspiracy theory iceberg because there's so many of them some are interesting some aren't some are too mysterious
We'll never know and some are very vague
There is no
conspiracy is
Often found on the lower levels if not the lowest level of the conspiracy theory iceberg and it's something I looked at on and off over the years
But that's an easy get right you could always say all conspiracy theories are fake that this is all some sort of
Mind manipulation or like I've said before a lot of conspiracy theories are fake to distract us from real conspiracy theories
And that's not a new idea a lot of people have said that even before I started saying that I'm not saying I made that up or anything like that
But it's a real easy one and so when I would see that on the conspiracy theory iceberg
I would think oh I could do an episode like that, but
I'm really not saying anything new
But a couple weeks ago I
Got an email from somebody and I think they solved the answer
-
There are no conspiracies
It's very very simple
belief
There are no conspiracy theories and this is it and I'm
Paraphrasing what this person sent me and I'm not gonna reveal this person's name, but this is the theory
Conspiracy theories are used to pass information from one person to another
That information we are not privy to
Conspiracies don't really exist. They're simply coded messages
Now I've talked about that before
With certain stories and I've talked about hitting codes being passed back and forth
But it actually that's just scratching the surface of this one. So for example, let's say I wanted to let's say
I'm a member of an organization because you'd have to be really powerful to do this
We're not talking about low-level theories like monkeys don't exist, but it would explain why theories like monkey don't exist
Doesn't become popular, but birds don't exist do
Birds don't exist as a very very well-known conspiracy theory
We covered it on the show a long time ago Carson was the first person to recommend it to me. Thank you very much Carson
There's flyers in every major city. It's very it's it's a meme
It's fake. It was set up as a parody of conspiracy theories
Why is that one more popular than monkeys don't exist?
Which is which is earnest at the very least that they're both dumb
But one of them people honestly believe it that monkeys do not exist. It's hilarious
Right and it makes more sense. I was talking about this on a live stream the other night
We don't see monkeys in our daily life. You can actually convince someone that monkeys don't exist
It's a lot harder to convince someone that birds don't exist because we interact with birds all of the time
Why is birds don't exist more popular than monkeys don't exist?
Because what's happening is one group of people are trying to spread a message to another group of people
They're using the conspiracy theories as code and we've talked about this before on the podcast
But we're gonna go more in-depth now because conspiracy theories blow up very quickly
They get publicized very quickly the message gets spread very quickly and people are just looking at the surface of it
They're not looking for the code
It's an easy way to spread your message is to actually make it controversial to make it
Shocking look at that Lil Nas X dude
He came out with that song called call me by your name
Montero whatever it is and this video he's like banging Satan and he's like doing a lap dance for Satan
And then he breaks off Satan horns and becomes Satan and
Everyone like this song had like millions of downloads and he was selling those shoes and all stuff
no one would have ever downloaded that song if it was him at a
Concert if it was just video of him singing to his fans exact same song you make it controversial
You're gonna get the message out
Nobody would he would have had the same hundred thousand people who downloaded his last song download this song instead
He has all of these YouTube videos and these political pundits talking about it
It was 100% strategy
100% strategy behind that so if I want to send a message to you
I will craft a conspiracy theory called birds don't exist and you know what the message is
I know what the message is and I also want to take this moment to say a
Good example of this in Dead Rabbit recommends this
I don't want to go into detail about it because it's such a good movie
I don't want to spoil it
Beyond the Silver Lake or under the Silver Lake. I want to recommend that I should know the name of it
I'll put it in the show notes. I think it's under the Silver Lake
It's a movie about this about how conspiracy theories are actually in hidden messages and music and all the stuff that we think is satanic
Illuminati stuff is actually two groups of people communicating with each other two powerful groups of people communicating with each other
It's a brilliant movie. It's a great movie. I recommend checking it out
But for what we're talking about here, let's get back to this core thing
There is no conspiracy theory conspiracy theories are just ways of people to pass messages back and forth. That's still super vague
right
Like it's easy. It'd be easy for me to make that statement and then be like, okay, that's the end of the episode
I got an email from somebody who actually not only can specify what the message is
but he
made good on it
Boogers let's hop back in that carbonicopter. We're leaving behind the conspiracy theory iceberg. We're headed out
To the New York Stock Exchange
Carbonicopter lands in the middle of stock exchange everyone has to stop trading for the day economic disaster
But we're here and the reason why we're here is this is the theory if you take a conspiracy theory
Like the great reset which we talked about yesterday and you strip it of
All of the satanic stuff of all of the Illuminati stuff you boil it down to its essence
its stock tips
when they start talking about ways to
We're gonna invent this microchip and we're gonna put it in your hand and all that stuff when that's the conspiracy theory
invest in biometric technology
when you can find a conspiracy theory and
boil it down to
How the private market would benefit from that?
That tells you who to invest in
Think about it this way monkeys aren't real the conspiracy theory is
NASA is trying to prove that God doesn't exist that evolution is real and monkeys are a part of evolution
So they're faking it. They're faking all of it
Technically, I guess you can you can invest money in NASA birds aren't real is all about how birds are actually spy technology
They're like drones. They're sent out to
Investigate us and they're all fake their robots
You would then when that conspiracy theory started
You would go okay, let's start moving investments towards unmanned aerial vehicles
Let's start putting some of our investments in drone technology and surveillance technology
Who's the hot camera maker right now?
Who's making the best optical cameras for these drones invest in them?
the theory is is that conspiracy theories like birds aren't real was a way for
people to spread stock tips to commit insider trading that they're all fake
When you look at stuff about microchips being implanted
invest in the biometrics when you start looking at stuff about the
Singularity and the singularity is going to take stuff up start investing in companies that are trying to do AI
One organization is looking at the stuff and they know that they're going to have a huge product come out
They see that they're going to have their stock is going to blow up
They know something's going on to alert their fellow conspirators
They craft a conspiracy theory that's based on what they know is going to happen
And it's not that they know that the great reset is going to happen the great reset
The reason why that's more popular than other conspiracy theories in this theory is
It's being pushed because they're trying to get other people to invest in the products that prop up the quote-unquote great reset
It's fake. It doesn't exist
But you will eat bugs is a thing that people are constantly saying when they talk about great reset
The whole thing in this theory the whole thing was set up. So you would start investing in companies that
Grow bugs now you go Jason
Maybe that's the horse leading the cart or the cart leading the horse if the great reset is coming
They're gonna force everyone to eat but I can't believe I'm still talking about the stupid great reset
But the great reset is coming. They're gonna force everyone to eat bugs. Of course you should invest in bugs
But the great reset is something it's so hypothetical. They're not saying it's gonna happen tomorrow
But according to this theory if you invest in bugs now if you invest in bug farms now
You're gonna start making money now. In fact the person who sent me this story
Claims to have made hundreds of thousands of dollars
By simply following the biggest conspiracy theories out there stripping them of the satanic and the Illuminati nonsense
Investing in the core technologies talked about in those conspiracy theories no matter how outlandish the conspiracy theory is
Even if it's something that's not supposed to take place until the future not supposed to take place for a while something like transhumanism
You boil it down to stuff you can invest in this person has claimed to make hundreds of thousands of dollars
This isn't and they were trying to get me to invest in them. I've talked to this person a lot
Way before this we were actually interacting they listened to the show
They're a fan of the show and they approached me one day and said hey
Do you know of any new big conspiracy theories that are coming up and I said no not really and they said well
This is why I'm asking because here's my theory and I've actually taken this theory over the past couple months and made a lot of money
So if you could figure out what the next big conspiracy theories are going to be it can give people tips on how to become rich
Is that the reason and this has been a question that I've talked about a lot on the show why some conspiracy theories are more popular than others
Is it because some conspiracy theories are artificially propped up not because of you know Russian disinformation
Trying to prop up flat earth to make Americans look stupid. That's a popular conspiracy theory out there
Not because it's they're building up these fake conspiracy theories to blind us from the truth the reason why
Trees are mountains or mountains are trees and trees are bushes. However that one was set up or monkeys don't exist because those are
Organic conspiracy theories those are actually thought up by individuals. It's just an interesting piece of this puzzle
Because that is always a question. Why is flat earth more popular than
So many other conspiracy theories. It's dumb. It's observably dumb
YouTube promotes it YouTube lets the algorithm run with this flat earth stuff. Why is someone benefiting from it?
Is it as simple as when you see the flat earth stuff come up?
It was to promote GPS technology when you can boil down these suit
It doesn't work with every conspiracy theory doesn't work with the obscure ones
But when you can boil down these popular conspiracy theories that everyone knows about and find out how the private sector would benefit from
Technologies in that conspiracy theory you can make money apparently
You can make a lot of money
Now again, you could argue if you if people are talking about putting biometrics inside of you and
That's being talked about in the news and you invest in those companies
It's because they plan on putting biometrics inside of you
They've been talking about putting biometrics inside of you since 1992
I've been hearing about the microchips under the skin since 1992 and you could go well
They're doing it in Sweden. They're doing it at this nightclub in Sweden. Da da da da
They have never ever been able to fully implement a microchip under the skin
They've been talking about this almost my entire life
But companies have been making these things and I you may be able to take a look at
When those conspiracy theories started when those conspiracy theories start to dip and they're not as popular and then they peak again in popularity
And look at the profits look at the stock increases of those companies
it's not that people
legitimate stock investors are
Reading godlike productions and they're super scared that everyone's going to get a microchip
It's not that the conspiracy theory makes people worried and they're investing in it or makes them hopeful
And they want everyone to get microchip and they're investing in microchips. It's that the conspiracy theory is false
It's 100% fake and it's a way to tell your friends what you are investing in and what you should invest in
Without ever getting caught for insider trading without it ever being tracked back to you and the conspiracy theory just lives on
It would explain why some conspiracy theories are more popular and longer lasting than others
All these conspiracy theories we investigate and we're trying to solve these mysteries
could be just
Wrapping paper
Around a gift that the rich people are giving each other
We never get to
Until you crack the code and start investing as well
So the next time you see a conspiracy theory pop up and you start to see it gain popularity
And you have a little money to throw around
Maybe you should try this too
Boil it down to its essence. What are the technologies needed to make this conspiracy theory work?
And see if it actually could be insider trading
However the flip side could be that it's not that it actually is
Investors knowing the conspiracy theory is true and they're trying to make as much money as they can
Before the world ends
You could be investing in a microchip company
And making some short-term gains because you thought it was just a code
But when that microchip is being forced into your head against your will and you cry one final teardrop
Before your emotions are completely overwritten
You will remember that your investment helped in the future of mankind
Dead rabbit radio gmail comm is gonna be your email address
You can also do this up at Facebook comm slash dead rabbit radio Twitter is at dead rabbit radio
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great one guys
You
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]