An Oxford professor believes that aliens may be breeding with humans, and the world goes "eh".
And then we take a look at the saga of the charred pants, a story from my past,
blending both the creepy and the criminal, today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
What started off as a normal episode talking about two stories, one,
are there alien hybrids on the planet? The other one, about charred pants,
became a benedryl soaked rant, where I only got to cover the first story,
and then just kind of petered out at the end. Hybrids, aliens, and what I don't like about them,
is what we'll talk about today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter,
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. We got a lot to cover,
and I'm on quite a lot of Benedryl right now. I'm super sleepy, I'm recording it late,
and I still have to edit it. So let's go ahead and get started before I pass out in front of my mic.
Now, the story's been going around that there is a professor, an Oxford professor,
who is claiming that aliens are breeding with humans. And it's one of those stories that,
once you start to look into it, it really isn't as clickbaity as the headlines would read. Shocked,
I know, I know you guys are shocked by that, but this professor has a name that's Dr. Young H.
Cheek, and he's a Korean instructor, not for Oxford itself, but Oxford has like a,
and it's still technically Oxford, but it's a separate, kind of like a satellite school,
I guess, would be a good term for it, for Oxford's Oriental Institute. Now, I was always told that
Oriental was actually a huge racial slur. You never call an Asian person Oriental. I was
corrected of that fact when I was probably like 15, 16, my dad's like, don't say that,
they actually find that very offensive. But so I'm actually, either my dad was wrong and I could use
it, or this place is super racist, I don't know, maybe both. But anyway, so at Oxford's Oriental
Institute, there's this doctor who, and he actually put this theory out before, I think it was like
closer, it was a couple years ago, maybe close to 2012, and it didn't really generate any waves.
And he, so then, but recently he's done another interview, he wrote this book a while back called
Alien Visitations and the End of Humanity. And this was what, this is really what it was saying.
It's again, that hippie-dippy alien nonsense that I absolutely can't stand. We'll get to that in a
second, but there's four alien races. They're small. That's very descriptive, Professor. Thank you for
that. There's tall and bold. I read multiple articles and I'm like, do they mean tall and bold?
Because generally when you describe, if someone goes, so what did the, what did the alien look
like? You're not like, well, he seemed a little cocky. Like, I mean, tall and bold is basically,
you kind of have a crush on him. Oh, he's so dreamy, he's tall, dark and handsome. He's so bold,
he can take charge. Professor, you have to give, how is that going to help me identify whether or
not there's an alien hybrid walking around? All you've been giving me so far is small,
which could be anyone. Gary Coleman, Webster, I'd have forgot that actor's name, any small person,
all the munchkins, or just people who are generally small and not like have some sort of medical
problem. Tall and bold. So that's basically Tony Robbins. The other four, he had, the other,
sorry, the other two he has is, now again, these are four more descriptive. We had small and tall
and bold. Now we have aliens with scales and snake eyes. So did the other two look like normal
humans, just one shorter and one taller and he's kind of bold, like a Laurel and Hardy type of thing?
Because those ones are kind of specific and really all he had to say was reptilian,
because that's what he's describing. Alien, I'm getting these, I'm not paraphrasing.
These phrases were in multiple articles. Aliens with scales and snake eyes, just say
reptilian dude, don't be a contrarian, you're trying to save the human race. Don't confuse us.
I start just running around pushing every small person down. Anyone who's over six feet tall and
has and is like an alpha male, they're getting, they're getting, they're getting alien smashed.
I'm gonna think they're an alien. I'm calling Will Smith. And then insect like aliens. So
that, those last two, if I saw a man in a bar who looked like a larva about to hatch and turn
into a giant bug, I would go, that is an alien hybrid. See, that is a description, insect like
aliens. I can find those and kill them in the real world. Tall and bold is how you describe a cigarette.
Like this, but anyways, so these are his four races that are here now. And he says that actually,
they may be standing right in front of you, but we can't see them because their eyes don't work
that way. So it's kind of like this, he doesn't necessarily say it's a alien from outer space
thing. It could be some sort of interdimensional thing. He says the insect ones rule all of them,
conquered all of them. And, but this is this, so that, okay, fine, whatever. You've created four
classes that if I ever want to do some cheesy role playing game, those are the four classes you get
to choose from. Maybe a human player who's kind of like the baseline and then the insect is better
at like, range the tax and he has the flying ability and then the reptilian dude is just like,
can sit on a rock and control his own body temperature. Short guy can like squeeze through
tight spaces and turn invisible like the halflings from the, and then the tall and bold guy is your
traditional, he'd be an elf actually, dude. Oh my God, these are just the indeed classes. But anyway,
so he has these four classes and you think, okay, that's cool, like whatever. There's aliens walking
around us. What are they planning on doing? And this is where it gets into the lame stuff. He goes,
they're breeding with us and you're like, oh, that's kind of cool, kind of sexy,
banging a fly person. How would you have sex with an insect human? And how would you have babies?
Would there be like a hundred little human babies pop out of a maggot sack? But anyways,
they're here to interbreed. Okay, that's, that's compelling to help us change the environment.
I hate that part of UFOology. I hate it honestly. I hate, there's two parts of UFOology that I
just can't stand. One is the aliens are coming here to help control the environment. I think that
is one of the dumbest things possible. I think if you look, what was that movie called, The Arrival?
Actually had it more, if there's any truth to it, more close to the truth, where the aliens were
purposely making, changing our atmosphere to terraform the planet to match theirs. So all the
pollutants that were going in, it was this huge alien conspiracy, spoiler alert, for a 20 year old
movie with Charlie Sheen, but it was, they were basically working at changing the atmosphere of
the planet to make it more like theirs. That's far more realistic. Why an alien would care if
bottlenose dolphins got soda can rings on their noses? It doesn't make sense. It doesn't make
sense at all. And he tries to say, you know, well, because they live here too and they're
flotpin' in and out of alternate realities, but then just go to an alternate reality where it's not
so grody? Plus, they really should have started 200 years ago because if they have this advanced
technology, they should have said, well, we got here, but we had to suffer through this phase of
pollution. So in the 1800s, they should have said, hey guys, don't do coal. I read this really
interesting Tales from the Crypt, I gotta keep this episode short, but I read this really episode
Tales from the Crypt comic book back in the day. And what it was was that planes of the, like back
in the 1950s, planes kept crashing. And first there's a big plane crashing like 200 people die,
and then there's another plane crashing 100 people die. And the comic story continues, we're
saying that eventually people became too scared to fly because if you got on a plane, the chances
of it mysteriously breaking down was too high. And then only the military flew, but their planes
began crashing into cities. So eventually, and this was worldwide, the world made an agreement,
no more airplanes will do everything by boat. And then 20 years after everyone stopped flying
planes and the technology was an advanced and people weren't trained to be pilots, the aliens
invaded. And that's, they were interfering, they were like shooting down radio waves hidden from
behind the moon or whatever. It was, it was the 1950s comic book, but how they did it was technically
stupid, but the idea was interesting, how they were interfering with little tiny mechanical devices
on our planes, making them crash to make it ripe for their invasion. There'd be no air force for
them to fight. That would make more sense to me than an alien coming out and putting a little like
daisy in a pollution pipe and being like, we're here to bring peace and clean energy. Like that's
so stupid. It doesn't make sense for an alien race to care how sparkling clear our water is,
because technically if they're super advanced, they could bring a ship down, they can put up a
purification system, they can build a desalination plant. It doesn't pass the smell test. And I hear
constantly that aliens care about our environment. It's so stupid. The thing that really bugs me is
the aliens, the spirituality and the aliens, they want to like help us achieve a spiritual thing too.
I think all that's nonsense. We don't even know if aliens exist and we're already assigning motives
to them. And you notice the motives are generally indicative of the person researching them.
So a paranoid nut job believes that the aliens are abducting humans and feeding babies to
reptilians and Antarctica. And then a new age person will be like, but they're here to like raise
our level to the age of Aquarius and they're all in Mount Chaston, they wear these long white robes.
And then this dude and a bunch of environmentalists are like, no, no, they're here to help us change
our environment. This is the true problem our generation is facing. I want to see a hippie
really digging into ufology and they have like all of these beads and necklaces and crystals in
their outmountain chastah and they see a reptilian just tearing apart a dude just like eating his
guts down. He's like, this is why we're really here. And then he has to change his whole world of you.
But they don't because really I think at the end they're just selling books. This dude knows
that this hippie message of aliens are beneficial to our environment will sell with a particular group
of people, people who are Oxford educated, college educated. While the other guy who writes the book
about the reptilians, that was an episode we did a long time ago, reptilians stealing people from Idaho
and raping and eating them in Antarctica. He knows his audience of people who are going to read that
book, i.e. people who get all their information from the internet. So they're never going to cross
over. I absolutely there may be alien hybrids, I don't know. There may be tall bold people who
are actually aliens, I don't know. But until we actually confi- what's interesting is no one ever
really assigns motives to anything else. No one says Bigfoot does X because of Y. Sometimes you'll
talk about him being like close to nature or something like that. Which is kind of an old
brainer because he lives in the woods, of course. But with most other things, like popular things,
they're not really assigned motives. People don't assign motives to every ghost. I guess they assign
motives to demons, but I just can't, I can't grab my head around how you go from there's unidentified
flying objects in the sky. Therefore we need to start recycling our plastic bottles more or the
aliens are going to be upset. I don't understand that leap of logic. I have an easier time understanding
there's unidentified flying objects in the sky. People go missing, ergo the aliens are taking
the people. I get that line of logic because we do have people missing all over the planet all the
time. We don't find them unfortunately. It is most likely, most likely with the little asterisks
I'm not for sure, but it's most likely natural causes are serial killings or people just getting
lost in their bones or somewhere in the woods, which is technically a natural cause. But you know
what I mean? Like I can see if there's UFO sightings in a particular area and then there are cows dying
of heart attacks, but you think that they got mutilated by laser beams, whatever. That makes
more sense. There's, I don't can't think of a time I've ever read a story there was UFO sighting
in the area and then the next day in Flint, Michigan you could drink the water coming out of the tap.
So I don't understand how they go from bright lights in the sky all the way to smoky the bear
is an alien. Like environment, they're pro environmental. I don't get that. The spiritual
thing I can kind of get because you can say, well this is what the old people saw when they
look up and they saw angels and stuff like that. But even that it's super bizarre and you know what
I mean like whenever I, when I read this I basically groaned out loud when I got to the
part about environmentalism. Humans barely care about the environment. Why would people who aren't
from here care about this environment? If you go to Mexico, you're most assuming you're not
Mexico, if you go to Mexico, I'm sure you're probably more likely to litter than you are to
litter in your hometown. If you're from Mexico and you come to Hood River, I'm sure you're more
likely to litter in Hood River than you are in your hometown. You don't go to another country
and tell them to start recycling. Otherwise they're, well I guess some people do. I guess
environmentalists do but oh dude I just realized something. What if all the aliens
are like the same race and some of them are just like hardcore environmentalists so they're like
that's their thing and then other ones are like complete psychopaths and that's their thing.
Because think about it, if you put, if all of a sudden we started sending masses of people across
the planet, let's look at it this way. When we loaded up the ships, let's say so, you have the
Spanish Gallians, you know what I think so funny? Portugal used to be an empire. I don't know why
I find that funny but I always chuckle to myself when I'm reading something about history and they
mentioned Portugal. It just, just kind of, kind of fell off the map. So bizarre. I was reading
something the other day and it said when Spain and Portugal were vying for control, I just,
I just kind of chuckled and I'm like poor Portugal. Aw. I mean who remembers them? There's like two
countries who speak Portuguese and Portugal's one of them. Poor guys. But anyways, so I'm sure
they'll get back on top eventually right? So anyways, so when these empires were sending out
their ships they would have loaded them full of tradesmen. No they wouldn't. They loaded them full
of soldiers and missionaries and priests. And so depending on who you met first, really was how
you assumed that that civilization was. If you happen to meet a conquistador, you're going to
be like oh my god these dudes are super militant. They have awesome armor and they might be a god
but they're pointing that giant hollow tube at me. But if you met a priest first, you'd be like oh,
this guy is dressed in like brown robes and he has a little shave circle on his head because I
assume they all look like Fryer Tuck. And there's a fox and a bear dancing next to him and he seems
pretty chill. He keeps telling me that I'm worshiping the wrong dude and I'm pretty sure the guy I'm
worshiping is right but this guy's not like putting a metal tube like and shooting bullets or whatever
they're called through my body. And you know there could have been some environmentalists on there
as well. They're out of that group of soldiers and missionaries. There could have been some people
who really like nature and they're like don't step on that butterfly. That butterfly will inspire a
poet a hundred years from now. Don't do it. So maybe that's what it is. Maybe that it isn't that all
the aliens are pro environmentalists or all the aliens are super. I just realized man I think
blew my own brain. Maybe it's not that all the aliens do have a exact goal. Maybe it's the alien
you meet. Maybe it is just this one giant fleet and what their main purpose is we don't know. We
know that the Spaniards their real main purpose to coming over was conquering and setting up outposts
and stealing all the gold and doing all sorts of stuff and then you know convert some people along
the way and maybe steady the culture and steady the sciences and stuff like that. Like pick berries
and send them back to Spain and stuff like that. So wow maybe that's why we get all these different
reasons for why aliens are here. Whether it's military and they're like hurting us or trying to
enlighten us or just trying to make sure we recycle our milk jugs. I still think the environmental
stuff is completely stupid and if I did meet and I said this in an earlier episode if I met an
environmentalist alien I'm beating it up. I don't care. I don't care. I will fight an environmentalist
alien any day. You can put me in a gladiator arena that's made out of recycled water bottles
and I will just mash them one by one by one until they finally take me down which will probably
not happen because they're lame. Send me out one of the war aliens. If I get abducted by an alien
please let it be one who's like going to try to eat me rather than one that's going to like preach
to me. I would rather be anally probed than be strapped down on a table 30,000 miles up in space
being told about my lord and savior Glopgloop. That would I be like you just break out the
anal probe. He's like I am man I'm not into that. That's Nornex over there. That crazy Nornex guy.
You know I'm like dude if you say one more thing about whatever made up guy that I just mentioned
to you I don't remember and the guy's like oh sacrilege. I'm like dude seriously just get the
anal probe let's get it over let's get back on earth and then the anal probe of course is
recycled so that makes it twice as awkward. Dead Rabbit Radio at gmail.com is going to be our
email address you can also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio. Twitter is @jsonocarpenter.
Dead Rabbit Radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't
have to listen to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today. Be careful how much
Ben or Drill you take and have a great weekend guys.
[BLANK_AUDIO]