What happens when a young woman has her heart broken?
Does she get over it or does she combine a religious text and YouTube to create the
ultimate black magic spell?
And then we finish off the week by traveling to Georgia to meet a young man working at
a gas station late one night.
He thinks it's just going to be an easy shift like all the others that have come before.
Instead he's going to have to fight for his life to take on a slime filled woman crawling
out of Georgia's sewer system today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carvin or I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I hope you guys have some fun plans for the week and this is a short week.
We're only doing 4 episodes this week.
The next week we'll be back to our regular schedule.
Someone who always is regular, I'm assuming they don't have any bowel obstructions.
Coming into Dead Rabbit Command right now is one of our newest Patreon supporters.
Everyone on your feet.
Give it up for Boll Weevil.
Wooo!
Everyone give big round of applause.
He's rolling on and in.
Isn't that like a hedgehog or something?
Or it's either that, it's either a hedgehog or some sort of pestilent bug.
Boll, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode.
If you guys can't spread the Patreon, that's fine too.
Just help spread the word about the show that really, really, really helps out a lot.
Talk about it online.
Talk about it to your friends.
Spreading the word of the show helps the show grow.
Boll Weevil, whether you are fuzzy and cute or super disgusting with a thousand legs,
let's go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider.
We're going to glide out of Dead Rabbit Command.
We're flying all the way out to York University.
If you don't know, if you didn't have Google to look that up, we're headed out to Toronto,
Ontario.
We're up in Canada.
That's where York University is at.
And we're walking around campus.
We got on like our little backpacks.
I'm cool so I only have like around one shoulder.
I have searing back pain, but it's okay.
I look flippity flopping it.
We're walking around campus playing a little Frisbee golf, just enjoying the college lifestyle.
And also attending this campus, maybe, this is really, right when I'm one sentence into
the story, this is really where we get into a bunch of bizarre stuff.
Possibly going to this campus a couple years ago was a young woman named Sarah Ali.
Now I got to give a shout out to a user online, it goes by the name of Amdrey.
Amdrey, thank you so much for bringing this to my attention.
I just found out about this yesterday.
This is so weird.
And already, pieces are starting to be removed from the internet.
So now I'm going to put it in this podcast.
Hopefully this episode doesn't get removed.
Let's just get into it.
So Amdrey, though, did a really good job of laying out this mystery.
What happens is there is a YouTube channel that goes by the name Sarah Ali.
And Sarah Ali posted two videos three years ago.
There's only two videos on the channel in this whole time.
One is called Koran, as in the Muslim holy book.
And the other one is called Koran for sleep.
And they both basically are the same thing.
They are a long passage of the Koran.
Specifically, it's a recording of the Surah al-Bakarah, which is the longest verse of
the Koran.
And it's something to fall asleep to.
While I was researching this, they do this for Bible as well.
It's just so you can fall asleep to Bible verses and stuff.
I'm assuming it's some of the good ones, like Proverbs and it's not like.
And David slew all of his enemies.
He killed the babies because they were phyllis thieves.
I don't know if that part's in the sleeping part for the Bible, but it's something to
fall asleep to.
So these videos are both about three to four hours long.
And it's just the recitation.
Now the one that I looked at the most was called Koran.
There's the two Koran for sleep and the one titled Koran.
But they both are the same thing.
They're both something to listen to while you fall asleep.
The one called Koran, it shows still photographs while this voice is reading this.
These passages from the Koran and the photographs of our two well-renowned Muslim clerics.
They have nothing to do with this mystery.
They have nothing to do with this mystery at all.
Imagine you're going to go to sleep at night.
You want to hear the Koran as you're sleeping.
It's going to help put you to sleep.
It's going to put peace in your heart.
It's going to get you ready for the next day.
You hit play and you start listening to it.
And once you know something is up with this video, you pick up on it right away.
But if you are just googling, going to YouTube and you're like, "I just kind of want to listen
to something beautiful as I fall asleep."
So I think that sparks the divine light inside of me.
I'm going to listen to the Koran.
You just hit play and you're probably asleep, you know, in a couple of minutes.
But Sarah Ali has laid a second audio track underneath this recital of the Koran, of the
Sarah Al-Bakra.
Now on the one titled "Koran for Sleep," which had 6.5 million views until it was removed
just yesterday.
In three years it racked up 6.5 million views.
And in the video known as Koran, which has a lot less views, it only had about 200,000
views.
That one's still up right now.
200,000 views.
And if you look at the YouTube comments, people are warning each other.
Don't listen to this video.
There's something wrong with this video.
And the reason why this one got less plays, and the reason why people are calling this
out, is because in the video known as the Koran, which again is like three to four hours long,
the audio of the recital of the Sarah Al-Bakra drops out for a moment.
And we clearly hear the reason why Sarah Ali posted these videos.
This is insane.
These video are up for years.
Koran for sleep played 6.5 million times.
And you can hear the background check, but you don't hear it drop out as drastically.
Let me play for you what Sarah Ali, that might just be a pseudonym, right?
But let me play for you right now what people heard when that audio, and this is like three
hours into the video.
This is quite a ways in.
Here we go.
My mind is blocking any unnecessary fears.
Let me read it to you if you weren't able to catch that.
I'll read you some of it.
First off it starts by going, "My mind is blocking any unnecessary fears.
My mind is releasing any unnecessary fears."
That's great, right?
You shouldn't have unnecessary fears.
Maybe this was my first thing when I heard this.
My first thing when I heard this was that it's actually quite disturbing.
But afterwards I go, "Okay, let's be skeptical."
Maybe she made these videos for herself, intended them to just be on a private channel, something
to help her sleep, something to help her get over some things.
Because earlier in the video around an hour into it we hear a voice say, "I can swallow
pills easily.
I can swallow pills like anybody.
I overcome my fear from swallowing pills.
I can swallow pills easily.
I can swallow pills like anybody.
I overcome my fear from swallowing pills.
I can swallow pills easily.
I can swallow pills like anybody.
I overcome my fear from swallowing pills.
I can swallow pills easily.
I can swallow pills like anybody.
I overcome my fear from swallowing pills.
I can swallow pills easily.
I can swallow pills like anybody.
I overcome my fear from swallowing pills.
I can swallow pills easily."
And that says, "I can swallow pills easily.
I can swallow pills like anybody."
Or yeah.
And I overcome my fear from swallowing pills.
So it sounds like maybe she's trying to do some introspection, right?
It might be that she's trying to self hypnotize or law of attraction this.
And she takes the Quran which she finds solace in and she puts this underneath.
But let's listen to the rest of this track, the one that's really disturbing people.
So again, I cut it off after she says my mind is blocking any unnecessary fears.
Listen to this now.
My mind is blocking any unnecessary fears.
My mind is releasing any unnecessary fears.
Owen Brown gets dumped and ghosted by any woman he is talking to.
Owen Brown gets dumped and ghosted by any woman he is dating.
The relationship between Owen Brown and any woman he is talking to get destroyed.
The relationship between Owen Brown and any woman he is dating gets destroyed.
I seek refuge with Allah from the accursed Satan.
In the name of Allah, the Gracious, the Merciful.
Praise be to Allah, Lord of the worlds.
It's a spell.
Right?
I mean, law of attraction is one of those things that does kind of stand in between
the world of magic and science.
But you know, there's always that big thing about law of attraction.
It's attraction, right?
You're trying to bring stuff to you.
This is definitely going after somebody named Owen Brown.
Owen Brown gets dumped and ghosted by any woman he is talking to.
Owen Brown gets dumped and ghosted by any woman he is dating.
The relationship between--it goes on and on.
And remember, we only know this is what she says here.
Because this is what we can hear clearly.
The rest of the video--it's three to four hours long.
There's two different videos.
One's four hours long, one's three hours long.
What in the world is she saying the rest of the time?
We do have a clip.
I can actually tell you one of the things she says in this video.
And this is why people have kind of started to piece things together.
She says, "This is four hours and seven minutes into the video, Quran."
Oh, I'm not going to play it again.
Owen Brown is spending the rest of his life with me.
Owen Brown is coming back to York University for me.
Owen Brown, listen to every word I say to him.
Owen Brown, listen to every order I give to him.
And people have started talking about this online.
This really blew up recently on this Reddit thread that Omdri posted.
Apparently, there was a woman by the name of Sarah Ali who was attending York University
three years ago.
I haven't been able to verify that.
People have been like posting LinkedIn's and stuff like that, but I think someone said
they got it wrong and they were trying to find another one.
I can't verify that as a fact.
But based on--as she's saying, Owen Brown is coming back to York University for me, whether
or not--I'm not going to include links to the LinkedIn stuff because I'm not down with
that type of stuff.
But by her own admission, she's saying that she's at York University.
This is the stuff we can hear.
So you could say--I think I could see a benefit to somebody who takes a religious text.
They find a lot of peace and fall into sleep to it.
I can also see someone taking a religious--this might be a little more sagacious, but it's
your personal communication, your personal link with God to taking a religious text that
you find solace in and combining it with something like the law of attraction.
You know, I could see that.
But this is--there's no other way to think of this other than some sort of black magic
spell.
She's not--it's not that she's just asking Owen Brown to come back.
She wants every relationship he's in not to work.
So you have that.
You have someone spending four hours minimum, right, just getting the file together, casting
this spell, and then--remember, these are the portions we can hear on the video that
was only heard 115,000 times.
On the video for Quran for Sleep, you can hear a female automated voice playing underneath
it.
You just can't tell what she's saying.
There's no--as far as I could tell, because now the video is gone.
I think someone's trying to get the video back up.
It may be back up by the time this is up, because someone saved it.
But I saved the audio.
That's how I got this stuff for the video called the Quran.
But unless there's that dramatic drop-off, you can't really tell what it's saying.
Imagine cast--this is fascinating.
It's super sacrilegious, right?
It's super sacrilegious.
So we'll set that--that's obviously not what these holy texts were intended for.
But on a--on a--on a parapsychological level, Sarah Ali, or this person going by that name,
crafted a spell that was played minimum 6.5 million times for hours and hours and hours.
And really, with Law of Attraction, one of the most--really, people would argue, the
most important time for Law of Attraction is the moment before sleep.
That is when the subconscious is the most ready to accept your impressions upon it.
And that's what this does, but it not just does it to her.
She's not just sneaking it in for Owen Brown, 6.5 million plays of people listening to this
right before they fall to sleep.
And really, 4 hours into their sleep, maybe with the headphones on, this voice talking,
this voice cursing, Owen Brown.
I think it's a very--has a very, very, very low likelihood of an ARG.
That's one of the things that I think you have to be aware of when you're a paranormal,
investigator paranormal, podcaster, YouTuber, whatever label you want to use.
ARGs, while they are fun, are not good things to cover because they're just kind of--the
ending's kind of like, "Oh, and a bunch of people made it up."
I don't like--ARGs are very, very fun.
I'm not knocking ARGs, but I don't cover them personally.
I don't cover them.
But there are people who do, and they get a lot of fun, and they have a lot of fun with
them.
But I don't think--I don't think the average ARG would take a holy text and wrap clues in
it like that.
So, I kind of--I did think that it could have been an ARG when I first saw the post,
and once I started looking into it and watching the videos for myself and taking--taking a
fall asleep, I'm like, "I'll test this.
Owen Brown, here comes another horrible relationship for you."
As I started looking at it, I go, "It's most likely not an ARG."
I think either she made it for herself, and she didn't realize that you could private
a video, and she made it for herself to listen to, which still makes it a black magic spell,
right?
A lot of attraction is to bring stuff to you.
Once you start cursing other people, then it's a curse, right?
But then you have to realize that Sarah Ali has 34,000 subscribers.
So while she could have uploaded the videos for herself three years ago and not knowing
that there was a private function to watch the video privately, I'm not--she would know
that she had 34,000 subscribers.
She would start to see the comments come through.
She would start to be notified, "Hey, you reached this many, so that's more subscribers than
Dead Rapper Radio's YouTube channel has."
And I'm constantly getting little notifications and stuff like that when I hit these benchmarks.
So if you--and if you are subscribing on YouTube, I appreciate it.
But if you're not, that's fine too.
Most of the listeners are podcast listeners.
But so I think--I thought maybe she meant for it to be private, but at this point she
would know she should know that it's no longer private.
So what it seems like is a spell that she meant to get out there, a spell that she was hoping
millions of people would listen to and millions of people would play and millions of people
would put that message out there and really hear that message in their sleep when we're
the most vulnerable when they hear that sleep.
The pill-popping thing--you know, and I was a little cautious about the pill-popping thing
because on the one hand she might have a hard time swallowing pills.
I was not able to swallow pills until I started doing drugs in college, which my drug of choice
because I was college student, I was doing a bunch of stuff, is this stuff called Minithins.
It was pure ephedra.
I could never grow enough, I could never take a Tylenol or an ibuprofen or nothing like
that, but you got me a pack of Minithins from the gas station.
I was working at the newspaper all night long.
They stopped selling them over the counter because people easily turned them into meth.
You can no longer buy Minithins or at least the ones we took.
It was just taking pure ephedra.
But until I was in my 20s, I couldn't swallow pills.
I go to the doctor and they would have to give me medical medicine in a unicorn shaped
bottle because I couldn't actually take any pills.
Painkillers either.
But yeah, so I could see someone wanting to--because it sucks, right?
It's super embarrassing and medicine can be way more efficiently delivered in a pill form.
But yeah, I could see you're trying to get over the pill.
But what if someone's trying to be like, "Oh dude, I have this pill addiction.
I need to stop taking pills.
You know what?
I'm going to work on that.
That'll be something I work on."
But while I'm working on that, while I'm awake, while I'm asleep, I'm going to listen to this
video and it says I can swallow pills easily.
I overcame my fear from swallowing pills.
So this is one of the problems with magic, right?
Is it getting out there and getting loose?
It's always been a thing when you talk about doing rituals, whether it's some goofy made
up one like one man hiding go seek or it's something real where you're trying to bend
the laws of reality by having a repeating verse go on and having a belief system go
on in your head while you're sleeping.
Owen Brown is going to have horrible relationships.
Owen Brown is going to have horrible relationship.
And then you play at 6.5 million times to a minimum of 34,000 people.
Even if she was the only one listening to it for most of the time.
She has 34,000 subscribers.
It's insane.
You have to be careful of the rituals getting loose.
The one man hiding go seek you're supposed to do in your house because if you take a
doll and you get some dumb creepypasta, basically you walk up to, you put your fingernails in
the doll or fingernail clippings, put down those pliers guys.
You don't need to pull off your whole fingernails.
Put fingernail clippings on, I think a drop of blood in a teddy bear and you sew it up
and you put it in your bathtub and then you find it.
This is gone from talking about the Koran to a Japanese creepypasta, but you go into
your bathroom and you touch the bear and go, you're it and then you have to hide in your
house and the teddy bear follows you around.
It doesn't work.
It doesn't work, right?
And so I'm super scared.
I was like, oh no, I forgot I was playing one man hide and go seek.
I thought I had to do this episode as this little doll is trying to get out of the bathroom.
You're not supposed to do it outdoors because apparently then the doll will just ravage the
city.
You'll never see a doll walking down the dark cities of Detroit one night.
Somebody didn't follow the rules.
That doll is looking for some vengeance.
But yeah, or this, right?
You have to be careful of the rituals you put out there because if she did not intend
this to blow up, if she did not intend this to be repeated 6.5 million times, she failed
miserably at that.
And it has been played that many times and who in the world is Owen Brown?
I mean, for all we know, this guy, for all we know it's you.
Owen Brown's listening to the spot guys right now.
York University diploma on the wall and he can't realize why none of his relationships
work.
Well, it could be because a woman that you had a bad breakup with or you turned down
on a date or whatever convinced millions of people to play a spell against you while
they were sleeping.
And this is insane.
This is crazy.
So what I'll say, let me wrap it up like this.
I said one of the videos was already taken down.
What happened apparently was the video Koran for sleep got copyright strike by a group
out of the United Kingdom.
So and Omdri has been really good at updating the Reddit about what's going on.
They did a copyright strike against it.
So that one's taken down, but the other one Koran with the obvious audio drops so you
can clearly hear what's saying.
That one's still up.
It's just a unintelligible audio track.
And in the world of magic and the world of curses and black magic, even an unintelligible
noise underneath something else.
So that's good enough because you're getting the thoughts into the subconscious of someone
listening to it while they're sleeping.
Absolutely fascinating story.
We'll see what happens.
These videos have become so popular in the past 24 to 48 hours.
I'll be surprised if anyone can get rid of them now.
I've already saved a couple copies.
As now the FBI is going to come after me.
I've saved a couple copies of Koran, that video just for research purposes.
And I'm not going to re-upload the video itself, but we do have the video here.
Just fascinating.
Who knows?
Maybe Owen Brown will come forward.
Maybe Sarah Lee will come forward.
We don't know.
But if there are any major developments, we will circle back around.
Because I've never seen black magic.
I've seen people try to...
Remember there was that weird thing.
What was it?
TikTok versus Trump or Twitter versus Twitter, witches versus Trump or whatever it was.
We've seen stuff like that.
I've never seen something on this scale.
I've never come across something that's been able to hide for so long and be played so
much.
And it wasn't some viral moment.
This was created by someone and did it serve its purpose?
Did Owen Brown never have another happy relationship?
Dude, what if Owen Brown right now, he is listening to this York University diploma on the wall
and he's married to Sarah Lee.
And he's hearing this.
Owen Brown, if that is you and you can verify your identity, hit me up.
We would love to interview you and your wife, Sarah.
But hopefully you are doing well, sir.
Bull, Weevill, let's go ahead and touch the keys of the carbonicopter.
We are leaving behind York University.
I really do feel bad for this dude.
That's rough.
And you're just like, why are none of my relationships working?
Well as we're waving goodbye to a young man, just kind of having his hands in his pocket,
walking around the grounds of York University all sad.
We got a slimy story to cover.
So let's leave.
Let's help Owen Brown get on the copter.
We're going to hop in the carbonicopter.
Bull, Weevill, take us out of here.
We're going to cheer this young man up as we fly all the way out to Georgia.
[HUMMING]
Recently on the export, we talked about this earlier in the week, but there was a thread
about Georgia spooky stories.
Weird stuff that happened in the state of Georgia.
We covered one, what was it, two episodes ago about the car in the clearing.
Really liked that one.
Very, very good.
We also talked briefly about the guy who was just making up stories, pretending he was
ex files meets supernatural meets wasting my time man.
As I'm trying to do research for our podcast, as he regaled us with the stories of a wasp
with a slug body, haunted pirate swords.
It was just too good to be true.
Too good to be true.
But anyways, I was able to find another really cool story to wrap up our Georgia week.
That was the theme this week.
You didn't know?
Georgia week.
This story comes from a young man.
We're going to call him Brent.
That's your real name is just the guess.
I am not psychic.
Brent works at a gas station somewhere in Georgia.
[MAKING NOISES]
He actually works the overnight shift.
So three cars drove by that one after another.
It'd probably be one of his busiest nights.
He worked the overnight shift at this gas station.
He says, you know, for the most part, totally chill job.
A lot of truckers would come through.
And the way it was set up was just for safety, right?
We're in the middle of Georgia.
The front door was locked.
And he goes, what I would do is when a trucker would come up, I'd put down my phone.
I was mostly on my phone all the time.
I'd go, I'd open the door, let the trucker in, and he'd pay for the gas or he'd buy his
munchies, whatever he needs.
And sometimes I would help him do stuff.
Sometimes I'd help him do stuff.
Just those two bodies.
He's like, I got these oil drums with a family of four in them.
Here's 20 bucks.
No, he did not implicate himself in any crimes.
He was pretty chill.
He was either on his phone or briefly talking to a cross-country trucker driving through
the area.
But one night, he's on his phone.
Yeah, high score.
And then he looks outside.
Apparently his phone is from the 1980s.
It has Gallagher on it.
He turns and he looks outside and he sees this old woman digging through the trash cans.
Now these are the trash cans.
So let me give you a layout of American gas stations if you don't know.
You have the trash cans right next to the door, like the front door of the gas station.
But then generally where you have the gas pumps, there's also trash there as well.
So where she is at, she's not at like the front of the gas station.
This is actually important.
We do have to give this distance here.
She's by the pumps where those garbage cans are.
And she's kind of riffling through the garbage.
Now Brent goes, listen, that's not new, right?
We see a lot of people come through this area.
It's not super out of the way, right?
It's not next to the Okifanoki swamp.
There's no ghost pirates walking around with their made up swords.
He goes, you do get people coming through the area, homeless people, and they'll dig
through the trash looking for cigarette butts.
And trying to get one or two last puffs off of that camel cigarette that some wayward
traveler wasted.
He's like, what?
You wasted this.
Ah, delicious goodness.
This is all covered in motor oil.
He explodes.
Ah, it was worth it.
People would go through the trash cans looking for their nicotine fix.
So he has the perfect fix for this, right?
He doesn't want this person here.
He doesn't want this person going through the garbage can.
Last week, a guy lit a cigarette covered in oil, almost blooped the entire gas station.
So the gas pump's here, and a lot of it, again, this is something that's pretty common in
American gas stations.
They have an intercom system.
So the driver of the vehicle and the gas station attendant can talk to each other without
actually having to meet each other.
Because heaven forbid, we actually have conversations of any meaning with our neighbors.
Brent hits the intercom button.
Hey, go away.
Get out of here.
I don't know if he sounded like Beavis and Thor Butthead, but he told the lady to scram.
Just get lost, right?
I don't want you to go rifling through my trash, making a big old mess.
And the intercom goes off, and the woman looks up, and she hears the intercom, right?
But she looks at the gas station.
And it's probably separated by maybe, like, what would they normally be like?
Maybe 15, 20 feet, and it's not that big.
She looks at the gas station.
Now it's one of those mini-mart-type things with the big, giant windows.
And Brent can see out of the gas station, but because of the huge decals for, like, energy
drinks and slurpees or whatever it is, she can't see in.
He can see her kind of looking around, trying to get a good view of him, or whoever said
that, right?
She just got her scram.
She thinks it might be the great Cornholio.
He's looking at her, and she begins to walk towards the gas station.
And basically, she's headed right to the front door.
Now as she is moving towards him, he's able to kind of figure out more of what's going
on, because even though he can see out through the decals, it's still hard to see full detail
when there's a giant slurpee in front of you.
And she was far away.
She was obscured by the gas pumps as well.
As she's getting closer to the store, he realizes she's holding something metal.
Doesn't know what it is.
It doesn't even really venture a guess.
But, but late at night, anyone, anyone who's strange with any metal in their hands, right?
Not good.
Unless the leprechaun's there to give you some coins.
Most likely it's a weapon of some sort, whether it be a crowbar, a knife, or a handgun.
You don't want to have any part of it.
Luckily, you know, the doors are locked.
He knows that she's not going to be able to get in.
So she's walking towards her front door.
I don't know if he was taunting her at this point.
He's like, "Ha ha ha!
Try it!
Try to use that metal against my glass!"
As she's walking towards the door, he knows that she can't get in.
And she realizes that quickly as well.
She tries pulling the doors open, and they won't open.
They're locked.
Then she begins banging on the glass.
She's banging on the glass with her hands, or plexiglass most likely.
And she begins shouting at him in Spanish, but he says some of the curse words were in
English.
So, it was mostly Spanish, but every so often there was an F word or a B word or whatever
thrown in it.
He has the upper ground, right?
He's inside a locked building.
He has phones.
He has technology.
He has unlimited slurpees.
Nothing can stop him.
He tells her, "Hey, get lost!
Get out of here!
Get out of here!"
Or, "I'm calling the cops."
And when he makes that threat, she punches the glass door.
But she's not the Hulk.
She punches the glass door.
It just goes, "Wah!"
Does that vibrate when you punch something that's a little too strong for you to actually
penetrate?
And then she runs off.
She leaves the scene in quite a hurry.
The faster you would think that a homeless woman carrying a metal something could run
away.
Now, Brent is actually pretty smart.
He's smarter than I would.
Because he waited an hour.
He waited a full hour to make sure she had left.
I probably would have went out right away.
I probably would have been like, "Those are my cigarette butts.
How dare she try to steal this from me and I'm all smoking them."
I probably would have went out and checked earlier because I'm kind of dumb when it comes
to stuff like this, right?
He waits an hour and his motivation isn't to go steal cigarette butts.
He wants to see if she damaged the door.
When she punched it really hard, he wants to see if she scratched it or anything like
that.
And he goes out and he opens the door and the first thing he notices is all over the
ground right in front of the door is green slime.
He says that this slime looked like, he gives us a pretty vivid description.
If you're eating green jello right now, stop.
He says that it looked like if someone was eating green jello and begin to vomit it all
over the ground.
So there's probably like chunks, chunks of green jello.
There's also probably like a smear.
This episode brought to you by Crafter who ever mixes stuff.
He's probably like a smear of it too.
I imagine it to be like thick and sticky but also you can see through it and there's just
kind of like chunks of wobbly green things kind of poking out of this ooze.
He says that's what it looked like.
He goes, it looks like someone threw up green jello all over the place.
And that's bad, right?
That's not good.
But also it's not just on the ground.
It's all over the door as well.
It's all over the handle.
And he's saying that's weird.
Now maybe I figured, maybe I figured she had green jello when it was falling out of her
jacket or something like that.
But I don't remember when she was banging on the door.
I don't remember seeing green jello like it flung all over the place.
And while he's looking at this disgusting mixture of fluids and solids, what he's really
worried about, he's really worried about how it came to be, the smell.
The smell is, what's the, what's the, what is the, if something loud is deafening,
for your hearing, it's that but nose related.
I'm sure there's a word for it.
Overpowering is probably the word for it.
His nostrils immediately are engulfed with the smell of rotting animal flesh and burnt
rubber.
A smell that is so natural and a smell that is so of the modern world colliding together.
So he figures, I'm gonna have to clean this up later.
Like I'm gonna have to get like some gloves and a hasmetsuit and a new job and just quit
this one.
Because I'm gonna have to clean this up later because this is super disgusting and super
smelly.
I'm not ready to do this yet.
So he goes back into the gas station, locks the door.
And a short time later, like a couple minutes later, a car pulls up.
He's like, great, man.
Now I'm gonna have to explain what this smell is and why I didn't clean it up and all this
stuff.
And the customer is walking up to the front door and Brent opens the door to let him in.
And as the dude's walking inside, Brent goes, hey, listen, I know, I'm so sorry about that.
So sorry about that mess out there.
I'm just super gross, but I'll get it in a second.
And he says the customer looked at me like I was the biggest idiot in the world.
Like he, the customer was like, he didn't say this, but he got the impression the customer
is thinking, what mess?
What are you talking about?
The customer goes about his business and his Brent is taking him back out of the store
because he has to lock the front door again, opens the door up.
The slime is gone.
It's all gone.
The next day, Brent brings us up to his manager.
The next day he goes, hey man, you won't believe what happened.
This woman came, crazy homeless lady.
I'm sure that part you believe that happens all the time, but crazy homeless lady came,
told her to get lost.
She's bang on the door and then all of a sudden she left this green slime everywhere.
It's super stinky.
It's kind of freaked me out because it just disappeared at a certain point.
And he says the manager looked him dead in the eyes and said, quote, next time you should
mind your own business.
To which I Brent doesn't say what his reply was, but technically it was his business.
He was literally in a business, but he kind of just let it drop.
He didn't understand why his manager had their reaction.
Brent says to wrap the story up, one day he mentioned this story to a friend of his.
This is a story you would want to tell people because it's just so weird.
The friend who actually works for the city, we don't know what city this is, but Brent
says in the city they're at, his friend goes, you want to know what's weird.
Like, yeah, that's weird, but I have a story.
I'm a one upper.
I have a story we're doing.
We so often hear from people working in the municipal district and the sewage workers
and stuff like that.
He goes, they'll be down there.
And this happens all the time.
The walls will be coated with green slime.
Something down there is oozing its way around the city.
To wrap all of this up, Brent says to this day, when he shows up to work, when he walks
up to that front door, to this day he can still smell the slime.
We don't get enough of these.
I love urban legends, but I love when the urban world collides with the supernatural.
It's really cool.
And it's an underrated, I'm sure it happens way more often.
We've covered homeless shapeshifters and we covered that predator, that giant who was
in the subway system hunting humans.
I'll try to find those episodes for the show notes.
The older episodes, sometimes those little stories are hard to find, but it's the perfect
hunting ground for a cryptid, the cities, because people go missing all the time.
Chicago has a really big problem.
They have a really big problem with a lot of stuff, but one of the problems cryptid-related
is there is a winged creature stalking Chicago.
It's been sighted so many times.
This Batman of Chicago.
I would move to Chicago if Batman was there.
But I've become a criminal.
But there's some sort of gargoyle-esque winged creature flying around Chicago.
There's been sightings of it for years.
It's not like some old, old legend.
I mean, like years as in the past 10 years.
So I love the idea.
And when you have a gas station, those also live in those weird spaces in between the
urban and the suburban.
Gas stations always seem to be, even when the gas station in a city, it seems to almost
have its own atmosphere.
Little gas stations, little mini-marts seem to have their own ecosystem.
And when you have this cryptid or whatever this was, I think more of cryptid.
Originally I was thinking it could be some sort of demon, some sort of cursed spirit
or cursed person.
But the fact that it's leaving residue in the sewer system starts to give it a feeling
that it's part of an ecosystem.
Demons don't really recycle their cans, right?
Demons aren't looking for cigarette butts, but someone who was in between a cryptid and
a human, they're not worried about finding the eternal battle for their soul.
They're a cryptid.
The cryptids, I think, do exist in some sort of biological reality versus a ghost or an
alien.
Aliens, but they're from the final.
You know what I mean?
My point is that I think that's what I would classify this story.
If this story is true, right?
This story could be totally made up.
But if this story is true, that's what I would classify it as, as a cryptid, that again is
savvy enough to disguise itself as someone who for the most part is ignored.
Homeless people are completely invisible for the most part, unless there's too many of
them, unless the crime rate gets too high, unless they're screaming right in your face.
Other than that, they can exist right next to you and you would never know.
You've learned to just ignore them.
Very, very interesting, very, very interesting story.
But we're going to put a Dead Rabbit radio twist on it to wrap this up.
The problem with cryptids are that they don't procreate.
We hear stories about fairies stealing human babies.
That's how they keep their race going or they drop off their changeling and it's raised
by human people.
But cryptid procreation is not a well-studied thing.
Do chupacabras lay eggs?
What's the infant mortality rate of a unicorn?
These things aren't really well known.
One thing we've talked a lot about Bigfoot is, one of my fascinating theories about Bigfoot
is that you can become a Bigfoot.
We've had stories of people turning into Bigfoot.
I'm going to have to find so many episodes for the show notes for this one.
People turning into Bigfoot and then Bigfoot's wearing remnants of human clothing.
So I've always thought, I don't think Bigfoot's are actually, they have a biological life
cycle.
I think people can turn into Bigfoot.
It's against their will, almost like a werewolf.
So I'm a little concerned for Brent because the fact that he's the only one who saw this
slime and to this day he can smell the slime along with his boss's admonishment, is that
a word?
I'm not going to edit it out, I'm sure it's fine.
To say, you should mind your own business, what if this is the life cycle of this cryptid?
They go about their business but when somebody gets in their way, they slime them.
And now that essence is slowly taking over Brent.
Like he may have not have physically seen the slime enter on him but no one was able
to physically see the slime in that area where she left it.
But he does and to this day he still smells the slime.
It's still part of his reality.
It's actually breaking his reality because he shouldn't smell anything and nobody else
smells anything, just him.
So right now he's smelling the slime but what happens when a year or two from now he begins
to find it leaking?
He's the one who's smelling the slime around his bedroom.
He's like "What?
Why do I feel something cold between my butt cheeks?"
He gets up out of bed, he's a little piece of poop.
That'd be the most startling thing ever.
If you got up out of bed one night and in between your butt cheeks was a giant piece of green
jello oozing out.
I haven't had green jello since I was six and I might not have even eaten it then.
Green stuff is gross but dude, I would have eaten it if it was cold 9-1-1.
I was like dude you gotta give me up to the hospital.
Green jello just came out of my butt and I don't know why.
But he just, he's just like "Ah whatever, I'll deal with it."
Then he's taking a shower.
He's all washing his hair and he doesn't realize that green jello's coming out of
his pores in the back of his head or maybe he doesn't care.
Maybe he's becoming more jello than man at this point.
And then one day he just doesn't show up to work.
And you know the boss goes "Young kid, college kid, whatever."
He's probably off, he's probably off casting spells against somebody.
He'll be back, he'll be back.
Then another weekend comes around and Brent's still not at work and the boss gets more
concerned.
Can't get a hold of him, friends don't know where Brent is.
And then another week passes, missing persons report file.
They probably did that earlier.
But my point is, is that time is passing and people are worried about Brent and he's
never seen again.
But the manager of that gas station that sits on the edge of town, he has a theory, one
that he would never state publicly.
Because this isn't the first time he's had an employee just quit.
Supposedly leave town, never to be seen again.
It's not the first time.
He's had it happen many times before over the years.
There are always young people and police know that young people just leave town, try to
find themselves in another city.
But the manager, he knows better.
Every time before one of his employees goes missing, they say they have a run-in with
somebody oozing out green slime.
The first couple times, manager didn't put two and two together, but Brent is the sixth
guy this has happened to, the ninth.
Who knows, I've lost count.
The manager just tries to forget about it.
Maybe he's wrong.
He has no proof.
Maybe these are young people just dropping out of college and finding themselves by traveling
the country.
Maybe there is no connection to these people that they always say are coming to the gas
station late at night, dripping green slime at the front door.
The manager, he doesn't know for sure.
And he never will.
He'll never look into it.
The manager will be sure that he will never work the night shift.
The manager will be sure he will always find a new employee.
And most of all, the manager will be sure that he just won't ask too many questions.
And he won't offer too many answers.
The manager knows one thing above all.
He knows how to mind his own business.
I'm going to be back.
Thanks for watching.
Bye.
(upbeat music)