What do you get when you mix water and oil? This episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, thanks for tuning back in. I'm Jason Carpenter and this is another episode
of Dead Rabbit Radio. It's Monday, July 9th. I think it's July 9th. Actually, I think it's Monday.
Took a long nap. I came home from play practice. Only got two hours to sleep last night
because my tooth, I'm still having the sinus pain and I couldn't get it. Couldn't get sleep because
the pain had to work, had to go to play practice. I came home. I was going to do the podcast
and then get to sleep and there's a band once again playing at the ice cream shop right next to my
apartment complex and they played for probably about an hour and a half. I just had to take
a nap and if I wake up in time to do the podcast, I will. I'd like to keep my daily podcast schedule
up and of course I woke up at 1030 so now I'm here recording this podcast. So it all worked out,
I guess, in the long run. So here's the thing before we get started on the episode because you know
I'm usually so on top of stuff and I don't ramble but I saw last night I was up. This might help
somebody. Last night I was up with the worst toothache. I've been having tooth problems for a while now
and it's gotten much, much worse since the sinus infection because my gums have swelled up so my
teeth are moving up against each other and all of that. I have a dentist appointment. I doctor them.
They put a filling in and it causes some complications or something like that but anyway so I was online
and I'm looking like what are some remedies that I can use because the pain was just imbearable. I
couldn't sleep. It's like three in the morning and they're like you know rub a clove and lavender
oil across your gums while kissing a salt block and I'm like I don't have any of that stuff and I
would make love to a salt block if I thought it would help and I'd been doing salt rinses
and that kind of helped. I was using the ambasol and that kind of helped and I just don't have,
I'm not a cook so I don't have a lot of stuff here and they're like you know rub
turmeric, make a turmeric paste. I'm like I don't even, I don't even know if I'm pronouncing
turmeric right let alone have any of it. One of the thing I kept seeing pop up was garlic.
Rub garlic on your gums. Rub garlic on your gums. They go it burns but it helps and I'm like well
I have some garlic powder because they make you know I get the pre-frozen hamburger patties because
I'm a bachelor and I don't actually like make food. I'm like the lowest level of bachelor.
I have a lot of friends who are bachelors and they're really really good chefs like they'll come
to work and they're like oh yeah I made this hamburger patty and I put like little chunks of
cheddar in the middle of it and then I put like a single jalapeno that I released its spirit and
and entered the soul of the patty and they make this delicious food and I buy 20 frozen patties
at a time at Walmart just like a box of patties and just throw them on a George Foreman grill
but I you know so that's just a that's just a Jason thing. I've never been that good of a cook.
I microwave my spaghetti for crying out loud. I throw spaghetti noodles in a bowl for 15 minutes
in the microwave. Opened up a can of sauce and poured on there. Very very low maintenance but
anyways so I don't have a lot of stuff but I did have garlic powder and they kept asking for
cloves of garlic cloves of garlic and I'm like you know what I have nothing to lose at this point
it's three in the morning I have to be to work at five so I grabbed some garlic powder and I
put it all over my mouth and it worked it actually worked. It reduced the inflammation enough for me
to be able to get some sleep and so I've been doing that sparingly because I know I you know
make me smell like garlic and then I actually went out and bought a little clove of garlic from
Walmart it was like 18 cents for a clove and I've been doing that too, true in that a bit as well
and it does sting but it definitely reduces inflammation the last maybe an hour and you
can really kind of do it as much as you want as long as you know because you're gonna stink
you're gonna be stinky from it but if you're having a toothache and you're not allergic to
garlic go ahead and give that a shot because you know and I yeah it worked for me. I usually
poo poo homeopathic stuff well there I guess there's no between homeopathic stuff and stuff
like this I'm not gonna buy a jar of essential garlic oil that's one drop of garlic in a bottle
of water but you know chewing up a clove it worked I mean chewing up a clove of I guess there is
something called cloves I guess that's a different plant but then you can have a clove of garlic
so that's kind of weird I don't get that you don't have like a stalk of corn and then a corn of
tomato it does but anyway so yeah try that if your teeth are hurting I saw the most beautiful
woman today ever and again don't want the upset to run late so I'm just gonna make this real quick but
Vanessa that's what I'm gonna call you because you look like a Vanessa if you're out there and
you're still in Hood River and you want to go hunt ghosts hit me up dead rabbit radio at gmail.com
or you can hit me up on Twitter @jasonocarpenter gorgeous gorgeous I was with a couple friends
and we all noticed her right away she's perfect perfect long blonde hair she had that tone to
her skin where you couldn't tell if she was tan or it was ethnic amazing body and and as she passed
me I must she must have heard me say something I think I might have said oh my god like I there was
a I had an initial reaction to her the reason why I think she heard me say something because we
passed each other I was with Veronica actually and another friend of mine who I don't have a fake
name yet for so I can't I don't know what to call him but he knows who he is we walked past Vanessa
Vanessa I must have said something because as we walked past each other I turned around because
I was like I I I'm usually not like a total creep but I gotta see what she looks like from okay I
am kind of creepy but I was like I gotta see what I gotta see the rest of her right so she walks past
me I turn around to check her out and as I'm turning around she's already turning around looking at me
and so I had to like just take in like a brief momentary information like how to get as much
visual information in as I turned back so I didn't she didn't see I was staring at her
but she had to know I must have said something out loud there's not a reason why she would have
turned back around unless she because she was when I turned around she was looking at me
but I don't think it was any sort of like ooh he's hot I think it was like uh is this guy checking
me out but anyways I could be misreading it Vanessa could be madly in love with me she could
be recording her podcast tonight about cooking with garlic and we're separated by miles of darkness
here in Hoodie River just two podcasts broadcasting through the night if you're out there Vanessa
I love you okay so let's go ahead and we will get started on the episode right now
and we're going to talk about two conspiracy theories today now they're not the governmental
type of conspiracy theories where people are trying to take over their science based conspiracy
theories a little bit of paranormal in one of them but both of them have always kind of intrigued me
and one of them I'm pretty sure is real and if it is real it I'm totally like I remember hearing
about it back in the day and I said that's awesome the other one I heard about and thought it was
awesome did some research and it wasn't so much so we'll see if you can figure out which one which
one I like so the first one we're going to talk about it's a conspiracy theory about oil now you
know I was going to college back in the late 90s early 2000s and that was a time where you're
reading a lot about peak oil and that was kind of the big movement at the time there's always one
there's always like one big ecological social disaster movement at a time this is before 2012 but
I think for the intellectuals it was peak oil we're going to run out of oil we're going to run
out of oil someday and you know the end of suburbia we watched that movie in college and I remember
thinking oh no this is really bad like we're running a oil and it could be like this huge
disaster thing and they always kind of pitched it as it's not mad max but it's kind of like mad max
but you know as I got older and I kept looking at stuff and especially when Deepwater Horizon
popped off if we were at a level of peak oil you'd be like oh this is definitely accelerating the
you know now we're real but there's just so there's so much oil under the ground it can get harder to
find and sometimes we need new technology to access it like fracking but the idea of us running out of
oil I don't have a I really don't think it's an issue now I especially don't think it's an issue
because when I was looking into the issue of peak oil and things like that I came across an
interesting conspiracy theory and that is oil is not only plant-based or carbon-based now we are
always taught in school that oil is caused from dead plant matter and dead biological matter but
you know mostly plants being compressed over thousands hundreds of thousands millions of years
and it gets compressed down and basically when it breaks down to its parts it can it forms petroleum
and that's a real kind of dumb down explanation but that's I don't think you're dumb down I'm sure
you guys may have a more succinct way of putting it but that's that's probably the most succinct
way for me to understand it it's basically millions and billions of tons of biological
matter pressed down you got oil over time and pressure makes oil with okay anyways
there's been this theory that's been going around that that's not the only place where it's from
so the theory is called a biogenic petroleum a biogenic petroleum and you you think of it as
in the term asexual where it's like you don't have sexual interest a biogenic petroleum is
petroleum that does not need biological matter to form so how does it form the earth has it
inside of it it's almost like the earth's blood so the theory is is that this theory originally
gained traction in Russia where the scientists were saying it's possible that it doesn't oil is
a natural resource that's intrinsic to all planetary bodies which would mean that the moon has oil
that meteors have oil or asteroids that all the planets that have a rocky form have some form of
oil now the the common understanding was that no oil is biological matter that's compressed over time
so at first people or other scientists there was a lot of pushback from them what has what's happened
is that when they've people have done tests in areas where there weren't they shouldn't be any oil
if it's because of the biogenic thing I remember there was a researcher in Sweden I think it was
in Sweden or Switzerland or one of oh I have a listener in Sweden hey if you're listening to
this one maybe you can help me clear this up too there's one of the Nordic one of the high European
states this researcher was like no there's I will prove there's oil there and he was able to drill
an area that there shouldn't have been oil and it there was a trickily black substance and the
scientists were like haha it's not oil and he's like well it's kind of oil so that's been the
complication sciences had to come back and say that okay guys it is possible that there is some
oil that is a biogenic we just can't access it science can't rule it out completely because tests
have been done to show that it may exist you'll see some article I'm going to post two articles
and as I researched more into it you'll see other articles pop up if you've researched it on your
own and they're like well it's not that that's not true because it's there's not huge deposits of it
so therefore it's not true so and and when you really dig into the the meat of it though science
has to say it's possible it's just the oil that we're pumping out of the ground is definitely
biological matter because we can find biological markers in it but it's also possible that oil
in other parts of the planet are are um a biogenic and then the a biogenic people says
that's all we're asking we're not saying that all oil is from the earth we're saying that some of
it may be there's the argument too that the biological markers in oil we pump up is enzymes
eating the oil so that was that's going to be our first conspiracy is is oil something that is just
is it basically the lubricant for the planet could you drill anywhere deep enough and find
oil reserves that's that'd be the question is all oil plant-based matter or is only some oil
plant-based matter because even the i biogenic the a biogenic people aren't saying no all oil
absolutely every single drop of oil is um this is this so i think that's an interesting conspiracy
theory second conspiracy theory and then i'll go i kind of do a quick rundown of the end here the
second conspiracy theory involves water now water is one of those weird substances that
we don't really understand i mean we we're surrounded by it but we don't understand on
the level of that and we i mean we have a basic understanding of it but it's the only liquid
that it's solid form floats on the top and they'll say you know there's reasons why air pockets and
stuff in the ice but it's still puzzling it's still interesting because every other form if you take a
if you have molten lead and you drop a molten if you drop a solid piece of lead in it just sinks to
the bottom every other um form of liquid if you freeze it or you make it a solid sinks but water
it doesn't you know surface tension blah blah blah but it is something that's puzzling it's
something that we're surrounded by all the time now one japanese doctor doctor masuro masuro
emoto some of you people are probably like oh great he's going on this because he's he's fairly famous
in this field you might be really the only one he's doing this in his field but dr emoto has a
theory that he he feels that he's proven is that water is sentient water is intelligent it's alive
and we can communicate with it now 70 of the world is water and 75 of our bodies are water
that's not actually true i found out that men have more water in them than women or vice versa one of
the two anyways anyways i probably should look that up anyways men and women have different volumes
of water in them that being said dr emoto's theory is that you can take water and you can
communicate with it and if you say beautiful things to it it will form beautiful ice crystals
so if i have a glass of water and i say venessa i love you and i saw you in hood river at rosars
at seven p.m. you're beautiful if i froze that water right when the ice crystals it's this weird
timing he has so the ice crystals form and then he lets them melt and right when they hit zero
degrees i don't know celsius or something yeah i guess it'd be zero degrees celsius he's from japan
right when they the very second they start to melt he takes a picture of them and it'll be this
most beautiful ice crystal in the world now let's say i have water and i go oh my swollen gums you
are the representation of my swollen gums i just want to rub garlic all over this glass
and then do the same thing freeze it and then right when it starts to melt it'll be this ugly
won't be crystallized we'll just be like this ugly doll up and you can do it by saying nice stuff
to it you can say do it by saying mean stuff to it if you play beautiful classical music the crystals
are just intricately formed if you play heavy metal it's just like chaotic it's not from the
vibrations necessarily because you've played the music and they froze it and so he's done all these
experiments thousands tens of thousands of experiments oh he's dead i didn't know that
anyways he's just looking at this he does tens of thousands of experiments on this
and he says you know water ascension how we react to water water reacts to us and the reason why
this is important because not only are we surrounded by water but we're mostly made up of water so the
way that we think about our own bodies and the way we talk to other people influences the way that
their water molecules are forming so it's an interesting theory i remember hearing about that
the first time when i saw that old documentary down the rabbit hole it was the follow-up documentary
to what the bleep do we know the only reason i watch it because i have a crush on marley mattlin
and she was the star of that and armin shimmer man was in that too and he was quark on deep
space nine but anyways anyways in that he they had this theory about water being sentient the way
that she talked to water determines the water molecules so we see it in that brief moment
when it's melting but if i every day drink a have a glass of water and i talk about how beautiful
it is and i drink it i'm basically communicating with the water so again it's an interesting theory
now i think it's interesting i think what you know going back to the whole water being fascinating
thing i think water is is fascinating i go on and on about the depths of the ocean but one of the
things that i've observed is humans relationship with water now as far as we know as far as we know
liquid water is the most rare element in the galaxy we have not been able to really detect
liquid water in i definitely in our solar system we've done those big telescopes and go oh maybe
that planet has some water maybe but liquid water is so rare and we pee in it we poop in it
we fill holes in our backyard with it we spray it on ourselves when we get wet
well obviously we get wet we spray it on ourselves when we get hot
we put it in little bubbles little rubber balloons and throw them at each other it's this
increase it's more when we look at the galactic scale it is more rare than the most precious metals
on this planet and we just treat it like it's completely replenishable it's completely disposable
it's rainy and and it's just everywhere now i know there's countries that have water problems but i
think you get where i'm going with it is that you know it's that's the most rare we talk about gold
we talk about diamonds which you know aren't really that rare but we talk about rare earth
metals that we pull out of africa for cell phones and stuff like that but water when we look at a
galactic scale water is the most rare thing in the galaxy and we treat it as an afterthought
we mix powdered colored powder into it and drink it as kool-aid and it's amazing it's amazing when
we look at it that way so to think that we're on a planet with all this water and not only is it
here to help us but it's actually sentient and we can communicate with it in some way it I think is
amazing on some level so i looked into both of those conspiracies over the years and both of
these conspiracies are on the conspiracy theory list that i like to go through kind of the odder
conspiracy theories the the deeper lesser known ones one of these conspiracy theories is absolute
garbage pseudo science and the other conspiracy theory i think is possible and i'm really excited
by the idea of it let's see if you can imagine which one i'm gonna give you a second i'll put some
little theme music right here okay so we're back i'm sure that you're like oh man which one which
ridiculous theory is jayceen gonna propose is actually proof is actually possible right now
is he gonna talk about water because aliens come from underneath it he's gonna talk about oil
i think the idea of water being sentient is amazing but it's absolutely ridiculous and it
is the height of pseudo science and like i said i watched that documentary and then i was like oh
i'm gonna write his name down and i went and did some research on it now i i'm fairly skeptical on
a lot of this stuff and i think i've kind of said in the past like if you show me something that
proves that it's not true then i'm more likely to believe it that it's not true now when i looked
into this the basically every skeptical article said listen this is the way that it works you take
thousands of foot you yell at some water you talk you call water venessa and you say it's the most
beautiful water in the world you take pictures of thou you take pictures of all these ice crystals
you're going your premises that when you talk about it the ice crystals are more beautiful
so what are you gonna do with all the photos you take where they're not beautiful
will you dismiss those oh i took it at the wrong time oh i'm not gonna assuming he his heart was
in the right place he was looking at and goes ah that was taking the wrong time that was taking
the right time that one's beautiful put that one up that one's beautiful put that one up
it's selective too selective there's no real control and he did start having a glass of water
that he didn't say anything to and he's like well look at these photos they're just natural
crystals but again this actual selection of the photographs and the photographs you're presenting
as proof to us is is the issue if you made access if you said well i took one photo of each and eat
this was each time like i took one photo just one photo of the beautiful glass of water and it was
this crystalline form it laid laid more credence to his theory but people have tried duplicating it
they haven't been able to or they've been able to but they have to take so many photos and
they just cherry pick the beautiful ones i love the idea to think that water is sentient on some
level i do believe that you know positivity and negativity go out into the world but again i could
walk around town and be super positive to everyone and then one person be like thank you jason that
would you gave me like hope that was such a great day and then tell everyone i have i exhibit some
sort of positive energy i can cure people i can cure their bad moods and you're like well yeah
you talk to a thousand people and ten people said that you helped them you know and then 50 people
are like and then you know a bunch of other people just told you to slag off so it's just selective
it's selective information and then of course as i was doing research for this podcast i did realize
that i didn't know that he has passed away now but at the time he was selling like again he was
selling products happy water water that people talk to and said beautiful things to him and you
could buy it for an excessive amount of money and drink it and feel positive and that's just you're
just ripping people off just throughout the theory he has some other theories about rice and i actually
you know people have tried to people have tried duplicating that as well if you're nice to rice
it doesn't spoil or whatever it's pseudoscience it's nonsense the oil thing which again this was
a story that i heard you know maybe 10 15 years ago and found fascinating and again i had to do
some more digging on this and as it stands right now the consensus is is yeah i guess it's possible
it's not what we're pumping out but it's possible and so the scientific community is still more
divided on on this on the oil issue and i think the idea of the planet actually producing a lubricant
like oil is a natural substance that exists on every planet is fascinating is a fascinating
thing it's just another layer to how amazing science works now again it's probably not the
oil that you're putting in your car and even the even the people who are supporters of the
a biogenetic what it was that you know the petroleum that doesn't have plant matter aren't
saying that but i just think it's a made like that just shows another layer of mystery we don't know
anything about this planet we don't know anything about the human body we don't know anything about
the universe around us or the universe in the microverse or anything like that i find that fascinating
that new stuff is being discovered stuff that we've taken for granted is being discovered today
because like i said people have tried dismissing the abiogenic oil and
the really the best thing to come up with is it's not in huge huge amounts at least huge amounts
that we can access but if that's true if something that is as ubiquitous as oil ubiquitous you i think
there's a t in there but something that's such a part of our life as oil you know that there's
we're still discovering stuff about that i find that amazing and i don't believe in peak oil either
if you believe in peak oil that fit fair enough to you but you know when i was a little kid i remember
watching a pbs special with tony dan not tony danza who was the guy from cheers not tom selic
ted ted dancin ted dancin he was one of the tea brothers as i call him along with tron and
i don't know tommy keel figure anyways um i forgot his name again um ted dancin was doing a pbs
special and he's like the african rainforest not the african rainforest the the amazon rainforest
is going to be gone and this i was like and this is probably the 80s he's like by the year 1992
the amazon rainforest will be gone and i remember being like super scared i'm like oh my god all
these parents are going to be gone and we're just gonna and it's not it's not it's not we always
hear these stories of these ecological disasters if you ever want to and i'm not saying pollution's
great pollution we need to work on there are things that we do that don't help the planet and we need
to control them the problem is is that we always seem to go and we go okay so if if we're polluting
in 20 years the world would be uninhabitable if we're cutting down trees now in 20 years there
will be no trees there are always this incredibly alarmist behavior with it if you ever want if
you're like no jason you're an idiot and all this go to a used bookstore go online and buy books
buy um you can do this with no ceramic books too all right if you want to have a you know a good
laugh buy a no-strandomist book that was published in the year 1980 and they all say the world was
supposed to end in 1997 like they're adamant about that fact but if you but you know that's all
nonsense not stonomous is nonsense anyways he was a half of his prophecies were jelly recipes
when you look at you can go buy books about ecological disasters um the coming ecological
disasters buy books from the 70s and 80s and they're like by the year 1992 you know women will
be barren and men will be half horses as the sun just pierces through the sky and melts everything
you can watch how many science fiction movies from the 80s and 90s took place in a world where
there was no more ozone layer this is all it's just this alarmist stuff yes there is a hole in the
ozone layer yes we're pumping chemicals cfcs and stuff like that but the idea was like oh no the if
we don't stop this now it's completely reversible and the world will be destroyed you know it's
alarmism it's alarmism it's you're scaring people to sell books to to sell ideas to make money yeah
that's that's what peak peak oil is in the dustbin of the ecological catastrophes i'm not saying again
like oh no we need to cut down every tree in the amazon rainforest but go back and read those
books or watch those specials that were done decades past and what they talked about just
never happened it's never happened do i believe that climate change is happening sure do i believe
that man is having a part in that climate change sure but when you but because i've been around
for so long and i've been watched these ecological prophecies just fail just the same thing how many
ministers do you have to hear say i've done the calculations and jesus is coming back this day
like how many times do you have to say that before you start going okay i'm not going to listen to any
of them so when you oh i people say climate change is really go yeah is your climate yeah sure it's
you know the climate is changing and do you think man had plays part in well yeah sure i don't think
i think you know we're having an impact on the planet and then they say yeah and then in five years
everyone's going to de-evolve into a totes tool okay that's a strawman argument but they'll say like
you know in in one year or 10 years it'll be irreversible we got to start doing stuff now
otherwise the world's gonna be and i'm like okay guys let's talk on a on a on a smaller scale
if you take it off to this is going to happen and the world world's gonna end and blah blah blah
and the water levels are going to rise and all these cities are going to be destroyed
just say hey stop polluting you you jason carverner stop polluting stop wasting stuff
city of hood river stop polluting stop wasting stuff state of orgin stop polluting stop what
that stuff and then you go and your water quality will get better okay let's we can work with that
when you try to sell it as if you don't recycle the ice caps are going to melt
you know and then france is going to be wiped off the map that you come on guys
i know that's not true you know that's not true so that's my rant about i guess today is kind of
like the ecological episode but that's my rant about that i i've just been burned so many times
about these disaster scenarios that in 30 years you know 20 years from now people are going to
look back and go oh my god yeah i remember when they were saying that england was going to get
flooded and blah blah blah because we didn't do the x y and z and then it's not going to happen
it's not going to happen you can take that to the bank when this podcast is broadcasting its
five thousandth episode five thousandth episode i'll revisit this i'll revisit episode 23 and we'll
talk about how it didn't happen the earth abides the earth abides it's a big place it's really hard
for us to do lasting damage to the planet we can do damage to our local areas we can have you know
damage and Fukushima that's going to be another story coming up but you know but i remember even
then they're like oh all the fish are going to be gone california is going to be irradiated
here's these tide you know in five years the yeah it's all nonsense it's all nonsense
fear cells just remember that whenever someone's trying to scare you they're probably trying to
make money at the same time so that's another episode of dead rabbit radio episode 23 i think
we're almost at our 25th episode that's going to be a little landmark for me doing it every day
so that's again this is a really good podcast for me i'm having a lot of fun doing it
hope you guys are having fun listening to it like i said i'm seeing the downloads all the time
and that just makes me feel like it's worth it we do have that youtube channel dead rabbit radio
that is not getting a ton of hits but i think that's just more of the format of dead rabbit oh oh
and i wanted to do a quick update a couple episodes back i talked about that guy who said his dog was
spying on him i've kept in touch i've kept looking at that forum and he's hasn't done anything to the
dog i kind of want that that story i kind of left you hanging i was like this guy thinks his dog is
spying on him see you later and i was like you know i should retouch on that as far as right now the
dog's still fine and hopefully the guy gets some help i don't think that anything bad is going to
happen to the dog so that puts you at at rest then good dead rabbit dot com is our website you can
email us at dead rabbit radio at gmail dot com and my twitter is @jasonocarpenter so that is going
to be it for tonight's episode i hope you guys have a great day we're going to be back tomorrow
with some good stories some more good stories i think they're all good stories but i hope to see
you then i still don't have an outro i kind of i'm actually might call you guys the rabbit
league i don't know i was listening to that today and i was like oh that kind of works i don't i don't
know what to call you guys except i'll call you my friends you guys are my friends and i'm glad
you guys are listening have a great night and i'll see you tomorrow
you
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]