Then, we take a look at the KGB and a close encounter of the "turned" kind.
And then we take a look at a man who made it his life mission to not only count, but
contact the aliens in our very own solar system that, by his estimate, numbered around 22 trillion.
Today, I'm Dead Rabbit Radio.
[music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you're having a great day too. I lied. I am having a great day.
But it's snowing outside. I hate this snow. I hate everything that has the word snow in it.
I hate snow cones. Those are quite disgusting. It's just water with gross kool-aids spilled on it.
I hate snowboarding. I think it's kind of lame. Skiing is better, but I hate that too.
I never saw a movie snow piercer, but if I saw it, I'd hate it. I hate Supreme Leader,
Snoke. Anything that has the word snow in it is terrible. Snowballs are pretty dumb. I'd rather
throw a rock. And it's snowing outside right now. And I sometimes despise humanity for not being
allergic to snow. Snow is nature's dandruff. And people always talk about, "Oh, snow looks so pretty."
Okay, it does. When it's hundreds of miles away on a mountain—I guess people don't have eyesight
that good—when it's tens of miles away on a mountain, yes, snow is beautiful. But when you
have to walk through it, it's terrible. And humanity, I wish we never settled in areas with snow.
The idea that a sentient species could go, "This place is cold and inhospitable for two months
out of the year. Let's live here." I wish everyone just lived in the desert. Including me,
despite it's dangerous it is. You got Mongolian deathworms and desert yetis everywhere.
Cacti chasing you down the street. The snowmobiles—yeah, I don't like those either. Well, I mean,
comparatively, they're okay. But anyways, anyways, I like the sound they make. But other than that,
and they kind of look cool with the treads, but whatever. I hate snow. I hate it all. Snow was a
bad guy in Hunger Games. Nothing good comes out of snow. And snowmen—I know your secret. You're
not really a snowman. You're just three balls of snow with some carrots on your face. Usually just
one. I hate you, snow. Don't make me slip and follow my way to work tomorrow. I hope you didn't
hear me say I hate you. Okay, let's go ahead and get started with this snowless episode. I'm never
going to do a snow spiericy. We're going to move on to our next—our first story has no snow. It's a
no-snow zone. This is an interesting one. It's short, but it's still interesting. So a lot of you
guys—let me back up here for a second. So back up, and I haven't even started yet.
Back in the 1980s, there was this voodoo priestess in Congo, I think, a place in Africa.
I'm still stuck on that Ebola episode. There was a voodoo priestess in Africa. She saw that there
was a civil war going on in a place. I don't remember the name of it, but details are not
important. And she decided to exploit the divisions in this country that I don't remember. So she
raised an army, but she didn't have any weapons. So she gave her army sticks, stones, and voodoo dolls.
Spoiler alert, they got stomped. But her nephew, also a practicing voodoo—whatever the term is,
I know this episode's off to a great start. Also—well, he's a warlord, basically. Also a
practicing—he's a voodoo practitioner and a warlord. Let's say that. You know him. Everybody
knows him. His name is Kony. So Kony started the Lord's Resistance Army. It was a huge contingent
of it was child soldiers that he kidnapped from villages, made the kids kill their parents so
they'd have nowhere to go, so they have to stay in the army. He's a brutal, brutal man. He controlled
them through fear and violence and voodoo. He was a practitioner of the voodoo religion. I don't
know if it's called voodoo over there, but similar practices. I don't know. Similar—okay,
let's see, guys. I'm just reading articles on this stuff. Anyways, so if someone's like,
"No, no, it's not actually called voodoo. It's called this. I apologize." But anyway, so he uses
dark magic, we'll say. He uses dark magic and fear and violence and all this stuff to control
his army. Now, the reason why we know about Kony was back in 2012, there was that big social
movement, Kony 2012, and Jason Russell had a group called Invisible Children, and his goal was to
bring about the end of Kony and to free those child soldiers. Admirable goal. Admirable goal.
And so they started this huge social movement, and people were changing their profile picture.
It was called slacktivism because people were doing very little things, but they felt really good
about it because they were part of this Kony movement. The video, Invisible Children, I think
it was called, the video that Invisible Children produced was one of the most watched videos of
that year. It was this huge phenomenon, and it did bring a bunch of attention to Kony. And people
who had never heard of the Civil Strife, never heard of the child soldiers, never heard of many of
that were now aware of it. The eyes of the world were on Kony. Now, how do you strike at a target?
Kony didn't have drones. He couldn't really send over a 12-year-old assassin with an AK-47.
So how do you strike at an opponent 2,000 miles away? Magic, of course. So, I mean,
whether or not Voodoo works, I think depends on your own personal beliefs. I'm personally not
scared of Voodoo. I don't think it would work. I know Voodoo wouldn't work on me. I see it as
something that is more something that you buy into the superstitions for it to work. But I could
be wrong. I've never had anyone cast the Voodoo spell on me. Maybe they did. Maybe that's why
it's snowing. But what's interesting is you had Jason Russell, and Kony 2012 is blowing up, and
everyone's looking at this guy, everyone's looking for him, and Jason Russell starts to have
weird thoughts, we should say. Now, he is under a lot of pressure because he went from being a
nobody to being world famous like that. Like, it is very, very hard for a average person to become
famous. It's a lot of pressure. It's a super weird attack on the human psyche. I think athletes,
it's interesting because athletes start off, they're usually famous at their high school,
and then they go to college, and now they're famous nationally to a certain degree, but definitely in
their state. And then if they play pro ball, now they're nationally famous, but they have that slow
buildup of the fame. Whereas singers and actors and activists and stuff like that, politicians
can become famous overnight, and they can really, really mess with you. All of a sudden you feel
self-important stuff like that. But anyways, so Jason Russell is this normal guy who now is world
famous, and he's feeling the pressure of it. He's starting to have these weird thoughts. He needs
to take a break. Him and his family go on vacation. They go to see the movie The Lorax, the movie about
Danny DeVito trying to get people to recycle, and that's a bad description of it. But anyways,
which would have made it a better movie? He's in The Lorax and he's watching it, and he said
he felt that the movie The Lorax was talking to him. And then he got this nugget in his head,
not literally, but he got this thought in his head, a kernel, again not literally, in his head,
that if he didn't get to New York within 12 hours, Coney would win. Becoming obsessed with this thought,
he needs to get to New York in 12 hours. And then the next thing that happened was the famous footage
of Jason Russell nude in public walking down the sidewalk, freaking out. People said that he was
masturbating in public that actually wasn't true. Self-park made a big joke about that. That was
kind of the meme. He wasn't doing that, but he was like doing jumping jacks and calphexetics and
walking back and forth, and mutter knew himself and things like that. He went mad. He had a nervous
breakdown. And the conspiracy theory is that that wasn't just because of the fame, that wasn't just
because of the pressure, that was because of a successful voodoo spell that Coney actually cast on
Jason Russell. It's an interesting theory and there's not much to back it up. Really, the best
evidence I found was from TMZ, where they're interviewing someone who knew Coney. I think it
was a child soldier or someone who had worked in that region. He's like, "Oh yeah, no, that was
totally a voodoo spell." Absolutely. That's exactly what it looks like. A voodoo spell got cast on him.
That's what it looks like when you're cursed. So, I mean, in the realm that we live in, in the realm
that Dead Rabbit Radio exists in, all the craziest stuff we talk about it, that's not the craziest
thing I've ever heard of. It is interesting because after that, Jason Russell became a meme. Coney
pretty much disappeared from the spotlight. Invisible children still around. It's still trying to free
those soldiers, but definitely crippled the movement. Definitely cast a long shadow on the Coney 2012,
because now you really can't discuss Coney 2012 without discussing Jason Russell's breakdown.
He's doing better now. He said that it took him about a week or two to get back in to
find himself again. There's actually a great video I'm putting in my YouTube links
called the story of Coney 2012. There's Internet Historian did, and it's a great video.
It's great overview, and it has the interviews from Jason Russell where he talks about that breakdown.
Was he cursed by Coney? Was the spell successful? Did Coney use ancient magic to take out an enemy
who was using modern technology to stop him? Who knows? But it's definitely an interesting theory,
and I wanted to share it with you guys. Next story we're going to look at is an interesting one.
Again, it's fairly short, but I think it shows one of the problems that I have with modern UFO
ology. So apparently there was some KGB documents that the CIA got a hold of. Now right there,
I'm like immediately suspect about this story, because it already sounds a little too James
Bond-ish for me. But anyways, the CIA gets a copy of these KGB documents. All the articles I found
said one of two things. One, President Gorbachev, President Mikhail Gorbachev, President of the
Soviet Union at the time, believed that UFOs existed and more steady needed to be done on them.
And the UFO sites are like, see look at this president of the USSR believes in UFOs. And yes,
everyone believes in unidentified flying objects. And yes, we should do more investigating on them
to find out if it is a plane or a duck or a balloon. I don't think Gorbachev is saying when he says
UFOs are real, he's not saying aliens are real, and that's a problem I see with a lot of conspiracy
sites. He's just saying, yeah, we don't know what they are and we should figure it out. And there's
a huge leap there between that and they're coming from another planet. And I do believe in aliens,
but you know, I've talked about that before on the show either. I don't think they come from
other planets. I think they're from here. But see, that's the thing. I could quibble all day long
with people who believe in crop circles and reptilians and Arcturians and Pleiadians and
stuff like that. We can quibble about the details all day long. We're both idiots,
because we both don't have anything to back any of it up. I have my theories, they have their theories.
But Gorbachev said that we should study UFOs, which is, and of course you have a giant country and
you have a bunch of nukes and you're at war with another country. Of course you want to know what's
flying in your sky. But in your life, that's not the whole story, because that would just be lame.
I wouldn't just cover that. I would just waste your time for three minutes talking about it.
Also in these documents came a story of KGB soldiers facing a UFO. And again, the UFO sites are
like, "Oh my god, it's proof." I'm going to read you this story. And if you've ever done any research
on UFOs or aliens or ever watched an episode of the X-Files or got stoned and watched H and Aliens,
whatever your information is on aliens, you tell me if this story sounds like any other event you've
ever heard of. And the reason why I say that, because generally, if it is a real, if aliens are real,
if I see a tiger in the woods and 50 years later someone else sees a tiger in the woods, we're going
to describe the same thing. We're going to be like, "Yeah, it's like a big cat has these stripes."
If I see eight penguins carrying a keg, I'm going to be like, "Oh, this is what they look like. There
was eight of them. This is what a penguin looks like. They had a keg." And then a couple years later,
you see eight penguins carrying a keg. Or just eight penguins and a keg sitting there. You're going to
go, "Those penguins are awfully long-lived." And then you're going to be able to describe to me the
same thing. That's the problem with aliens and UFOs is like they're constantly being described in
different ways. And yet we're supposed to believe all of them. Anyways, I thought debunking aside,
debunk all that stuff aside, I thought this was a funny story. But again, it has nothing,
it's completely bonkers. The fact that any UFO site gives us any credence just diminishes the whole
idea. Bunch of, they don't even know when this happened. I'm angry. I've realized how angry
this story makes me. Because I had to read about it over and over and over again. And they're like,
"This is proof." And it's so funny because now that I realize, I don't really get angry that much on
this show. Or at least I don't show it. Anyways, undated event in an unknown location. Proof.
Remember, this is proof. This is being held as proof. Somewhere in Antarctica. So maybe there are
penguins with a keg. These KGB agents, for whatever reason, are in Antarctica. And they start to see
these glowing lights, these red, green, and yellow lights in the sky. In one of the articles, it said,
"For an unknown reason, someone picked up a SAM, so a surface air missile. For an unknown reason,
someone picked up a surface air missile and fired it." Well, I'll tell you the reason why
he fired it. It's not unknown. There's a big object floating around, flashing lights at you.
And you're the KGB. You beat up shop owners. It's not like they're like, "Let's have a reason
discussion with this orb." They're gonna blow it up. They blow up everything. The KGB was like one
of the most brutal secret police in world history. And they're like, "I wonder why they did it?"
Because they're nuts. And also they're in Antarctica. There's not a lot to do there. That's why the
penguins have the keg. Anyways, so the KGB shoot down this craft of blinking lights and it crashes.
And then five aliens with large heads and large black eyes come out. And you're like,
"Jason, that is familiar. What are you talking about? Those are gray aliens. Everybody has seen
those before. I've seen those in movies. Wait, hold on. Let me finish." The five aliens then
merge Voltron style into a giant ball. So they go, "Bleugh." And like with 1991 Terminator 2,
special effects. Blup. Not even that. 1991 Lawnmower Man special effects. Blup. And begin spinning
around as a giant ball. I have never in 30 years of researching UFO stuff encountered a story where
five gray aliens turn into a ball. If this story was real, then all the... you encounter ball aliens
constantly. Again, if it's real, it's real. And you would have common things among the sightings.
The Roswell aliens weren't just all like their bodies. You're just laying in the desert and then
it's like liquid metal and they start blub blub blub blub and turn. I've never heard that before.
This is obviously made up in these websites. Multiple websites were running this story.
It doesn't pass the smell test at all. Anyways, it gets stupider. It gets way stupider. So the ball
spinning around now. The alien ball is like, "Woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh, woh,
woh, woh, woh, woh,