Is the Mongolian death worm still hunting its prey today?
And we take a look at an infamous film
Detailing an infamous event today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you're having a great day that my great day comes with a little bit of
quotation marks
The heat's getting to me man
Dang it. I just realized I have to talk about the desert for like 10 minutes in this episode because we're talking about Mongolian death worms
You know I did
Let's see. Let's see if my brain can
Process what I want to talk about
death worms
Walking around
Okay, here's a question for you
Why is hot sauce why does hot sauce taste so different from other hot sauces, but all ketchup tastes the same I
Don't know let's start the episode. It's just way too hot
Actually that is a good question, but you know what I mean like all I did never mind. Let's get started with the episode
Oh, yes, the Mongolian death worm
So the Mongolian death worm is one of those legends that have seeped into the current day
so we have creatures like
Gnomes and fairies, which you know like I think Iceland still believes in gnomes and stuff like that
But for the most part people go. Oh, you know gnomes may have been around back in the day
I don't think most people think gnomes are around, but you know what I mean like there are
Creatures that are considered far far in the past that we don't have to deal with any more dragons is a good idea of that
And then there's creatures that have old
Old legends about them and they're still being seen and that would cover stuff like bigfoot
And that also would cover the creature the Mongolian death worm now if you're not familiar with what the Mongolian death worm is
It's interesting because just like the Jabu foe fee
The giant spider we talked about on Tuesday, I believe
The Mongolian death worm
All the sightings are secondhand
There's been no Western Explorer to actually be able to say oh we saw that not like it's important that it has to be Western
but you know what I mean like most of the
sightings we have is someone talking to someone else and then being like oh, yeah, I saw that and the
The descriptions are all fairly the same
If I saw a monster and then you saw a monster
Independently we may have different versions of what that monster looks like but if we both saw a tiger
I may see it from behind and I may describe it a little bit differently than you but you could compare both
Events and say well, they're probably talking about a tiger
They're probably both that they one person saw it in the shadows
So it just looked like a giant cat with a certain type of ear structure and the other person saw it in the day
And they had stripes, but he couldn't really see his head because he was I don't know drinking water or
eating an ostrich and
So the Mongolian death worm all I won't say all but most of the descriptions are the same
It's it's not you'll you'll watch movies and
Mongolian death worm is I've seen it in a couple movies
I actually saw one really good one that I'm gonna put the link to it's not a movie so much. There was a
Television show. I don't know if it's still around. I don't think so called the Lost Tapes
And it was basically a found footage television show. It was really good
It was about I think it was these three young men on ATVs
Doing some cross-continent race and they their ATVs breakdown in the Gobi Desert
And the Mongolian death worm stalking them
So kind of has this tremors vibe because as long as they're on the ATV and totally immobile
The Mongolian death worm doesn't know that they're there
So it was really good. I'll put that link in there. I recommend you watching him
But generally in movies they portray this Mongolian death worm as this giant creature the size of a graboid from tremors and
The local descriptions of it or it's about three meters long
I don't know what that is in English
Because you know the only real measurement system is feet and inches, but I think three meters long
I think is something like four feet or something like that. I don't know but anyways, so it's relative
I mean that's the size. That's a size of a medium-sized snake. That's fairly believable
What makes people doubt that it exists is that it has two other attributes that people are like
And maybe that's just made up one is it spits out some sort of toxin
So you have this three foot long worm that it burrows underground and
When somebody's walking over it it jumps out at you and bites you it can also jump out at you and spit a toxin at you
And you're like well, you know, there's animals that do that. There's animals that shoot out toxin. They're definitely toxic animals
The Mongolian death worm has another attribute is that it can release electricity
It can shock people near it
So if you're or animals if you're walking on the ground the first thing you may feel as opposed to walking in the sky
I guess but as you're walking the first thing you'll feel is a sharp electric shock
It kind of stuns you and you'll fall down and then it can kind of take its time with you spray the poison in your face
Eat what's left
Now this creature has had sightings going back as long as there are people in the area
It came to the West's attention. I believe like back in 1920 and at that time
So the Mongolian Prime Minister at that time was like I've seen the death worm
He could describe it and what's funny is that for a long time?
There was actually a ban in the country for hunting the death worm
They just didn't want to deal with people going out there now. It's not the most
I'm sure they're having a bunch of crackpots going out there and dying of dehydration because it is a desert after all
But I always think it's just for interesting when governments enact rules. I think it's in
Nepal or
Somewhere out there out east where it's against the law to harass a
Yeti you can't go yeti hunting. They're like a protected species. So sometimes it's a publicity stunt
I actually think it's illegal to hunt bigfoot in Washington as well. I might be a publicity stunt
It might just be you know
And it might be publicity star. It may be real. They're like man
We don't want people going out there and getting killed by these Mongolian death worms. It's most likely publicity stunt
But so you have this creature. It's blood red because what happens is it lays its eggs inside a camel's
Intestines and they eat up the I'm assuming dead camel they eat it up and it just like gives them this red coloring and
They say that it's just a silent predator. It just lives in the desert
It'll kill anything. It'll eat anything. It just like most cre- and this is an interesting fact of it too
when you're making stuff up
If it's made up you can make up whatever it does you can be like yes
It's the size of a house and it will swallow your firstborn child and it'll come over to where you work
And it'll start knocking pins off your desk like you just make it up
If you're making up that's actually a fairly relative size for something that's
You're like, well, how big was it? You're like, I don't know three meters. I mean, you know, that sounds more realistic
Also, they generally don't hunt humans. They prefer to hunt animals, but will kill a human if need be
So again when we look at stuff like the Groot Slang and they're like it was created by the gods
And it's one of the most intelligent creatures on the planet and it steals people's gold
That sounds far more made up than there's a really big worm in the desert
That shoots acid and can shock you and it will usually eat an animal, but it might eat you too
so
The Mongolian to see the stuff like the Groot Slang. I
Like the idea of it. I don't think it exists the giant spider from Tuesday's episode and the Mongolian death worm
I think are very likely to exist if not existing today
Existed at some point in human history and that's why those legends have been passed down. I'm not saying you can you know
Book a flight to the Gobi Desert right now
Parachute in and find one because no westerner has ever seen one or at least ever seen one and survived to talk about it
But again if this creature isn't necessarily hunting humans and it is under the ground
What are the chances of you trying to find it in a desert? It's a massive desert. They don't know how many of these things are
But this is one of those cryptids that if we found evidence of it
I want to be surprised at all if we found giant spiders and you know giant spiders have exoskeletons
But when they die, I wonder how they fossilize. I'm sure we found fossilized spiders from the past
But I wonder how they oh and that's dope about this thing too
Mongolian death worm actually has an exoskeleton as well and
When it's damaged when it's attacked it can actually molt off its armor and grow new armor
So they're fairly difficult to kill. They're not impossible. I mean obviously if you shot one it's dead
But it's mostly built for protecting against like animal attacks where if I don't know what else lives out in the Gobi Desert if a
Paku-paku attacks it it can be like ha ha ha and then just like drop take off that piece of broken armor
Have some new one and then he shocks him
And eats him
So I don't know the mongolian death worm
Mongolian death worm I'm gonna put in the possible category of
My cryptid category. I just made up for this episode. I'm gonna count it as possible
It may not have the elect I think the least likely thing out of everything. It's described is the electrical ability
I don't think the size is ridiculous. I don't think the venom is ridiculous
I don't think the environment or what it hunts and all that stuff the electric electrical shock thing is probably the most
fantastical thing
But the only thing that really makes people doubt this is they've never seen one
Everything else fits into how big of these type of creatures can be what it would eat
How it would live and things like that and again with the giant spider the only every it acts like a spider a hunts like a spider
Does everything like a spider the only thing people debate is I can't get that big
As opposed to the Groot slaying which is completely mythological or the Atowah the tiny tiny ant sized humans
I mean those aren't just on its face
completely untrue so I
Do recommend I haven't watched I said I seen those other death war movies as in I've seen they exist
I haven't watched any of the other death war movies, but actually I probably am going to but I recommend you guys watch the
Lost tapes and again, I'll put that link in below
Now we're gonna move on to our next story
Which is actually currently being made into a movie
But you guys are gonna get a little spoiler on that you guys don't have to wait for the movie to come out
Back during World War two
Joseph Goebbels I think that's how you pronounce his last name if I if I'm wrong I apologize not to him
To you he I don't care about him
Goebbels and might be Goebbels. I don't know any anyways Joseph you got he was propaganda minister for the Nazis
so he
believed that film was one of the greatest propaganda tools around
Available and it was it was it is still to today
So he made a movie one of the movies he made was called suss the Jew and
It was a drama about an innocent German girl being raped by a Jewish man and audiences around Germany loved it
And he's like okay. I'm on to something. I just need to make propaganda films to keep the Germans because this is like in
1942-1943 so things weren't going well
He's like well, I'm gonna make these Nazi propaganda movies keep the spirits up
This is how we're going to keep people fighting keep people in line with the Nazi idea
So it dawns on him
What is one of the greatest tragedies in recent human memory other than the whole Nazi Holocaust thing?
It was the sinking of the Titanic
And so Goebbels I'm gonna mispronounce his name every single time I say it so let's just go on there
But he decides to make a tight movie about the Titanic with a twist
He wants to put the onus on
Capitalism the reason why the ship sank was capitalism the Nazis were national socialists
They were a socialist movement who believed that the government should control everyone gets a job the government controls the economy
Capitalism is not something that they were too fond of
so they basically wrote this script where it's these businessmen in New York and Britain who realized that the
Company that owns the Titanic, which I think was the red star line was not doing well
So they go what if we take we take this new boat?
We built the Titanic and we race it across the ocean as fast as we can and it will win this award
And what we'll do right now is we're gonna short sell our stock because the stock is low and then once it completes the race
We will buy the stock back or something like that. Oh, they were gonna cover it or whatever
They were going to make a ton of money once it won the race
So basically girl bulls is figuring this to be like it's a mad mad mad mad world
But with the Titanic just this wacky race
so
That's the plot so that's the start of the plot and then they inserted they created a German character
Who's like an officer on the ship and he's like as the captain's who's like speeding across the ocean the German guy's like
We shouldn't go so fast sir and the British captain's like you don't understand anything German
We're we we're gonna make it and this is gonna be the fastest boat right ever
And so then of course spoiler alert the boat ends up hitting an iceberg
so his girlfriend was this the the
German first officer had a love interest and
He's like he has to get to her to get off the boat and they show all like the rich people on the boat like totally cowardly
They're just like no no save me first save me first
While this German guy is like running through the boat saving poor people and all the Germans are like come with us
We're all on this together and we'll take care of you and at one point
The German officer the star grabs this little girl because the boats starting to like go under and there's like this
These little girl is trapped in her cabin because her parents are like capitalism rules. See you later kid
The German guy gets the kid he then jumps off of the boat and
Lands on the water and his girlfriend shows up in a rowboat and they get in and the Titanic falls into the water
And then there's this whole thing at the end where the Germans like the company was trying to make us go fast
And the courts are like well we're capitalist too so you're innocent
And it was this whole thing about how the system is rigged against the working class and how Germans are noble and the British
New Americans are all about money
So as a propaganda film that would work that was the plot
But what happened was when they were making the movies when the weird stuff started to happen
Gobbles gobbles. I can't believe okay. Anyways, he
Personally picked the director to do this film. He had worked on other propaganda films for him. He goes. I want you to direct this the movie
Cost at its time a hundred and eighty million dollars
Well with inflation or maybe not inflation. Let me check
Yeah with inflation a hundred eighty million dollars. Remember there were there a war. This is not like in
1937 they're in war. This is in 1942
They got other stuff to spend their money on
anyways, he personally picks this director they're shooting the movie and
the Nazis send over a bunch of
Advisors to the film to be like this is what it's like being on a boat and the advisors are constantly drunk and
They're sexually molesting or assaulting the women working on there and the directors like okay guys
Let's get it together and they won't listen to him. So he starts complaining now
That's one thing you don't want to do in a totalitarian state because it gets back to Gobbles
he
Personally pulls in the director and says did you say this stuff and the director's like looks him goes. Yeah, I said that stuff and that really made
I'm just gonna stick with Gobbles. It really made Gobbles mad
I really hope that's how I say his name anyways
It really made him mad because this was a guy he personally picked and now he's basically like throwing that in his face
He sends him to jail, but luckily for the Nazis that he hangs himself the next day
So the director's dead and it's real to suicide
so then the cast is like what you know, that's not he didn't die and they kind of get upset and
Gobbles is like hey listen man
You can complain all you want. I got a nice jail cell with an extra bed sheet. So the cast was like, okay, we're done
We're done with this
So they get another director
We continue to make the movie he gets finished. It's way over budget
Gets finished now and also there they actually had like they were shooting it on a real like liner a real big boat
And there was Lena obviously pick up shots other place
But the set was an actual boat that was sailing out in the ocean
so they shoot the movie and
Gobbles is watching it at one point. It's all done and there's scenes to show how like uncaring the capitalist are towards the
Poor people in on the boat
So there's a few scenes of like, you know
They'll pull down gates and lock them so the poor people can't get out and you saw that actually in the James Cameron movie
Titanic like the safety gates came down and they'd lock them
But he prevented people from getting out to surface so they could not drown
So there are scenes of these gates coming down and like families being separated and like reaching through the gate
Like the German mothers like come to me my daughter and the German daughters like I'm so scared
I can't get through the gate. I can't get through the gate and
They think that's one of the reasons why this movie was never aired in Germany
Because that's kind of like what was going on in concentration camps and in ghettos and on trains
people were basically having gates put in between them and crying as
In this movie was the capitalist the uncaring capitalist and in reality. It was the uncaring
national socialists
They also say that it wasn't released another reason why it wasn't released was that
it made
It was coming towards the end of the war and it was basically a movie about a hopeless event and a few people surviving a hopeless event
and
Historians feel that it might as gerbils was watching and he might have thought they the German people might
think more of the Titanic being this horrible hopeless event and
Making that the equivalent to what they were going through like they're literally on a sinking ship both sides of two different armies
Are just pushing them in
So the movie was never released in Germany
After the war it should it was aired in Russia sometimes and they called it a trophy film
Which I think it was almost like that's almost like a hate song like they
Destroyed Germany and then they would watch this movie and laugh at it about how stupid it was
There was a VHS copy that was floating around Germany for a while
They say would air on television every once in a while and it did start to get shown in other places because
German films
The cinematography is pretty good like they they really pioneered some filmmaking techniques
And eventually did get restored and you can watch it now. I haven't seen it
I'm assuming it would be all in German, but that could be a bad assumption
So what happened to the boat? What happened to the boat that they filmed the Titanic on well apparently
It was towards the end of the war. It's like almost over and
The Germans were like, oh man
You know, it's all we're almost out of here. What can we do?
We're almost done. What do you want to do and the other guys like, you know what I want to do
I want to kill some more Jewish people
So they loaded a bunch of Jewish people onto this boat turned it into a prison boat and sent it out
Going okay, two things are gonna happen with the wars ending two things are gonna happen either the British are gonna blow it up
or we're gonna sink it
one of the two and
Some British bombers spotted a Nazi ship in the water and they dropped bombs on it and killed them
And it would they kill ended up killing three times the amount of people who died on the actual Titanic
That is the history of it's generally called the Nazi Titanic and it was actually the first movie on the subject that was called
Titanic or the Titanic before they were called like a night to remember. I think was the first big
Titanic film this one was just called the Titanic or no actually was just called Titanic. I don't know how many times I have to say that
This one was called Titanic. It was the first movie about the event called Titanic
There had been other movies about that. I know one of them was called the night to remember
Which sounds romantic, but it's not as much people drowning
Movies are a very good propaganda tool
but you may want to think
long and hard
About what you're trying to prop gan propagandize
because obviously they had some things in mind about
corruption in the government and
uncaring bureaucrats separating families and
the hopelessness of being surrounded by darkness and
slowly drowning
Probably aren't messages you want to give to people who live in a brutal totalitarian regime
where they've seen families separated and
They are getting bombed daily probably not a good idea
Nazi Germany was full of bad ideas. This was probably their least bad idea. I
Do have to say I would I would watch this not the movie Titanic because again
It's probably on German, but I would watch a movie about the making of Titanic
I think that sounds far more interesting than the movie they made. I think I would watch that
I'm not a big fan of World War two movies in general. I
Think they're all kind of the same
It's saying private Ryan was okay. Same Ryan Ryan actually only had one good
Scene and that was the beach scene everything else was kind of lame honestly
And it made every game be washed out gray after that call the dude and all that stuff
It's like they just put grace around wrap over their graphics and said hey
It's like saying private Ryan. I'm not a big fan of those that era
That storytelling era. I'm not a big fan of it
But I had watched this maybe if it was on stars or something like that on YouTube
We'll find out when it comes out if it ever does
Dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be oh, I have a I am curious
So what happens if when they're making this movie about the Nazi Titanic?
That boat sinks - that'd be crazy
You know a guy died making James Cameron's Titanic. Maybe just that story is cursed
I'm not gonna make a slain Dion joke either. That's kind of low hanging fruit
Dead rabbit radio gmail.com is going to be your email address
Facebook comm slash dead rabbit radio is our Facebook on Twitter. We are at Jason. Oh carpenter
Dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
This it's so high
Dead rabbit radio. Oh
Man dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great day. Stay hydrated people stay hydrated
You
(upbeat music)
[MUSIC]