Today we take a look at a trio of stories all involving myself. I'm not egotistical.
These are actually interesting stories. First off, what happens when I come face to face
with a victim of a notorious true crime case? Two weeks ago I was house sitting for a friend.
I thought I was just going to have a fun time wrestling with her cat.
Instead I saw the shadow people. And then while I was house sitting,
something came to my house to pay for this. Something from out of this world. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day. I hope you guys are having a great day too. I hope you guys had an
awesome weekend. We got a ton of stuff to cover, so we're going to get started right away. First
off, let's give a shout out to today's supporter Cameron. Everyone give a round of applause to
Cameron. He is driving a tank into Dead Rabbit Command. He's running over a bunch of stuff.
Move out of the way. Tanks coming. Cameron actually made a very generous donation during a recent
live stream. So Cameron, today you're going to be our captain, our pilot. We're not taking the tank.
We should have a tank though, but we'll figure that out. We're not taking your tank, but you can
park it here. You're going to be our captain, our pilot this episode. If you guys can't support the
Patreon or can't make a donation during a live stream, I totally understand. Just helps to
rid the word about the show. Really, really helps out a lot. We also have a merch store. I always
forget that. Merch store in the show notes. So everyone, let's take a walk through Dead Rabbit
Command. We're all wearing our Dead Rabbit uniforms. It's just pajamas. We're very casual here. We're
wearing really cool pajamas. And before we go anywhere, the stories I'm going to talk about,
I talked about during a live stream I did recently, the one that Cameron donated on so generously.
But if you watched that live stream, this episode is going to have more information. This isn't a
repeat. I'm not replaying the audio from that episode or anything. It's not a clip show. Even if
you did hear the live stream this episode, I implore you guys to stick around because there's a ton
of new information involving all the stories. I talked about two of them on the live stream. We're
going to go in a more detail now. And then the ending is definitely something that wasn't on the
live stream. So Cameron, I'm going to go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason Jalopy. We are
leaving behind Dead Rabbit Command. I want you to hit that back in time button. We are traveling
back in time to the early 2000s. We're specifically going to one of my favorite places in the world,
Cameron make a left here. We're now in Orangevale, California. So the Jason Jalopy is pulling into
Orangevale, California, a suburb of Sacramento, California. I spent a lot of my life there.
Some of my happiest memories are there. Not all of them. I'm having happy memories here as well,
but Orangevale, California is dope. If you can stand all of the meth and the hardcore white
supremacists openly just walking around, just walking around a super bizarre, super bizarre
little suburb. You're just like, what? Did I just see that? Well, I remember once I was driving on
the road and a gangfight broke out between two rival groups of white supremacists and blocked
traffic and people were like honking their horns and then the fight just kind of ended and then
we just got in their cars and drove away. It wasn't spectacular. I remember being like, oh,
come on man. I'm trying to get to my ground loss house. These guys are picking each other up and
throwing each other into the concrete and then they all got in their cars and drove away and then
everyone just went about their business. People went to the jack in the box. That's Orangevale
for you. You watch a gang war of two white supremacist gangs beat the crap out of each
other at three in the afternoon and then you're like, can I get a grande frappuccino please?
We're in this area. We're in this area. Okay. But it is a really nice area other than that stuff.
Other than the white supremacist gangs and the meth. It's great. It's totally great. You should
live there. We're there. It's the early 2000s. I was staying with my grandma. My grandma,
miss her dearly. She's an amazing woman. My great-grandma, my grandpa and all that. Really,
really awesome family. I would visit my grandma all the time. I used to live with her and then
even when I got my own place, I'd be over there all the time. Free food man. Free food dude.
Chili and spaghetti and all sorts of stuff. But anyways, I remember once I was there and I was
spending the night and I'm sitting there on the couch and my uncle's there, my grandma, because
my uncle did live there. My grandma's there. My grandpa's there. There's always a really crowded
house and it's probably like eight o'clock at night. I don't remember the specifics. I remember it
being nighttime and this guy comes over. Super drunk. Now again, not like Rodney Dangerfield,
lampshade on head, drunk. Not wild and crazy guy drunk. Depressingly alcoholic drunk.
And I'm thinking, uh, this guy drove here. This guy drove here. Because he's just like,
"Hey, what's up?" Again, that makes him sound funny. Hey! No, he was one of the drunkest people
I'd ever seen in my life. And I remember sitting on, I don't like being around drunk people or
really, I don't like being around. It's different like when you're kind of at a party and people
are buzzed, but I don't like being around drunk people. I don't like being around people who are
high because they're just too unpredictable. Like someone who's stoned, sure, I can deal with that.
I can deal with someone with a buzz. But once they start getting into the mind altering, like they're
super rip and stoned or they're drunk, you just can't predict what they're going to do.
And so I'm always on edge around these people. Because you could say the wrong thing, right?
They're going to snap. And I've had that happen. So I'm super nervous, this dude that I don't know
comes out of my grandma house and my uncle's like, "Hey, what's up man? My uncle."
I mean, that's a whole different story as well. That's a whole different story as well.
So the fact that he knew this dude wasn't helping, wasn't helping me relax. My grandma's like, "Oh,
hi." Whatever his name was, Jerry actually looked his name up, but I don't want to give it.
It's in court documents, but my grandma's like, "Hey Jerry, how you doing?" Haven't seen you in a
while and he's like, "Uhhh." Like, unintelligibly drunk. He was barely able to stay. Again, he drove
here and he was like swaying back and forth in the living room. And I'm sitting on the couch and
I'm like, "Oh dude, I'm going to have to beat this drunk dude up because I'm going to like move my
left arm." And he's like, "No one moves their left arm when I'm around because he's that drunk."
And I was like, super ready to just fight this guy. My grandma's talking to him and he's like,
"Hey Ida, how you doing?" And I think she made him some food because that's what grandma's do.
The grandma's have unlimited food to give to people. My uncle's talking to him for a bit and
I'm just super stressed out. Dude, just leave. Like, sure, you're drinking and driving, but
just go. Like, I just remembered basically I was sitting like Liam Neeson the whole time,
which he sits like a normal person, especially the actor Liam Neeson. I'm sure he drinks orange
juice all the time. I was just, I was a coiled spring. But after, I mean, after an ungodly amount
of time, I'm surprised I didn't get an ulcer. It had to have been a couple hours, I think.
He ends up leaving and I was like, "Uhhh, finally I can relax and I can drink orange juice." Just
like Liam Neeson. I go, "What, what was that? Dude, that was the drunkest human being I've ever
seen. He was 50% alcohol and he drove away. You guys let him drive away." And I think it was a little
bit more sober at that point, but again, I wasn't really, I was looking for things I could use as
a weapon, which at my grandma's house is literally everything. Everything was either sharp or heavy.
And she goes, "Oh, Jason. Oh, Jason. Yeah, he does have a drinking problem. He's serious alcoholic.
His marriage is in the shambles, but he has a good reason to drink. He has a good, good reason
to drink." And I was like, "What the heck? What's a good reason to be that drunk?" And she goes,
"He was there when Michelle Montoya died." So let's go back a little bit farther in time.
The year is 1997. It's May 16th, 1997, to be exact. And we're standing outside Real
Linda High School, which is another suburb of Sacramento. It's probably 10 miles west or north
or south or east. One of those, it's actually west of Orangeville, because I remember always claiming
I was east side. But Real Linda, it's a real hick area. It's a literal one-stop light town. They
might have more infrastructure now, but back when I was there, it was in my stomping grounds. They had
the one-stop light. It's funny, for someone from Orangeville to be making fun of Real Linda,
they're just like shaking their heads. They had a huge math problem as well. But yeah.
I really can't cast stones. But anyway, Real Linda, it's this real rural community.
Real Linda High School, it's May 16th, 1997. There is a senior. Her name is Michelle Montoya.
She's 18 years old. And her teacher says, "Hey, can you stay after school? I want to have a meeting,
a school meeting with you." Now, this meeting was supposed to take place at 2.30. It got delayed to
2.50. Michelle Montoya is just hanging out. So, after the meeting, she needs to make a phone call
to call her guardian to pick her up. And the teacher says, "Hey, you can use my phone." She had a
cell phone, but cell phones weren't in wide use back then. And they cost money. They cost per
minute. Michelle's like, "No, no, no. I'll find a phone." And the teacher thought that was odd.
She figured Michelle would just go to the office and make a phone call there.
There was a custodian named Alex Dale Thomas. He had just got hired on May 5th, 1997. He'd only
been working there for three days. Now, back then, California had a stupid rule that a temporary or
substitute employee of a school could be hired and start working before their background check
cleared. So, Alex Dale Thomas definitely needed to have a background check then. He had eight
felonies before he got the job as this guy. And they were like a tempted murder. I think one of
them was aggravated manslaughter. He's not Liam Neeson. He was a member of a street gang. He was
a member of the Crips. I mean, he had, he was like the 107 Crips or something like that. And he had
107 tattooed on his forehead. He's not a huge fan of the radio station. He's a huge fan of engaging
in gang activity and to cover it, he just put makeup on his head and went into the job interview
and they're like, "You seem like a great candidate. It says on your resume, you spilled a lot of blood."
He's like, "Yes." And then I cleaned it up to not get caught, but he got caught anyway, so it
didn't matter. There's two custodians working in the school as well. And I gave them the fake names
of Joey and Kevin. I don't remember what did I call the guy earlier? I don't remember what the fake
name, but in my notes. So just to make things, just to make things logical, Kevin is the one I was
talking about earlier, whatever that guy's name was. What I just called Kevin from here on out. So
Kevin is the guy that I ran into in my grandma's house. So what happens is he's walking around the
school, he hears a loud noise, and Alex comes running out of a room and he's like, "Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh dude." And he's like rubbing his hands on the ground with paper towels. And Kevin
and Joey are looking and they're like, "What?" They're like, "Alex, what's going on?" He's wiping
his forehead. He's like, "Man, it sure is hot in here." They see the gang tattoo. No, he stands up
and he's like, "Oh dude, dude, I'm so glad I found you guys. Do you know how to clean this room?"
I'm like, "What? Why are we just all sweaty running around? Because you don't know how to
clean this room." And Kevin goes, "That's weird." Because he cleaned that room just the other day.
So he knows how to clean it. It was like a shop room. He's like, "Fine, Alex, I'll show you."
Alex and Kevin go into the room and it's like this shop room. And Kevin's like, "Yeah, this is how
you do this, Alex. You know, here's how you move all this stuff around and everything like that."
Then Kevin goes, "I'm going to go into this closet and get more supplies." And Alex goes,
"Okay, you do that. I'm going to stand right here." And then Kevin, as he's coming back into the room,
here's horrible screaming. It's like, "What's going on?" And Alex comes running out of yet another
room all sweaty. And he goes, "Kevin, Kevin, you got to see this. You got to see this." And he basically
grabs Kevin and pulls him into the wood shop room. You got to see this. You got to see this.
And Kevin, even from a distance, can tell what he's looking at. It's the
body of a young woman laying on a table. And Alex is basically pushing Kevin towards this body.
"What is this? What is this? I just came and I just saw this. What's going on? What's going on?"
And Kevin is getting pushed closer and closer to this woman and he's starting to see the extent
of her injuries. Her throat is slit. She has stab wounds in her body. And as he gets closer to her,
he realizes the full extent of her injuries. Now, I normally don't get gruesome on this show,
but I'm going to, so you can skip ahead a minute or two if you want.
She was hit so hard with a blunt object, which police later realized was a crowbar,
that it shattered her skull. It smashed into her to the point that her brains came out of the other
side. When the EMTs got there, they thought she had been shot in the head. That's how powerful
this blunt object impacted into her. It wasn't just a little trickle of blood coming out,
someone goes bonk with a bat. She got hit so hard, her skull basically disintegrated and
brains are coming out of the back of her head. And Kevin is watching this. And he's basically
being held there by the, he doesn't really know this at this point, but the murderer of her is
holding him there. The police are called, they come out very, very shortly. Alex just kind of
becomes flippant and he's like, yeah, yeah, whatever. And he does get arrested. He gets charged with
the rape and the murder of her. He said, listen, I didn't know who murdered her, but I didn't rape her.
And then he goes, okay, I might have murdered her, but I still didn't rape her. Because that would
mean the death penalty. Well, in the end, he did get the death penalty. He's currently sitting on
death row to this day. And Kevin, Kevin's life fell apart after that. Like from what my grandmother
told me, because she knew him as a kid, my uncle knew him, they were friends growing up. It ruined
his life seeing this. Now you could go, Jason, I watch gory videos all the day. Trust me, it's not
the same thing. And to make matters even more grim, she was still alive. She died on the way to the
hospital. She was still alive when Kevin was pushed towards her. There was still a spark of life in
her despite that massive injury. There's a difference when you see it in real life versus when you see
it in footage. I've seen a bunch of gory, like faces of death type stuff. And then I've seen people
die in real life, like right in front of me die. And it does affect you. I know probably if you're
doing it all the time like an EMT or a cop or a soldier, it's different. But for people who aren't
those things, it's unsettling to say the least. And I've never seen a murder, I've never seen a
murder victim die. I've seen people die in car accidents, like you get there, you're watching
them, you're trying to help them and they die. I've had that happen to me a couple times. And I've
lost count of how many just dead bodies I've seen. Because I used to work at a crematory. And you get
used to those. Totally different seeing a dead body versus seeing somebody who's still alive die.
But it ruined his life. He actually, after that, he developed a obviously serious drinking problem,
serious, serious drinking problem. His marriage has fallen apart. And that's really the last I
ever heard of him. I think it's interesting, it's a tragic story. But it's the story of all the
effects that happen with true crime. You know, when we read about him in books, when we watch the news,
it's always so sanitary. Sanitary is true crime can get where you always think, you know, the victim
obviously has suffered. And then you think about the family members around them having to suffer,
even the perpetrator's family member. Maybe the person was mentally ill and they wanted to get
help for their son or their daughter and they didn't. And then they ended up doing something
awful. But yeah, I never thought about those even side victims. That story went longer than I thought,
but I think it's an interesting story. We're going to keep moving forward. We got to say goodbye
to Orangevale, California. Wave goodbye to my grandma, my grandpa, my great grandma.
Wave and Adam, they're four ghosts now, but they're still watching over us. Everyone give them a
good wave. Cameron, I'm going to toss you the keys to the Carbitercopter. We're leaving behind
Orangevale, California. We are headed back home. Carbitercopter is flying up north. We're going
to land at a little house in the middle of the town of Hood River. This happened, it's funny,
I probably should have looked up the dates. It wouldn't be too hard. I actually, this happened,
I believe, on the 15th or the 22nd, one of the two. It happened very recently and I talked about it
in the live stream. I was house sitting for a friend. I went over there to stay there for a
couple of days to keep an eye on her cat and to beat him up. To beat up cats. I love wrestling
with cats, taking a little pause. I mean, like, no, no, don't claw me in the wrestling. And, you
know, we had a good time. I had a good time hanging out with Jenny, little cat person.
But the house is weird. The house is really weird. At one point they had to do renovations
in the house because the floor was falling apart. The floor was disintegrating. So they crawled under
the house and right underneath where the bedroom is, underneath the house, they found a cat skull
and a wand. The cat skull is the cat skull, but you go, the wand was it just like a stick? No,
apparently it was like wrapped with leather. It was made to be a wand. It wasn't just like a cat
walked in there with a branch and then died. And then every other bone disappeared except the skull.
It was a cat skull and a wand were right underneath the bedroom. I hang out there a lot. And I remember
at one point I turned to my friend. I was there really late one night and I turned to my friend and
I go, "Have you ever saged this place?" She goes, "What?" And I go, "You need to sage this place.
You need to sage it." I felt negativity there. Like as much fun as I had with my friend hanging
out there, I could feel a negative presence there. And she did sage it. And she said that she felt
like something was fighting back. After she had saged it, she had woke up the next day, she had
scratches on her back. But that was it. You're like, "Jason, that's it?" She got assaulted by this
interdimensional creature. That was the end of it. Like I went over there. I didn't feel negative,
nothing anymore. But I'm house sitting. I'm someone who leaves the lights on all the time
because I'm scared of the dark because I've just seen too much stuff. When you meet people who are
scared of the dark, they're either not, they're all they're nine years old, or they're people who
have had pretty bizarre experiences and they know what's in the dark. Because they're stuck, guys,
I'm gonna be honest with you. They're stuck in the dark. They're stuck in the dark. Like I sometimes
I don't really hit that hard enough. But they're stuck in the dark. They're stuck in the light
that's not too pleasant either. But there's definitely stuff in the dark. So I sleep with
lights on and if I'm a nine-year-old boy, if I'm at a place that's not my home, I do sleep with a
nightlight here as well. But I get a lot of moonlight, so I'm good most of the time. But if I'm at
someone else's house, oh, I'll house it for you, but your electric bill is gonna be much higher.
Have the lights on. The first two days went fine. I'm laying there on the ground doing research
for the show. It was a nice research weekend. I just spent the whole weekend pulling up information.
And I'm kind of, I'm laying on the ground. I have my laptop there and I see, I feel something to the
left of me. I keep feeling myself kind of get drawn to look towards the left. And there's like,
it's a very open home plan. It's a very nice little home. It's a very open home plan. And I feel like
I'm, my eyes keep getting drawn to the left of me. Now there is a cat. There is an open sliding
glass door. At this point, it's probably like around 7 p.m. There's an open sliding glass door.
And there is a drape kind of blowing in a slight wind. But there's maybe a good six or seven feet
between the curtain and the sliding glass door and this bookshelf full of plates, full of these
really nice plates and doll houses and stuff like that. And I'm looking over, I keep, my
attention keeps getting drawn over there. I don't see anything. And at one point I'm looking over
there and I see a shadow move. A figure move. A shadow person. Now it wasn't super distinct.
It was like just simply movement, but it was tall. This bookshelf is probably a round as tall as I
am. So close to six feet. And I just see something move out. I see a shadow move out of the shadow.
Now I was not standing up. I was laying down. Jenny is not giant. There was nothing that could
project her shadow that way. The drape couldn't make that motion. Couldn't blow that much because
I tried all that stuff on the live stream. Now at the top of this bookshelf, there's this elephant.
So it actually gives the, because you normally a bookshelf just has a shadow, like a rectangular
or kind of a diffused shadow. But because there's an elephant at the top of it and the way that
the light was hitting it, it did make it have a unique form. There's this elephant at the top.
I see this shadow move and it catches my attention obviously. That's unusual. It's been years since
I've seen a shadow person, years. So now my attention is fully drawn to the corner of this house.
And I know that I saw something. I know that I absolutely saw something and I'm kind of looking,
now I'm laying and I'm looking to my left and then maybe a couple feet from the shadow cabinet.
Because at this point I'm thinking maybe I should do a live stream. Like this would be really
interesting. I know this house has a history of it. The owner says she's never seen a ghost there.
Like she did. She didn't get scratched by a ghost. But she figured maybe there's just like
negative energy. I'm looking over in the corner and I'm thinking should I live stream this? Like
this might be interesting. Also I'm scared and I want other people to talk to. I'm looking at the
corner here and I see closer to me a couple feet from the wall where this shadow was. I see
what could only be described as from the knees down a shadow child. I see two legs from the knees
down. It was like a grayish shadow. Now normally the shadow people I've seen are pitch black.
They're darker than reality. You can see them at night. It's very, very bizarre. You can see a
shadow person in a pitch black room. They're darker than the absence of light. It's very bizarre
phenomenon. Now I've seen them in fields. I've seen them in dark rooms. They're beyond black.
Very, very bizarre phenomenon. This was a diffused gray. It was almost like a...
You know what's funny now that I think about it? Didn't we cover recently a shadow person that was
staticky? Did we do that? Did I cover that story? This seemed like it was a diffused shadow,
like a shadow that wasn't fully formed. It matched the type of shadow that was being projected from
the wall, but now we're feet away. We're now three or four feet away from the wall. In the middle of
the room, this wasn't against the wall. This was a 3D shadow walking not necessarily towards me,
but in my direction. I see just the movement of two legs go doot, doot, doot. But I did the
livestream. There was actually some confusion of when the livestream was actually aired, because I
wasn't really paying attention to it, but it's going to play a part in our next story. So I posted
this on YouTube. When did the livestream go up? And I want to give a shout out to FreeEXP,
Cthulhu, and Alejandro News. They were able to actually figure out the time that the livestream
was going on. A lot of people were giving helpful suggestions, but they're the ones who actually
were able to nail down when the livestream was going on. So thank you so much for figuring that
out. We did the livestream. Now I asked her later, I texted her that night and said, "By the way,
your house is haunted. Your electric bill is even going to be higher." And I talked to her when she
came back and I go, "Did you get anything new recently? Did you get any?" Now I hadn't really
told her much about what I'd seen, because she's on vacation and I didn't really want to go over it
on text. I go, "Did you guys get anything new in the house recently?" And it's so funny,
because when I said that I already knew the answer, I knew that I just knew the answer. It was the
elephant. And she goes, "Yeah, I got a couple little elephant toys." And I was like, "Yep." That's
exactly where I saw this figure coming from was the bookcase with the elephant on it. It was all
seemed to be in that area. And I asked, I go, "Where did you get it from?" And basically she got it
from a friend and the friend found these elephant toys. Are the toys themselves haunted? Are they
some sort of conduit? Who knows? The first two nights, it was there all by myself with Jenny,
and there was nothing weird at all. Stand-up plate, researching spooky stuff, nothing weird at all.
It wasn't until that night where, again, it was like 7 p.m. It was around 7, 7.30 p.m. that this
was going on and then I start the livestream. So you think that's the end of it? I thought it was
the end of it. A nice little cool livestream that we did in a possibly haunted house. But then I come
back home. I'm house-sitting in my own house. And one night, I get a message from my neighbor, Erica.
She texts me on the phone and she goes, "Hey, what's up? How you doing?" And I say, "Hey,
she goes, "Hey, did you hear that noise the other night? Was that you?" I said, "What?" No, I don't
think so. I mean, what noise? And she sends me this audio clip that I'm about to play for you in a
second. But this noise, we figured out because she goes, "I wasn't even home that day. I was
house-sitting across town." She told me this happened around 7.45. She said it happened four times.
And that's why I needed to find out when the livestream was going on. While I was live streaming,
this noise was happening at my place. So I'm going to play it for you. I'm going to play
two different versions of it. The first version is the raw, completely unedited file. It's going
to be hard to hear. So you might want to turn your headphones up and then I'll give you a warning
when we're going to play another version. But here's the original raw audio file from Erica.
[silence]
The stories are real.
And as we continue to investigate the world of the paranormal,
they're going to become even more real.
They won't just be glimpses
and faint whispers in a hallway.
We may come face to face
with the truth
we were never ready to see.
[music]
DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be our email address.
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio.
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio.
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily
paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast.
You don't have to listen to it every day.
I'm glad you listened to it today.
Have a great one, guys.
[music]