An unusual disease caused by an annoying hobby.
And then we take a look at the alien abduction of Johnny Sands.
Who's Johnny Sands you ask?
Why he's the most rootnest, tootnest alien abduction victim you'll ever meet today on
Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Chase Carpenter, I'm having a great day.
I hope you guys are having a great day too.
I'm sweaty, I'm just a puddle of sweat.
And just think about it, a year ago today was the day before Dead Rabbit Radio started.
I still don't know if I'm gonna do anything special for tomorrow's episode.
Because I kinda did my look back episode for the New Year's Eve episode and I thought
that I don't...
I don't think I can do another one six months later.
The last six months have kind of been a blur.
The first six months was pretty rough.
The last six months they've been kind of rough too but it just kind of flew by.
And I've had a lot of good stories but I haven't had a lot of bad, like that first retrospective
I was able to say like this was my least favorite episode.
Here's some of the drama that was happening behind the scenes.
We even had anything like that since.
Which is good.
I haven't had an episode that I've recorded in the past six months that I've been like
this episode sucks.
I've had episodes I've recorded that I've re-recorded and it's just funny because that's part of
the thing of becoming skill.
I don't think I'm...
I'm sure I could do much better at this than I am doing but through practice I can be
recording something and I'll go this isn't working.
In the past I would've just released the episode because I wouldn't know if it was working.
I would've just been like oh that was great Jason.
You talked for a half hour.
Episode's done but now when I record stuff as I'm recording and I can go this isn't
working for whatever reason then I gotta like re-record it.
But even that doesn't happen as often so.
Within a year I think I've come a long way skill-wise.
There's still a lot of stuff I wanna work on but yeah.
I mean that's it.
I don't... there wasn't any craziness that's happened in the past six months.
Other than the stuff that we cover on the show.
Let's go ahead and actually get started with our first story.
Now for our first story we are going to England.
The year is 2014 so not too long ago.
There's an old man.
Actually not that old.
He's only 62 years old.
That's old to you if you're young.
When you're 42 that's not old anymore but there's a 62 year old man laying in a bed
in Britain.
And they're like old man whose name we can't disclose because of medical privacy laws.
Just hang on a little bit longer.
I can't.
There's a scientist doctor dude doing stuff in another laboratory.
Doctors like going over these readings and stuff like that.
And he's like I got it.
I know what's making him sick so he's running through the hospital.
Get out of the way nurses.
Move out of the way burn victims.
I got a person to tell something to because it's too late to actually save this person.
This person is eventually gonna die but the scientist doctor kicks in the door and goes
I got it.
I know what's killing you and he's like thanks a lot.
Is there a cure?
And they're like no no there's no cure but I thought you would want to know what killed
you.
He's like I'd rather have a cure.
So this man who they haven't named we'll call him Seamus.
We'll call him Seamus and the reason we'll become clear in a second.
So Seamus in 2009 he was diagnosed with this thing called hypersensitivity pneumoniumitis.
I know how to say pneumonia this had a couple extra little vowels at the end of it.
Hypersensitivity pneumitis.
And what happens is this horrible lung disease where you're basically like getting in mold
and stuff into your lungs and it's causing your immune system to basically attack your
own body so it just completely scars up the inner sides, the inner side.
It completely scars up the insides of your lungs.
So this gross little like it's basically remembered that movie Osmosis Jones that but it's a
horror movie.
They're crawling in you and they're like making Osmosis Jones shoot your own lungs.
He's like I'm doing such a good job as you're like slowly unable to breathe.
So Seamus has this disease and they can't figure out what it is.
The doctors are like okay well we know what causes this it's mold.
So let's go to your house.
So they go to his house and they're like checking for mold and they're like no there's no mold
here do you keep pigeons.
Are you a pigeon is that one of your hobbies is playing with pigeons and he's like no.
I don't like pigeons who collects pigeons.
I mean I know they don't collect pigeons they raise pigeons they're not running around the
neighborhood like throwing nets on random pigeons but I know Mike Tyson plays around
with pigeons and stuff like that just seems such a like a weird hobby.
A pigeon person is the male equivalent basically Mike Tyson's a cat lady but with birds.
So anyways he's not a pigeon person.
He they they go do you do you have any birds around you because bird poop can also cause
this disease and he's like no I don't they're like do you smoke.
This guy didn't smoke he didn't smoke.
His lungs are grossly inflamed the doctors don't even like doing tests on him anymore
because they look so gross but this guy's not getting any better.
He's like you know what I'm gonna go on a trip I'm gonna go on a trip and I'm gonna
leave this hobby behind and the doctors are like what hobby he's like oh no I'll tell
you about that hobby later this hobby I'll leave behind.
I'm going to Australia for three months and the doctors are like okay hope you feel better
and they're just kind of like that poor sabby's not gonna feel better.
He goes to Australia feels great gets better actually starts to recover from this horrible
horrible disease can breathe again comes back starts his hobby back up and immediately
gets worse eventually gets the point that he can't walk more than 65 feet without having
to sit down and take a break that's how much he couldn't breathe and the doctors the whole
time could not figure out what it was but the doctors the whole time although they did
check his house for mold and they did check his bird his bird cages make sure he had none
wasn't hanging out with the pigeons on the roof they did notice he had quite an odd
and annoying hobby it was playing the bagpipes.
Every day he played the bagpipes he had this really nice bagpipe and it was a synthetic
bag now the old bagpipes had leather bags that every day you have to treat the leather
to keep it loose but as technologies moved on people have moved on to the synthetic bags
so you don't have to do that I mean you're recommended to clean them but you don't have
to do this daily treatment for them he played the bagpipes every single day until he went
to Australia for three months didn't bring his bagpipe with him got better came back
to the UK first playing Lance he unpacks his bags he's like oh I missed you honey as he's
hugging the bagpipe starts playing it again gets worse now it wasn't until he was basically
on his deathbed that the doctor said hmm let's look in the bagpipe is full of mold super
gross it was basically his lungs in a portable form which technically his lungs are portable
because they're moving around with him but you know what I mean like what was in his
lungs was in this bagpipe so he's blown into the bagpipe all these years and you probably
cleaned it out occasionally but not as much as you would need to because the synthetic
bag just holds all that gross disgust can you imagine how gross that cut open that I'm
getting kind of sick just thinking about it cutting open a bagpipe bag and just seeing
all like that growth and bacteria from him spitting into it for years whether he cleaned
it once a year or he didn't clean it all enough stuff gross stuff was able to breed in there
all of his breath and wet liquidy mouth stuff so I was the word I'm looking for hanging
out in here growing civilizations rise and fall within his bagpipe bag as bacteria and
mold just conquered that hole basically to them that was their universe so but but then
some of them decided to start a space program and flew into his mouth and then he became
colonized as well so he did pass away and this is now been called bagpipe lung and they've
had to warn people specifically people who use synthetic bagpipe bags clean them as often
as you can because otherwise you can have some horrible horrible problem but let's go
ahead and move on to our next story now our next story here is going to take us to the
magical magical year of 1976 the year I was born so in 1976 in January it's a cold Vegas
night let's go to Las Vegas guys heading out to Las Vegas city that never sleeps little
tiny town in the middle of Nevada basically one long strip I've been there a couple times
I think I've only been there once but technically I took an airplane so I flew out of there and
then I came back I've been a Reno quite a lot but Las Vegas is just like a big road
with a bunch of shiny buildings on it I don't know I saw it in Conair and casino so or did
casino take place in Reno it doesn't matter the point is is that we're in Las Vegas gambling
Mecca of the world we're in a car we're actually going to be in the car with this dude we're
all crowded into the back it's me you and Johnny Sands now Johnny Sands you don't know who
he is I had to look him up because I didn't know who he is but he knows who he is he's
an up and coming country musician now we'll spoiler alert the fact the story takes place
in 1976 and you don't know who this guy is should tell you the trajectory of his career
but in 1976 the whole world was open to Johnny Sands Native American kid turns into country
western singer actually made his bones doing stunt work for western shows and now he is
out to make his career as a country western singer he's getting ready to release his first
album he's in Vegas doing a couple shows and doing radio spots for his album but this
night he's just driving through Vegas just driving through the desert to get to Vegas
or to leave Vegas that basically the whole place is one big desert you can turn down
an alleyway and all of a sudden you're in shrubs it's a horrible horrible hellscape
but he's driving through the desert and he sees a blimp overhead and you know whatever
like I'm always fascinated by blimps I mean at least for the first two minutes I see one
and then I just go back to do whatever I was doing but they are kind of fascinating air
vehicles but in 1976 whatever he's like it's not 1932 this isn't the world's fair I've
seen a blimp before he sees a blimp doesn't really pay it any mind he has moves to make
he's got stuff to do but as the blimp gets closer overhead it's behind him his car starts
to die and he's like dang never oh man I know I should have gotten the extended warranty
on this car because now what I'm gonna do I'm out in the middle of nowhere and my car
is broken down and he gets out of the car and he goes over and he's like checking the
gas tank he's like kick it I read this in multiple articles it says that Johnny Sands
kicked the car so he can hear if the gas was swarming around in the gas tank I'm thinking
who is this guy the Hulk how can you kick a car so hard that you actually hear liquid
inside of it moving two articles said he kicked the car it's like that's okay so right there
I was a little suspicious of his story I've never I've heard of kicking the tires before
but I've never heard someone go hey how much gas you have in your car and then a dude just
goes ah he goes a quarter of a tank so anyways Johnny Sands he's able to kick his car hard
enough to determine he does have gas in his tank he then goes to work on his engine because
he's like well I kicked the car so that's not the problem and he's like kicking the
hood open he's like doing he's punching the engine he's like I don't know why these spark
plugs aren't working but as all that's going on we're just sitting in the car we're not
helping this dude we're actually a little scared because when he kicked the car with
us in it I felt the liquids in my own body move I go oh my god I drank too much water
today gotta go bathroom now so as he's working on the car though he realizes that the vehicle
has now passed overhead and it's not a blimp it's not a blimp now we knew it wasn't a blimp
because this is a story from the intro about a UFO abduction but he still sees it as like
a disc type shape flies overhead and he notices that it seems to have windows on the side
and it has and it has red and white lights flashing on each end and that's a funny detail
when I read that I thought that's something that a earthbound ship does red and white
lights like that's something you see on basically every plane so that made me think well this
might have been a US vehicle but it's just the red and white lights is such a mundane
detail it was also a rusty orange color now Johnny Sands is quite the colorful character
he's basically a down home country boy and so it makes sense that his ufo encounter he
sees it the color of a beat up Ford truck rusty orange UFO that is basically the general
lead that is basically like a trailer park truck color his ufo encounter is with this
thing and he flies overhead and he's like oh whoa that's kind of cool but he goes back
to working on his car because he really wants to get out of there and he's still thinking
it's a blimp but at that point his headlines turn on so he kicks the hood shut and starts
to walk back into the car but he's paralyzed you can't move but before he gets paralyzed
sorry I forgot this part before he gets paralyzed he turns and looks down the desert road when
the headlights came back on the headlights come back on he looks down the road and then
he's like better get back in my car now now he gets paralyzed and as he's paralyzed he sees
these two humanoids walking towards him from the craft so he said he has the aliens
like one of them stayed farther back but one of them approached him and he described him
as having the body of like a young fit man like just like a nowadays we'd say you know
he had the body of Ryan Reynolds as alien at the body of Ryan Reynolds young fit man
back then he would have said the guy had the body of who's deal with the big mustache not
Magnum PI not Bruce Willis because he did not he's never had a mustache he was Bert Reynolds
Bert Reynolds so imagine this alien with a burly Bert Reynolds body because 1976 that
was young and fit back then nowadays that's like monstrous man who why aren't there big
actors anymore why are all the actors super like lean like even the muscular ones are
super lean whatever happened to the Schwarzenegger's and the Stallone's they got replaced by the
Jean-Claude's like we need another like giant action star maybe not even action star we
just need like a giant even if he's in a romantic comedy not like Andre the giant giant but
we need more buff actors I want equal representation as a possibly buff man myself someday I want
to see my future self represented in the movies get to it Hollywood we need more buff men
so anyway that aside Bert Reynolds body but Johnny Sands says this about the aliens head
this is interesting exact quote but in his face facial structure I don't know something
gave me the idea that this guy was a 300 or 400 years old was very powerful face not ugly
powerful looking and that's kind of interesting he goes on a couple times in his descriptions
he talks about I know what powerful looks like when he goes into like he's like listen
I grew up on a reservation I've been around people who were like spiritually touched and
new things greater than I could ever hope to know and that's what these aliens look like
they just looked like they had the secrets the universe in them and the powerful powerful
and you're like calm down calm down dude powerful one of these articles actually is just a straight
interview with him and it's a hoot but so he's saying that they they looked like these
adonises from the neck down but they're and he's saying they weren't ugly they just looked
so knowledgeable they looked ancient but they also did kind of have wrinkles and stuff like
that this is how we describe them they were bald they were they were tall too they were
his height and they were bald no eyelash there was no facial hair whatsoever so no eyelashes
no brows no whiskers nothing now they wore black skin tight suits like basically unitards
from the wrist all the way down to the ankles and I've as I've been looking into more alien
abduction stuff it's so bizarre almost all of them to wear unitards almost all aliens
wear unitards I wonder how come there's no aliens wearing togas is it have something
to do with the way that they travel or is it just an easy detail to make up if you're
making up a story I don't know but there has to be some reason why they're always wearing
his unitards but he said that the suit was skin tight black so you can see they're perfectly
carved Burt Reynolds muscles he could see each hair pressed up against the tight tight
suit he said that it looked smooth but when he touched it because at one point one of
them brushed up against him uh-huh Johnny was like trying to make the moves on this
dude the aliens like stop it but no we come in peace get your hands off me he grabbed
he touched he didn't grab sorry he pressed up against the alien and the suit felt like
sandpaper so even though it looked super smooth it actually was quite coarse all of this going
on they had black eyes with white pupils so little little uh inhuman eyes something you
don't normally see a flatten nose a small mouth a little slit mouth that didn't move
when they spoke so these ones are again working on some sort of telepathy type stuff and very
interesting detail they had gills they had little gills on the side of their neck that
would constantly move constantly move so basically fish gills maybe like farther up
like on the head area but they're basically very visible there and but they still had
a nose and a mouth and all that stuff so there's this whole thing where they're basically asking
him like what are you doing here they ask him what are you doing here even though they
just flew over in their Chevy pickup landed paralyzed him and they go what are you doing
here and he's like I'm here promoting a music album it just the dude is so down to earth
like assuming this story is true he's meeting extraterrestrials for the first time and
they go it'd be the equivalent of someone goes take me to your leader and he's like
Trump you want to know about Trump why he's making America great again you better come
on down come to the White House like just instead of just being like whoa whoa whoa
wait a second your aliens he just goes into his sales pitch they go what are you doing
here and he's like well I'm in Vegas to sell my album you know I'm a country singer and
I got stuff to do I got moves to make I got moves make you're sitting here you're busting
my car I gotta go I don't know why he had a New York accent all of a sudden but anyways
and he said I I said that I didn't go off in that whole monologue of the Jason just made
up but he did say I'm a country Western singer I'm here promoting an album and he says the
aliens acted like they understood what I was talking about like that they understood what
a country singer was and things like that it was so odd now he doesn't reveal a lot of
what these aliens say because they told him don't tell anyone what we talk about he did
ask him questions like are you with the military and they said no but for the most part he
doesn't really reveal a lot of stuff about what was said now again this happened 42 years
ago so some of it has come out but he said they told me not to say anything and we'll
get to kind of a loophole in that later on but he's given us just a little bit of the
questions now I think of what's so funny so he's meeting these aliens and when he first
meets these aliens because again this is 1976 so we've had UFO culture around for about
20 years at this point he had all the movies and you had all the stories of these little
green men and all this stuff he says this is one of his great quotes well I'm not discriminating
nobody because I'm not wanting to say that I'm the only man who has seen somebody from
outer space but I do have a little bit of a problem with some of the stories that I hear
because I don't think those little balloony shaped head people with green dotted eyes
and crawl around and look like pizans I think their intelligence is far beyond that look
they're not three foot high these people I seen were intelligent people you could see
wisdom in their face you could see that strength in them now I know there was a three different
accents during that dramatic reading but he brings up an interesting point so he's saying
from his point of view listen I'm not I'm gonna have to translate hillbilly now I'm
not saying I'm the only person who's ever seen an alien before but every description
I've ever heard of an alien is wrong because that's not what I saw at all and and even
if aliens did look like that it doesn't make sense because aliens seem to be so much smarter
and so much more advanced than us and they look like pissants they look like tiny little
people so anyways he ends up bidding the aliens adieu and that's just the beginning of his
adventure he ends up talking to the government he like mentions it at a news conference or
something like that he ends up like mentioning it at a news conference or mentioning it to
a reporter and then he gets connected with this aerospace lab in Nevada and they tell
him then he tells story again and I'm sure they all just thought it was super amusing
they tell him to contact the government he contacts the government and they want to do
like a lie detector test on them and interview him and at one point he says I have an album
to publicize and this is actually not good publicity for me because everyone's just gonna
think I'm a big old kook buy my album you want to buy my album general and the guy's
like fine if I buy your album will you take a lie detector test and he's like you buy
10 albums I might everyone on the basis having to buy a copy of an album he does take a lie
detector test he quote unquote passes which basically means he wasn't being deceitful I
mean the thing lie detector tests are all it doesn't necessarily mean you're telling
the truth it just means that in your mind what you're saying is true but while they're
doing all this stuff the they bring in a guy to do a sketch of the alien described as the
best artist in Vegas so I'm assuming it was a velvet artist the guy just completed velvet
Elvis and now he's doing velvet dogs playing poker he's brought in by the government to
do velvet alien and as the best artist in Vegas is doing this and Johnny Sands is like yeah
and then the guy and he was bold he was bold but he had Bert Reynolds body and they're
like oh that's interesting I can draw that pretty easily and Johnny goes and he had
Gills he had Gills and the artist starts running and he goes why does he have Gills if he has
an ear and a nose now remember this is in a government area the government's getting
the artist to come out here and do all this stuff as the artist goes why does he have
Gills if he has a mouth and a nose a member of like an attache there's like a government
observer there he goes the reason why he has Gills it's evolutionary thing they're from
a planet from the serious star system that's half water half land and so as the water tides
move across the planet sometimes they have to be under water when it's super hot sometimes
they have to be on land they're kind of like a frog an amphibious race of aliens so that
basically meant this this guy knew what these aliens were and the artist goes now imagine
you're sitting there you had just seen an alien you thought it might have been a one
off thing you asked him these questions you're in a government meeting a guy goes oh no we
totally are aware of that race they're an amphibious race we know where they're at we know why
they're like that how would you react to that Johnny Sands goes well I don't know but that
sounds good to me as it is exact quote this guy now you realize why UFOs always land in
the middle of Arkansas because if this is your most credible witness a guy just tells
you that they have knowledge of an alien civilization on another planet and what you saw is verifiably
true to the point we know why they evolved that way and you're like aww shucks anyways
so eventually he says Johnny goes listen things did start getting a little weird so I have
an old cop buddy I have an old cop buddy who has an incredibly colorful back story he's
like he fought Muhammad Ali he fought Joe Frazier but anyways he was just super weird
Johnny Sands again I have a hard time buying into a lot of this stuff Johnny Sands calls
up his cop friend he goes things are getting a little weird out here I probably use a bodyguard
and then a local television producer named Dave Dunn was like hey we're gonna do a show
about this blimp flying overhead but we're gonna make a really low budget because we
don't have a lot of money but we're gonna drive out to the desert you show us where
it's at we're gonna shoot this show and Johnny's like fine but I'm gonna bring my bodyguard
with me and Dave's like yeah sure they all get into like two cars they drive out there
together and Johnny goes this is the place where the lights are at and the car just keeps
driving and Johnny's like no no no it was back there where we were supposed to stop
and the car keeps driving pro tip if you're ever in a car in Vegas and you say hey I'm
supposed to get out here and it keeps going further into the desert it's not gonna be
a good ending for you but for this story the first car stops everyone gets out the second
car stops everyone but Johnny and his bodyguard get out they're told to stay in the car and
all these bright lights appear around the cars and Johnny's like I'm gonna go find out
what's going on because this is dumb like I need to find out what's going on and he
notices like Dave is like talking to someone who's obscured by the lights and keeps pointing
at the car with Johnny Sans and his bodyguard in it and they roll down the window a bit
and they hear Dave Dunn goes what are we supposed to do he knows too much he knows too much
and they're like uh oh this is not good and at that point Johnny Sans is like I'm gonna
give him I'm gonna give him an old one too from a country boy and as he goes to open
the this is so as he goes to open the door to get out to confront the men behind these
bright lights in the middle of the Las Vegas desert he describes two two of these big like
just balls of fur they're like three feet tall giant balls of hair like cousin it from
the Anna's family come running out of the desert and slam against the car and hold the
door shut so he can't get out so now he's in the car with this bodyguard he's looking
at these two big balls of hair looking at him through the window and the bodyguard goes
are you still gonna get out and the most sensible thing Johnny Sans has done since the beginning
of this he said no I'm just gonna stay in the car and then eventually the furry people
left and Dave Dunn gets in the car and the cars just right back drop him off at the hotel
the next day when Johnny and his bodyguard went to Dave Dunn's production office to
find out what the hell happened the night of last night because no one said anything
on their way back who the furry people were what was going on they go to the production
office they had been to multiple times throughout the course of this whole that that Dave Dunn
story was actually like quite like weeks long they go to the production office no one's
there it's been completely cleaned out and the woman who rented the office out said no
one has no one's been in there for a while Dun Dun Dunn Dave Dunn that producer died
a thousand years ago Dunn it was this weird like he says that Dave Dunn was basically
one of the men in black and they were trying to figure out what to do with him but what's
weird about that story is they should have taken care of him months ago because he'd
already spread the story all over the place so where are we at now with the saga of Johnny
Sands Johnny Sands has done interviews since he basically says the men in black the guys
who were doing the Dave Dunn and all that stuff one of the first things they wanted me to
do was write a song about the aliens write it in one day had a hurry up and write a song
and I did I never released it and then I feel like all of the stuff the aliens told me has
kind of passed the statute of limitations like enough time has passed I think I can do it
so I am right I'm gonna release my song about the aliens I'm gonna spread their message
to the world and you can find it on my website myspace.com/JohnnySandsMusic with this album
we can finally have the message out about the aliens it's time it's time to let you
guys know what they said the interview kind of wrapped up with the interviewer saying
you know do you ever like think but you still think about this and Johnny Sands is like all
the time sometimes I just walk out of my house I throw my hands up in the air I look up at
the sky and say come back friends come back I want to talk to you now that's a kind of
a common thing we've seen with other alien and counter stories in the past people like
want to reach out and touch someone but of course your main question is Jason you listen
to the music right you found some of Johnny Sands stuff you listen to this alien song
right for this story it's gone deleted lost who knows Johnny Sands music is still up on
myspace page there's absolutely no songs listed there the only song I can find of him
with some honky-tonk song about Elvis there's always that saying they should have sent a
poet I think they're specifically talking about going to space for the first time they
said they should have sent a poet because that person could really use the language
to explain the beauty of what is going on and whether or not you enjoy country music
Johnny Sands is a poet he uses his words to create art until evoke emotions how many times
do we have artists encounter aliens it's not very often not very often at all so when
one does I think it's fascinating in his narrative that the men in black have him write a song
about what he went through very shortly to they didn't want him to overthink it they just
want him to put it out there right now just write it and he wrote it and he performed
it for him and I'm sure he made them buy his cassette but where is that song now was it
just another rinky dink tune from a guy who tried making it as a country western singer
and never really lived up to that potential or did that song contain truths artists are
immortalized by their work whether or not you're a famous artist or an obscure artist
what you create is your legacy Johnny Sands legacy is just a few interviews now a few
MP3's floating around the internet and a dead page on Myspace but the song that he wrote
on orders of a shady governmental organization is part of his legacy as well we may not be
able to hear it but this song that included first impressions of an alien encounter written
by a poet may be in some government archive somewhere just filed away with a little tag
on it Sands comma Johnny Desert Encounter 1976 we'll never be able to hear that song
but hopefully Johnny found some peace knowing that he became one of the most famous musicians
in the world of UFOs dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going to be your email address you can
also hit us up at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio twitter is @jasonocarpenter dead rabbit
radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast you don't have to listen
to it every day but I'm glad you listen to it today have a great one guys.
(upbeat music)