An entire island of Girl Scouts sounds like probably the most uninteresting place most
of us could ever imagine to be trapped, but to the spirit of one woman, it's her only
hope of finding some sort of peace.
And then we travel to Ashland, Oregon to take a look at the story of a young woman who was
out walking her dog late at night.
This young woman always considered herself a very practical, pragmatic, logical person,
but when she senses an unknowable danger staring at her from the darkness, she has no idea
what's coming next.
Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Garvin here, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a
great day too, I hope you guys are having tons of fun doing whatever you're doing.
The birthday presents are still rolling in for your favorite podcast host.
I'm sure Mark Marin might be his birthday too, but I'm talking about me.
I'm still getting them in and someone who just sent me a very deadly birthday present
walking into Dead Rabbit Command right now.
Everyone give it up for Christina Belk.
Woohoo!
Yeah, come on in Christina, she's sitting there, she's juggling knives.
This person who listens to my podcast, she says she's been listening to my podcast for
quite a while now, a couple years.
She started to buy me a knife, she's buying me a Smith and Wesson combat blade now, we
shouldn't blame Christina for my upcoming injury, okay, no one's blaming her.
I did put it on my Amazon wish list and she sent me this amazing note saying that her
roommate, Dirk Groberman, that's a long time listener, I remember Dirk Groberman back
in the day, introduced me to your show a couple years ago and I've been listening every day
since.
Christina Belk decided to buy me the knife that I one day just put on my Amazon wish
list and didn't think anyone would ever get it's a wish, right?
I already dropped it and I almost impaled my foot.
So thank you Christina Belk for buying me the weapon of my upcoming massive injury.
Christina you're gonna be the captain of the pilot this episode, she also said she
loved the vehicles.
You guys can't swear to Patreon, you don't have to buy me a weapon that'll injure myself
no it's not, I put it on my wish list.
You can't swear to Patreon if you can't buy me deadly weapons that's fine too, just
help spread the word about the show.
That really, really really helps out a lot.
Now before we get started I do want to say this too, I don't like having a lot of intro
stuff in the beginning but this is super important.
The Dead Rabbit Radio YouTube channel has once again been suspended and listen, it's
YouTube's thing, they can do what they want, they really wanted this video down.
It was the episode I did about Aquarium Gate and originally they said I was promoting violence
and so I appealed it and then they said I was being a cyber bully.
So they just didn't want the video out.
I have a one week suspension, I can't upload anything anyways but going forward we will
not be uploading the podcast to the YouTube channel.
We're gonna keep all the past content there, that was an old episode, that episode came
out probably about two months ago.
All of a sudden their AI didn't want that episode up there.
I can't also say I think it was a lot about AI control conspiracy theories but they don't
want it up there, fine, they took it down, I got a strike, I can't upload for a week,
fine, whatever, that's their right.
But I don't, I'm just not gonna upload to YouTube anymore, it's going to be strictly
a podcast and what we're gonna do, we're gonna see how this works is I'm gonna put up a note
each time an episode comes out because I still want to talk to you guys, that's why I like
the, that's really the main reason why I uploaded to YouTube.
So we can talk about the episodes so I can see your comments and get your feedback and
I can talk to you guys about stuff.
So we're gonna see how that goes but no more episodes are gonna be uploaded, I'm gonna
lean more into the TikTok as far as anything and then I'll probably upload shorts but
YouTube may nuke it because of the shorts as well, I really want to keep it up to do
live streams but I'm not going to, it would suck if it went, I'll be honest, it would
suck if the YouTube channel got taken down completely because that's four years of conversation
between us.
Right, that's the episodes you can find anywhere but the comments and the conversations we've
had and the laughs and everything like that, that'll be gone.
That'll bum me out if the YouTube channel gets taken down completely but going forward,
no more full episodes on YouTube but they'll still be available everywhere else to hear
them, hopefully we can get a little community post that we can comment on, we'll see how
it goes but I can't play by the YouTube rules because YouTube rules are super strict, we
can't talk about blood, we can't talk about killing or murder, that's all you ever talk
about that in diarrhea.
A lot of true crime YouTube to avoid the filter, they'll say stuff like he unalived her.
I'm not gonna do that dude, I'm not gonna do that, I'm not gonna do that, I'm not gonna
do that people will say he "graped" her, just say "raped dude."
I mean like if you're gonna talk about the subject, say kill, say rape, I won't play
by that and I'm not a cyber bully.
Okay there might be a couple of episodes that you can say well Jason.
Anyways, I'm not gonna play by the YouTube rules, those rules are set up, those are valid
rules for them and many many other content creators, we're not gonna do that.
I don't wanna water down the podcast so I can just be on YouTube.
I wanna be a podcast, I wanna be a podcast talking about what we talk about.
So sorry about that long intro but I can tell Christina's getting bored, she is getting
ready to throw that knife at me.
Christina let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the Jason jet.
We're gonna leave behind Dead Ravica Man and take us all the way out to Lake Yosemite.
Jason jet is rumbling across the west coast, splitting the blue sky in half.
Leaving Kimtrails, you didn't know that?
You didn't know that the Jason jet, we also lease out to the US government to drop Kimtrails.
We're headed all the way out to Lake Yosemite which is in Merced, California.
Beautiful lakes, like all lakes are, I don't ever think there's like an ugly lake.
Right, am I gonna be able to prove me wrong?
They're like oh here's a lake of raw sewage.
Okay you're right, a lake of nothing but raw sewage would prove me wrong but this, I
think that's a fair thing to say that Lake Yosemite is beautiful, I've never seen it,
I'm sure it's beautiful.
But anyways, it was many decades ago, many many decades ago.
Like 50s, 60s probably.
It was a hot summer.
But people are like running along the beach in slow motion.
They think that they're sick, they're like why can't we run fast?
They're running along the beach in slow motion, there's probably like a dude sitting there,
I'm assuming at any beach you'll find a guy sitting there.
And then you have a mother and her two young children enjoying the hot summer air and then
jumping in the cool water.
And that real kind of combining of the elements.
Splash, look at me, mommy I'm swimming.
One of the kids says, the mom goes that's the best swim I've ever seen and then the other
kid goes I can swim better than that.
Splash.
The mom's like yeah the first one was better.
A mom and her two kids go swimming and these two kids they kind of like, they're adventurous
right?
Super adventurous, they go why don't we climb to the top of that boat tower and jump off
of it into the water.
No I don't think it was like a, I don't know how tall this thing was right, I think a boat
tower would try to stretch the key detail in the story, I don't look it up but.
A boat tower I'm assuming is some sort of tower, you guys can't correct me in the YouTube
comments on this one so I can say whatever I want.
A boat tower I believe is probably some sort of structure near a pier, right?
So anyways it doesn't matter, these two kids climb up a boat tower and they go mom look
at us we're king and queen of the world.
One of them's a girl and they both jump off of the boat tower but they didn't realize
the key detail.
The water was really shallow where they were at.
So when they jumped off the boat tower the first kid smashes his head into the rocks
and instantly breaks his neck like that's how shallow the water is, I don't know how
they didn't see this.
Maybe the boat tower is pretty tall or maybe they're idiots.
And the second kid, this would suck right, you're at the top of a structure and you see
a dude jump off, you know a couple seconds before you do right and you're jumping off
too and now you're seeing him fall, now at this point he's probably like four or five
feet ahead of you and you watch him splash into the water and then see his neck snap.
And you have about .8 seconds before the same thing happens to you, that would be the worst
right?
I've always said being eaten by a cannibal isn't the worst thing, the second person to
be eaten by a cannibal is the worst thing.
Cause you can watch the first guy get pooped out of the cannibal, that was a very specific
cannibal related episode.
I can't believe YouTube doesn't want this show up there.
It would be bad enough to smash into the water and break your neck but to be the second person
like watching that guy break his neck and be like oh no.
Anyways, no matter what the order was, the mother was, besides herself obviously right,
she just saw her two children jump into the water and snap both their necks.
Well she is like totally freaking out, people see this and the authorities are alerted.
This is decades ago so someone had to go find a pay phone, I'm sure there was one nearby,
I don't think they were on their speed boat and went back to shore but the authorities
showed up and by that time the kids had floated away due to the current of the river or the
lake that we're in, I don't know why the mom didn't scoop them up immediately, maybe
she was so terrified.
Anyways, the kids floated away and the authorities get there and they never found the bodies.
They never found the bodies of these two kids who broke their necks in the lake.
So for years, the mother, the spondan, she watched her two children die in front of her
every day they say.
She would go to this lake and she would walk around being like kids where are you?
Kids, kids and she would walk around the beach not expecting her kids to say something back
and she just wanted to find their bodies, she wanted to put their bodies to rest but she
could never find them and people say to this day as you're driving down Old Lake Road late
at night you may see the phantom of a young mother walking down the street crying out
for her children crying out for children she couldn't even find in death.
Which is a creepy component to the story.
That's not all, we're still going to hang out at the lake because there's another even
creepier ghost story here.
But obviously there's an element of urban legend to this, we don't have specific names,
it's like we don't know when this took place, la la la la la.
We've covered these, these are the ghost stories that kind of border into urban legends but
there is something particularly terrifying if you think like the children, and this seems
to be, I never thought about this before because I come across this a lot in Ghost Lore where
you have a lover die or the children die whatever in this area and then the forlorn woman is
walking around looking for her lost lover, his head got blown off during the Civil War
and she went to the battlefield and she couldn't find him and now her spirit still walks around
or in this case and this is a very popular trope as well, the kids dying, the mother still
walking around the house or walking through the forest or at this point walking down the
shore looking for her lost children and you think it's terrifying that they don't even
find the spirits in death because the kids died, it's not like the kids are still alive,
they just swam to the other shore and they're like we're gonna have a new life together,
the children died in this location, the mom's looking for them in this location but she
still can't find them even though at this point they're all dead.
And obviously this is that type of ghost that could be just a recording, right someone's
in so much misery, someone has so much heartache that they soaked the environment with their
psychic residue so it's not a ghost you could interact with, it's just a ghost walking on
the street screaming for her children.
But then there's also the option, this one's a little scary or I think in Ghost Lore there's
that idea of not having a fullfiled your mission on earth, having something you've always wanted
to achieve and not being able to achieve it.
The children didn't have that, right the children broke their necks and they're like well that's
sucked, I'm supposed to go to Tommy's birthday party tomorrow but whatever I have a broken
neck what am I gonna do?
And then they go to heaven, they don't have these long drawn out heartaches and I don't
know what to do without my kids blah blah blah because they are the kids right?
So they both break their necks and they have a race to heaven look at me I'm the fastest
angel around come back Bobby I'm the fastest they go to heaven.
But the mom never went to the afterlife right?
The mom is so torn up about losing her kids that had she, this isn't her therapy podcast
right?
But had she accepted the loss and moved on maybe she would have gone to heaven that's
super not nice I'm trying to think of the right word for it right?
It's super not nice but you know like the fact that Callis was the word I was looking
for she could have accepted that they had moved on and then when she died she had moved
on herself.
You know what I mean like had she accepted it maybe her spirit would have moved on as
well that's actually now that I'm saying that's super Callis right?
It's super Callis but in this particular event not in any other event not in anything you
might be going through it is like had she accepted that and moved on not like found
other kids.
Actually that's a good segue for our next one.
Let's go ahead before I take myself into a bigger hole with my brand new knife.
Christina let's hop in the dead rabbit row boat we're gonna row row row on out we're
still at Lake Yosemite out to Girl Scout Island.
Splashy splashy rowing those oars all the way out to Girl Scouts Island now it's called
Scouts Island.
Now it's no longer Girl Scouts so I don't know if the Boy Scouts are finally allowed
there I don't know if the war has ceased they have made peace on this island but Scouts
Island if you want to check it out now again we have a story that goes back very urban legend
as far as the lore goes we don't know when this took place we don't know the names of
people but this one this one has an interesting twist to it.
Back on back in the let's say the let's let's update this one let's say this back in the
90s right back in the 1990s a mother and her daughter were at.
Girl Scout Island and while all the other Girl Scouts were asleep and I'm assuming
the scout masters is that what they're called Girl Scout Masters when the Girl Scouts and
their masters are asleep this mom she goes hey you know what you know what dear daughter
of mine you've done so good raising yourself without breaking your neck I'm going to reward
you with a trip a moonlight stroll in this row boat I happen to have so the mother and
the daughter get on the row boat and she's rowing out into Lake Yosemite and a whirlpool
appears and the water starts going around and around and the boat starts spinning around
and around they didn't see this apparently this is something that can happen naturally
or not a whirlpool just appears Ursula's down there she's like ah yes more kelp more kelp
for my army a whirlpool a whirlpool appears and the boat starts spinning around and the
daughter fly like falls out of the boat ah and she gets sucked in by the whirlpool now
this whirlpool is so like strong it actually flips the boat as well so now the mom is swimming
in the darkness she's screaming for help her daughter is underwater there's no there's
no married badge for how to survive a whirlpool right and she's trying to rescue her daughter
but she can't in the darkness of the lake she can't even find her but eventually she
does this is one where the she didn't she didn't turn into kelp she didn't turn into
a piece of seaweed her dead body simply floated to the surface but the mother also was still
completely freaked out about this and through the rest of her life was always looking for
her daughter right I mean she knew where she was she was buried in some sort of cemetery
but I think she was quite the point where she was crazy no one was like hey I know you're
really looking for Margaret you might want to go down to clear valley green the cemetery
she's buried at no she would walk around Girl Scouts Island looking for her daughter until
she died and now she's a ghost on Girl Scout Island so today this is how the ghost story
goes in modern times what will happen is you will be sleeping in your tent this you can
rent out this island for like 50 bucks a night but it says you have to be a kid like kids
you have a credit card it has to only be for like kid slash scouting events so we couldn't
do it that would be dope to rent out an island that seems pretty reasonable 50 bucks to own
an island for a night like Jason you don't get to own it you don't get to build a house
build a house in one night but you know like just camp on an island for 50 bucks it's cheaper
than a hotel anyways I'm not a scout so I can't do it but the scouts can 50 bucks a night
that sounds super reasonable now that you think about it because you pay 50 bucks and
then you fill it with as many scouts as you can like you have just all standing up you
could have hundreds of them on this island anyways I put my master plan into the side
you have Scout Island and they'll say late at night when the Girl Scouts are sleeping
in their tent the zipper of their tent this is so terrifying the zipper of their tent
will go zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz
I can't imagine if you were a kid if you were an adult and your tent unzipped and a ghost
stuck their head in your tent I imagine just everyone immediately would run out through
the ghost get ectoplasm all over you I don't think you'd be like I'm gonna see where this
goes and then she crawls in she's brushing her hair singing songs you're like Jason that
sounds way more pleasant than running through a ghost woman and getting covered in ectoplasm
here's my theory with this story there is a real issue in the ghost community where
I believe because we have seen this we've seen psychics make this mistake a lot as well
you'll have an actual haunting you'll have an actual ghost in an area and then people
go where did this ghost come from who is this ghost and they will make up a story they will
fill in the details so they'll say well this ghost looks like dressed in pioneer woman's
clothes in the middle of Nebraska she's in this old house let's see what we can find
in the family records oh a woman died in this house back in the period of close that I say
I already forgot pioneers that what I said pilgrim walks in big old hat buckled shoes
and you go oh that he must have died on Thanksgiving Eve he didn't even get a slice of that turkey
we make up the details and we'll put together kind of like shoddy research and things like
that we tell a story so when this ghost woman is sticking her head in the tent we don't have
the name of the woman who this happened to we don't have a year we don't know when this
kid died all this stuff so it's possible that there is a ghost on Girl Scout this also possible
this is a made up story to scare Girl Scouts into going to sleep but if there is a ghost
on Girl Scout Island unzipping your tent and sticking their head inside the idea of her
being a mother who lost her kid we don't know if any of that's true we've seen this before
in ghost stories where people make up the past this might be some crazy perverted woman ghost
like who has some horrible hair fetish and a singing fetish they always wanted to be
on American Idol who knows like this you think it's like oh a loving mother who lost her
daughter so now she's going to play with your daughter's hair but if if you were like walking
down the street and somebody walked up to your daughter and started brushing her hair you
would be like dude get away and you're like whoa my daughter died I just want to brush
your daughter's hair you'd be like okay that's horrible and also your maniac stay away from
my kid like even if the origin story is real it's kind of creepy but what if this ghost
just has like this weird like Girl Scout hair fetish or something like that like who's to
say that that's the actual backstory and they either don't know or you want to tell a kid
that right so I was like hey I saw a ghost in my tent last night and I brushed my hair
in the cub of master or whatever they're called will be like that was a friendly ghost that
was a friendly ghost and just listen I'm not talking about it anymore because they would
know it was a big old pervert ghost who knows right it's probably the first one it's probably
a mother who lost her daughter but I read that and I go who knows like isn't that creepy
like your tent gets zipped up and a woman sticks her head in and she's looking around
your tent and like what if she just really has like some insidious backstory like some
horribly dark origin and you don't know you go oh that's just the kindly mother who lost
her daughter and you're like do you want to come in our tent and she like slowly walks
in I mean I guess despite what her creepy origin story may be the worst she does is brush
your hair but maybe she does a bad job maybe have all these knots in your hair you're like
ah and she sings terrible songs you're like oh no no more clay aching please Christina
let's go ahead and toss you the keys to the world famous carbonicopter we are leaving
behind Girl Scout Island bumping a little clay ache in ourselves as we're flying out
take us all the way out to Ashland Oregon hi the friend long time listeners of the show
know I have a friend named Sabine we hang out a lot but it's funny because we couldn't
be more different as far as this subject matter goes for this podcast right she is super pragmatic
to the point that I think she completely ignores things like evidence evidence stuff I imagine
when Fox Mulder and Dana Scully were doing like assignments he Fox Mulder probably got
really really irritated at Scully a lot because like an alien would be shooting him with lasers
and she's like I don't know they could just be mirrors and it could be the sun bouncing
off the mirrors and the sun could have put a baby in my stomach and then abducted the
baby Scully come on like obviously there's aliens and ghosts and stuff like that you
see it every night now I'm not that irritated at Sabine but it's so interesting we went
to go see that movie the Northman together which is like a fantasy film I expected it
to be like a historical drama like 300 but no it's a fantasy film where the characters
like the great Norse gods actually have their fingers in the plot they're doing things and
at one point this old woman gets wrapped up in the intestines of a man like she's literally
like suspended from the ceiling like a yo-yo and I was like oh dude Odin doesn't mess around
he really wanted to wrap up that old witch it was a witch with organs and she's like
oh must have been a guy who did what I'm gonna possibly have done that there was no one around
to do that the star the Northman Charles North he also had a sword that he got from a zombie
that could only be pulled out of its sheath at night I go well how did you didn't you
think it was weird that every time someone tried to pull it out during the day it wouldn't
pull out but then at night he could pull it out kill a bunch of people she's like I can
she didn't pay attention to that part apparently she's like oh I don't remember that I don't
remember that key line so she's super pragmatic and but that's the type of person Sabine is
super pragmatic super practical now she also says her house is haunted so she believes
in ghosts and she doesn't take like human medicine she takes like thorn whistle and like peacock
juice or whatever you know like all that hippie-dippy homeopathic stuff as well so she believes
that hippies can apparently cure pain even though western medicine can she believes in
ghosts but she doesn't believe in monsters she doesn't believe in wizards she's like
chasing animal even that stuff in her now you're on the further extreme super pragmatic
person and really throughout her life you know she says I live in a haunted house better
than that other than that insane claim now I didn't think about it she's I guess she's
not that practical but out of her entire life there is one story that she simply can't explain
and very very terrifying experience let's go back to the year roughly we're back in
the year 1998 Sabine is a 22 year old woman and she decides to take her dog Sage out for
a walk and where she's going is the Ashland dog park which is located on Briggs Lane
in Ashland Oregon it was a full moon out so the landscape was completely illuminated
and sage was this big giant white dog but she goes she just glowed in the moonlight
this big giant white dog she told me the breed but I don't remember it's like a yellow lab
and mixed with the similarian or mixed with something else she's mixed with the one ring
I forgot what she was mixed with but she's this big giant white dog and Sabine and sage
go out to this dog park they have to climb over a fence she rode her bike out there and
they climb over this little fence and I wasn't there but they're at this dog park and sage
is out just kind of doing what dogs do having fun in the middle of the night now Sabine
was out there for a little bit right 10 minutes 15 minutes 20 minutes she's not entirely for
sure but she was out there for a while right sage is running around and then all of a sudden
Sabine feels something and she's standing there in the darkness but the full moon is
completely lighting up the entire area she feels something out there Sabine begins to
feel that her life is in danger it's a full on from like 0 to 12 right away she's standing
out there just enjoying some time with her dog and then all of a sudden she 100% is under
the impression that something is watching her with the intent of doing her harm it's
a full on I'm about to be attacked the landscape is completely illuminated she's turning and
she's looking everywhere and she can't see any movement she can't see any silhouette
out of place the only location where she can't clearly get a good view is there's a creek
nearby there's like a little goalie and there's a creek and she immediately goes whatever wants
me is down there it's down there because it's the only place that I can't see and I clearly
know that something is in this area that wants to do me harm I feel the caveman like instinct
of survival against some sort of unknown predator I feel it I know this is going to happen and
while she is processing all of this sage begins to feel it too a sage is a good guard dog sage
has always been there it's getting in between Sabine and some sort of threat brave dog that
if it sense something was wrong it was right there before the threat could even get close
to Sabine so when sage picks up on this threat full guard dog mode activated she watches sage
as he begins to snarl showing off those massive mighty dog fangs canines actually is what
they're called but what strikes her is odd is that sage doesn't immediately run out
towards the creek because that's where the threats coming from there have been times
where Sabine is walking with her dog and sage will take off go to a bend in a trail so means
like what I want to sage come back come back and then eventually two hikers walked by and
were coming in the opposite direction and sage ran off to be able to eyeball them before
they could present a threat like sage will go to head off an assault but sage didn't
immediately run off towards the creek and that struck her is odd because she knew that's
where the threat had to be coming from there was nowhere else around her where someone
could be hiding or an animal could be hiding or anything what sage begins to do is patrol
he begins to walk in this very very wide circle around her growling snarling the entire way
Sabine's watching him walk in this giant circle and that's when she realizes this isn't coming
from the creek he would have been out there he would have put a stock to this or he would
have made sure he was there between whatever it was in her but he's on this large circular
patrol she realizes whatever this is this isn't at the creek whatever this is sage doesn't
know where it's at either Sabine's watching sage make this large patrol and she's thinking
could it be a group of people like what could this possibly be like why does he keep moving
around me like this is there a group of people a pack of animals but at this point there's
still no visual on this threat obviously have a giant white dog may kind of make someone
a little more cautious about coming out to you but where's it coming from if it was a
human sage would have been right there it was an animal sage would have been right there
but he's walking this patrol and then Sabine begins to notice that this circle is getting
smaller and smaller and smaller sage is still ready for war snarling and growling and gnashing
its teeth ready to scare off anything that comes too close and if it keeps coming to
rend flesh but the circle is getting smaller and smaller and smaller sage is worried sage
has no idea where this threat is coming from she's getting as close as he can to his master
Sabine's still standing there trying to make sense of this until eventually her great protector
this dog who was stood between her and many threats throughout the years is rubbing up
against her legs the circle has become so tight he's literally just turning a quick
circle right around her legs he's rubbing up against her and the snarling has turned
to whimpering sage is terrified he doesn't know what it is he doesn't know where it
is but he does know he can't protect Sabine so Sabine realizes this situation has completely
gotten out of control and yet she doesn't know what the situation is and she stands
there and she says to sage when I say run buddy we run Sabine yells out run and within
an instant both her and her dog are barreling full force towards that fence she has to open
it up sage runs out she hops on her bike and they both head home as fast as they can I
talked to Sabine about the story I find this so fascinating because other than the fact
that she says there's ghosts in her house she is super practical I mean like if you ask
her about aliens she'll be like yeah sure universe is a big place or anything like that
but as far as like alien abductions as far as monsters or wizards or anything else that
I talk about on a daily basis she's like she enjoys the stories right she enjoys the stories
she enjoys the weirdness but she doesn't really believe it and she's a very practical logical
person and she grew up in a very practical logical family so when she experienced this
I've at like what do you think it was and she goes I don't know she goes but I know
this it wasn't flesh and blood it was not flesh and blood I don't know what it was
but if it was something that was alive sage wouldn't have reacted like that now I could
keep throwing out stuff as like do you think it was a ghost or demon she's like just and
I don't know I don't know what it was this is very telling though because even though
when she went into that moment and when it was going on she was still thinking this is
some sort of physical threat i.e. a human or an animal but as sage's behavior got more
and more odd and she started me and able to check off every possible thing it could be
and it came to what it as far as her logical brain would say couldn't be I said I go you
were looking around to see if you could see anything and go at any point did you look
up and she says I mean almost I don't want to say like ashamed ashamed but there was
kind of like a an odd emotion when she said this I go did you look up and she kind of
paused and she's like yeah at a certain point I looked up because obviously a logical person
wouldn't think there was a UFO floating overhead right but when she had run out of options
of what it could realistically be at a certain point she looked up to see I go what did you
expect to see she was I don't know but I looked up it's a fascinating story it's a fascinating
story of an event of someone who really doesn't believe in any of this stuff ghosts sure but
some sort of like demonic force or some sort of creature cryptid something hunting you
through the darkness right aliens this kind of second day but most people believe in ghosts
is like 70% of America believes in ghosts but when you start talking about aliens visiting
earth the the percentages get much lower or cryptids monsters really existing against
very low especially monsters that can do you harm Loch Ness monster people be like sure
bigfoot maybe but when you're talking about some sort of creature in the darkness that
can hurt you it's far percentage wise far less likely that people believe in that so
it's like that would be where I was at it's funny because I've you know I'm a friend of
her so I'm able to ask her these questions I said what would you have done if sage wasn't
there she goes you know it's interesting because do you listen to that gut feeling that you're
in a dangerous situation some people do and some people don't and she goes there's the
chance that I would have had this overwhelming sense of fear that gripped her from the moment
she first sensed this until she was on her bike racing away from the dog park like it
never abated she was always felt like she was under threat she goes if I wasn't there
with sage I might have just written that off right if I have there'd be no reason for me
to be a she actually said she goes why would I go to a dog park and late at night by myself
Jason I go well just saying she goes but wasn't there was sage there's a chance that I would
have just ignored that feeling but when she saw the dog also having such weird behavior
now it's definitely real dogs don't have a sense of imagination they don't have a sense
of wonderment or fear of the unknown the dogs reacting to a definite real sensation it's
not an anxiety attack it's not paranoia the dogs reacting to it so what was that in the
darkness who knows but the story may not end there November 19th 2011 about three miles
away from this dog park there's a bike path and really they kind of intersected a lot
of points like you have the creek that kind of cuts through this entire area and the bike
path is along the creek at one point and the dog path is by the creek and you just kind
of have this creek moving through this area November 19th 2011 there was a young man named
David Grubbs a 23 year old retail employee walking along this bike path late at night
near this same creek was attacked by something so viciously it almost completely severed
his head there were no defensive wounds he was found the next morning by someone also
going down this bike path he was laying down and they thought maybe he had fallen down and
gone to sleep until they got close enough to realize that his head was almost completely
removed from his body he had no defensive wounds they have no idea what the murder weapon
was they say it was something longer than a knife originally they thought it might have
been a sword they've also thought it was a machete possibly they just don't know what
the murder weapon was to this day this murder has never been solved now if you're in a big
city you're like that doesn't even make the newspaper anymore big cities have multiple
murders a week 2011 this guy was murdered in Ashland the previous murders there was two
of them they were both like tied to these people going insane Ashland had two previous
murders in 2004 and the murder before that was in 96 so Ashland Oregon is not a place
that has a ton of murders it's where the Shakespeare festival is the murders normally
only take place on stage and the police they don't know who murdered David Grubbs and they've
actually looked at someone who took the Rennesfair you know the Renaissance fair too seriously
and attacked David with a sword with a medieval sword or it was some crazy actor right killed
him with a sword or they don't even know it's a sword they keep saying it was a long blade
they were even looking into a link that he was a big part of the online gaming community
surrounding Assassin's Creed I was like I didn't know there was a thing I know Assassin's
Creed is a thing but I didn't know there was a gaming community around it's not really
a multiplayer but they're trying to figure out what who killed this guy it's an 11 year
old case they don't know who killed him they don't know how he was killed and they say
he was a big dude they go this wasn't someone you would think would be picked for just a
random murder but yet here it is this young man nearly decapitated by what coordinate
news report seems like just one swipe didn't even know it was coming now some might say
it's some say it's tasteless to combine a real world true crime story with a bizarre event
that happened a decade earlier two decades earlier almost right some might find that
insensitive some might find that cyber bullying but that's not the point the point is is that
what is in this area like I guess it isn't sensitive because I'm going to start saying
a ghoul attack Tim put is it the same thing is there something in this area that kills
right that it's not a guy with a sword it's not a guy with a machete but it's something
far darker and really even more unexplainable than that like what what what happened to
Sabine what was something that could scare such a logical person what could be out there
like what could be what what could scare a logical person and it's not even that remember
the dog was reacting to it as well it's such a terrifying story and I don't know if the
two are related but if they very well could be they very well couldn't be very well couldn't
be but the fact that you had someone experience such a dramatic feeling of dread and doom
and fear and the dog felt it too and the dog didn't know where the energy was coming from
didn't know where the threat was coming from to the point that eventually it laid down its
mantle as protector and just wanted to leave what could possibly do that is it the same
thing that could decapitate a man in one surprise strike I'm curious if there's other events
like this out I don't know what else has gone their head chopped off but I wonder if other
people have also sensed this dark energy in this area and have maybe told the story to
their friends and their family right Sabine doesn't have a podcast or newsletter nothing
like that she would just tell this story to people she's never reported this to any ghost
hunting organization or anything like that so are there multiple stories are there multiple
encounters of something like that out there I would love to find out and is it possible
that when Sabine felt that terror and she had that dog with her and she could see the dog
was also sensing that terror that got her to leave but David walking alone when he felt
that fear he just said I'm just being paranoid I've walked this bike trail a hundred times
all be fine what hides in the darkness along the Ashland bike path who knows but this is
one demonic force I'm in no hurry to face down myself dead rabbit radio at gmail.com is going
to be our email address you can also do so at facebook.com/dead rabbit radio tick tock
is at dead rabbit radio dead rabbit radio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true
crime podcast you don't have to listen to it every day I'm glad you listened to it today
have a great one guys
you
you you
you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you
you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you
you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you
you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you
you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you
you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you
you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you you
[BLANK_AUDIO]