Is deep fake technology a threat to our democracy?
And then we look at the wild conspiracy theories about why YouTube was shut down for one hour on Tuesday night.
Yes, there are already conspiracy theories about that. Today on Dead Rabbit Radio.
[Music]
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter.
I'm having a great day generally. I hope you're having a great day too. My sinus infection is getting a little bad.
It actually hurts to talk.
So I don't know how long this episode is going to be. Usually I say they're going to be short and they still end up being a little bit longer.
But we're only gonna do two stories.
And I really, I just kind of wanted to, the stories kind of flow together and keep things simple and then I'm gonna take a nap.
First off, after I had done
World War II was faked and then
Nuclear bombs don't exist. I was like, okay, though I can't do those type of subjects anymore.
I can't talk about people who don't believe something
happened. You can vary and say, well, I have a different interpretation of that event.
But to say no, those don't exist is very hard to do those episodes.
After I got done doing those two episodes, Mitcham sends me, I'm sitting there and I get a Facebook message from my friend Mitcham.
And it's just a photo of a power line with a flyer attached to it.
It says "Birds aren't real."
"Birds aren't real.com." And my soul died a little bit and I was like, are you...
And of course, I'm thinking this is most likely real.
Like it sounds like a joke, but it's most likely real. I went to their website.
Thankfully it is a joke.
It is a joke. They have a website where you can buy merch, "Birds aren't real" shirts.
They have quotes from famous politicians and world leaders exposing the bird plot.
Thankfully, you know, it's funny though, we've reached a point in conspiracy theory that you just don't know sometime.
If you saw a guy walking around the shirt that said, "World War II never happened."
You would probably think, oh yeah, there's no- nobody on earth would believe that World War II was a ten-
Wait, I bet you had about a ten-year act from the rise of
fascism and Nazi Germany to
drop into the bombs. It was all fake. I now know that anyone can believe anything at any given time
from doing those episodes. But thanks, Mitch, for the laugh.
And I'll have the show notes if you want to buy a shirt. Birds aren't real.
Okay, so let's go ahead and jump into our first story here. Let's talk about Deepfakes.
So Deepfakes is a slang term for technology. It's an AI-assisted technology that can
take- you have two sources of video. You have a source video and a target video.
The source video will make a facial expression or turn its head.
And then the target- it's really weird looking. And then the target video will make the same
expression and turn their head at the same time. Is it perfect? No. Will it be perfect?
Eventually. It will be imperceptible to tell the difference between the two.
This came out publicly in 2016. They said, this is technology we had. They used some footage
where they made George Bush and Obama do different things with their head. And you- we saw what
though the source guy was doing. He was like yawning or just kind of moving his head. And then
you'd see George Bush yawning and moving his head. And you can obviously- obviously it's not 100%.
But any imperfections right now that you see in it, you could attribute to film quality issues.
In 2017, and this is where the name Deepfake- or Deepfakes comes from, there was a Reddit user
named Deepfake. This technology is now consumer level. If you have a good enough computer,
you can actually do this yourself. Deepfake began to take high quality pornography videos and then
took images of famous actresses like Gal Gadot and Emma Watson and Taylor Swift, Katy Perry,
stuff like that. And it takes thousands and thousands and thousands of frames of your source
and thousands and thousands and thousands of frames of your target because you have to match it up.
You have to get all angles- you'd have to get like all angles of Taylor Swift's head. And then you
have all the angles of the porn actress moving her head. And where you start to see the imperfections
a lot of time is in the hair. Because- and I did watch this because it is quite odd to watch.
You see imperfections in the hair. If the porn actress moves her face in a way that the
source actress didn't, you'll see a glitch because it's trying to fill in that information. The
computer is trying to fill in information it doesn't have. And again, pornography is very,
very high quality. Generally, it's shot very high quality. So the imperfections stood out a little
more. But if they went with grainier stuff, like amateur stuff, it'd be very hard to tell. Not impossible,
but hard to tell. You know, you're basically putting people in pornography without their permission.
And that's true. So Deepfake was banned from Reddit. You can still- you can get this software online.
I think there's a- there's a couple of them out there. I have one linked in the show notes. But
again, you- you need a fairly beefy computer to do it, but not like top the line. And a lot of time,
because it has to take thou- it says one example was you had to have 20 minutes of footage for both,
and the footage had to be at 120 frames per second. That's how many frames you needed. Some people were
just taking still photographs and putting them in pornos, and it looked horrifying. You need to have
these things so when they turn their head, everything turns with them. There was a video that I saw
today, which was the same thing, but the technology's advanced to the point where it's not facial. It is-
you can do your whole body. So you had- what- you had two people and they were getting all the frames
they needed. Like, the source guy would be like, kind of moving around, turning around, and then
the target guy would be doing the same thing, moving around, turning around. And then the source guy
would begin to dance, and then the- you'd see a person who had never performed those dance moves
ever in their life begin to copy that same dance. It was weird. It was very- I had very uncanny
valley feeling, because I'm watching it, and you know this person has never done this dance, ever.
What you are seeing is 100% artificial, and you're like, Jason, yeah, but so is the ghost from House
on Haunted Hill. That's artificial, but it's different because this has a like a human head,
and it's a human, but it's doing these moves, it's doing something completely unnatural,
and because the technology isn't 100%, let's say that they had all the footage of the person
dancing, but the computer never had an image of him with his hand held out making a fist. He had-
when he held his hand out, his fingers around. It will actually digitally bend the fingers into a
fist, and it's just this weird blur. The computer's doing its best to create a copy of its source
with the information it has. It's very, very unsettling. All those videos are down below.
I- even though I said they're unsettling, they're really cool to watch. It's a really cool thing
of technology. Now, there's been two groups that have been very, very concerned about this.
One group is the Pearl Kletchine Media, who has announced, pretty much since this- actually,
pretty much since last summer, when the Deep Fakes thing came out. This is a threat to democracy.
No one will ever believe anything that is video again. Deep Fakes are a threat to democracy. That
phrase is used in so many headlines. It's a threat to democracy. And then in the conspiracy
theory circles, they're like, "Damn it! Now, when that Pizza Gate video gets uploaded,
of Hillary Clinton eating that baby, no one will believe them." It's because Deep Fake
technology- actually, Deep Fake technology may be fake itself. It may be a CIA cover-up. So,
when the footage finally gets released of Hillary Clinton eating that baby, no one will believe
it. The excuse will be like, "Guys, it's just Deep Fakes. That was someone else eating that baby."
Here's the problem with both of those things. This idea that video evidence is the end-all be-all
of evidence. And it is regarded quite highly. It is. But the idea that it is a threat to democracy-
let's tackle that one first. The idea that Deep Fake- Fake Videos is a threat to democracy,
that I can produce a video that is so realistic, you can't tell whether or not it's true.
Video evidence has been around for what? 67 years? Humanity has been around for
100,000? 50,000 years? Somewhere around there? Civilization has been growing. They were able to
try people and end corruption and expose terrible things for millennias before video cameras came out.
This- I get it. New technology is very scary. And there will be an adjustment phase. But the
idea that someone can show if someone put up a fake video of Donald Trump kicking a baby down the
stairs, down the stairs of the Capitol Building, this is exactly what would happen. Half the people
wouldn't even watch the video. They would see the title of it and write in the comments, "I knew
it. I knew it." Donald Trump is an asshole. The other half of the people would watch that video
would say, "What was the context of the baby getting kicked down the stairs?" Or, "I think it's
fake." Video evidence can persuade some people, but to think that it is a threat to democracy,
that somehow one fake video can bring down a world leader, I don't buy it. The only way that can
happen is if a video was released and nobody disputed it in the media, and I'm not talking about
like the mainstream media, I'm talking from the daily wire to HuffPo, nobody disputed it. Everyone
was like, "There was multiple witnesses there." And actually, it might be a good thing because I
think video evidence can be used, but we'll also come down to where there are other people there.
So if they show Donald Trump kicking a baby down the stairs, of course, Mitch McConnell
standing in the background and they're going to be like, "Hey, Mitch, do you remember that?" And he's
like, "No, that never happened." Generally, evidence is good if it's compounded with other evidence.
But the idea that just this technology alone that you can get on your home computer will
destroy democracy is ridiculous because most people have their minds made up about issues
before they go in, and video evidence only reinforces the conclusions they already have.
Now, as far as the conspiracy theory stuff goes, first off, the idea that there's a video out
there with Hillary Clinton eating a baby and trust me, that's just not something I'm making up.
That's just not an example. I'm like, "Look how wacky they are. I hear that example quite often."
That doesn't exist. That video does not exist. And I'll tell you why it doesn't exist,
because if you ate babies, why would you record it? Well, it's because of the
ceremony. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Why would you record it? No, no, no, because the
Illuminati... No, no, no. Why would you record it? With the information that you know about human
beings, why would you personally record that thing? I don't want to hear about anything about
secret rituals that you don't know about. I don't want to hear anything about secret cults that you
don't know about other than stuff you heard off the internet. Why would you videotape that yourself?
Well, I wouldn't. Yeah, exactly. That's the thing. A lot of times with these conspiracy theories,
they'll make some outrageous claim and then they'll go, "You know, Simpsons predicted 9/11. Why?
Well, because the Illuminati says they have to predict all of their disasters." According to
who? According to who? Well, I've read it on Henry Macau's website, Henry Macau's a lunatic for one.
And two, it's made up. I'm not saying the people trying to run the world is made up,
and I'm not saying there aren't people that eat babies. But when you make an outrageous claim,
you have to back it up other than someone said on the internet. Or an Illuminati defector said
this, "What's their name?" Well, they're going, they have an anonymous name. Then it's made up.
It's made up. There is no video of Hillary Clinton eating a baby. So when that video does get released,
it is fake. It was a deep fake. There's a photo going around right now of Obama in full costume
at some sort of satanic ceremony. And it's being used as proof that Obama is a Satan worshiper.
However, conveniently enough, the costume covers his face. What? But it's Obama, apparently. And
there's a guy, there's an overweight black dude in the background, and they're like,
"That's Eric Holder. What?" But it's so...
Guys, I don't deny that there are powerful people out there who do horrible, horrible things. But
you have to rein it in a bit. You have to rein it in a bit. If your goal is to expose Hillary
Clinton as a baby eating psychopath, that's not a good goal. Because there is no proof of that.
Now, listen, I'll admit it. I could be wrong on this, but I highly, highly doubt it. And if she is,
there's not a video of it. There's not a video of it. And again, I'm going to go back to my original
point. If a video does come out and the media is like, "That's a fake video that actually didn't
happen. That's deep fake technology," then you will have to make the determination whether or not you
think it's deep fake, whether or not when you see those blurs and those artifacts, you go, "Those
are blurs and artifacts that are part of the deep fake technology." Or you say, "Well, that's just
the problem with the film quality, or that's because of this, or that, or the other thing." But
again, generally, I mean, there are people on the internet who believe there's YouTube videos of
people moving their head and because of digital distortion, they shapeshift, their eyes turn
into reptiles. So, I mean, they already believe that any sort of digital problem in a video footage
is proof of reptilian blood. I want to say this too. The deep fakes thing is obviously up for
debate. If you're like, "No, we need to make sure that evidence is always 100%, feel free to leave
a comment, drop me an email, deadrabbitradio@gmail.com," we can discuss this. This is my personal view on
this. I just think that we've gone long enough without having video evidence being the most
important thing. I think we can do it for another 10,000, 100,000 years until they started doing
deep fake holograms and then we're in real deep, deep trouble. I wanted to add this in real quick
here. This is after I did the episode, so the audio quality might sound different. Sorry to
break the immersion, but I wanted to thank YouTube user Euphoria. I didn't know if I was really going
to do this story, but this user was interested in doing it and I want to make sure I take the time
out to thank the listeners who recommend stories to me. So, thanks, Euphoria. We're going to go
ahead and continue on with the story here. So, the next story we're going to cover is YouTube was
down for one hour on October 16th, 2018, and there are already three or four conspiracy theories
involving it. I think it's interesting because it shows what a social, social like landmark,
social joining place for society has become that YouTube goes down for an hour and people
within days are like, "What's going on? What's going on? This must have been this big thing."
So, I mean, it just shows like people like this is such a part of their lives that if it goes down
for an hour, conspiracy theories pop up. Now, if Netflix went down for an hour, people would go. It's
probably just some technical issue. The reason why it became more of a conspiracy when YouTube
shut down because all of the user uploaded content. So, people thought, "Oh my God, somebody
uploaded something to YouTube and the powers that be had to shut it down. They had to take it out."
Now, of course, people were talking about Deepfakes and stuff like that, but these were the three
big... There's quite a few actually. So, one of them was that there was a video of a man in
a military uniform saying an object is about to hit the moon and YouTube shuts down. And then
someone found a video of something hitting the moon and they're like, "Oh my God, look at this is a
reason why YouTube went down. Here's a footage of something hitting the moon and there's like this
huge dust cloud." I mean, that might work except everyone could have just looked up slightly and
seen it impact the moon. The video actually was from 2017. It was a special effects test and so
on and so forth. So, that theory fell to the wayside. The other one is that YouTube now has an AI,
which that's always the buzzword, AI. YouTube has an AI that now buzzes around YouTube looking for
live streams. Oh, you know, what's over here? Oh, someone talking about Fortnite. Oh, here's someone
else talking about Fortnite. What's this guy talking about? Fortnite. This guy's talking about
Fortnite. Oh, this guy's talking about some conspiracy that no one should know about. Shut the whole
YouTube down. Really? That seems like to be the most inefficient one. YouTube at the end of the day
is a business and they lost millions of dollars when they were shut down. So, if Andy Worsky is
saying something on his live stream that the AI doesn't like, the easiest thing to do is to just
nuke his channel, get him off of the channel. You don't have to shut down all of YouTube because
he's saying, "I hate Anita Sargeesian for the 20th time," and the website goes down. The other theory
was that there was a video released of a reptilian. Yes, yes, a reptilian. My favorite aliens of all
time. The seven foot tall reptilian shapeshifters that somehow shapeshift into a human size, but
the mass doesn't change. But anyways, so there was a video of them uploaded and YouTube's like,
"Oh my god, the CIA is calling them up. They're like, "Get this video off of here. That is proof
that a reptilian is on this planet." And they're like, "Yes, sir, yes, sir." You know how many videos
there are on YouTube of reptilians? I'm pretty sure if I searched for one, it would show up in
my recommended videos. I'm sure it would show up reptilian videos in my featured channel. There's
thousands of them. But Jason, though they're fake reptilian videos, then how would you be able to
tell a real reptilian video from a fake reptilian video? Because if I saw a video of a guy, you
just go back to the deepfakes thing, if I saw a video of a reptilian guy walking around, I would
immediately assume that was fake. I'd be like, "That's not real." No matter how good the special
effects were, I would be like, or if it was real, I'd be like, "That's weird because it looks real.
That has to be fake." I would almost have to watch it and be convinced that it was real.
Now, you could go by Jason. They know that, so that's why they shut down YouTube.
Let me tell you a little trick. If you want to... Okay, let's say you had video footage of alien,
like provable alien. You meet a real alien. You break into a laboratory, whatever.
You have video footage of two conformers, a reptilian, and eight grays just kind of like chilling
out in the lounge. And you're like, "I need to get this footage out there." First off, YouTube is
not the best place to do it. But YouTube has... You go, "Well, YouTube has the biggest group of
viewers." All you need to do is to initially get the video online and it will spread itself.
If you put it on YouTube, you're going to be battling 24/9 videos and like eight videos exposing
better help. And then you'll be somewhere on there. But anyways, here's what you do. You
blow the videos up. You set everything to private. You put them on all the websites. You put them
on LiveLeak. You put it on DailyMotion. You put it on any website where you can upload videos,
set everything to private. And then when you're ready to release it, you release... You put all
the videos from private to public. They appear simultaneously all over the place. And then,
at the same time, upload them to Torrent. Put them on Pirate Bay, if that's the leaving around.
Send it to WikiLeaks. You'd have to do a mass distribution of the information. Because that
way, if one of the sites gets shut down, they're not going to be able to shut them down all the
same time, they would literally have to like crinkle the hose of the internet to really to
get that information out. And I'm an idiot. And I came up with that. If I was a deep state operative,
if I was a CIA guy on the run or a super soldier or whatever, you could come up with something way
better than that. I'm an idiot. I came up with that as I was walking home today, prepping this
episode. I was like, that's... It's so easy to do. That's what I would do. And I'm a dork. And there's
a ton of people who are into this stuff way smarter than I am, and I'm sure they could figure out
something better. But anyway, so Reptilean Video got uploaded to YouTube. They shut it down.
PizzaGate was the other theory. Video got uploaded of politicians murdering a kid,
you know, onto YouTube. That's where if you had that footage of Tony Blair and Nancy Pelosi
just like straight up just like boxing this eight year old, I mean just like going at it,
you're going to upload that to YouTube? This is why it went down. This is the most logical
explanation. And I found this on 4chan and some guy just kind of threw it out there and people
are like, yeah, that is pretty logical. A couple weeks ago, Google announced that Google+ was a
bust. They just wasn't working out for them. It was a money hole. They wanted to remove it.
And the theory is that when they removed it, basically YouTube went down because Google+
and YouTube were so interconnected. They're both owned by the same people that to remove the one,
they had to take YouTube offline. Most likely they thought it was just going to be like a minute
or two and it lasted longer than they thought it was because computer code can be a little finicky.
They were getting everything sorted out. Why would they do that on Tuesday at five in the
afternoon? Well, they didn't because YouTube is a global brand. So for some users, it was the middle
of the night and they didn't even know it was off. For other users, it was like, oh my god,
the world's in that I can't get access to YouTube. And they could have also said, statistically,
this is our lowest viewing point. And I could be wrong on that. Someone could say, no, it's actually
their highest and fair enough. But they may have said, listen, for five minutes people will have a
problem. Videos will be running a little slow. But and I think I like because again, they lost
millions of dollars because of this. That's the most likely explanation. And here's the so this
is the thing. They announced that the Google+ they wasn't going to work. And then this happens.
So the idea that they had, they go listen, there's a video out there floating around of a politician
eating a reptilian baby on the moon. But we don't know when it's going to be released. Let's now
say that we're getting rid of Google+ and we're going to wait an indeterminate amount of time
until we detect that video getting uploaded. And then we'll shut it down. And then we'll
use the cover story that it was because Google+ getting shut down. Everyone's like, oh, yeah,
that's a great idea. That's a great idea. If the Google, I think that if the Google+ announcement
came out today and they said, this is why it's down Google+ sucks, we're losing a lot of money,
then the story would make less sense. Then it would sound like a cover story. But because they
announced it before, it's not like they were just going to wait until this horrible video popped up.
Also, lots of horrible stuff is on YouTube and it doesn't get taken down. Stuff that could hold
people criminally liable and it doesn't get taken down. So the idea that someone has this horrible
video of PizzaGate or aliens or the moon landing and that's why the moon being destroyed or whatever
it was, it's all nonsense. That was the reason why YouTube went down. It's backwards fairy tale
making. It's something happening and then people going backwards and trying to figure out why it
happened. That's all it is. It's a, there's two types of conspiracy theories. There's a conspiracy
theory that predicts something that is going to happen. There's a conspiracy theory that predicts
or explains why something happened or is happening. I guess there's three. There's one that explains
what's going to happen. Like there's a fault, going to be a false flag event during the earthquake
drills in California in two months. It's a conspiracy theory about what's going on right now.
And then Katy Perry is a member of the Illuminati and this video is about her worshiping Lucifer.
And then there's conspiracy theories that explain stuff that previously happened like
9/11 and like this where they're like, this event happened and this is why. There's a couple
screenshots of some legs and some dark stains on them and people are like, that's poop, that's poop
and that's pizza gate proof. People are like, what? No, that's from some art project.
It's completely ridiculous. There's a video of a, it looks honestly, it looks like a dead body. I
watched the video but it looks like a dead body on a beach and people are like, look it's a reptilian
and it looks like she's partially decayed and it could actually be a dummy. I don't know. It's
on video, it can be hard to tell the difference between a completely intact dummy and a completely
intact corpse. Not in real life though. It's quite easy. And then with the moon things totally been
debunked. So we have all these videos and these screenshots. This is going to, for the next
a year from now, people are going to be like, why did YouTube really get brought down?
A couple years ago, I think, and the internet time moves really quick. So it may have just
been last year but a couple years ago on 4chan, the website went down briefly and the theory was
that somebody posted a photo of an alien walking by a tree in the desert and they took down the
site or at least they took down the paranormal board. I wasn't there when it happened and actually
I will say no one was there when it happened because it's all anecdotal. Everyone was like,
no, I was on that thread and I saw the picture and it was a picture of an alien walking by a tree
and it was so realistic. To this day, there are people still putting up photoshop of an alien
walking by a tree and then other people do like thermal resolution. They're like, no, you can tell
from the way the scales are created. That is actually a model. I saw the real picture of the
alien walking by the tree. I love researching conspiracy theories. I think they're really fun.
I think that there's a lot of entertainment value in the stories they tell us.
I love mysteries and that's really what's at the core of these. Why was YouTube shut down?
But when you're reading a mystery or when you're investigating a mystery yourself
and they'll tell cops this too, you can't jump to conclusions. You have to really get into it
and try to figure it out and you're not always going to figure it out. But the worst thing we
can do is something happened and then immediately jump to the idea that it's something fantastical
and go, "Fordchan must have went down because the alien picture. You too must have went down
because of the alien video." I think overall that might be exhausting. I think we can run into
conspiracy theories. Like when I was making fun of the whole Hillary Clinton eating the baby.
Like to me, if I dwelt on that and was like, no, this is absolutely true even though I have
absolutely no proof of it, oh no, there's holes on her tongue. That means she eats humans.
If I was really pushing that, I'd almost have no mental energy to investigate other conspiracy
theories. You get obsessed with that one particular one. Sometimes you're going to be like, no, I
have a hunch about this. You start looking into it and there's just nothing to it and you have to go,
oh, I was wrong and move on. Conspiracy theories can be really fun but we can't let them override
our common sense or our judgment because then it becomes, it's not no longer a fun hobby or an
interesting investigation or seeking out some sort of the truth. It becomes an obsession where the
truth doesn't matter anymore. It's all just about finding the weirdest possible thing you can think
of and hanging your hat on it. DeadRabbitRadio@gmail.com is going to be your email address. You can also
hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio. Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter. DeadRabbitRadio is the
daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day.
But I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great weekend guys. We will be back Monday and
thanks again for all your comments. It's really awesome and I will be feeling better by Monday
hopefully and I hope you guys are too. I'm assuming you guys are healthy. Have a great one guys.