Did a book from the 18th century lead to dozens if not hundreds of deaths?
And then we traveled to California where one night a young girl answered the door and the unthinkable happened
There were no clues to her death
Until her ghostly image appeared on nearby billboard today on Dead Rava Radio
*music*
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rava Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you guys are having a great day, too. I gotta be honest man
I've recorded three versions of this. This is version three. This first story. I had a really hard time
Not being super depressing when I'm telling it
So let's see how I got it recorded eventually or I just ditched the whole story. I do think it's an interesting story though
Let's talk about suicide now
What I really want to get to is this really interesting story
So as I'm going down this internet rabbit hole is researching the Golden Gate Bridge because I was researching ghosts of San Francisco for an upcoming episode
They started talking about the suicides on the Golden Gate Bridge
And then I just kind of started doing all of this research on all of these weird things that pop up when they look at suicide
Not gonna talk about that. It's too depressing. So as I'm going down this rabbit hole though
I found out about a thing and it's pretty commonly known called suicide contagion and that is where
when
somebody who is famous or
In a particular peer group kills themselves. We see it spread
I've told people before I've talked to
People who are kind of like at the end of their rope and they're like I got I'm gonna end it man
I'm gonna do it and I always tell them this I have a couple different tools
for talking people out of suicide and
Who knows how effective well, I know it's been effective for me because they haven't killed themselves, but
One of the things I've talked to people and I said
It's a contagious disease
When we look at families when somebody in the family kills themselves, it's usually not isolated daughter kills herself
Uncle kills themselves
Brother kills himself brother kills himself, you know, it's so like that. It's a contagious disease
That came the reason why I discovered that is because of stuff like suicide contagion. There's a town
I think it's in Scotland or Ireland called Bridgend
And there was a documentary made about this town and they had this cluster suicide clustering at all the young people or a
Bunch of young people in town killing themselves as the documentary is being made one of the guys being interviewed for the documentary kills
Himself now it doesn't do it during the interview the guys not like hey
So tell us a little bit about your friends and he's like yeah sure
Let me get this chair set up first and the guys just filming it
But through the creation of the documentary that guy killed himself now
There's been debate about that documentary some people say that it's sensationalized and so on and so forth
But you do have these things suicide clusters suicide contagion and as I'm reading about this stuff
And again, it's fairly depressing as I'm reading about this stuff
I came across the story and it's actually suicide contagion has another name. It's called the Werther effect
Thought this was fascinating stuff fascinating. Let me tell you this story now. I haven't read this book
I'm sure a lot of you have
Let's go back in time to the year 1774
I tricked you there. You thought I was gonna say 1777. I was just looking at my notes wrong
1774 let's hop in the carboner copter
did it
And now we're back. It's provincial
Germany I believe so a bunch of little thatched huts with
Bell is what was her name Bell not Bella right Bell from Beauty and the Beast is walking around and
You know, she would have been okay if she'd ended up with Gaston she really would that I think they would have made it work out
I know a lot of bells who ended up with Gaston's in real life
It works out. He was a cad but he didn't deserve to die like he didn't go that extra level
He wasn't trying to really hurt anybody. He was trying to bed this beautiful woman
He would have been better off at those blondes anyways
But he wanted to marry this beautiful woman and then he found out that a monster kept her prisoner
Which was really going on and he gets the townspeople to rescue her which she really was a prisoner
He didn't know she had fallen in love with this monster and he falls to his death
I think he's probably one of the most tragic Disney villains
He said he is a cad but he it wasn't like he was like broken her house one night
It was like trying to rape her and then she ran and got kidnapped by the beast or nothing like that
He was just an idiot who wanted the best chicken town. I eat me
So I have a lot of sympathy for Gaston
they might have ret condom in the live-action movie where they made him more evil, but I didn't watch that garbage and as
And you're just looking at me as I'm seeing about beating the beast as I'm trying to navigate trying to land this helicopter in this
German village you're like dude
You just landed on all those sheep and I was like add another thing that little dude who was sitting here like
You jump out of the helicopter before we've even landed it's 1774 and there's a young German author named Johan
Wolfgang von Goethh
Goethh I think is how you pronounce it. It's spelt go the but I'm pretty sure it's not go the we'll call him goat
And this dude goat is writing this book
That's what it sounded like back then when you wrote
It sound like ants marching it's not like Dave Matthews band song
Don't don't don't that song was playing every time you wrote something. That's why there's not a lot of literature from back then
It's not true. There's a ton of it. So anyways, he's writing this book. Goethh is writing this book the sorrows of young Werther
So here's a story dude
There's this dude named Werther, right? He's like Werther's original. That's where they got that name from that delicious
Hard caramel. Let's put one in our mouth for the rest of this adventure
Delicious hard caramel is named after this lovable young scamp
Werther so he's chilling in this town in
Germany right and he meets this
Beautiful woman named Charlotte and he's like, oh dude. He's like hey, Char. What's up?
And she's like, oh, what's your name? And he's like I'm Werther here have a caramel candy
So she bites down on it breaks a bunch of her teeth and he's like no you're supposed to suck it
So he gives her another one anyway, so he's hanging out with Charlotte now
Charlotte is about to be married to this older man named Albert and Werther's totally in love with this chick though, right?
And Albert's just kind of like hey Werther, what's up? They all start hanging out together
So he actually moves in with them so Werther is chilling there and then you have Charlotte the love of his life
the only woman he's ever wanted to be with and then Albert is just kind of walking around and
You know living there too. He didn't just walk by the house. He's like hey, that's my house
And I'm just walking by so anyways
He's totally like just like oh my god like this
Their torment in my heart is killing me. I'm in love with this woman
She's with this other guy and it there's gonna get married, but maybe I can woo her
Maybe something will work out here. Maybe somehow against all odds
We can do this and then he's like no I can't I have to leave like yeah
We're really good friends, but I gotta leave so he bounces out and for a couple months
He goes to this other town now
I'm reading all of this from Wikipedia because I'm going down this suicide rabbit hole
So so I could be totally off of major details
You could be like no way Albert was a bricklayer and that was symbolic of him like putting bricks on stuff
Yeah, yeah, maybe I'm just reading the Wikipedia thing
So anyways here is a I don't understand this this makes me think it's a different novel an awesome novel
This is he goes to the other town and there's this sentence in Wikipedia
He goes to this other town. Okay, he quote
He suffers great embarrassment when he forgetfully visits a friend and
Unexpectedly has to face there the weekly gathering of the entire aristocratic set
He's not tolerated and asked to leave since he is not a nobleman
Which makes me think that all of a sudden he became a Rodney Dangerfield story where he's like yo I get no respect
The woman I love is with someone else
I'm like nothing over there and it's a bunch of people with their little like
Wine glasses going what I never he's not an aristocrat like he basically shows it
But his buddy's house with a six-pack. He's like yo Ralph let me in it's worther and he goes in and it's
Basically Wayne Manor during a ball where everyone's dressed up in their suits not their Batman suits dressed up in their suits and ties
There's violin music playing. He's like whoa. What kind of party is this yo Ralph things have gotten real snazzy for you
And they're like you're not an aristocrat please leave and he's like what I get no respect
I get no respect have my audience is like who the hell is Rodney Dangerfield and why doesn't he get respect?
And no one knows the answer to that question, but
Apparently so he goes to his buddy's house to chill and there's a huge party going on and they kick him out
So now he has no choice
But to go back to Charlotte and Albert when he gets back there when he goes back to Charlotte'sville
He finds out that they're already married and he's like are you kidding me? I truly do get no respect and
He can't live with the fact that he can't be with Charlotte
So he decides listen one of three things has to happen either he dies
She dies or I die and he goes well. I never want to hurt anybody else
So I'm gonna kill myself so he asks Albert. Hey, do you got two pistols I can borrow?
I'm gonna go on a quote an adventure and Albert goes. That's weird
Why did you say quote an adventure and he's like well, that's just what Wikipedia said I'm going on an adventure Albert
He goes fine. Yeah, sure. I don't know why you would need two pistols, but here you go Albert goes
Thank you, and he goes back to his house. Where was he living? Where did maybe he was doing this outside?
Anyways, the point is he goes somewhere away from him. He's not standing in front of him going like how you like me now like
He goes somewhere else and the story is written as like a collection of letters
It's posted like supposedly a true story and in some ways it is anyways
he goes and he pulls out a pistol and he blows his brains out and
He doesn't die. He basically just bleeds there for a while just sits there bleeding and the book
Let you know that it takes 12 hours for him to die. So it's not even just like it's this instant death
He's all uh as he's bleeding out dies
The book also wants you to know that at his funeral there was no clergyman and
Charlotte and Albert didn't even show up to the funeral. So totally died alone. That is the story of
Werther so that story
Was the story that made goath super famous like he became an overnight celebrity
It would be like one day you were walking down the street and the next day you were on
Jersey Shore level famous. He was the situation of the 1770s and
The book what?
I've been in that situation
multiple times in my life where I like me to chick and she's with the dude and
They're married and I'm like, yo dude. We'll hang out and then I've been there to be pining over a girl in a relationship
And I've lived with them like it's totally real
I've done this stuff and I've gone to parties and gotten kicked out of parties
obviously, I didn't blow my brains away, but
I've been there and so I'm reading this and I'm like dude. This is super relatable super relatable to me
I think I've done this twice honestly
I think I've been in love with a girl moved in with her and she was married or had a boyfriend at the time both
But both times I was like, ah, this ain't working out and bounced
But I totally relate to this character and this is one of the things that's fascinating
Everyone else related to this character too. Every show often a book will come along that people really or a movie or song
It's usually a book or a movie but
They take off because people can absolutely 100% relate to that character and this guy became so relatable that
supposedly
Young men all over Europe were reading this book and going
You got two guns and they dressed up like he became super fashionable to dress up as Werther
He's very emo character. He's very like tortured character
but people begin dressing like Werther and
Shooting themselves in the head and some people have said no no no that didn't happen or it didn't happen on the scale people think it did
It's a poker full. It's a rumor, but we do know the book was incredibly famous and
Historians and researchers say there was a spate of suicides of young men found
Dressed in the type of clothes or dressed in his style shooting themselves in the head
They said some people even went so far to get the same pistol that's described in the book to do the deed
Fascinating fascinating stuff and obviously goat wasn't like
Step one write a book about a young man killing himself step two
Everyone kills himself like that wasn't his plan
It wasn't his plan at all
But he wrote the book and it was based on his true story like his elements of it were that he obviously didn't kill himself either
But the emotional stuff and his time went on he distanced himself from the story
It was basically like again his first big novel
It's one of those things that you're a band you release a hit song you you really your
Destiny's Child and you release bootylicious and then 30 years later people are yelling at Beyonce. Hey, do bootylicious do
But yeah, I don't want to do that. That was basically his bootylicious
It made him famous, but he distanced himself for it. However thought this was an interesting little note, too
However, even though he distanced himself from this book that cost a bunch of people to kill themselves
He wouldn't let anyone else
Do anything to the book. I didn't know how this segue that there was this dude because the book was super popular
There was this other author named Frederick Nicolai and he wrote a satire of the book called the joys of young werther
And in the he changed the ending so basically the book's totally different and then he changed the ending where when he asks
Albert for the guns
Albert instead of putting bullets in the gun puts chicken blood in the gun
So when
Werther goes to shoot him
So it's funny because it's can't be that much of a different from the plot if it still ends with him trying to kill himself
But he grabs the gun pulls a trigger just a bunch of chicken blood shoots out which is that's
Incredibly traumatizing because he still goes through the whole mental process of deciding into his life
And then it's like what want he's just like covered in blood. He's like what?
That show that showed me no more depression for me
And then Albert gives charlotte to werther. It was a satire
And that made goath this was
Like from what I understand. This is like two decades after the original version came out
Goath had already distanced himself from his novel
Furious that someone would write the again. It was his life story in a way. It was his emotional journey
Furious that someone would write this so then goath writes a poem
Called nicolai on werther's grave so gets meta here. He writes a poem
That we're back in the werther verse we're back in the universe where werther actually killed himself
And his grave is underneath like a lime tree or a pine tree or something
What was it again?
Yeah, it was a lime tree. It was underneath a lime tree. Oh napoleon bonaparte loved this book so much. He carried it with him
That's it. That was not just factoid. Anyways, so he wrote this poem about werther's grave
Is sitting there
Obviously they'll move around their graves aren't known to be quite mobile and nicolai walks up to the grave
This is a poem by the way. Nicolai walks up to the grave looks at it
Pulls his pants down and takes a steaming fat dump
on werther's grave
And that's basically the poem and they became rivals until they died
Goath and nicolai began just constantly like hate writing people suicide contagion aka the werther effect based on the book
That inspired
Men to kill themselves and I can almost guarantee you sadly enough that this book probably still does that
I think it's probably harder to get a flintlock pistol and a big old floppy hat
But i'm sure the book is so relatable stories relatable that people are still reading it and going
Well, if it works for him it'll work for me. Yeah, bizarre stuff
But let's go ahead and we're leaving behind the story of werther
The sorrow of werther. Ugh
What a relatable story. Anyways leaving it behind
You're like jason
Are you over it and I was like, yes. Yes. I am over it. You don't have to have a place I can live for a while, right?
How's your wife doing here? Like, ah, you're never staying at my house now that I know that you have designs on men's wives
When you live with them like what no, I don't
That wasn't what I was saying as my eyes shift from side to side
I've never figured it. My mom thinks that I have a like mental disorder
She goes you always fall in love with women you can't have you're constantly falling in love with married women all the time
And I go that's not true
So I pull a pistol out of my okay, that was dark. I was sorry. Okay. She's like, where'd you get those two flintlock pistols?
I'm like, I'm going on an adventure. Okay, that's okay. Anyways, so
Uh, good old jokes about committing suicide and falling in love with the wrong women. Let's forget all that stuff
We are going to june. No, we're not. We're going to chula vista, california
It's june 19th 1991. You know, I'm not a big
Big person who believes in a lot of like numbers new
Merology and changing these codes up and stuff
I've talked about it. But this did strike me as odd chula vista, california. That part's not odd
That's just the city in california
june 19th
at 9 p.m. And
June is the six month if you turn it upside down you can an upside down six
Or there are that joke aside. There are a lot of nines involved in this
There's a lot actually very very weird. What I'm even seeing more. Okay. I got to start doing this chula vista, california
It's 9 p.m. June 19th 1999. There's a young girl in the house. Her name is laura arroyo
She's nine. She's nine years old. This is true story by the way. It's true story
She's upstairs reading a book with her mom and there's knock at the door knock knock knock and she jumps out of bed
And she goes all get it all get it and she runs downstairs now the mom is thinking it's kind of late
But this chula vista area they were in kind of a nice neighborhood and friends would always kind of like come over and be like
Hey, she doesn't really think too much of it. And then as she hears laura running down the hallway
She hears laura say who is it?
And then the door open
And then she doesn't hear anything and the mom goes. Oh must have been one of her friends talking about homework or something like that
But after about 10 minutes she goes
Uh-oh like where's my daughter at?
Like if it was a casual conversation
They would have come in
Where's she at? So mom jumps out of bed and laura is gone
from her front door
Obviously police are called very shortly fathers looking for her
Moms looking for her neighbors are all looking for this girl
She's disappeared at 6 30 a.m. The next morning
Four miles away her body is found at a business park
And she's been murdered
and there are
Uh
There there was signs of sexual assault
So obviously just the disappearance had the police working high gear now. They're absolutely freaking out about this whole thing
and
They can't find who did it
They are looking all over for the murderer of a nine-year-old and the salter of a nine-year-old girl
This is an interesting case. There's a paranormal angle. I'm just going to talk about this horrible crime
It's an interesting case because you can find it's very well publicized. You can find a ton of articles
detailing everything
A couple weeks after the murder we're in the month of july now
There in town was a billboard
That was no advertisement was put up on it was a blank billboard
It was in between someone saying hey, I want to put my advertisement on there
So it would stand there on the street corner just white with the lights shining up on it
That's the sound the lights at night in chula vista
And one day someone's driving down the road and they're looking at the billboard and they go
What?
They're kind of squinting
They're like, uh, that looks weird
Someone else driving down that same road at night's looking and they're like what the hell is that?
Now
missing girl
Young little nine-year-old girl her photo was plastered everywhere. Everybody knew what this girl looked like in town
Horrible horrible story. So people who had never met laura while she was alive knew what she looked like
So when people were driving down this road in chula vista and they're looking at this billboard
They see the light and the shadow
Make the image of laura's face
The billboard was two miles between the house and the murder scene. So it was like right in the middle
And word gets out in town now. This is again before social media
You actually had to walk up to someone and go hey, buddy. Have you seen that billboard or you would pick up the phone and be like, yo
What are you doing tonight? Let's go see the billboard
So it wasn't like someone could tweet something and then a bunch of people showed up
But a bunch of people did show up at one point
They were recording crowds of like
25,000 people which is mind-boggling to me. I don't know how big chula vista is
But people huge traffic jams cops have to come out
And direct traffic because people were driving by this billboard and that's one thing
We have a bunch of articles on this if this story happened today
We'd have video footage and and photos and everything like that
We don't have any of that at least in none of its posts that this was way before the internet was even really a thing
So the father of the girl luise arroyo says i gotta check this out
And he goes and he goes oh my god, that's my daughter
That's my daughter on that billboard
He took her brothers. He had she had like i think like a 12 year old brother and a 10 year old brother
They went there and the brothers were like
Laura Laura and they started crying. It's a tragic story tragic story, but
So the general consensus was this was Laura's image on the board and you're like light and shadow people are imagining things
The police are looking at it and they go can you take some photos of that? So they had other cops
photographing
Taking it as evidence
And there was a quote from detective wane maxi. He goes it's one of those things where we don't know where it could lead us
And they were they asked the billboard people
They said do you have another person ready to put up a sign there and the billboard company says yeah
We actually do have someone we were just in between putting up advertisements and the police said listen
Could you do us a favor
This we don't know if this is a ghost face or anything like that
It's funny because cops tend to be kind of superstitious
But this officer wasn't saying we think there's a ghost here and we're trying to contact her this officer said
Listen
We think this might help lure out the killer
Because if he believes there's some sort of supernatural force going on or something like that, can you not put up a new advertisement?
And he goes yeah, yeah, we'll give it some time. Maybe this will help catch the killer
So it wasn't so much like they thought a giant Laura hand a ghostly hand's going to reach out and grab him like the state puff
Marshall oh man, it was just that maybe the guy in the area would just be so overwrought by guilt
But at some point this the image didn't go away
At some point the traffic jams are so much
Some I think that city disconnected the power to the sign
And then the people in town got up there and reconnected the power now
There was also stories that you could see the image of the killer in the background
Now I heard that out of my national directory of haunted places book
I wasn't able to find any verification any news articles saying and some people said you could see the killer
So I'm not for sure about that detail. But anyways
Eventually though enough time passes
Traffic dies down
Company throws up another billboard the image is no longer seen
It wasn't until
When the cops break down a door and this is what 14 years later
Put your hands on your head put your hands on your head. Oh guys wrestling
Smash hopefully smashed his head into the floorboard
Manuel brocca montes 42 year old man
So he would have been in his what what's 14 minus 4 42 would have been 28 something
I think it would have been 28 when this happened used to live in the area
Moved out a week before the crime
Had access to a tool that they believe was used in the murder
And they caught him because of the dna he left at the crime scene
He ends up getting sentenced to death
He ends up getting sentenced to death and it's interesting because when you look at the early articles it said there's no sexual assault
This child was not sexually assaulted. She was just chopped up with this weird looking tool
That he used at his construction company or something. It wasn't like a normal weapon that you would see
So that kind of helped him kind of narrow it down
But it was the dna that finally got him and it was one of those things that it was a cold case
And they're like just run the dna again and then like six seven years would pass and they're like just run it again
Can you run it one more time and they're like, yeah, you'll run it as much as we want this guy murdered a kid
Let's do it and they finally caught him. But he gets guilty
sentence to death
And that's where we're at now the last real article I saw him
This was 2005 so i'm assuming that he was appealing his death sentence or something like that
I think it's an interesting story because we have that convergence
We have there we're at that intersection of paranormal and true crime
Which when I started the show I said that's going to be a common theme
And it pops up every now and then every now and then so it's always interesting when it does
but the idea of
the billboard
And the little girl looking out from the shadows and the light out at the street below her
The father said, you know, I worked on the street
That the billboard was like looking down and I figured that was a way for my daughter to watch over me and to send me a message
But I don't know what she's trying to tell me
Damn, that's horrible. I mean I get that's awesome that he finds that uplifting thing but
Imagine it's one thing to lose your child
But then imagine if you saw your child frozen in time if you truly believe that was her frozen in time her image looking at you
giant looming
Over the night sky scape
Of chula vista and you just being this father looking up at this image of your daughter and thinking what are you trying to tell me
And then have it go another 14 years before you finally have any piece
About what happened to her
And then let's say that it was some ghostly apparition up there
I think the creepiest part is
There's a chance that it was
And there was that brief moment in time where there was no billboard up there
And people were driving by and they happened to recognize the way that it looked as laura
but what if
There was a billboard there
What if there was a eat a Kentucky fried chicken colonel sanders taking a big old bite
And yet somehow the soul of this young girl her ghostly image was still impressed on that
Thing and people just continued to drive by
Drive by this billboard and you have the soul of this young girl looking out trying to send her father a message
But it's simply being ignored
I find that infinitely more creepy
How many messages could be out there people who are lost people who are dead
That they're trying to send to their loved ones, but we just don't see because of all of the information overload all around us
Is it possible someone's trying to reach out to you right now?
You just don't notice it
You just drive by that sign as a ghostly presence is trying to send you a message
From the other side
DeadRabberAidu@gmail.com is going to be our email address
You can also hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabberadio
Twitter is @deadrabberadio
DeadRabberAidu is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listened to it today. Have a great one guys
[Music]