Is it possible to gain weight even after you're dead?
Now take a look at an old conspiracy, I'm surprised it's actually back.
Why can't we dig today on Dead Rabbit Radio?
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio.
I'm your host Jason Carpenter, I'm having a great day, I hope you guys are having a great
day too.
I hope you guys have some awesome plans for the weekend that is coming up.
Unless you're listening to this episode on Sunday in the year 2025 and then hope it's
a good Wednesday.
Let's go ahead and welcome into Dead Rabbit Command one of our newest Patreon supporters,
walking in right now.
Give it up for Hips.
Wooo, yeah, come on in Hips.
Shake those you as you're walking into Dead Rabbit Command.
Hips, you're going to be our captain or pilot this episode if you guys can't support the
Patreon, I totally understand.
Just help spread the word about the show that helps out so much.
It really, really does.
And look at this awesome fan art we have for today.
What a really cool drawing that is from the one and only longtime supporter of the show,
longtime fan art Friday contributor, Rudy Jazz.
It's a picture of, I guess who at this point we should just call Dead Rabbit.
I never thought that the logo might have a name, but Dead Rabbit with a voodoo theme.
Really, really love that artwork, Rudy.
Really, really cool.
Hips, let's go ahead and toss you the hair hang glider.
We're going to jump off the highest point at Dead Rabbit Command.
We're going to glide all the way out to Alabama.
Didn't think about it.
Probably should have taken the Jason Jalopy.
We're going to do a lot of driving.
So maybe hang glide right into the Jason Jalopy.
We'll get this bad boy started.
First off, let's head, oh I got to do the sound effect.
Hips drive us out to Coleman County, Alabama.
And right off of Highway 31 North is a place known as Cry Baby Hollow.
Now back when this area was first being settled by settlers, there was a family in an old
wagon.
Back then it was a new wagon, but to us it was like an old timey wagon.
You have like the cloth cover and the big wooden wheels and a horse pulling it.
Hopefully the dad doesn't have a strap to his shoulders and he's been like, oh man,
how many more states do we have to go to?
California, what?
Oh man.
Pulling this wagon.
This family in this wagon is crossing this wooden bridge when all of a sudden the wheel
snaps off.
It's the thing that rappers have been warning us about this whole time.
The wheels fall off.
And apparently maybe this wagon didn't.
This wagon wasn't a stereotypical wagon.
It didn't have the cloth covering because apparently there was a baby on board.
This is the origin story for those signs.
You didn't know?
There was a baby on board this wagon and when the wheel broke, the baby rolls off the wagon
and falls into the creek.
I'm warning you right now.
This segment involves a lot of ghost kids.
This band, but they were normal kids and then they died.
It's pretty grim, but this is a fascinating phenomenon.
I've never seen anything like this before.
I mean, unfortunately we have covered babies drowning on this show, but baby rolls off the
wagon into the creek and drowns.
To this day, when you're in this area late at night, you can hear the sound of a baby
crying as you're driving over the bridge.
You're listening to your baby crying CD, that new grunge band.
This is a phenomenon.
That's not the whole story.
That's just the setup because you're like, oh man, this is totally common.
It is.
This is a very common phenomenon.
All over the country, you can find crybaby bridges, really all over the world.
I think there is a rational explanation to that.
I think it has to do with a...
I don't necessarily think it's always paranormal.
I think it's water rushing under a bridge, creates this kind of echo effect tied into
an urban legend.
You already have a heightened fear because you're in an area where a baby rolled off
a wagon and you're like, oh, I don't want that to happen to me.
I think that's a natural phenomenon because we see a lot of stories, like I said, there
are crybaby bridges everywhere.
You have to wonder after maybe, I don't know, the third or fourth baby dying in a bridge
accident, I don't know, maybe strap the baby down to something.
But that's not what we're focusing on because again, it's a very, very common phenomenon.
This is a phenomenon I have only seen in Alabama.
I was going through this really cool website, theshadowlands.net.
A lot of you guys are really familiar with it.
It's an old website.
Luckily, they're still up.
It's just tons of ghost sightings.
Now, I read about ghost stuff all the time.
Ghost stuff is my number one favorite paranormal phenomenon.
I love UFOs and Bigfoot, stuff like that, but ghosts are my favorite.
I've seen ghosts.
I used to be a ghost hunter.
I technically, I still am.
I just don't do a lot of field work.
I've never seen anything like this in my years of research.
And in Alabama specifically, has this over and over again.
Now you could say it's the urban ledger just spreading to different communities.
But let's go ahead and get into what I'm talking about.
If you go to cry baby hollow, you can hear the baby crying in the water.
And if you leave a candy bar on the bridge and walk away and then you come back, there's
a bite taken out of the candy bar.
Can you go Jason?
Jason, no duh.
No duh.
You're going to leave candy bar at night.
You walk away for a couple of minutes.
Like a raccoon could get it.
Sure.
Possible, right?
That would be the rational explanation.
Well, hips, go ahead and drive us out to Clanton, Alabama.
This time we're going to a place that is specifically called cry baby bridge.
And this story, this origin story was on a foggy night during a war.
There's no specific one.
You could be any of them.
During a war, a woman and her baby were being chased by men.
Well, I guess that means it's probably an American war.
I don't think it was like the Russian-Japanese war of the late 1800s.
I don't think they'd be running away at that point.
They're like, oh no.
A woman and her baby are running away.
They're being pursued by men.
So civil war, revolutionary war, maybe something like that.
And I don't know why she did this.
I'm not a mother.
I would assume this is something you don't do.
She's being pursued by these men and she probably figures, well, I can probably run
faster if I wasn't carrying a baby.
Because as she's running across the bridge, she throws her baby into the water.
Now it could be that she was sparing her child the horrible torment that these people are
going to do to the baby.
There comes the tickle monster.
She's like, no, not the tickle monster.
Not again.
And she's running with her baby.
She's like, no, not the tickle monster.
So, if you're a baby crying and if you take an unwrapped candy bar and leave it on the bridge, it'll be gone.
Like I said, I have not seen this legend in any other state.
And there's a lot of states with crybaby bridges.
In Alabama, we have Hartzell, Phoenix City, Smith Station, all have stories of candy bars disappearing.
So if this phenomenon is a natural phenomenon, shouldn't you see it everywhere?
Also, I have the question, why are those centers constantly carrying around candy in Alabama?
Like, how did they even test this theory in the first place?
Why were these candy bars showing up on bridges?
But this phenomenon seems to only be in Alabama, despite the fact that crybaby bridges exist all around the world.
Bridges over water often have these legends associated with them.
And I should say bridges over water in rural areas.
I don't think the Golden Gate Bridge has a lot of stories of hearing a baby crying as you're driving over it.
But these bridges in the middle of nowhere with the small creeks or the small rivers, you often see these legends.
But the candy eating thing is only in Alabama that I've seen in like 30 plus years of paranormal investigation.
So putting on our conspiracy caps, let's say that this is not raccoons or bears or me.
I'm part of your ghost hunting crew and I'm like, can we go back to crybaby bridge?
Let's test that candy thing again.
They're like, sure, Jason.
And I'm like, also, why do you suddenly have diabetes?
I don't know.
Also, let's see if the ghost will eat beef jerky.
That sounds delicious.
And they're like, what?
Let's put on our conspiracy caps here and take a look at this.
If this phenomenon is paranormal, it is utterly bizarre.
Because here is the thing.
Where is the candy going?
I'm not sure.