breaking news out of San Francisco as US Marines make their way through the city trying to capture an
Elusive target and then we take a look at the story of a babysitter who has a close encounter of the delicious kind
And then we visit Ohio University
Considered one of the most haunted colleges in America
Are these hauntings caused by a past of suicides and murders or is it something even more?
Today on Dead Rabbit radio
Hey everyone, welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit radio. I'm your host Jason Corbin or I'm having a great day
Hope you guys are having a great day too. Hope you guys had fun with yesterday's episode. Yagoonies
I hope you guys really enjoyed it. Hope it gave you guys some great ideas about what to do this weekend
But before you guys destroy your entire life, let's go ahead and welcome our newest patreon supporter. He is a vehicle himself
There's a bunch of little kids hanging out of his window
He's like I don't have kids. It's Thomas the dink engine
Everyone give a round of applause to Thomas the dink engine is all these little kids are like help us
Help us. We're trapped in this interdimensional train. Tom. We laugh. We laugh at the children's plight
Thomas you're gonna be our captain our pilot this episode you guys can't support the patreon
Or if you have kidnapped children from across the dimensions, that's fine too. Just helps rid the word about the show
Really really helps out a lot. Thomas. I'm gonna go ahead and toss you the keys to the Dead Rabbit dirgeable
We're gonna leave behind Dead Rabbit command. We are headed out to the city of san francisco
Came across the story the other day. I'm sure you guys saw it in the mainstream news
Who am I kidding the mainstream news more like the mainstream lube
Concerns that's what they should be called right? I got this from the real news
The news that doesn't need to be prepared the news that has no sanitary conditions whatsoever real raw news
It's may 3rd 2021 go go go go go go bunch of marines are running through the streets of san francisco
There's a bunch of mucking taking place. We don't have time to stop that
We don't have time to actually maintain law and order in the lawless city of san francisco. No
We have one target in mind go go go. They're doing the hand signals game fingers are shooting them. They think they're from a rival gang
Ah, the marines are making their way through the city of san francisco target
house speaker nancy polosi
She if you're part of the 95 percent of the world population who cares nothing about us politics
She is currently the house speaker. That's why that's her name. She's the speaker of the house of representatives in the united states congress
and she's wanted for
unspecified crimes
Apparently she's committed several crimes the article did not make it clear
It went into great detail about who was in charge of this operation
But did not really make clear to me what nancy polosi is being charged with but anyways the us marines that are still under the control
of president trump
Trump still president joe biden not president. He's at like a sound stage
It's like a fake white house that's in the same location of the white house
The sound stage is actually in the white house. So when you see his car is driving around
He's just going to the sound stage. He's not actually going to the oval office
this is the slightly lopsided office where he's at and
The us marines are looking for house speaker nancy polosi. Go go go go go. She's like 78 by the way
I don't know what he even said that a full platoon
It's not like she's gonna go straight up tony montana and start like shooting them up with a bunch of cocaine or will she
We'll find out the us marines are moving through the city. Go go go go go
And they see her they actually plan to this operation. They waited till her husband was at work
Because if there's one if you think there's gonna be complications taking down one 70 year old person
You don't want to face two of them. So they wait till her husband's at work
They see house speaker nancy polosi leaving her house the marines throw a bag over her head zip tie her throw her into a van
Go go go. They told the marines have sent this entire operation
They can't say any word other than go go go. They have to say three times in a row as this van is speeding away
Duly elected house speaker nancy polosi is in the back of this van that's speeding out of the city of san francisco
They take the bag off of her and they realize something
Go go go one of the marines says and the other one goes go go go. It turns out
That they did not nab nancy polosi. They nabbed
a decoy
This was a another woman a much younger woman
Who was wearing a realistic
realistic nancy polosi mask
And also had like her passport her id
Everything on her that detail didn't
Have any sense but that detail specifically didn't make sense if she has a life like nancy polosi mask on
What does she need her passport and her driver's license license for right?
And if she has nancy polosi's passport and driver's license, what does the real nancy polosi have?
Does she have the doppelganger?
Does she have the person with like photos of the person without the mask on?
Why would you give doesn't make sense? You wouldn't want your decoy to flee the country
You wouldn't want to make sure they didn't have a passport anyways
turns out that nancy polosi
who
Regularly works in washington dc all the time and is well known in san francisco where she was elected
They can't find her. They can't find her even though she's on television all the time
Very very well known schedule where this woman's at they can't find her
And this is i wanted to read you this quote from this article because i just love this stuff. I just love this stuff quote
us military assets have fudged a covert mission to apprehend house speaker nancy polosi
Arresting instead a polosi doppelganger
Donning a lifelike mask that mimicked every hideous detail of polosi's face
Right down to the most deeply ingrained wrinkles
unquote
I don't think the marines put that in their interaction report. They're like like dear dear general
We thought we got nancy polosi because no one would like this. She doesn't look that ugly
Nancy polosi is an elderly woman. She's not so
Yes, if I was describing if I held him a mask of nancy polosi, I wouldn't say
Every hideous detail. She's an elderly woman. It's not just that nancy polosi
Has a doppelganger with a mask, but it's a disgusting mask
The author wants to let us know that this mask was super hideous
But anyways, who am I? I'm not a real journalist the people at real raw news
Know how to undercook the facts and give them to us raw. So who am I to judge?
This isn't a beauty podcast. This isn't a special effects podcast
And this definitely is not a real raw news podcast
So semper fi gentlemen your mission in san francisco is halfway complete. You capture nancy polosi's
face
Thomas the dankenjun, let's go ahead and leave behind san francisco
I'm gonna toss you the keys to the jason jalopy. We are headed out to
Fort Wayne, indiana
Seeing a train drive a car is not something I thought we would ever see but here we are. Thomas the dankenjun is somehow making it work
It's a long driver. Smelling is exhaust the whole time. We're like, uh, he's a coal burning engine. We're all passing out
Eventually though, we're taking a fort Wayne, indiana hospital
We are revived from carbon monoxide poisoning and it is time to start this story
It's march 1993 and there's a young woman. Let's call her
Let's call her nancy. Let's call her nancy. There's a young woman named nancy. She is babysitting a baby a little baby person
Parents are gone. Nancy is taking care of this kid
Rainstorm starts
But she's an experienced babysitter the rain doesn't super scare her right. It's just something that happens from time to time
But then the power goes out
Rainstorm power outage. You're alone with the baby now things are getting a little nervous and the baby starts screaming
She's trying to figure out what to do like this is a strange house where are the candles?
Where's the flashlight got the screen don't want to trip on the baby. Where's the baby?
While she's trying to figure that out a bright light shines from outside the house
The entire house is illuminated now
But it's not a comforting light. It's a mysterious spooky light. It shouldn't be there
And then
There's a knock at the door
Nancy slowly turns her head. I don't know. He might have turned it super fast. That wasn't in the notes
It didn't say how fast she turned her head Nancy ever so slowly looks towards the door
She sees the doorknob turn
Then the door opens
And she sees
in the darkness
A four foot tall man
He's purple
Her eyes must have really adjusted at this point to determine that he's purple
with a curved nose
large ears
And he stands there looking at her for a second
Nancy is frozen
Little man staring
Nancy's staring
And the little man runs into the house
Passed Nancy passed the baby into the kitchen
She sees the refrigerator door open up
That one's also a haunted refrigerator door
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
They got it from Strange Magazine number 13 Strange Magazine has served us very well in the past as well
So think about it docks.com has a really good
Track record as far as legit stories in Strange Magazine 13 the one time we covered it
We covered it twice one was I think a monster in a basement
The other one was the puff balls that rock people's skin
I'll try to find those two stories for the show notes. I'll try to put those episodes in the show notes
But this is an interesting story for me
Because it makes this is a Pepsi commercial, right? Like when when
I'm pretty sure there is a I'll actually try to see if I can find on youtube
I'm pretty sure there's a soda commercial with this same setup
Or a Snickers commercial butterfingers or something like that. I know the Reese's pieces had the alien but this seems set up
This story seems fake
This story seems fake and that's why I want to cover it
At what point
Do we dismiss stuff out of hand? I'm not going to go on a huge tangent with this
But at what point when you hear a UFO story or an alien story do you go? That's not true
And this is an interesting one for me because on the one on a
If you never if he had not walked in to get the soda
It would just be a babysitter meets an alien story
It would actually have been so mundane. I wouldn't have covered it
Because we see stuff like this happen all the time the fact that it goes in and gets a soda doesn't say the brand of soda
So it's not the best advertisement in the advertising the alien's hand is covering the soda the whole way. You're like, is that coke?
Is that Pepsi? I don't know what to buy
At what point do we dismiss alien stories or really any of these stories imagine a story
Where a ghost walks into a house and turns to the camera and goes choice of a new generation
You're like, what?
What what is that ghost story have an advertisement in it at what point do we decide to dismiss these things?
I'm not saying the story is fake. I'm saying I highly doubt that it's real
Because it reminds me of a commercial and is that fair
For me to say because her story. I mean, I would think that this young woman saw
A commercial like this and then she dreamt about it or was imagining it
But I am dismissing the story because it reminds me of a commercial
I feel like
The story is not true because it seems so ridiculous, but we've covered a lot of ridiculous stuff on this
So, I mean the story is kind of meta for me
The cassa blanca invasion is one of the most ridiculous alien stories. We've ever covered. I'll put that in the show notes
But any reminder remind me of a commercial
So I just want I want to include the story one because I think it's an interesting but two on that meta level at what point
Do we decide this is too ridiculous for us to believe because in essence all
Alien things all ghost stories all bigfoot stories are too ridiculous for 70 to 90 of the population to believe
So I just think it's interesting when we come across stories. Otherwise, this is fairly legit
It's from two sources that I've gotten good stuff from before
I distrust this I can't even say I distrusted like again
I'm in that weird mode, but I wanted to cover this because of that meta moment and for you guys to examine that as well
At what point do you go? I don't believe that because it's too
It's too wacky
It's interesting because we do come across that even though at its core everything is wacky and it's possible
That the story is so wacky that it is true
It's super bizarre and I think it would be hoove aliens to do more wacky and weird stuff
They really want to stay off people's radar the weirder they get like making people pancakes or having talking bears show up
Which are both stories we've covered on this show the less likely people are to believe them
So it actually makes sense of aliens did things that mimicked pop culture
Like the next files episode where the men in black were jesse ventura and alex trebek
Because they knew no one would believe that they were visited by jesse ventura and alex trebek
The aliens actually plan to be that ridiculous
Thomas the dinkage and let's raid this babysitter's fridge and take all the sodas. We're gonna leave her. We're gonna say goodbye to the baby
Hopefully they'll be okay. Hopefully no more aliens show up, but it's really doesn't matter to us
We have another story to cover. I'm gonna touch you the keys of the carpenter copter. We're leaving behind
This little house in fort Wayne, indiana. We're headed out to afton's ohio
We've actually been to ohio university before I covered it a long time ago on episode
200 what was it episode
Because at ohio university part of the college campus used to be an insane asylum
As the campus was they built the campus and then 70 years later
They thought it'd be a great idea to build an insane asylum right next to it
And not a good idea. Not a good idea, right? It's gonna definitely interfere with your grades if you're afraid some lunatics
Going to break in at any moment
Eventually the asylum was shut down and the campus absorbed it
So the campus got bigger and now the asylum is some classrooms and some teachers offices
But we covered the ridges in ohio university back on episode 276
But I started looking at some other ghostly activity that brought me back to
Ohio university that I wanted to take a look at with you guys. So we're now college students. We're walking around campus
We got on our college clothes. Those are different the regular clothes. They're smarter
We're walking around ohio university, which is the alma mater of not only richardine anderson a k a magyver
But ed o'neill
Everyone's favorite television dad no matter what generation you're in you have good memories of ed o'neill
Richard Dean Anderson and ed o'neill we wave hi to them. They're like, dude, we don't go here anymore
We graduated decades ago. We're like see you in class. They're like, what are you guys even talking about?
We're gonna take a little tour of this supposedly haunted college
So you have east green so it's divided up into sections. So first off, let's start off on the section
Oh, and is east green. There's a place called wilson hall
That's where we're going to be dormant with our buddies. I don't need Richard Dean Anderson
They're like, dude, we don't go here anymore. We're like, let's be bunkmates. They're like, oh man, they're stuck in this story now
We go to get our dorm room. It's room 428
But it's boarded up
We're like, what how are we supposed to get in here and the hall monitor or whatever they're called the
chauffeur, what are those guys called the hall monitor?
The floor dude the floor dude walks up and we're like a floor dude. He's like, dude, I'm called the din mother
What are they called the people who run the dormitories the mayor? He goes, hey guys
I know you guys supposed to be in room 428, but that one's actually even sealed off
We don't let anyone in that room anymore and we go. What's what happened there? He goes, let me tell you a story
Also, sorry for sorry for booking you in a room that doesn't exist anymore
But let me tell you a story
This room used to just be a normal dorm room and back in the 1970s. There was a student
Let's just call him Barry. We don't have his name
But he was in there
Fun loving guy probably the description of him whatsoever. They just says a man in the 1970s
So he could have been could have been anyone. It could have been Henry Kissinger. It could have been
Ed O'Neill. We don't know probably wasn't either of them. They didn't die
mysteriously room 428
But a young man died in room 428 that was in the 1970s
Everyone in Wilson Hall had heard this story and some people. Oh, did he commit suicide?
Well, maybe was he murdered? No, they don't think he was murdered. He just died mysteriously and this story went around
But people went in and out of this room through the semesters through the years other people use this room
Didn't really have a problem with it
But a couple years later there was a girl who had heard about these stories
And heard about this guy who died mysteriously and she was really into
Black magic astral projection talking to spirits stuff like that
She's in that room and she goes, you know, this is perfect because since this guy died mysteriously here
This would be a vortex for me to make my powers greater
People are like, what are you talking about you weirdo? So she begins to talk about astral projection
She's trying to harness the power of this room and then she dies
Supposedly some say that she killed herself by slitting her own wrists
Other people say well her wrists were slit
But she didn't do it
She was murdered not by an assailant well technically an assailant but not by a human assailant
But the dark forces came after her
She was brutally murdered
Because she was pushing the limits of what a human should know what a human should be capable of when it comes to the world of the paranormal
So now the room had an even darker reputation. You had two people who died there one mysterious circumstances the other one
May or may not have committed suicide, but definitely was involved in some dark arts black magic things like that
Time marches forward. This is a dorm room students are filtering in and out of the college
People are still using the room
But what they're starting to run into is that when students would come in they'd put down their keys or their coffee cup or whatever
You had reports of things being thrown off of shelves smashing against walls smashing into the floor
Doors would open and close by themselves
Sometimes you'd be in the room all by yourself
Sometimes you'd be in the room by yourself and you'd hear a loud shout which i'm not going to emulate that
Just imagine this voice but way louder right in your ear
And then on the door people said that they could see the outline of demonic faces in the woodgrain
That is the one I call the most bs on anything because that could easily be what is it periabola
Where you're just looking at patterns and you're seeing it wrong and stuff like that
But everything else could definitely be possible when we talk about the world of paranormal even the faces appearing on the door
But I couldn't find any photographs of that the 1970s people had cameras if this is something that was happening all the time
It'd be easy to document. I'm not saying there's not photographs out there. I couldn't find any
Eventually the university got so many reports of paranormal activity in the room. They just sealed the room off
We've covered that before we've talked about another university this episode is going to be full of past episodes of the show notes
We talked about another university before I don't remember where I think it was actually now that I remember it was in
Athens, but it was a different university where they also had walled up a room
There's a staircase that leads to nothing. It's walled in
There's a lot of legends behind that and so we have this same thing you have this room this dorm room
That is not accessible. I was actually watching a video by the post. I believe it's called
It is a Ohio University newspaper. It's their journalism program
And they were investigating it. I mean, they were kind of goofing on it as well
But they showed the door the door does exist
You can't enter it. So it actually is a real place that can't be entered. It's not an urban legend
It's not like room 428 doesn't exist at all. Even to this day on campus. They hear these stories about this room
this building is also
apparently in the middle of a pentagram of
Native American cemeteries. So some people think that's why Wilson Hall is haunted but looking into Ohio University. That's not all
Jefferson Hall, which is another building on campus
Has what's called the marble sound. This would be weird to pin down
They say sometimes when you're walking around Jefferson Hall, you're on the top story
It sounds like someone's dropping thousands of marbles on the roof. There's nobody up there
If you go to Washington Hall
There is an entire this is huge actually. There's an entire ghost
There's an entire ghost basketball team
A high school girls basketball team all of them. It's an entire girls basketball team haunts, washington hall
The story goes
There was a girls high school basketball team. They visited
Campus, they're like, oh, this place is great. I can't wait to go to college here
I'll probably be here forever and ever and ever
I'll see that at the same time even the coach is all ever and ever and the tour guides like oh, that's creepy
and then they died in a car accident on the way home
And now instead of their ghost going back to their loved ones instead of their ghost inhabiting the places
They grew up and no they're just all at washington hall a place they visited once
Which means i'm never going to go to a sucky plan
I'm never going to go visit a sewage treatment plant
Well, all this place is kind of cool and then my ghost then I died like eight years later
My ghost is floating around a sewage treatment plant. I'm like, oh it sucks
So that's the backstory
But this okay, so if you heard that backstory you're like, oh, that's kind of sad, but you know
They're in washington washington hall first. There's no basketball court there. It's apparently like a dormitory
So it's not like they're like, oh, we can always play b-ball and who would they play against they're playing against a bunch of demons
They're trapped in washington hall these girls are trapped in this dormitory
That whole backstory is created because sometimes when you're in washington hall you hear the sound of basketball dribbling
So here's what i'm gonna tell i'm gonna tell you what happened i'm telling you what happened
Sometimes you can hear a basketball dribble in washington hall i'll give them that it probably is a phantom basketball dribbling
I think the high school basketball team is made up because i actually heard several versions of this story one is
You just hear the basketballs the second one is it was a men's basketball team an adult men's basketball team that was trapped there
And then the story that I found was the most fascinating and sad
Was the all high school girls visiting one single time and being trapped there
So I think what happens is there and this is very common in ghost stories
There is a singular ghost event that may happen once or twice
It may happen on a regular occurrence and the backstory is made up and I actually think that leads us into the answer of 4 28
Most likely the room is sealed off for one reason or another
Apparently the official answer is it's not safe
That could mean anything from asbestos black mold the foundation's giving out
There's a bunch of nails the place is infested with cockroaches
It could be all sorts of things now most of those would affect the rest of the school
It's not like they just nail a door shut and they're like cockroaches you'll be in there forever
Could also be that it wasn't safe because you got a couple students complaining about
Doors opening and closing there could have been a paranormal thing there
But I think the story is made up from the 70s about the younger those are probably made up
They're probably
Backtracked they probably have a story wise. Why can no one go in this room?
Someone goes. Oh, it's just not safe and then people over the years have made up these myths
And that's the most logical answer
But I don't want to end with the most logical answer
Let's put on our conspiracy caps here because I found something really cool about this university
That opens it up to a whole other
set of theories
This school
Has one of the most powerful
Particle accelerators on the planet that's capable of sending a particle up to 14 of the speed of light
It's one of the most powerful on the planet
It was opened in 1967 which predates
The ghost story of wilson hall the man who died mysteriously
So with our conspiracy caps on it would be interesting to think that this particle accelerator
Which is used for all of these experiments
What if it actually has opened a rift of some sort?
and so we do have
More ghost act because this by a lot of accounts. This is I've just covered the ghost in this particular like wilson hall
Washington hall
There's a ton of ghost stories in this college. It's considered one of the most haunted colleges in the united states
It's one of the oldest colleges in the united states
But what if this you have this normal ghost activity people walking up and downstairs stories being shoved this particle accelerator has actually opened up
Some sort of gateway that allows this phenomenon to be more apparent
To be so apparent it can actually be violent and actually kill people
So that's an interesting way to look at it. You have science and the paranormal blending together
The side effect of this particle accelerator is causing that but then I thought of something even crazier
and
And I am not I am not implying I'm not implying in any sort of legal sense
That ohio university or the people who maintain the particle accelerator
Or this is conspiracy cap fully on do not sue me
What if the experiments of the particle accelerator is what killed those two kids?
Somehow a little particle
A little particle was flying around so fast and it went crazy
Grabbed a little particle knife a little did a little particle Ted bunny. What if by some sort of fluke
That particle accelerator killed the kid in 428
You're like Jason
That's not how particle accelerators work conspiracy cap fully on
What if the particle accelerator killed the kid in 428 in the 70s? So after it was operated some guys are like let's do this
Let's see what happens. Let's type in particle plus 14 speed of light plus
Charles Manson like what are you doing? Don't type that in
The thing starts up. What I'm saying is what if that's why the room is not safe
It's like right in the right in the path
Like people are disintegrating at 14 of the speed of light that young woman in there
She really is trying to do black magic, but it's not working. She's trying to astrally project. It's not working
And then one day she's sitting there. She's walking around the house and she feels something but doesn't feel it
and she looks down
and
A particle
A particle hit her wrists a particle like she was she was holding a bag
She was holding a big piece of bread
She was walking with a piece of bread and she had her hands out
And the beam the little particle went and cut across both of her wrists and it cut it so deep that she dropped a baguette and
She died and so it didn't look like they're like no one would ever kill themselves if they were about to eat a giant baguette
What happened? What if the particle accelerator is the reason why this room is unsafe?
It's probably more it's probably more likely my original theory the particle accelerator may have something to do with ghostly activity in the area
but
Since we're already going down that path. I thought what if the particle accelerator is actually killing people there
So does this particle accelerator open up gateways to other worlds as a few particle?
have
A few particles gone rogue and murdered students
Who knows we don't know right it could be neither of those it could just be a particle accelerator
A bunch of kids telling ghost stories making stuff up
But the answer to these stories lie locked away behind the door to 428
Maybe the school's right. Maybe it's not safe to go in there, but you try your luck anyways
You want to prove the existence of ghosts you want to disprove the new conspiracy theory about murderous particles
So you are able to sneak in
You're in there for a bit waiting for something to happen asking the spirits to show themselves
It's been 20 30 minutes
You know you should leave because eventually the school authorities are going to find out you're in there
And as you go to reach for the doorknob
You realize
It's wet
It's sticky
And it's warm
That's when you look down and you see your own blood
dribbling off of your fingertips
onto the stained carpet
You thought you were going to prove the existence of ghosts and you were right
You became part of the story
For decades students will tell the tale of a ghost investigator who forced their way into room 428
And by the time anyone realized they were in there, they had been dead for days
Their ghost now wanders the campus
Hoping no one else makes the same mistake of walking into room 428
DeadRabbitRadio.com is going to be our email address. You can also hit us up at facebook.com/DeadRabbitRadio
Twitter is @DeadRabbitRadio
DeadRabbitRadio is the daily paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast. You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today
Have a great one guys
[Music]
[MUSIC]