Why ghosts are normally seen wearing white bedsheets
Ghosts who aren't really ghosts and it's the government trying to control our pancreas today on Dead Rabbit Radio
Hey everyone welcome back to another episode of Dead Rabbit Radio. I'm your host Jason Carpenter. I'm having a great day
I hope you're having a great day, you know
We're gonna dispense with a lot of the pleasantries the little introduction
I normally do because we have a lot to cover and the first story is probably one of the most important
That's the story that Art Bell has passed away now a lot of you may not know who Art Bell is but honestly
I'm sure a lot of you do
Art Bell was the host of Coast to Coast AM. It was a radio show and
He was the host of it for quite a long time
It basically was the precursor to every sort of paranormal talk show you could possibly think of including this one
Art Bell
was an inspiration to anyone who is a fan of the paranormal of conspiracies
He had this great way of letting people say whatever they wanted. He didn't judge them
He had a lot of great content. He produced over the decades that he ran the show
Unfortunately, there was an event involving his child. I remember that
He stopped doing the show and people thought oh, you know, it's
Because of the government's trying to silence him. He's he's revealing all of these truths and it turned out
It was much more mundane and far more evil his child was molested
so he took some time off to be with his kid and
He ended up stepping away from the show George Norrie took it over who I also feel is a great host
I used to listen to coast to coast AM all the time all the time. It was really the best place
It's you know, I think in a lot of ways it probably still is the best place to get that type of information
It's just very conversational
I used to what it was kind of my late-night routine a lot of truckers will listen to it people who work night shifts
It's just a great show. It's just a really great casual show
But unfortunately Art Bell has passed away now and of course there's already conspiracy theories about that
He passed away. He had some painkillers and some muscle relaxants in his system that were legally prescribed to him
He was in his 70s and people are already still saying that the government killed him
I mean at a certain point you kind of have to accept that sometimes
Great men pass away. So for those of you who aren't familiar with him
I wanted to play a quick segment from one of his shows to set this up
And this is a very famous segment to set this up a man called the radio station because it was an open call show
So you'd get all sorts of crazy people on there a man called the radio station and
Said that he was calling from area 51
There's been statements where they said that they found the man who placed the call and he was faking it or they found
The man who placed the call and he was off of his meds or whatever
The phone call you just heard is I believe from like the 90s of the early 2000s
So again enough time has passed but at the time I didn't hear that live
But I knew of it at the time that was a very panicky moment for people in the paranormal conspiracy because it sounds so real
Is it's more likely that it's from a crazy guy and it was a weird coincidence
You know, but again, it's just kind of a terrifying call and a terrifying moment and an overall terrifying show
So Art Bell, thank you for bringing us something new and opening up the
The market of paranormal radio paranormal
Podcast paranormal books. We appreciate everything you've done and we're gonna miss you
Let's get started with the show
So we have some great stories for you today
Some really cool ones actually one of the ones I found when I was looking up
Murderous ghosts, but I'm gonna save that one for a second because I'm gonna get into one that was on the conspiracy list iceberg
It's another one of those weird ones that you just look at a couple words put together and you think oh, that's just made up
You know before I do though, I'm gonna open this can of delicious diet Pepsi diet Pepsi the choice of a new generation
We're still we still don't have any sponsors by the way
So what this is is this is a theory called pancreas denial
Pancreas denial a lot of people have questioned. What does that mean?
What does it mean are people denying the bakery pancreas exists or is it something else now the course I?
Found nothing initially when I started my research
The only thing I had to go off of was again some posts on 4chan where people said that
Wizards are trying to keep us from accessing the chakra in our pancreas
So they're poisoning us with food to ruin the pancreas and eventually have to have it removed
Now the pancreas is basically what keeps every human on the planet from having diabetes. It's a digestive organ
Very important you can live without it, but you'll have diabetes
So I looked into that and I was like, you know, okay magic
That's my favorite topic and I kept looking around so I had to do a bunch of research on what the pancreas did and
Like what I just told you could you live without it, but I didn't feel like I had the whole story
I felt like there had to be something else
So I kept looking and I kept digging into this now apparently yes
The third chakra which is related to the basically the power of you
The power of who you are as a person is
Located in the pink pink real area. I guess there'd be a good way to put it
So this pancreas is
According to this website it controls feelings of power self-esteem and our relationship with our inner self
So this chakra is basically what would balance us and make us feel good
And it's located in that area
So by basically infecting the food supply and the drink supply with toxins
Whether that be like heavy toxins like lead things that can definitely affect us or just quote-unquote
Poisons like high fructose corn syrup which definitely affects your pancreas and definitely affects issues with diabetes
You're basically polluting that what it does is it breaks down your self-esteem
It breaks down your connection to who you really are
So you would be more likely to say follow a strong man leader or follow an authority figure because you don't have any self-esteem
Yourself and I'm thinking there still has to be something else about this
There still has to be another idea behind pancreas denial. I finally hit on something
It found something a lot of times these stories get broke on these very obscure
websites now I have I know that
Sometimes coded messages will be sent on the internet sometimes if I want to send a message to somebody else in an organization
I will write something out on
Say a website for the babysitters club and you will then I'll tell you hey if you want to know where the drug shipment is
Go to the babysitters club forum see the post about is Michael cheating on Becky and you'll find the instructions there
It's very common technique. That's nothing new. It's a very common technique people to be able to communicate with each other
so I found
the term pancreas denial on a gay erotica
Fanfiction about the band BTS now if you're not familiar with who BTS is they're the hottest boy band right now
I don't know why but anyways, they're also known as the Bangtan boys at seven kids from South Korea
The huge band so I found this I just saw this story that one of the all the store all the tags were like
Boy on boy and BTS and all the stuff and then out of all of those one of the tags was
Pancreas denial so I thought okay, maybe I'm onto something
Maybe somewhere in this gay erotica about the Bangtan boys
I will find the answer I've been looking for and I then went to proceeded to read a
5,000 word
Gay romance novel about the Bangtan boys. I don't know who these characters are
I don't know anything about these guys, but now I know that they are all banging each other and
I'm reading the story and you know it's a young author. Hey more power to you
I'm not gonna criticize this the writing in of itself because I think it was written for a particular audience
I'm not a member of that audience
But anyways halfway through the story the guy says you know
The the the hunky one the one with all the tattoos. I think he was a yungi yungi
Do you know do you know these guys the main story was yungi and
Jung cook
Those are the two leads in the story anyways, so I'm reading this story and
Yungi is like this motorcycle riding bad boy with tattoos all over his arms and
Jung Kook is some sort of communist who keeps keeps going on the side like
side diatribes about how
Marx is a hero and capitalism has failed and the patriarchy is being destroyed and feminism is ruling the planet
It's really bizarre to say the least and then halfway through it
Yungi is like I'm gonna be a doctor
I'm gonna study the pancreas and Jung Kook is like oh, okay
That's that's cool and then later on in the story after they've been banging for like two months
And they went to a Soviet film festival and he's like yungi's like oh, yeah, I love watching Soviet cinematography
I don't I
Anyways, so then at you yungi calls up junkook and says I
Need to meet you. I have something to tell you and
Junkook is like oh my god like I don't know how to deal with this like is he gonna break up with me
Guys and I'm sparing you like two-thirds of the story
I don't even know why I'm explaining this much of it
But anyways, so I the first two-thirds of the story was them meeting and a bunch of like gay gay sex
So so where was I oh, yeah, so yungi meets up with junkook and says I'm a member of a cult
We believe and I'm like yes, here we go in this totally obscure story
I'm finally going to get maybe a little bit more evidence of what is going on
With pancreas denial it was in the tag it had to they have to talk about it
Yungi yungi sitting there all steadily with his arm tattoos looks at
junkook in his shiny eyes as it's described and says
Yes, I am a doctor and I want to stay to the pancreas, but I'm a member of a cult
We believe wizards
We believe wizards are trying to poison the food supply and
Make our pancreas is not work so they can control us. God damn it
I read 5,000 words about a fanfiction about of a band that I know next to nothing about
Spent all that time and they're like texting each other and all sorts of nonsense to get the same
Stupid information. I got in 30 seconds from a reddit post
But I still had to follow my lead I thought maybe this is some sort of coded communication
I tried finding the author had a Twitter link the Twitter is not there anymore
Which is a little odd the story was just written in July of 2018
So it doesn't really pre-date any of the posts I've seen online about pancreas denial
I was hoping once I saw that because I did finish the story they end up happily ever after I
Don't want to you know a hobo shows up and says
You know junkook. I know it scares you that he's in a cult
But do you love him for who he is in junkook?
Oh, you know what you know what hobo I do so they end up together
I didn't want to not tell you how it ends
But the link will be provided if you want to read yourself and don't hurry like the author was doing
She's having fun. So I don't think any of you guys would ever harass anyone like that. But yeah, I mean all of this stuff
I hope when you're hearing this stuff, you're not like oh, we're gonna go after that. Yeah, it's just she's just a kid
having fun, but and I know you guys are better than that the
Thing was as I go. Okay. Well, maybe it is still some sort of code and information
But it's not she writes a ton of this stuff is where she wrote a lot of it close together
But I mean I was grass minutes draws at that point
I think that the pancreas denial she had also read
something like I had just a short phrase and
Somehow built a story around it, which I guess is kind of the same thing I do but it was just such a weird aside
So I was back really to square one
I think if from a conspiracy standpoint the idea works that pancreas denial is the idea that
the pancreas is one is a
It's a major
Chakra that can be that you can live without so you can't live without your brain chakra
You can't live with or head chakra or whatever it is
You can't live without the heart chakra
But you can live without the pink that the chakra there
And so if I was a wizard and I knew that if I was a wizard, oh my god, I can't believe
If I was a wizard and I knew that the pancreas was important
I knew people could live without it. I would poison the food supply like I make sense. I don't believe that that's happening
I don't believe that wizards are actually doing that but from a conspiracy standpoint. I can see that I can see people
believing that anyways, we're gonna go ahead and get on on the next story so
The next story I found when I was looking up
Murderous ghosts and I talked about that before I was trying to find stories about people who had been murdered by
ghosts or supernatural creatures in general
And I found one of the most compelling articles
I've read in a long time and I remember when I finished it. I thought I'm so glad I'm doing this podcast
Because just a month ago if I had found this article, I would have maybe read a first couple paragraphs and then
Skipped it because my time, you know, my time was so important even though I did nothing with it
But now that I'm kind of forced I guess compelled is a better thing to read these articles and find stories
I've read it and I'm like this was a fascinating article. It covered a lot of amazing things
So what happened the narrative hook is at the very beginning of this article and this is all true
This is all historical is that a man killed a ghost. He's on trial for killing a ghost
But it wasn't a ghost so this guy shot
Like a laborer who was wearing all white walking down the street and a man jumped out of the alleyway and shot
The laborer killed him because he shot him because he was a ghost
So you're thinking well, why would a guy jump out and the story the article gets you hooked right from there
You're like, why would it guy jump out and shoot at a ghost?
So what happened was back in the 19th century in Britain? They had a major problem with ghosts
What it was so back then if you were poor
They wouldn't necessarily really wouldn't put you in a coffin. They'd bury you
But you're poor they would wrap you up in the bed sheet that you died in if you died in bed
Or they would just grab a bed sheet if you're dead somewhere else
They tied the feet and the and the head and they throw you into the ground and bury you so most bodies
Were covered in white sheets now that is why ghosts traditionally are just a white sheet
I had never known that I and I had wondered that before why do ghosts appear in?
Traditional media as just being a white sheet walking around so right away
I'm like this article is fascinating
but the problem they had in the 19th century was people dressing up as ghosts and
Jumping out at people as a practical it started off as a practical joke
Then people started putting a white sheet on and mugging other people give me your wallet
Give me your pincers or whatever give me your shillings and it would scare people so badly because they actually thought these were
Zombies they thought these were ghosts. They thought this was the dead popping up out of nowhere and attacking people and then
People started wearing the sheets and raping women now
I'm sure halfway through the rape they realized they wasn't a ghost
But that's not the point the point is the initial attack would shock you because you honestly thought it was a ghost attacking
What made it worse was that all around?
Britain people would say there's a ghost in the area
There's a ghost because you would see first it like I said it was a practical joke
People would stand in the graveyard in a white sheet and freak people out
And so when you were walking down a dark alley and a guy jumped out in a white sheet
Your first inclination is going to be that's the living dead because you've already heard all the stories about that and
It got to the point where so many women were being harassed by ghosts who people thought were ghosts
That they began forming vigilante teams and they would walk through the cities
Looking for ghosts. So there was that clown scare in America not too long ago
This would be the equivalent of that but when we see people in clown outfits, we are like, oh
They're just they're just ghosts. I mean, they're just people dressed up as clowns
These people honestly thought these guys were ghosts
So this one guy he wore all white because he was a labor that was the clothes that he wore and other people in town
Were saying hey, you shouldn't be out at night. You kind of look like a ghost and he's like, I don't care
What are they gonna do to me? I'm not a ghost. I'll beat him over the head with my billy club or whatever
I have a hammer but one day he was walking on the street and his
Who's I believe it was at his sister's house and she's like, please don't go out or at least change your clothes before you go home
Because you look like a ghost and he's like whatever
He's walking on the street another guy who was part of one of these vigilante groups looking for ghosts
Saw a man in all white thought it was a ghost pulled the trigger and immediately realized that he was wrong
Shot a man and killed him. He was arrested
Charged and found guilty for killing a ghost for killing this man within 45 minutes
He's convicted of manslaughter and this is how crazy things were back then with the trial system
He gets tried for manslaughter. The three judges say no, that's not good enough. You can't split it down the middle
he's either guilty of murder or he's totally innocent and
You have to figure it out and then the jury goes
Well, I guess he's guilty to murder then he was sentenced to hang at next Monday. None of this 10 20 year thing
He was sentenced to hang next Monday now
Luckily the King got involved and said, you know what? No, we're not going to have we're gonna delay his execution
And then eventually this had just parole him like it was a tragic mistake
It shouldn't happen in the first place and that kind of quelled down the fake ghost scare of that time because it just
I mean nobody wanted to get shot and it was the same thing you've heard the legend
You may have heard the legend of Spring Hill Jack who apparently was a supernatural creature who leapt around London and was harassing women
Well, he was sexually assaulting women is what he was doing and so people used the paranormal
to cover for their activities
Dress up as a ghost
Pinch a woman's butt dress up as a ghost, you know drag a woman into an alley
Your Spring Hill Jack you're attacking women who's driving people insane
Plus they have the superstitions that these things were real
So I know you'd like to think well, we've advanced we've changed
We've evolved but people still use this ploy and unfortunately it still works
This just happened this year by the way
So there is this young 15 year old girl who was super petrified of the paranormal of the occult of the supernatural
She would never listen to this show. She would never watch X files anything like that. She's totally terrified of that
She starts hearing noises in her house late at night and she's petrified
She can't figure out what it is. She thinks the ghost is coming after her then one night a little note gets passed underneath your book door
Gets up. She reads it. It has very clear instructions
If you want me to stop haunting you have sex with Liam Clark
No, I don't know if it actually said that but that was the intent because Liam Clark was a 35 year old neighbor
or he wasn't a relative but he knew the family and
She kept getting these notes saying if you want me to stop haunting you you have to have sex with Liam Clark
And she didn't want to have sex with him. She's 15. He's 35
But she wanted the haunting to stop so badly. So what does she do?
She has sex with him and of course this happens in Britain too. Maybe it's a weird thing over there now
Of course eventually he's arrested
because she
Tells somebody this guy who pretended to be a ghost is now in prison for 26 years
He put this girl through psychological and physical torture
Pretended to be a ghost preyed on her worst fears and really that is what they did back in the 17th 18th 19th century
It was the same gimmick prey on their fears make them vulnerable
Attack them. So maybe people societies don't change. I don't know. It's it was just kind of a weird
Side note a weird kind of I don't want to say end cap to this story because I'm sure it's gonna continue on whenever someone can figure out
Someone's weakness like this. They're gonna keep doing it
Well, I guess that's kind of ending on a sad note, but you know not all of our stories are gonna be super happy
Yeah, actually this episode was quite depressing, but I thought they're really interesting. Well the the bangtan boys was pretty funny
That was worth it. That was the hot
That was the funny moment of the episode deadrabbitradio@gmail.com is gonna be our email address
You can hit us up at facebook.com/deadrabbitradio at Twitter
I'm sorry. Twitter is @JasonOCarpenter. You can hit me up there
We have a lot more episodes to come out. We're doing we have more than enough stories
But if you ever have a suggestion hit me up on one of those channels. We're also still putting together our street team
We're getting everything set up for that. So if you're interested in that you can always email me share the show
That really helps us grow. I love seeing people in jail if you can't share it
Just let me know that you love the show. That's always fun. It always makes my day dead rabbit radio is the paranormal conspiracy and true crime podcast
You don't have to listen to it every day, but I'm glad you listen to it today. Have a great day guys and Art Bell once again
Thank you. You you were quite the entertainer slash educator and we're gonna miss you. Have a great day guys
You
(upbeat music)